[lana]
so, that bag is clothes.
That bag is diapers.
The cooler is breast milk,
Which obviously needs
to go in the--
where do you buy breast milk?
[sighs]
you don't, archer. You--
[laughs]
oh, my god, will you relax?
Here. Have a cold-- wow.
So no beer?
Why would I bring beer?
Because you don't want me
drinking liquor?
I don't want you
drinking anything!
What, that's all for her?
I'll find a sitter.
Lana, relax.
I won't drink while you're gone.
I take this very seriously.
Well, or at least
woodhouse does.
Yeah, and if he was here--
wait. What?
Where is he?
[whispers]
rehab.
Oh, seriously?
I know. At his age,
it's like, why even bother?
Well?
I'm kidding.
It's his annual
three days off.
It's normally two,
but I let him roll over one
from last year.
Your largesse knows no bounds.
Well, it's not paid.
Ugh!
Have you at least
baby-proofed this place?
I don't think a baby
can hurt anything.
No, not-- ugh!
I mean, like firearms,
for instance.
Are they stored securely?
[rattles]
yes.
I'll find a sitter.
Lana, go.
A.J.'s in good hands.
I know what I'm doing.
E read ten
the   baby-sitters club   books.
Really?
Yeah. I'm totally
a kristy,
With maybe, like,
a dash of claudia.
Because I won't have my phone.
So when you realize
you can't handle it--
I won't.
But when you do--
please shut up--
This is the main number
at the zen center.
And a staff member
will come and find me.
In your stupid--
what is it, a wigwam?
It's a yurt.
Wow. Even stupider.
Archer, I'm serious.
Me too.
Paying to spend 24 hours
sweating in a yurt
Is literally the dumbest thing
you've ever done.
Oh, I can think
of a few more.
You're right.
Maybe this will help you shed
some of your negative energy.
My--
have fun. Say hi
to your spirit animal.
Ugh! Okay.
I'll see you tomorrow night.
[singsong voice]
but I bet you call
before then!
[scoffs]
I bet I won't.
[muffled muttering]
[gulps, coughs]
Holy shit,
I gotta wash that down.
See that, a.J.?
That was a teachable moment
[cooing]
About a little thing
called confidence.
And contrary to what
you may have heard,
You can never have
too much of it.
Or bourbon.
Where's the bourbon?
Okay, I gotta have some irish,
or at least some scotch,
Or blended, or--
Jesus christ, woodhouse,
stock the bar!
Okay, here we go.
So we have...
Ugh, tequila and coffee liqueur.
All right.
So we can make...
I guess this will be
a... Black mexican?
[fussing]
what? No, that's not racist.
That's what it is.
If you added milk,
It would be a white mexican,
but all we have is breast milk--
Eww, which would make it
a rusty krieger.
[slurps]
oh!
Oh, god. Wow.
That is   mierda.
And also between us, okay?
Because your mom
likes to worry, a.J.,
But she doesn't need to,
Because when
you're with me, kid,
You're as safe as a bug in a...
[door thuds open]
Archer!
Help!
Please help!
He's been shot!
[groaning]
[a.J. Crying]
oh, good.
For a second,
I thought you were lana.
[groaning continues]
[belches]
♪
[slater]
where's the goddamn
first aid kit?
[archer]
behind the bar.
And quit yelling.
[man]
aahhh! Ow!
[blow lands]
Why did you hit me?
'cause!
Get your shit together!
Get your shit together, man.
[a.J. Crying]
You're the one
who's bleeding to death.
Yeah. From my ears.
So shut up!
[archer]
everybody shut up,
Because, spoiler alert,
this is a baby.
And why do you
have a baby?
Well, slater.
When a mommy and a daddy
Love each other very much--
In your apartment!
Yeah. Or a motel
or a porta-john,
Or--
are you trying
to piss me off?
[chuckling]
not really.
Well, you are, so...
Why do you keep your
first aid kit in the bar?
Because that's where over
80% of home accidents happen.
Wow. Really?
They happen in the bathroom!
Not in my home.
Speaking of which,
Why are you in it,
and who is he?
Sterling archer,
this is farooq ashkani.
Yeah. Hi.
Black mexican?
What?
Uh, hey, dick,
I happen to be pakistani.
[speaking urdu]
I was offering you a drink,
But all I have is tequila
and coffee liqueur.
Sorry. I thought
you were being racist.
No. If anything,
you were,
If you think black
or mexican is an insult.
My child is actually
multiracial, so--
Hang on. Go back.
You speak urdu?
Huh? Oh. No. No, no.
Just that one phrase.
The only phrase
you know in urdu is,
"no, shit,
you goat-raping pig-devil"?
What? I thought it mean,
"I'm sorry."
Huh. Probably why that night
in a karachi whorehouse
Suddenly went from pretty bad
to much worse.
I'm gonna stop you there.
Somebody should.
I mean, this is a baby.
Because time's
a bit of a factor.
Until yesterday,
farooq was a cyberspy
For pakistani intelligence.
But now he wants
to come over to our side.
Are we not
on the same side?
Eh...
Anyway, I was walking him
into a cia safe house,
But a bunch of his former
colleagues were waiting for us.
I had to shoot
our way out of there.
But how did
they know where the--
[gasps]
Oh, my god,
could the cia have a leak?
That's what I said!
Anyway, until I find the leak
and plug it,
I need you
to babysit him.
And I object
to the term "babysit,"
Because clearly
I am not a baby.
And I'm already babysitting
What clearly is
an actual baby, so...
[cooing]
She sure is.
Can I hold her?
Uh, yeah. Okay.
But, you know, be careful.
I got her.
There we go.
Archer, come on.
No.
24 hours.
No!
And a hundred grand.
Yes!
Okay, good. I'll call you
after I deal with the leak,
Then you'll bring him
to the new safe house.
And payment will be...
By wire transfer.
Is that a problem?
No. I just didn't know
If I should bring my sack
with the big dollar sign on it.
Just bring him.
And I need to borrow a shirt.
Farooq?
Um...
Why do you-- [scoffs]
never mind.
There's a logic to all of it.
Aw, you're
absolutely insane.
[chuckling]
crazy...
[muttering]
[door closes]
is he gone?
Yeah, he's--
because he's kind of
a dick, right?
Right.
And what's the deal
with that safe house?
Am I right? Come on.
They should call it a...
Misnomer house.
But this place is safe,
though, right?
Yeah, I mean--
yeah, I mean,
it's the penthouse.
And I assume that's
the only door, so--
Well, except for
the terrace, but--
Yeah, so maybe we should
lock that?
[fussing]
hey. Shh.
Sorry. I was just
kind of freaking out.
I just saw a guy get shot.
Well, if you
get her started again,
You're gonna see you
get shot, so--
yeah, okay.
So you have guns here, right?
Yes. I literally
have tons of them.
Yeah, but--
hang on.
Not literally,
but a lot.
Yeah. Okay.
But on you, I mean, like...
Are you strapped?
[laughing]
Am I strapped?
No, homie, I'm not.
Okay, so you don't
have a gun on you,
Is what I'm saying.
And no is what I'm saying.
Okay, good.
Wh--
That's just gonna make
this next part a lot easier.
Well, for me.
[laughing]
Oh, my god.
Okay. Good stuff.
You had me going
there for a second.
[laughs] I'm sorry.
I can't believe
lana set this up.
Just so I'd call
and ask for help.
And you got slater in on it?
With the fake blood?
Oh, man.
She is pathetic.
Aah!
[crying]
What the shit?
You shot me!
I wanted your full attention.
Well, you nailed it, asshole!
Jesus christ! Did lana pay you
extra too shoot me?
Okay, I don't know
this lana, but--
I'm sorry?
Yeah. Me too.
She sounds like
a real practical joker.
But I assure you, mr. Archer,
this is all very real.
Hey, hey, now, listen to me,
all right?
Listen. I don't know
what's going on,
But you're gonna
hand me the baby.
No, mr. Archer,
I am not.
Not until you take me
to your headquarters
So I can access
the mainframe computer.
Yeah, I heard you,
but I'm not going anywhere
Until you put it up there.
Fine. Whatever.
[tires screeching]
Wow! You drive like
a gaping dickhole.
[grunts]
♪ [muzak]
so I guess there's
no cia leak.
Nope. My follow team
created a diversion
So that slater would
bring me to you,
So that you
would bring me here.
Just don't hurt her.
Well, I hope
it won't come to that.
You really, really should.
Just make sure
there are no surpris--
[pam]
god damn it!
What the--
it's Friday night.
Why the hell are people
still here?
I don't know.
I guess it's--
Jeezy petes!
An inside straight?
[all grumbling]
Got three on the hip,
I need four for the weekend.
I'm going to hotlanta.
Have fun,
I hope you get hate-crimed.
Hey, whoa!
Goddamn, woman.
Seriously.
I'll hate-crime your ass
right here.
[gillette]
you know what?
Guys, come on.
Can't we have one poker night
without a hate crime?
Okay, a, the thing last month
wasn't a hate crime...
Because I will
straight-flush your brains
Out the back of your skull!
It was just a regular crime.
And obviously now I put my gun
In the time-lock safe
until the game's over.
And so basically,
the only thing keeping you
From murdering each other is
a lack of access to firearms.
Works for canada.
Nothing works for canada.
[archer]
hey guys...
[greetings]
Is-- are you playing
strip poker?
[together]
no.
It just gets hot
as balls in here.
Literally.
Okay, well--
hang on.
Yeah, literally.
Right, I just came by
because, uh--
aha!
Because you need help with the
baby and you can't call lana,
So you came to ask
one of us for help.
For your information, cyril,
I don't need help with a.J.
Because I, uh...
Hired a manny.
Hey, I'm... Manny.
[general mumbles of greeting]
Black mexican?
No, thank you,
I probably shouldn't.
Shouldn't what?
Uh, swarm across
the rio grande?
From pakistan?
Where's woodhouse?
My guess, avenue d.
Anyhoo, we just,
um, gotta grab...
Some baby stuff.
So, we're gonna go do that.
Manny?
Good luck with your...
Hate-cards.
Pff, go back to canada,
guy lafleur.
Okay, ante up,
ya goat-raping pig devils!
Nothing wild but the dealer.
Hang on a sec.
Did archer seem a little,
like...
Scared to you guys?
[dismissing]
Ya know, now that you
mention it,
He did actually seem
a little nervous.
[accepting]
I bet he's just on the c.D.L.
The what?
Canadian down-low.
Please, like you all
wouldn't bang alan thicke
If you had the chance.
I think we should
go check it out.
Well, if we're not
gonna play poker!
I thought this was ouija.
So, those guys...
Kinda dicks, right?
Right?
Totally. Okay, now enter
the command sequence string.
Okay good, now once you've...
Entered that...
Wow, still working on it.
You also type
like a gaping dickhole.
Sorry, I don't wanna mess up.
Man, you are nothing
like your file.
All these stories about
what a badass you are,
But I gotta tell ya,
farooq's not seeing it.
Well, in those stories,
I'm probably not
Changing poopy diapers, so--
So do you seriously
not even care
What I'm doing
with your mainframe?
I honestly don't.
Okay, I'm going
to tell you anyway.
I'm using it to backdoor
my state-of-the-art
Spyware into the cia network,
so pakistani intelligence
Will know everything
they do in real time.
And... Why are you
telling me this?
I'm -- wait, what?
I mean, now I'm just
gonna tell the cia,
And they'll find the spyware.
That was only one
of many, many
Possible things
I could be doing.
Okay.
No, no, and the very fact
that I told you
That's what I'm doing,
I mean that was
Clearly misdirection, right?
Okay.
Plus, I doubt you'll
be talking very much
After I shoot you
in the face.
Take it easy, I--
(small gasp)
Shit! I don't have a will!
I'm a notary!
Wha--?
What the shit, manny?
[struggling, baby crying]
Pam! Baby!
[pam screaming]
What the heck's going on in--
[growls]
Well, ya don't see
that everyday.
I didn't even see it today...
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
[crashes]
So, here's the thing, farooq.
I don't know about any stories,
But whatever badass shit
that you heard I did,
You really need
some context, because
Pretty much my whole life,
pretty much right up until
This minute, my default setting
has been "half-ass."
But that was before
I had a child,
A child you threatened to harm.
A child, I just realized,
who's probably on her way up
To the roof so aunt pam
can swat at biplanes.
Wait, what the hell am I doing?
The roof's the first place
they'll look.
So imagine, as I literally
beat you to death--
Hang on. Yeah, literally,
That a giant hand
has turned my dial
From "half-ass"
to "quadruple-ass."
Wow. That is a lot of ass.
Yeah, basically eight times
the ass.
Can I just say one thing,
before we get into all
The beating to death?
What?
[gun unsheathing, being cocked]
I still have a gun?
Oh, right.
[gillette]
well? What's going
on in there?
Okay, so...
That lesbian au pair has a gun.
I think she's robbing
mr. Archer.
[together]
wait, what? What au pair?
The black mexican.
Oh for--
so what should we do?
Nothing!
Until we consult the ouija.
God I love poker night.
So, before you shoot me,
can I just say one thing?
What?
[screams]
What the shit, cyril?
[gasping]
Really?
Take cover!
C'mon, cyril.
[panicking]
There's other desks.
This one's good.
Ow. Damn it!
This is exactly
how brett died.
[sigh]
man, I wish he was
still with us.
[chuckling]
he could soak up
some of these bullets.
God, finally. Okay,
that's eight rounds,
Including the one
in my shoulder, so he's--
[farooq]
reloading!
God dammit.
Oh! Ray, gun.
It's in a time-lock safe.
What? Why?
Because cheryl.
[farooq]
I'm calling for backup.
[speaking urdu]
What'd he say?
Well, my urdu isn't
as strong as I thought.
[speaking urdu]
Meh.
But I'm gonna assume
he just called for backup.
So we gotta get to the armory.
It's empty.
It's--
What do you mean, it's empty?
When we got shut down,
that guy--
Kevin. Kyle?
Keith? Kenny? Kieran.
Rodney?
Rodney.
Why was I thinking kev--
He stole everything.
He set himself up in europe
as some kind of arms dealer.
Gentlemen, I'm afraid you
mistake my hospitality
For weakness.
The price is the price.
If you wish to negotiate,
you may do so
With my associates.
[evil laugh]
And apparently
he's doing quite well.
[yelping]
[farooq]
reloading!
[annoyed sigh]
remind me, if this asshole
doesn't kill all of you,
To do it for him.
[chuckling]
uh, no.
And take that
ridiculous thing off.
Make me.
Ow, stop it,
cut it out, stop, ow!
[gasp]
wait a minute.
Ow!
Gimme that.
Okay, on my signal,
I'm gonna draw his fire.
You idiots make make a run
for it, find pam and a.J.,
And get them to safety
before the rest of these
Jerk-dicks get here.
What about cheryl?
Who cares?
No, I'm genuinely asking.
So while we're getting
a.J. Out of here,
What're you gonna be doing?
Krieger, the hvac ducts
Are still chock full
of nerve gas, right?
Wait, what?
Yeah, but--
But shut up,
just get a.J. Outta here,
I'll take care of the rest.
Archer, that's--
pretty heroic, I know.
I was gonna say overkill, but--
what're you, on their side?
That asshole
threatened to hurt a.J.
Although now that
I think about it,
This whole thing
is totally her fault.
What? As far as
field operations are concerned,
She's a huge
liability!
Now shut up
and wait for my signal.
[farooq]
reloading. I should probably
stop saying that out loud.
Should we just go now?
I mean, yeah you should have,
But it's probably
too late now, so...
Now!
[speaking urdu]
Quit saying that.
[yelling]
We should've gone then,
I bet.
[speaking urdu]
[chuckling]
where do you think
you're going?
Must...
Protect... Baby.
[slow clapping]
What the...?
Not bad.
I'm gonna give you a seven.
Wait, what?
Me, or him?
No him, slater said
you were great.
Aww, he's sweet.
You, I took off a point
Because pam was feeding
a.J. Vienna sausages.
Idiot!
She's not on solid food yet.
They weren't solid.
The fact that you were
pre-chewing them
And spitting them
into her mouth--
What the hell is going on?
[baby crying]
Shhhh.
What is wrong with you?
Well for starters,
I got shot. Twice.
Where did you get a real gun?
My cousin. The one you gave me
looked like, so fake,
And I thought a real one
would help me
Get into the character better.
Oh, give it a rest,
james lipton.
He's an actor?
Well, mostly improv, but--
You set this whole thing up?
You had me shot?
You had slater shot?
No, the cia guys
did his make-up.
Looked pretty real though, huh?
So cool.
Were you assholes in on this?
[denials]
Oh, please,
you can't tell them anything.
Why... Would you do this?
I wanted to see
if I could trust you
To take care of a.J.
By yourself.
Oh!
Yeah, let's talk about trust.
Oh, let's talk about drinking
a gallon of black mexicans
Before driving around in a car
with your infant daughter!
Good point
I was at gunpoint.
Also good.
[lana]
well...
You still lied when you said
you weren't gonna drink.
You knew I was lying.
That doesn't ex--
wait, that's your excuse?
Yes! Lana.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I am in fairly desperate need
of medical attention.
[baby cries]
all your fault!
God damn it!
Why are you going up?
All right, I'd call this...
A qualified success.
Yeah, I really feel like
I nailed it.
So... You do improv, huh?
Yeah, at dream
the improovable dream,
Down on twenty-third and lex.
You guys gotta come down,
maybe take a class,
It's good for confidence,
or just, at least come out
to a show...
Here's some flyers.
Our upcoming shows are on there,
plus there's a coupon
For a free drink
if you're a lady, so...
Wait, is it not
the imprahv-able dream?
Huh.
That makes way more sense.
♪