Malory (o.S.): No, coordinate
with rome, then get me the
Latest intel, then tell rodney
they need travel documents
An hour ago...
Then bring me the file I asked
for!
Gillette: Why don't I shove a
broom up my ass and sweep the
Floor while I'm at it?
Malory: What was that?!
Gillette: Nothing.
Malory: Good. Saves you the
embarrassment of an incredibly
Homophobic remark.
Cheryl/carol: Aww.
Gillette: Ew!
Malory: Go!
Gillette: Ow!
Lana: Ow!
Gillette (o.S.): Sorry!
Lana: What's going on?
Malory: Where?
Lana: Uh, this new place
called here!
Malory: Nothing
lana: Wh-? Malory.
Cheryl/carol: Good luck, she
just had an electro -
Malory: -- Electromagnetic
lock installed, are you serious?
Lana: Malory
malory: Because I'm seriously
Asking, did krieger give you
robot hands?
Krieger: Not yet!
But you just say the word.
Lana: The -
[zzrrrzz].
Lana: Out.
Malory: Can't have anything
nice...
Malory: Krieger!
Krieger: Jazz hands!
Malory: Should've never taken
him to see "the wiz."
Lana: The broadway show or the
movie?
Krieger: Jazz hands!
Malory: Both.
Lana: I -- whatever, look,
obviously there's -
Malory: Nothing! Is going on,
lana! If there were, I would
Tell you, but -
[dooot]
Cheryl/carol: Uh, there's a
cardinal corelli on line one
For you? Something about a
radical faction of the swiss
Guard assassinating the pope
tomorrow night?
Lana: You need to get that?
[theme music]
Lana: Do you. Need to get that.
Malory: No, I'm sure whoever
it is -
[dooot]
cheryl/carol (o.S.): It's the
Vatican! Line one! Jesus!
Cheryl/carol: (gasp) shit, I
hope he didn't hear that.
(gasp) or that, shit!
Malory: Just put him through,
you idiot!
Cheryl/carol (o.S.): Okay,
jesus! [gasp] shit...
Malory: Uhhhhh
ah ha ha, giancarlo! Como stai?
Corelli: Molto meglio, cara
mia, now that I see your eyes,
Your lips, your...
Malory: Giancarlo! Siete senza
vergogna.
Corelli: And you, are the only
woman who ever made me regret
Taking the holy orders.
Malory: And you are the only
man who ever made me -
Ron cadillac: Come oonnn!
I'm right here, ya know!
Malory: Why?!
Ron cadillac: Gettin new
carpet in my office. Which,
Speaking of...
Malory: Ron?!
Corelli: Malory, you have
married?
Malory: Ehh...
Corelli: You are a fortunate
man, signore.
Ron cadillac: Ah, blow it out
yer cassock.
Malory: Ron!
Corelli: Malory. We don't have
much time. Your agents of isis,
They are ready?
Lana: Or they are confused
verging on angry?
Malory: Lana, it's an
undercover mission. At the
Vatican?
Lana: What, they don't have
black nuns? Although granted
I've never seen one. But that's
not like, a rule, is it?
Corelli: Ehh...
Lana: Well since you're not
sending me, and I assume you're
Not sending ray...
Malory: To the vatican? You
think all those catholic
Priests wouldn't peg him -
[cough, cough] as american?
With that hillbilly accent?
Corelli: Malory, I must go
now. Please hurry!
Lana: So not ray, and not me,
which leaves...
[gregorian chant]
lana: [sigh]
Archer: In nomine patris, et
filii, et spiritus sancti, et
Cetera, et -
lana: You can't.
No one is gonna believe
archer is a priest.
Archer: For your infor - I'm
in! Turn it off!
Cheryl/carol (o.S.): Okay!
Jesus! [gasp] shit.
Archer: For your information,
lana, I have totally prepared
For this mission.
Lana: Well there's a firs -
archer: First thing I did was
Watch every episode of "lucy,
daughter of the devil." which
By the way, was grossly -
lana: Inadequate preparation,
For an undercover mission
protecting the pope from an
Assassination attempt!
Archer: I was gonna say
"underrated," but -
Lana: But even if you were
prepared -
Archer: Which I truly feel
that I am.
Lana: -- But which you're not,
who's your backup if ray's not
Going? Cyril?
Archer: No...
Malory: No, it turns out cyril -
cyril: Aaagh!
How bout a little warning?!
Malory: Has a thing. About
church stuff.
Lana: Since when?
Cyril: Since none of your
beeswax, and -
Archer: Bwoohahaahaaa!
Cyril: Aaagh!
Lana: Well...
Cyril: And I think I need a
spanking, because I have been a
Very naughty baaaaagh!
Lana: Guess that explains
that. But it doesn't explain
How archer's gonna run this
mission by himself.
Malory: Well, if you were
"confused verging on angry"
Before...
Cyril (o.S.): Aaagh!
Pam (o.S.): What?!
Pam: Jesus christ... Shit. God
damn it.
Malory: Pam!
Pam: What.
Lana: Pam?!
Pam: What?!
Archer: Paaaam!
Pam: Whaaat?!
Archer: I dunno, what're we
doing?
Lana: Esatto! Che cosa stiamo
facendo?!
Pam: Aww man, we have to learn
latin?
Archer: Ew yeah, that's a
dealbreaker.
Lana: You were speaking latin
when you walked in here -
Archer: Mmmmno...
Lana: -- Whereas I was just
speaking italian, which neither
Of you speak nor even
understand, obviously, so -
Archer: So?! Lana, the
assassination plot is being
Hatched by the swiss guard?
Lana: So...?
Archer: So it's an eight-hour
flight, so we get some tapes
And brush up on our -
lana: Swiss?
Archer: Duh?
Lana: Well, since swiss isn't
a language, maybe you should
Get some tapes on german,
french, italian and romansh.
Archer: Maybe I will.
Malory: Alright. Lana pack a
bag, you're -
Archer: No! Mother come on, we
don't need -
Malory: Lana! Is going!
Lana: Ha!
Malory: And pam, if you keep
your eyes open and your big
Mouth shut, you just might
learn something from her.
Pam: Ha!
Archer: Why are you going ha?!
Pam: I dunno, what're we doing?
Lana: I'll tell you what we
should be doing. So, who does
The pope remind you of?
Malory: Ha!
Archer: What.
Lana: Haaa!
Archer: Shut up! And you also
shut up.
Woodhouse: Yessir.
Pam: Haaa!
Archer: Why are you still
going ha?!
Pam: Pink panther's on.
Father guido sardoochbag.?
Archer (o.S.): Oh really?
Archer: Because she didn't
specify an agent in-command,
Lana, so I would argue -
lana (o.S.): With a fence post.
Archer: I wouldn't argue with
a -- oof! Move, idiot!
Pam: I'm goin as fast as I can!
Archer: Not you, the -
pam: The fence post?
Lana (o.S.): Ha!
Archer: It was a bollard! And
my point was -
Lana: Fine! You're agent-in-
command! Now shut up, brief
Corelli, and get the access
code to the pope's apartment!
[doot]
archer: I... Will, because I
Command me to.
Lana: And you should eat, this
could be a long night, and
You're... So teeny.
Woodhouse: Hm?
Lana: Seriously, eat, you're
like a slow loris.
Woodhouse: Oh, no, bit off my
feed, I'm afraid.
Lana: Woodhouse, you need to -
oh c'mon, you need to fix?
Woodhouse: [whimper]
lana: Well, is there some
Amount you can shoot up to get
right for the mission, without
Gettin all... Trainspotty?
Woodhouse: Back in a tick!
Lana: Oh for the -- and thanks
for making me carry your bag
Through customs!
Woodhouse (o.S.): No, thank
you!
Archer (o.S.): Grazie.
Grazie mille,
vostra... Majesty-o?
Corelli: Your italian is, how
you say, shit?
Archer: Then you are not gonna
like my romansh.
Corelli: Mio dio! You think
this is funny?!
Archer: I thought that was.
Corelli: Assassins plan to
kill the holy father in his own
Bed, on this very night, ma tu
stai qui con la testa nel culo!
Pam: Whoa whoa, take it down a
notch, st. Louis! His head is
Not up his ass!
Archer: How'd you know what
he said?
Pam: It was an eight-hour
flight.
Archer: Wow, did you learn
romansh?
Pam: Who am I, cypher? The
gayest x-man?
Archer: I dunno, gambit looks
like he knows his way around a
Pair of -
corelli: Basta! Here is the
Access card to the holy
father's private apartment. I
Assume you have a plan once
inside?
Pam: We call it the old
switcheroo.
Archer: We absolutely do not
call it the old switcheroo.
Corelli: Mio dio!
Lesser cardinals: [gasp]
archer: I know, right? Trope
Alert!
Corelli: Che?
Pam: Eh... Non si traduce bene.
Lana: Feeling better?
Woodhouse: Sound as a pound,
my dear.
Where the hell are we?
Lana: Uh, this new place
called Italy?
Woodhouse: How'd I get all the
way downtown?
Lana: Wh-? Not little Italy!
Italy, Italy!
Woodhouse: Bloody hell. What
are we doing here?
Lana: Thwarting an
assassination attempt on the
Pope. Using you as a decoy.
Woodhouse: Back in a tick!
Lana: With ken and your weekend
weather. And you may need an
Umbrella because it's going to
be raining.
Dead ass popes.
Pam (o.S.): Aw crap, he's
already dead.
Archer: No he's not, he's just
old. That's how woodhouse looks
When he's asleep.
Pam: I'm gonna get a mirror.
Archer: Right until he wakes
and sees me staring at him
With night-vision goggles and
literally pisses himself. Hey,
Does woodhouse seem unhappy to
you, or -- what the hell're you
Doing?!
Pam: Gonna see if his breath
fogs it up.
Archer: Put the stupid mirror
back, he's not -
Pam: [gasp]
archer: Dead. Nice job, oliver
Cromwell.
Pam: I killed the pope!
Archer: Yeah, that's why I
said oliver crom -
Pam: Jesus christ I'm going to
hell I'm going to hell I'm
Going to hell I'm -
[thwak! Thwak! Thwak!]
Archer: Pam.
Pam: Yes?
Archer: Get off the pope.
Archer: Heeey,
your holiness...
Pam: Is he dead?!
Archer: I dunno, shut up, I'm -
pam: Should I get another
Mirror? But like, a much much
smaller one?
Lana (o.S.): No, you're half
heroin already!
[clunk]
lana: Okay, here's junkie
Brewster, let's...
Where's the pope?
Archer: Soo, here's the thing.
Pam: Promise you won't get mad?
Lana: I -- actually
do not promise I won't get mad,
Because here's what thing?
Archer: Um...
Lana: What, why is there a
giant mirror on the oh my god
You crushed the pope?!
Lana: Don't just stand there
idiots, help me get it off and
Pam! Woodhouse!
Pam: Huh? Oh!
Woodhouse (o.S.): Oof!
Woodhouse (o.S.): Ow!
Pam: Ow! What the -- is
that a needle?!
Archer: [chuckles]
lana: Rrrrrgh!
Pope: [gasping]
lana: Oh thank god!
Pope: Chi siete voi, dove sono
le guardie?!
Lana: We're -- your holiness,
do you speak english?
Pope: Yes, of course, but -
archer: Ha! Way to waste your
Time learning italian, pam!
Pam: Aw, stai zitto, testa di
cazzo. And could you...?
Woodhouse: Sorry.
Pope: Dio mio! He look just
like me!
Lana: Yes, your holiness, he's
a decoy. We have reason to
Believe a faction of the swiss
guard will make an attempt on
Your life tonight, so -
archer: So if you don't mind
Hopping out of those pope-
jamas...
Lana: Archer? We'll hide you,
put him in your place, wait for
Them to come in -
pope: And then what?! You are
Only two!
Archer: Well three, so -
pam: Better make that two.
Think I mighta grabbed the tail
of the dragon here...
Woodhouse: Ooh, then you're in
for a treat!
Archer: Shut up! And with all
due respect your holiness,
It's the swiss guard...
I think we can
handle a few court jesters
With, whatever, halberds.
Lana: Which, you realize are
just ceremonial.
Archer: Obviously they're
ceremonial, they were made
Obsolete by the arquebus.
Lana: Which is why now they
use mp-5's.
Archer: Oh.
Lana: Which is why where's the
gear bag with all of our
Automatic weapons?!
Archer: Well I assume in the
hotel room, but -
Lana: God -
archer: I thought they just
Had halberds!
Lana: Do you at least have a
sidearm?!
Archer: It was ruining the
lines of my cassock.
Lana: Dammit!
Archer: And again, I honestly
thought they just had -
[rattle rattle]
archer: -- Halberds. Although
Technically I think they're
called voulges.
Swiss guard (o.S.): Santo
padre! La porta, per favore!
Pam: I got him, just toss him
down!
Lana: I'm not tossing the
frickin pope!
Archer: Somehow this is all
your fault.
Pope: Che?
Archer: Oh for the -- this is
the pope!
Lana: Oh, then
woodhouse (o.S.) [yelp]
Woodhouse (o.S.): Oof!
Pam: Ow! Oh for shit's sake,
already!
Archer: [chuckles]
lana: Archer shut up and find
Us some -
[krunch!]
Swiss guard: Sparale!
[brrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrpt!]
lana: Oof! Transport! Are you
Shitting me?!
Archer: Well it was this or
the vespas! It's not my fault
Italy's so gay. Which, by the
way, pope, on the gay thing...
Pope: La sacra bibbia says it
is a mortal sin. But get me out
Of here alive and I will pardon
you for it, my son.
Archer: Wh-? No, I -
pam: Haaaa!
Cheryl/carol (o.S.): So why
are you scared of church stuff?
Did the unspeakable happen?
To your slender, hairless,
adolescent body?
Cyril: Wh-? No!
Cheryl/carol: Aww...
Cyril: Eww!
Cheryl/carol: Right?!
Cyril: First of all, I'm not -
I'm not scared of priests or
Nuns or -
cheryl/carol: Bishops?
Cyril: No, I just --
cheryl/carol: Bishop the
Android from aliens?
Cyril: No! I told ms. Archer
that because I didn't wanna go
On another mission with the
world's worst colleague.
Cheryl/carol: Bishop the
android from aliens?
Cyril: Archer! You think he's
a dick here? On a mission he's
Ten times worse.
Cheryl/carol: That's impossible.
Archer (o.S.) oh really?!
Pam: Yes, really! A, I was a
race car driver! And b -
Lana: Archer.
Archer: Your holiness, a
little help?!
Pam: The pope could drive
better than you!
Pope: No no, io non guido.
Pam: Ugh, esatto?
Pope: (chuckling) oh, capito...
Archer: Why're you taking her
side?! She's lutheran!
Pope: Eh, luther had some
valid complaints.
Lana: Archer! Owwwww!
Lana: Drive the ffffffffrickin
car!
Archer: Okay, lana! What is
your problem?
Lana: Well there's you... And
also that.
Archer: Why aren't they on
horseback?!
Lana: Because why would they
be?!
Archer: Right, halberdsmen are
foot-soldiers.
Pope: Mi scusi, the bigger
question is, if they really are
The swiss guards...
Pam: Why are they wearing
swiss guard uniforms, driving a
Swiss guard car?!
Pope: Esatto.
Lana: Holy sh -- it's a false
flag operation! To make it look
Like the swiss guard!
Pope: Who told you I was to be
assassinated?
Archer: Cardinal corelli! He -
lana: He wouldn't, by any
Chance, be next in line for the
papacy, would he?
Pope: Well, there would be an
election -
Archer: Right, with the smudge-
pot...
Pope: -- But corelli would be
sure to win.
Lana: Pretty good motive.
Pam: (laughing) yeah, you must
make a shitlo -
[brrrrrrrrpt!]
everybody: Ahhhhhhhh!!!
[skreeech]
lana: Go! What're you
Doing?!
Archer: I'm letting them catch
up!
Everybody: Why?!
Archer: Can I finish?! He
asked, agent-incommandingly!
Take the wheel and maintain
speed! Woodhouse, lighter!
Woodhouse: I'm only ninety
pounds wet, sir!
Archer: What? No you idiot,
your spoon-cooker!
Woodhouse: Oh right.
Archer: Like pulling teeth
with you people. Lana! Head
Toward swiss guard hq!
Lana: What, while you request
freebird?!
Archer: Ha, ha. Ha, ha, ha.
Ahh.
[brrrrrrrpt]
actually that was pretty good,
For you at least, but no, while
I do...
Shit, I had a pun about flares.
Lana: Fake dynamite?!
Pam: That's your plan?! So
hey, can I squeeze in a
Confession?
Pope: (chuckling) oho, ora
dov' il tuo martin luther?
Pam: Fine, I'll buy a damn
indulgence! Oh wait...
Archer: Wait until they're
right beside us, then swerve
Into em!
Lana: What, so you're crushed
between the -
Archer: Woohoohoohoooooooooo!
Lana: Shoulda seen that comin...
Archer: Hey, I can see st.
Peter's from -
Lana: Archer look ooouuut!
Archer: Goddammit, quit
telling me what to do! I'm the
Goddamn agent-in-command!
Pope: Figo, he really drops
the g.D. Bombs...
Pam: Plus he's a whoremonger.
Lana: Cough.
Pam: Oh please, who hasn't
paid for it?! Still talking
About indulgences.
Archer (o.S.): Lana now!
Lana: He said, last
wordsingly. Hang on!
Everybody: Ahhhh, oh!!
Driver: Sparale!
Sparale!
[brrrrrrrrrpt!]
archer: What the-?! Pam,
What'd he say?!
Pam: What do you think he
said, dicknuts?! Pay attention
To the frickin context!
Archer: Well sorry I don't
have your language-nerd skills!
Hang on... Pambit!
Pam (o.S.): Wrong x-man,
dumbass!
Archer: Still though...
[brrrrrrrrrrrrpt!]
driver: Non lui! Il papa!
Spar'al papa!
Swiss guard: Ohhhh...
Lana: Ohhh, shit! Pam!!
Pam: Get doowwwn!
Woodhouse/pope: Ungh! Ungh!
[brrrrrrrrrrrrpt!]
lana/pam: Unghh!
Archer: Lanaaaa!
Lana: Rrrgh. I'm fine!
Pam: Yeah me too, asshole!
Archer (o.S.): Oh good.
Lana: Is the pope hit?!
Pam: Uhh... No, he's, they're
both good.
Driver: Recarica! Spara di
nuovo!
Archer: Really wish I hadn't
focused so heavily on the
Romansh...
Archer [snoring]
woman's voice: Lesson
One. Leshau untg.
Pam: Context! They're
reloading!
Archer: Ohhh... That's what
you mean by context?
Driver (o.S.): Spara!
Lana: What else could she
possibly mean?!
Archer: Who am I, william
safire?! Oh and speaking of...
In the hole!
[shump]
lana: What?
Archer: Safire in the hole,
lana, it's a -
[kabrooooom!]
everybody: Waaaagh!
Archer: Lana look oooooouuuu -
[krooom!]
[car alarms blaring]
archer: Ow.
Commander: So. The good news
is, my men have apprehended
Cardinal corelli, who
immediately confessed to the
Plot.
Pam: Hey heyyy, that is good
news!
Lana: You know how the whole
"the good news is" thing works,
Right?
Commander: The bad news is -
pam: Oh right.
Commander: -- The men you
killed were camorra.
Pam: What're they, like the
mafia?
Commander: (chuckle) the
camorra is like your mafia
Like...
Lana: Seal team six is like
the girl scouts.
Commander: Exactly.
Pam: So... Equally sexy?
Lana: Eww!
Pam: Oww!
Archer (o.S.): Oww!
Archer: But the real good
news, ow! Dick! Is that we
Saved the pope's life.
Commander: For which we are
grateful. However...
We cannot tell
these two apart, so...
Archer: So I actually have an
idea about that.
Lana: Is it take them both
home, see which one's a better
Butler, and give the other one
back to the catholic church?
Archer: Never mind.
Lana: Then why don't we leave
them both here until they come
To. I'm sure woodhouse never
gets a vacation.
Archer: Are you kidding? I
didn't even let him go to his
Brother's funeral.
Pam: What?!
Lana: Oh my -- you asshole!
Was he crushed?!
Archer: Probably woulda been.
If I'd told him about it.
Lana: Ugh. But wait, why did
corelli hire isis to prevent
The assassination?
Commander: To show the
cardinals he was trying to
Prevent it, all the while
assuming -
Lana: What, that we'd totally
bl-ow my god he assumed we'd
Totally blow it?!
Commander: Well... Isis has a
certain reputation.
Archer: Hey, whoa! Not cool,
payne stewart!
Lana: Oh, my god, if malory ever
hears about this -
Archer: Which she won't!
Because pam?!
Pam: What?
Archer: Promise you'll never
tell mother!
Pam: Okay, I promise! Swear to
god!
Malory (o.S.): What?!
Archer/lana (o.S.): Pam! Pam!
Pam (o.S.): Haaaaa!?
[theme music]