[ FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING ]
>> Rick: MORTY, YOU GOT TO COME
ON.
YOU GOT TO COME WITH ME.
>> Morty: WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> Rick: I GOT A SURPRISE FOR
YOU, MORTY.
>> Morty: IT'S THE MIDDLE OF THE
NIGHT.
>> Rick: I GOT A SURPRISE FOR
YOU.
>> Morty: OW!
OW! YOU'RE TUGGING ME TOO HARD.
>> Rick: I GOT A SURPRISE FOR
YOU, MORTY.
WHAT DO YOU [BURPS] WHAT DO YOU
THINK OF THIS FLYING VEHICLE,
MORTY?
I BUILT IT OUT OF STUFF I FOUND
IN THE GARAGE.
>> Morty: YEAH, RICK, IT'S
IT'S GREAT.
IS THIS THE SURPRISE?
>> Rick: MORTY, I HAD TO I
HAD TO DO I HAD TO I HAD
TO I HAD TO MAKE A BOMB,
MORTY.
I HAD TO CREATE A BOMB.
>> Morty: WHAT?! A BOMB?!
>> Rick: WE'RE GONNA DROP IT
DOWN THERE JUST GET A WHOLE
FRESH START, MORTY.
CREATE A WHOLE FRESH START.
>> Morty: T-T-THAT'S ABSOLUTELY
CRAZY!
>> Rick: COME ON, MORTY.
JUST TAKE IT EASY, MORTY.
IT'S GONNA BE GOOD.
RIGHT NOW, WE'RE GONNA GO PICK
UP YOUR LITTLE FRIEND JESSICA.
>> Morty: JESSICA?
FROM MY MATH CLASS?
>> Rick: WHEN I DROP THE BOMB, I
DON'T YOU KNOW, I WANT YOU TO
HAVE SOMEBODY, YOU KNOW I
WANT YOU TO HAVE THE THING
I'M GONNA MAKE IT LIKE A NEW
ADAM AND EVE, AND YOU'RE GONNA
BE ADAM.
>> Morty: [ GROANS ]
>> Rick: AND JESSICA'S GONNA BE
EVE, AND SO THAT'S THE SURPRISE,
MORTY.
>> Morty: NO, YOU CAN'T!
J-JESSICA DOESN'T EVEN KNOW I
EXIST.
BUT BUT BUT FORGET ABOUT
THAT, BECAUSE YOU CAN'T BLOW UP
HUMANITY.
>> Rick: I-I GET WHAT YOU'RE
TRYING TO SAY, M-MORTY.
LISTEN, I'M NOT YOU DON'T
Y-Y-YOU DON'T GOT TO WORRY ABOUT
ME TRYING TO FOOL AROUND WITH
WITH JESSICA OR MESS AROUND WITH
JESSICA OR ANYTHING.
I'M I'M NOT THAT KIND OF GUY,
MORTY.
>> Morty: WHAT ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT, RICK?
>> Rick: YOU YOU YOU DON'T
HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT ME GETTING
WITH JESSICA OR ANYTHING.
SHE SHE SHE SHE
SHE'S ALL FOR YOU, MORTY.
>> Morty: I DON'T CARE ABOUT
JESSICA!
>> Rick: YOU KNOW WHAT, MORTY?
YOU'RE RIGHT.
LET'S FORGET THE GIRL ALL
TOGETHER.
SHE SHE'S PROBABLY NOTHING
BUT TROUBLE, ANYWAYS.
>> ARMING NEUTRINO BOMB.
>> Morty: THAT'S IT THAT'S
IT, RICK.
I'M TAKING THE WHEEL.
>> Rick: GET OFF OF ME, MORTY!
>> Morty: I'M TAKING CHARGE OF
THIS SITUATION, BUDDY.
>> Rick: WHAT'S GOTTEN INTO YOU?
>> Morty: I'M I'M I'M
I'M NOT GONNA STAND AROUND LIKE
SOME SORT OF DUMB...
>> Rick: WHAT ARE YOU, CRAZY?
>> Morty:... PERSON AND JUST
LET YOU BLOW UP THE WHOLE WORLD.
>> Rick: ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
I'LL I'LL LAND.
I'LL LAND. I'LL LAND.
I'LL LAND THE THING.
BIG TOUGH GUY ALL OF A SUDDEN.
WE'LL PARK IT RIGHT HERE, MORTY.
RIGHT HERE ON THE S-SIDE OF THE
R-ROAD HERE.
>> Morty: OH, THANK GOD.
>> Rick: YOU KNOW WHAT?
THAT WAS ALL A TEST, MORTY.
JUST AN ELABORATE TEST TO MAKE
YOU MORE ASSERTIVE.
>> Morty: IT WAS?
>> Rick: SURE. WHY NOT?
I DON'T I DON'T KNOW.
YOU YOU KNOW WHAT, MO
[ SNORING ]
>> NEUTRINO BOMB ARMED.
[ BEEPING ]
>> Morty: UM...
[ BEEPING INCREASES ]
>> Jerry: I SEE THERE'S A NEW
EPISODE OF THAT SINGING SHOW
TONIGHT.
WHO DO YOU GUYS THINK IS GONNA
BE THE BEST SINGER?
>> Summer: OH, MY GOD.
HIS HEAD IS IN HIS FOOD.
I'M GOING TO PUKE.
>> Beth: MORTY, ARE YOU GETTING
SICK?
I TOLD YOU NOT TO PRACTICE-KISS
THE LIVING-ROOM PILLOW.
THE DOG SLEEPS ON IT.
>> Morty: I WASN'T KISSING A
PILLOW, MOM.
I JUST I DIDN'T GET A LOT OF
SLEEP LAST NIGHT.
MAYBE MY DREAMS WERE JUST TOO
LOUD OR SOMETHING.
>> Summer: OR MAYBE YOU WERE OUT
ALL NIGHT AGAIN WITH
GRANDPA RICK.
>> Jerry: WHAT?!
>> Beth: DAD?
>> Rick: WHAT, SO EVERYONE'S
SUPPOSED TO SLEEP EVERY SINGLE
NIGHT NOW?
YOU REALIZE THAT NIGHTTIME MAKES
UP HALF OF ALL TIME?
>> Jerry: DAMN IT!
>> Beth: JERRY!
>> Jerry: BETH!
>> Summer: OH, MY GOD.
MY PARENTS ARE SO LOUD.
I WANT TO DIE.
>> Rick: MM, THERE IS NO GOD,
SUMMER.
YOU GOT TO RIP THAT BAND-AID OFF
NOW.
YOU'LL THANK ME LATER.
>> Jerry: OKAY, WITH ALL DUE
RESPECT, RICK WHAT AM I
TALKING ABOUT?
WHAT RESPECT IS DUE?
HOW IS MY SON SUPPOSED TO PASS
HIS CLASSES IF YOU KEEP DRAGGING
HIM OFF FOR HIGH-CONCEPT SCI-FI
RIGAMAROLE?
>> Rick: LISTEN, JERRY, I-I
DON'T WANT TO OVERSTEP MY BOUNDS
OR ANYTHING.
IT'S YOUR HOUSE.
IT'S YOUR WORLD.
YOU'RE A REAL JULIUS CAESAR.
BUT I'LL TELL YOU SOME TELL
YOU HOW HOW I FEEL ABOUT
SCHOOL, JERRY.
IT'S A WASTE OF TIME A BUNCH
OF PEOPLE RUNNING AROUND,
BUMPING INTO EACH OTHER.
G-GUY UP FRONT SAYS, "TWO PLUS
TWO."
THE PEOPLE IN THE BACK SAY,
"FOUR."
THEN THE BELL RINGS, AND THEY
GIVE YOU A CARTON OF MILK AND A
PCE OF PAPER THAT SAYS YOU CAN
GO TAKE A DUMP OR SOMETHING.
I MEAN, IT'S IT'S NOT A PLACE
FOR SMART PEOPLE, JERRY.
AND I KNOW THAT'S NOT A POPULAR
OPINION, BUT IT'S MY TWO CENTS
ON THE ISSUE.
THIS WAS A GOOD BREAKFAST, BETH.
YOU REALLY MADE THE CRAP OUT OF
THOSE EGGS.
I WISH YOUR MOTHER WAS HERE TO
EAT THEM.
>> Beth: OH, DAD.
>> Jerry: WHAT?
FOR REAL?
>> ALL RIGHT, NOW, EVERYBODY GET
SETTLED.
GET AWAY FROM THE WINDOWS!
NOW, LOOK, WE'RE GONNA BE
DEALING WITH SOME REAL SERIOUS
STUFF TODAY.
YOU MIGHT HAVE HEARD OF IT.
IT'S CALLED MATH.
AND WITHOUT IT, NONE OF US WOULD
EVEN EXIST, SO LET'S JUMP RIGHT
IN TWO PLUS TWO.
>> Morty: JESSICA.
>> FIVE PLUS FIVE.
>> Morty: TENSSICA.
>> OKAY, GOOD.
IT'S TIME FOR THE QUIZ.
[ ALL GROAN ]
YEAH, YOU KNOW WHAT?!
AW, TOO BAD!
TOUGH!
FIRST ROW, TAKE ONE.
PASS IT BACK FOR ME.
THE STAKES ARE HIGH IN THIS
ROOM.
THERE'S CRUCIAL THINGS HAPPENING
HERE EVERY DAY.
PEOPLE GETTING SMARTER.
SOME OF Y'ALL GETTING DUMBER.
SOME OF Y'ALL AIN'T GONNA SEE
3:00.
>> HI, MORTY.
>> Morty: WHOA!
HI, JESSICA.
>> CAN I SHOW THESE TO YOU?
>> Morty: WOW.
TH-THEY'RE BOTH GREAT.
THANK YOU.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT I NAMED THESE?
MY LITTLE MORTIES.
>> Morty: UH, THAT'S
FLATTERING... AND A LITTLE WEIRD.
>> DO YOU KNOW WHAT I WANT YOU
TO DO WITH THEM?
>> Morty: RENAME THEM?
>> SQUEEZE THEM.
MANHANDLE THEM.
GIVE THEM THE BUSINESS.
SEE IF YOU CAN SHUFFLE THEM.
I MEAN, REALLY GET IN THERE AND
KNOCK THEM AROUND.
NO WRONG ANSWERS.
>> Morty: WOW.
WELL, OKAY, JESSICA.
L-LET'S GIVE THIS A SHOT.
>> MM.
OH, MORTY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING TO ME?
>> Morty: UH, I-I'M JUST DOING
MY BEST.
>> MORTY!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING TO ME?!
>> Morty: JESSICA.
>> MORTY!
>> Morty: [ Mumbling ] JESSICA.
>> FIVE MORE MINUTES OF THIS,
AND I'M GONNA GET MAD.
>> Morty: JE-JESSICA.
[ Mumbling ] JESSICA.
>> NOT MY FAULT THIS IS
HAPPENING.
[ SCHOOL BELL RINGS ]
>> WELL, WELL, WELL.
>> Morty: UH, MORNING, FRANK.
>> "MORNING"?
WHAT WAS WHAT IS THAT
SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
YOU MAKING FUN OF ME?
ARE YOU TRYING TO SAY MY
FAMILY'S POOR?
>> Morty: OH, GEEZ, FRANK.
I DON'T KNOW IF A KNIFE IS
NECESSARY.
I MEAN, YOU KNOW, Y-YOU KIND OF
HAD THINGS HANDLED WITHOUT IT.
>> YOU TELLING ME HOW TO BULLY
NOW?
BIG MISTAKE, MORTY.
AND NOW I'M GONNA CUT YOU,
'CAUSE MY FAMILY'S RICH.
[ GASPS ]
>> Rick: THERE YOU ARE, MORTY.
LISTEN TO ME.
I GOT AN ERRAND TO RUN IN A
WHOLE DIFFERENT DIMENSION.
I NEED AN EXTRA PAIR OF HANDS.
>> Morty: OH, GEEZ, RICK.
W-WHAT'D YOU DO TO FRANK?
>> Rick: IT'S PRETTY OBVIOUS,
MORTY.
I FROZE HIM.
NOW LISTEN I NEED YOUR HELP,
MORTY.
I MEAN, WE GOT WE GOT TO
GET GET THE HELL OUT OF HERE
AND GO TAKE CARE OF BUSINESS.
[ BURPS ]
IT'S IMPORTANT. COME ON, MORTY.
>> Morty: I DON'T KNOW, RICK.
I-I CAN'T LEAVE SCHOOL AGAIN.
>> Rick: DO YOU HAVE ANY CONCEPT
OF HOW MUCH HIGHER THE STAKES
GET OUT THERE, MORTY?
WHAT DO YOU THINK I CAN JUST
DO IT ALL BY MYSELF?
COME ON!
>> Morty: AW, GEEZ. OKAY.
I GUESS I CAN SKIP HISTORY.
WHAT ABOUT FRANK?
I MEAN, SHOULDN'T YOU UNFREEZE
HIM?
>> Rick: I'LL DO IT LATER,
MORTY.
HE'LL BE FINE.
LET'S GO.
>> Summer: [ Thinking ] OH, MY
GOD.
I'M ABOUT TO WALK PAST
FRANK PALICKY.
THIS IS THE STORY WE'LL BE
TELLING OUR CHILDREN.
HI, FRANK.
[ CRACKS, SHATTERS ]
AAH!
[ HORSE WHINNYING ]
>> Beth: SCALPEL.
>> SCALPEL.
[ DOOR OPENS ]
>> Jerry: KNOCK, KNOCK.
>> Beth: JERRY?
>> Jerry: MY MANAGER GAVE ME AN
HOUR FOR LUNCH, AND I THOUGHT,
"HEY, WHY NOT SWING BY WHERE
YOUR WIFE WORKS?"
[ FLATLINE ]
>> WE'RE LOSING HIM.
[ BEEPS ]
OKAY, HE'S BACK.
>> Beth: JERRY, PLEASE TELL ME
YOU'RE HERE FOR AN INCREDIBLY
URGENT REASON.
>> Jerry: WELL, IT'S LUNCH.
I MEAN, IT'S ONE OF THREE MEALS
THAT HAVE EXISTED FOR MILLENNIA.
[ FLATLINE ]
>> LOSING HIM.
[ BEEPS ]
STABILIZED.
>> Beth: OKAY, I ONLY ASK,
JERRY, BECAUSE, AS YOU KNOW, MY
JOB INVOLVES PERFORMING HEART
SURGERY.
>> Jerry: WELL, YEAH, ON HORSES.
>> Beth: EXCUSE ME?
>> Jerry: OKAY.
LET'S NOT REHASH THATFIGHT.
I SENSE THAT YOU'RE BUSY AND
WILL NOW BE ON MY WAY.
WHOA!
WHAT IS THIS ON THE FLOOR?
SOME KIND OF LITERATURE FOR A
REALLY NICE-LOOKING NURSING
HOME.
HEY, HONEY, CRAZY IDEA BAD
PITCH LET'S PUT YOUR DAD
HERE.
LET'S PUT YOUR DAD IN A NURSING
HOME.
[ FLATLINE ]
>> WE'RE LOSING HIM.
>> Beth: HEY, TOM.
WE KNOW WHEN WE'RE LOSING HIM.
WE CAN HEAR THE BEEPS!
>> Rick: THERE SHE IS.
ALL RIGHT.
COME ON, MORTY. LET'S GO.
>> Morty: OH, GEEZ.
OKAY.
OH, MAN, RICK.
WHAT IS THIS PLACE?
>> Rick: IT'S DIMENSION 35C, AND
IT'S GOT THE PERFECT CLIMATE
CONDITIONS FOR A SPECIAL TYPE OF
TREE, MORTY, CALLED A MEGA TREE,
AND THERE'S FRUIT IN THOSE
TREES, AND THERE'S SEEDS IN
THOSE FRUITS.
I'M TALKING ABOUT MEGA SEEDS.
THEY'RE [Burping] THEY'RE
INCREDIBLY POWERFUL, AND I NEED
THEM TO HELP ME WITH MY
RESEARCH, MORTY.
>> Morty: OH, MAN, RICK.
I'M LOOKING AROUND THIS PLACE,
AND I'M STARTING TO WORK UP SOME
ANXIETY ABOUT THIS WHOLE THING.
>> Rick: ALL RIGHT. ALL RIGHT.
CALM DOWN. LISTEN TO ME, MORTY.
I KNOW THAT NEW SITUATIONS CAN
BE INTIMIDATING.
YOU'RE LOOKING AROUND, AND IT'S
ALL SCARY AND DIFFERENT, BUT,
YOU KNOW, M-MEETING THEM HEAD
ON, CHARGING RIGHT INTO THEM
LIKE A BULL THAT'S HOW WE
GROW AS PEOPLE.
I'M NO STRANGER TO SCARY
SITUATIONS.
I DEAL WITH THEM ALL THE TIME.
NOW, IF YOU JUST STICK WITH ME,
MORTY, WE'RE GONNA BE HOLY
CRAP, MORTY, RUN!
>> Morty: [ SCREAMING ]
>> Rick: I NEVER SEEN THAT THING
BEFORE IN MY LIFE.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT THE HELL
IT IS!
WE GOT TO GET OUT OF HERE,
MORTY!
IT'S GONNA KILL US!
WE'RE GONNA DIE!
WE'RE GONNA DIE, MORTY!
>> Rick: OH, MORTY, TAKE A DEEP
BREATH.
BREATHE THAT BREATHE THAT
FRESH AIR IN, MORTY.
Y-YOU SMELL THAT?
THAT'S THE SMELL OF ADVENTURE,
MORTY.
THAT'S THAT'S THE SMELL OF
OF OF OF A WHOLE DIFFERENT
EVOLUTIONARY TIMELINE.
>> Morty: ALL RIGHT, RICK,
LOOK HOW MUCH LONGER IS THIS
GONNA BE?
SHOULDN'T I BE BACK AT SCHOOL BY
NOW?
>> Rick: ARE YOU JOKING ME?
I MEAN, LOOK AT ALL THE CRAZY
CRAP SURROUNDING US.
LOOK AT THAT THING RIGHT THERE.
W-WHAT THE HELL IS THAT THING?
YOU THINK YOU'RE GONNA SEE THAT
KIND OF THING AT SCHOOL?
LOOK AT IT JUST LUMBERING
AROUND.
IT DEFIES ALL LOGIC THAT
THING.
>> Morty: YEAH, RICK, I GET IT.
WE'RE SURROUNDED BY MONSTERS.
THAT'S KIND OF THE REASON WHY I
WANT TO LEAVE.
>> Rick: TA-TA-TA-TA-TA-TA.
MORTY, YOU SEE THIS?
YOU SEE WHAT WE JUST STUMBLED
UPON, MORTY?
ANY IDEA WHAT THAT IS DOWN
THERE?
>> Morty: THE MEGA TREES?
>> Rick: THAT'S RIGHT, MORTY
THE MEGA TREES WITH THE MEGA
FRUIT ON THEM.
AND THAT'S WHAT I'M TALKING
ABOUT, MORTY.
THAT'S WHERE MY SEEDS ARE.
IF WE WOULD HAVE DONE WHAT YOU
WANTED, I WOULD HAVE NEVER HAVE
FOUND THEM, BECAUSE Y BECAUSE
YOU'RE SO IN LOVE WITH SCHOOL.
>> Morty: ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
SO, WHAT'S SO SPECIAL ABOUT
THESE SEEDS, ANYWAYS?
>> Rick: YOU ASK A LOT OF
QUESTIONS, MORTY.
NOT VERY CHARISMATIC.
IT MAKES YOU KIND OF AN [BURPS]
UNDER [BURPS] UNDERFOOT
FIGURE.
JUST TAKE THESE SHOES, MORTY.
THEY'RE SP [BURPS] SPECIAL
GRAPPLING SHOES.
WHEN YOU'RE WEARING THESE
THINGS BA THESE BABIES,
YOU CAN BASICALLY JUST WALK ON
ANY SURFACE YOU WANT, MORTY
UP, DOWN, BELOW, TURN AROUND TO
THE LEFT.
THESE THINGS REALLY BRING IT ALL
TOGETHER.
>> Morty: AAH!
>> Rick: YOU HAVE TO TURN THEM
ON, MORTY!
[ THUDS ]
THE SHOES HAVE TO BE TURNED ON!
>> Beth: I AM NOT PUTTING MY
FATHER IN A HOME!
HE JUST CAME BACK INTO MY LIFE,
AND YOU WANT TO GRAB HIM AND
STUFF HIM UNDER A MATTRESS LIKE
LAST MONTH'S VICTORIA'S SECRET?
>> Jerry: I TOLD YOU I WAS
ORDERING YOU SOMETHING FOR
VALENTINE'S DAY.
MORE IMPORTANTLY, YOUR FATHER IS
A HORRIBLE INFLUENCE ON OUR SON.
>> EVERYTHING COOL IN HERE,
BETH?
>> Beth: IT'S FINE, DAVIN.
>> OKAY, COOL.
YOU KNOW, WE DID SOMETHING GREAT
TODAY.
THERE'S NOTHING MORE NOBLE AND
FREE THAN THE HEART OF A HORSE.
>> Jerry: SINCE WE'RE FIGHTING,
IF YOU EVER HAVE AN AFFAIR WITH
THAT GUY, I WILL COME TO THE
HOTEL ROOM AND BLOW MY BRAINS
OUT ALL OVER YOUR NAKED BODIES.
>> Beth: LOOK, I APPRECIATE THE
STRESS YOU'RE UNDER, BUT MORTY
WAS HAVING TROUBLE IN SCHOOL WAY
BEFORE MY DAD MOVED IN, AND THE
ONLY INFLUENCE I CAN SEE RICK
HAVING IS THAT, FOR THE FIRST
TIME IN HIS LIFE, MORTY HAS A
FRIEND.
[ TELEPHONE RINGING ]
>> Jerry: [ SIGHS ]
WELL, MAYBE YOU'RE RIGHT.
>> Beth: UH, YEAH, MAYBE I AM.
I'M MY FATHER'S DAUGHTER.
I'M SMART.
WHY DO YOU THINK I'M A HEART
SURGEON?
>> Jerry: HORSE HEART SURGEON.
>> Beth: HELLO?
>> MRS. SMITH?
THIS IS PRINCIPAL VAGINA NO
RELATION.
I WONDER IF YOU AND MORTY'S
FATHER MIGHT BE ABLE TO HAVE A
CHAT WITH ME THIS AFTERNOON?
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> Rick: MORTY, OH, YOU REALLY
D-DID A NUMBER ON YOUR LEGS
RIGHT NOW.
>> Morty: [ GROANING ]
>> Rick: YOU KNOW, YOU GOT TO
TURN THE SHOES ON, MORTY, FOR
THEM TO WORK.
YEAH, LOOK I TURNED MINE ON.
I HAD NO PROBLEM GETTING DOWN
HERE.
IT WAS A LEISURELY BREEZE.
>> Morty: I'M IN A LOT OF PAIN,
RICK.
>> Rick: YEAH, I CAN SEE THAT.
BUT DO YOU THINK YOU'LL STILL BE
ABLE TO HELP ME [BURPS] COLLECT
MY SEEDS, MORTY?
>> Morty: ARE YOU KIDDING ME?!
THAT'S IT, RICK!
THAT'S THE LAST STRAW!
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS I'M
SITTING HERE WITH BOTH OF MY
LEGS BROKEN, AND YOU'RE STILL
ASKING ME ABOUT GETTING THOSE
SEEDS?!
OOH! OW! OH!
Y-Y-YOU'RE A MONSTER.
Y-YOU'RE LIKE HITLER, BUT
BUT EVEN HITLER CARED ABOUT
GERMANY OR SOMETHING.
>> Rick: OKAY, HOLD ON JUST A
SECOND, MORTY.
>> Morty: [ GROANING ]
[ PANTING ]
OOH.
OHH.
WOW, RICK.
THAT STUFF JUST HEALED MY BROKEN
LEGS INSTANTLY.
I MEAN, I'VE NEVER FELT SO GOOD
IN MY LIFE.
THANK YOU.
>> Rick: DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT,
MORTY.
JUST COME HELP ME GET THESE
SEEDS, ALL RIGHT, BUDDY?
>> Morty: SURE THING, RICK.
>> Rick: NOT THAT YOU ASKED,
MORTY, BUT WHAT JUST HAPPENED
THERE IS I WENT INTO A FUTURE
DIMENSION WITH SUCH ADVANCED
MEDICINE THAT THEY HAD
BROKEN-LEG SERUM AT EVERY CORNER
DRUGSTORE.
THE STUFF WAS ALL OVER THE
PLACE, MORTY.
>> Morty: WOW, THAT'S PRETTY
CRAZY, RICK.
>> Rick: THERE'S JUST ONE
PROBLEM, MORTY ONE LITTLE
HANG-UP.
THE DIMENSION I VISITED WAS SO
ADVANCED, THEY HAD ALSO HALTED
THE AGING PROCESS, AND EVERYONE
THERE WAS YOUNG, MORTY, AND THEY
HAD BEEN FOREVER.
I WAS THE ONLY OLD PERSON THERE,
MORTY.
IT WAS [BURPS] LIKE I WAS SOME
SORT OF, YOU KNOW, CELEBRITY,
WALKING AROUND.
I-I WAS FASCINATING TO THEM.
THERE WERE A LOT OF ATTRACTIVE
WOMEN THERE, MORTY, AND THEY
THEY THEY THEY ALL WANTED
TIME WITH ME.
I HAD A LOT OF FUN WITH A LOT OF
YOUNG LADIES, BUT I SPENT SO
MUCH TIME THERE, MY
INTERDIMENSIONAL PORTAL
DEVICE IT'S GOT NO CHARGE
LEFT, MORTY.
IT'S GOT NO CHARGE LEFT.
>> Morty: WHAT?!
>> Rick: IT'S AS GOOD AS
GARBAGE, MORTY.
IT'S NOT GONNA WORK ANYMORE,
MORTY.
>> Morty: OH, GEEZ, RICK, THAT'S
NOT GOOD.
W-WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO?
I-I HAVE TO BE BACK AT SCHOOL
RIGHT NOW.
HOW ARE WE GONNA GET BACK HOME?
>> Rick: THERE'S WAYS TO GET
BACK HOME, MORTY.
IT'S JUST IT'S JUST GONNA BE
A LITTLE BIT OF A HASSLE.
WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO GO THROUGH
INTERDIMENSIONAL CUSTOMS, SO
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO DO ME A
REAL SOLID.
>> Morty: UH-OH.
>> Rick: WHEN WE GET TO CUSTOMS,
I'M GONNA NEED YOU TO TAKE THESE
SEEDS INTO THE BATHROOM, AND I'M
GONNA NEED YOU TO PUT THEM WAY
UP INSIDE YOUR BUTTHOLE, MORTY.
>> Morty: IN MY BUTT?
>> Rick: PUT THEM WAY UP INSIDE
THERE, AS FAR AS THEY CAN FIT.
>> Morty: OH, GEEZ, RICK.
I REALLY DON'T WANT TO HAVE TO
DO THAT.
>> Rick: WELL, SOMEBODY'S GOT TO
DO IT, MORTY.
TH-THESE SEEDS AREN'T GONNA GET
THROUGH CUSTOMS UNLESS THEY'RE
IN SOMEONE'S RECTUM, MORTY.
>> Morty: [ WHIMPERS ]
>> Rick: AND THEY'LL FALL RIGHT
OUT OF MINE.
I'VE DONE THIS TOO MANY TIMES,
MORTY.
I MEAN, YOU'RE YOUNG.
YOU'VE GOT YOUR WHOLE LIFE AHEAD
OF YOU, AND YOUR ANAL CAVITY IS
STILL TAUT, YET MALLEABLE.
YOU GOT TO DO IT FOR GRANDPA,
MORTY.
Y-YOU'VE GOT TO PUT THESE SEEDS
INSIDE YOUR BUTT.
>> Morty: IN MY BUTT?
>> Rick: COME ON, MORTY.
PLEASE, MORTY.
YOU HAVE TO DO IT, MORTY.
>> Morty: OH, MAN.
[ SCHOOL BELL RINGS ]
>> THE FACT IS, YOUR SON, MORTY,
HAS ATTENDED THIS SCHOOL FOR A
TOTAL OF SEVEN HOURS OVER THE
LAST TWO MONTHS.
>> Beth: WHAT?
WHY DIDN'T YOU NOTIFY US?
>> I DONE BEEN NOTIFYING YOU.
HAVE YOU NOT BEEN GETTING THE
MESSAGES I'VE BEEN LEAVING WITH
MORTY'S GRANDFATHER?
>> Jerry: BOOM!
TOLD YOU! IN YOUR FACE!
HE IS RUINING OUR CHILD!
WAIT, WHAT AM I CELEBRATING?
>> YEAH, SEE, I THOUGHT
SOMETHING WAS FISHY THERE,
BECAUSE IT'S USUALLY MORTY'S
GRANDPA THAT'S TAKING HIM OUT OF
SCHOOL.
>> Beth: SUMMER?
>> Summer: [ Sobbing ] WHAT KIND
OF GOD LETS THIS HAPPEN?
>> WE HAD A LITTLE INCIDENT.
A STUDENT WAS FROZEN TO DEATH.
AND THERE'S NO EVIDENCE THAT A
LATINO STUDENT DID IT!
EVERYONE WANTS TO TAKE THIS TO A
RACIAL PLACE.
I WON'T LET THEM.
>> THE GLARP ZONE IS FOR
FLARPING AND UNGLARPING ONLY.
>> SO, I TOLD HIM, "GIVE ME THE
BLIMFARX," YOU KNOW?
THIS THIS GUY HE DOESN'T
UNDERSTAND INTERSTELLAR
CURRENCY.
>> IT'S, LIKE, I'M TRYING TO EAT
A FLIMFLAM LIKE, THAT'S WHAT
WE EAT ON GIRVONESK.
>> THE GLARP ZONE IS FOR
FLARPING AND UNGLARPING ONLY.
>> Rick: I DON'T LIKE IT HERE,
MORTY.
I CAN'T ABIDE BUREAUCRACY.
I DON'T LIKE BEING TOLD WHERE TO
GO AND WHAT TO DO.
I CONSIDER IT A VIOLATION.
DID YOU GET THOSE SEEDS ALL THE
WAY UP YOUR BUTT?
>> Morty: YEAH, RICK.
LET'S JUST GET THIS OVER WITH,
OKAY?
I MEAN, THESE THINGS ARE POINTY.
THEY HURT.
>> Rick: THAT MEANS THEY'RE GOOD
ONES.
YOU'RE A GOOD KID, MORTY.
THOSE MEGA SEEDS ARE SUPER
VALUABLE TO MY WORK.
YOU'VE BEEN A HUGE HELP TO ME.
I'M GONNA BE ABLE TO DO [BURPS]
ALL KIND OF THINGS WITH THEM.
IT'S GONNA BE GREAT, MORTY.
[ BURPS ] ALL KINDS OF SCIENCE.
>> OKAY, NEXT THROUGH.
EXCEPT YOU. YOU GO OVER THERE.
>> Rick: WHY DOES HE HAVE TO GO
OVER THERE?
>> RANDOM CHECK.
HE'S GOT TO GO THROUGH THE NEW
MACHINE.
>> Rick: WHAT NEW [BURPS]
WHAT NEW MACHINE?
>> IT'S A NEW MACHINE.
IT DETECTS STUFF ALL THE WAY UP
YOUR BUTT.
>> Rick: RUN, MORTY! RUN!
>> Morty: AAH!
>> RED ALERT!
[ ALARMS BLARING ]
>> Rick: [ GRUNTS ]
>> [ SCREECHING ]
>> Morty: OHHHHH!
[ COUGHS ]
>> [ CRYING ]
>> Morty: [ COUGHING ]
>> HEY! OHHHHHH.
[ GROANS ]
>> Morty: AAH!
>> Rick: DON'T THINK ABOUT IT!
>> Morty: OOH!
[ SHOES BEEPING ]
>> Rick: OH, NICE, MORTY!
THE STUDENT BECOMES THE TEACHER.
[ BUZZING ]
[ BOTH SCREAMING ]
[ BOTH GRUNT ]
>> Morty: WHOOOOOO!
AAH!
>> AW, HELL, NO, DAWG.
YOU KNOW ME I'M JUST TRYING
TO
>> Morty: AAH!
>> Rick: I NEED TO TYPE IN THE
COORDINATES TO OUR HOME WORLD,
MORTY.
COVER ME.
>> Morty: OH, MAN.
I MEAN, YOU KNOW, I-I DON'T WANT
TO SHOOT NOBODY.
>> Rick: THEY'RE JUST ROBOTS,
MORTY!
IT'S OKAY TO SHOOT THEM!
THEY'RE ROBOTS!
>> AAH!
MY LEG IS SHOT OFF!
>> GLENN'S BLEEDING TO DEATH!
SOMEONE CALL HIS WIFE AND
CHILDREN!
>> Morty: THEY'RE NOT ROBOTS,
RICK!
>> Rick: IT'S A FIGURE OF
SPEECH, MORTY.
THEY'RE BUREAUCRATS.
I DON'T RESPECT THEM.
JUST KEEP SHOOTING, MORTY.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA WHAT PRISON IS
LIKE HERE!
>> Morty: HOLY CRAP!
THIS IS INSANE!
[ CROWD SCREAMING ]
>> Rick: COME ON, MORTY!
WE GOT TO GET THE HELL OUT OF
HERE!
[ ALL GASP ]
>> WOW.
DID YOU JUST COME INTO THE
CAFETERIA THROUGH A PORTAL?
>> Morty: UH, YEAH.
WELL, YOU KNOW, MY MY
FERRARI'S IN THE SHOP.
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
JU JUST KIDDING.
>> YOU'RE MORTY, RIGHT?
>> Morty: YEAH.
>> Rick: YOU CAN GET HIS NUMBER
LATER.
COME ON, MORTY.
WE GOT TO GET OUT OF HERE.
YOU GOT TO GET THOSE SEEDS OUT
OF YOUR ASS.
>> Jerry: OH, LOOK, HONEY.
IT'S OUR SON WITH
ALBERT EIN-DOUCHE.
>> Beth: WHAT?
>> Jerry: I'M AN ANGRY FATHER,
NOT AN IMPROVISOR.
>> Rick: OH, HI, JERRY.
OH, MY GOODNESS, MORTY!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING OUT OF CLASS?
WE TALKED ABOUT THIS.
YOUR YOUR PARENTS AND I ARE
VERY DISAPPOINTED IN IN THIS
BEHAVIOR.
NO? NO TAKERS?
YOU GUYS SHOULD REALLY NOT BE
TOUCHING THAT STUFF.
IT'S BEYOND YOUR REASONING.
>> Jerry: YOU'REBEYOND OUR
REASONING!
>> Rick: TAKES ONE TO KNOW ONE.
>> Beth: DAD, HOW COULD YOU MAKE
MY SON MISS AN ENTIRE SEMESTER
OF SCHOOL?
I MEAN, IT'S NOT LIKE HE'S A HOT
GIRL.
HE CAN'T JUST BAIL ON HIS LIFE
AND SET UP SHOP IN SOMEONE
ELSE'S.
>> Rick: WHAT WHAT ARE YOU
GUYS DOING WITH MY STUFF?
>> Beth: WE'RE MOVING YOU... TO A
NURSING HOME.
>> Rick: A NURSING HOME?
WHAT ARE WHAT ARE YOU, NUTS?
I'M A GENIUS.
I BUILD ROBOTS FOR FUN.
>> Jerry: WELL, NOW YOU CAN
BUILD BASKETS AND WATCH
PAUL NEWMAN MOVIES ON VHS AND
MENTALLY SCAR THE BOY SCOUTS
EVERY CHRISTMAS.
>> Beth: WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
>> Jerry: IT'S PERSONAL.
>> Morty: DAD, MOM, C-COME ON.
RICK JUST NEEDED MY HELP IS ALL.
>> Jerry: MORTY, STAY OUT OF
THIS.
YOU ARE OBVIOUSLY NOT CAPABLE OF
JUDGING THESE SITUATIONS ON YOUR
OWN.
>> Rick: WHAT ARE YOU TRYING TO
SAY ABOUT MORTY?
THAT HE'S STUPID OR SOMETHING?
>> Beth: OH, DON'T HIGH-ROAD US,
DAD.
YOU KNOW FULLY WELL THAT MORTY
IS THE LAST CHILD THAT NEEDS TO
BE MISSING CLASSES.
>> Rick: I-I-I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU MEAN BY THAT.
CAN CAN CAN YOU BE A
LITTLE BIT MORE SPECIFIC?
>> Jerry: OH, FOR CRYING OUT
HE'S GOT SOME KIND OF
DISABILITY OR SOMETHING.
IS THAT WHAT YOU WANT US TO SAY?
>> Morty: I DO?
>> Jerry: WELL, DUH DOY, SON.
LOOK, I LOVE YOU, MORTY, BUT WE
BOTH KNOW YOU'RE NOT AS FAST AS
THE OTHER KIDS, AND IF YOU WANT
TO COMPETE IN THIS WORLD, YOU
GOT TO WORK TWICE AS HARD.
>> Morty: AW, GEEZ, DAD.
Y-YOU KNOW, THAT'S A LOT TO DROP
ON A KID ALL AT ONCE.
>> Rick: MORTY, T-TELL YOUR
PARENTS THE SQUARE ROOT OF PI.
>> Morty: OH, COME ON, RICK.
YOU KNOW I CAN'T.
>> Rick: THE SQUARE ROOT OF PI,
MORTY GO.
>> Morty: 1.77245385.
WHOA!
>> Beth: WHAT THE HELL?
>> Jerry: HOLY CRAP. HE'S RIGHT.
>> Rick: MORTY, TELL YOUR
PARENTS THE FIRST LAW OF [BURPS]
THERMODYNAMICS.
>> Morty: "THE INCREMENT IN THE
INTERNAL ENERGY OF A SYSTEM IS
EQUAL TO THE INCREMENT OF HEAT
SUPPLIED TO THE SYSTEM."
WOW! I'M SO SMART!
>> Jerry: BUT
>> Rick: I TOLD THE BOTH OF
YOU SCHOOL IS STUPID.
IT'S NOT HOW YOU LEARN THINGS.
MORTY'S A GIFTED CHILD.
HE HAS A SPECIAL MIND.
THAT'S WHY HE'S MY LITTLE
HELPER.
HE'S LIKE ME.
HE'S GONNA BE DOING GREAT
SCIENCE STUFF LATER IN HIS LIFE.
HE'S TOO SMART FOR SCHOOL.
H-HE NEEDS TO KEEP HANGING OUT
[BURPS] AND HELPING ME.
>> Beth: JERRY, I DON'T WANT
WHATEVER'S HAPPENING HERE TO
STOP.
>> Jerry: NO, I-I UNDERSTAND.
UH, MAYBE WE OVERREACTED.
BUT HE HAS TO KEEP GOING TO
SCHOOL.
>> Rick: OKAY, JERRY.
YOU DRIVE A HARD BARGAIN, BUT
[BURPS] WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO
DO?
SAY [BURPS] SAY NO?
YOU YOU REALLY WEAR THE PANTS
AROUND HERE.
I JUST WANT YOU TO KNOW, BETWEEN
US, FROM NOW ON, IT'S GONNA BE
100% HONESTY AND OPEN, CLEAR
COMMUNICATION.
>> Summer: FRANK PALICKY WAS
FROZEN TO DEATH TODAY!
>> Rick: NO IDEA WHAT YOU'RE
TALKING ABOUT.
>> Summer: [ SOBBING ]
>> Jerry: OKAY.
WELL, UH, MORTY, IT'S YOUR
BEDTIME IN AN HOUR.
DON'T STAY UP ALL NIGHT AGAIN.
THIS IS GOOD, THOUGH.
THIS CAN WORK.
I THINK WE CAN BE A FAMILY.
AND NOW, BETH, IF YOU'LL HAVE
ME, I WOULD LOVE TO HAVE YOU.
>> Beth: YOU KNOW WHAT?
OKAY.
>> Morty: HOLY COW, RICK.
I DIDN'T KNOW HANGING OUT WITH
YOU WAS MAKING ME SMARTER.
>> Rick: FULL DISCLOSURE,
MORTY IT'S NOT.
TEMPORARY SUPERINTELLIGENCE IS
JUST A SIDE EFFECT OF THE MEGA
SEEDS DISSOLVING IN YOUR RECTAL
CAVITY.
>> Morty: AW, MAN.
>> Rick: YEAH, AND ONCE THOSE
SEEDS [BURPS] WEAR OFF, YOU'RE
GONNA LOSE MOST OF YOUR MOTOR
SKILLS, AND YOU'RE ALSO GONNA
LOSE A SIGNIFICANT AMOUNT OF
BRAIN FUNCTIONALITY FOR 72
HOURS, MORTY.
STARTING [BURPS] RIGHT ABOUT
NOW.
>> Morty: OHH, MAN.
[ GROANING ] OH, GEEZ! OHH.
>> Rick: I'M SORRY, MORTY.
IT'S A BUMMER.
IN REALITY, YOU'RE AS DUMB AS
THEY COME.
AND I NEEDED THOSE SEEDS REAL
BAD, AND I HAD TO GIVE THEM UP
JUST TO GET YOUR PARENTS OFF MY
BACK, SO NOW WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO
GO GET MORE.
AND THEN WE'RE GONNA GO ON EVEN
MORE ADVENTURES AFTER THAT,
MORTY.
AND YOU'RE GONNA KEEP YOUR MOUTH
SHUT ABOUT IT, MORTY, BECAUSE
THE WORLD IS FULL OF IDIOTS THAT
DON'T UNDERSTAND WHAT'S
IMPORTANT, AND THEY'LL TEAR US
APART, MORTY.
BUT IF YOU STICK WITH ME, I'M
GONNA ACCOMPLISH GREAT THINGS,
MORTY, AND YOU'RE GONNA BE PART
OF THEM, AND TOGETHER, WE'RE
GONNA RUN AROUND, MORTY.
WE'RE GONNA DO ALL KINDS OF
WONDERFUL THINGS, MORTY.
JUST YOU AND ME, MORTY.
>> Morty: OH, NO, NO.
>> Rick: THE OUTSIDE WORLD IS
OUR ENEMY, MORTY.
WE'RE THE ONLY [BURPS] FRIENDS
WE'VE GOT, MORTY.
IT'S JUST RICK AND MORTY
[BURPS] RICK AND MORTY AND THEIR
ADVENTURES, MORTY.
RICK AND MORTY FOREVER AND
FOREVER.
100 YEARS, RICK AND MORTY'S
THINGS.
ME AND RICK AND MORTY RUNNING
AROUND, AND RICK AND MORTY TIME.
ALL DAY LONG, FOREVER.
ALL A HUNDRED DAYS.
RICK AND MORTY FOREVER 100
TIMES.
OVER AND OVER,
rickandmortyadventures.com.
www.rickandmorty.com.
www.rickandmortyadventures.
ALL 100 YEARS.
EVERY MINUTE, rickandmorty.com.
www.100timesrickandmorty.com.