Ugh, what is that?
I've never smelled
that smell in America.
I live in a
"transitional" neighborhood.
As the crack dealers
move to nicer ones?
This better be good, Krieger.
I mean hula girls, a replica volcano, some --
I have something better!
A surprise!
I hate surprises.
Except surprise fellatio.
That I like.
The non-Midnight Cowboy kind.
Yeah, no, you
can breathe easy.
Actually I can
barely breathe at all.
- Oh, probably the bathroom...
- Jesus, it's a --
A shared bath.
I was going to
say a literal shithole.
Krieger, how and why do you live here?
I use my salary
for "pet" projects.
Nope! Nope!
I had Korean barbecue for lunch, I
cannot look at a Dr. Moreau pig-baby.
Relax, you're gonna love this.
No I'm not, and
also I need to pee.
Don't be nervous,
I'm not gonna rape you.
Jesus Christ!
But you were gonna flay
me like a perch?!
Wh-?
No, that's a wetsuit!
Of human flesh?!
Neoprene!
I'm a certified diver.
Why's it skin-colored?
It's not if you're black.
What is it with
serial killers and skin?
I'm not a... serial killer.
Wait, why'd
you emphasize serial?
I didn't, what?
Are we doing, did I mention
I have a surprise for you?
Krieger!
Equal parts soju sangria and fear-induced
adrenaline means I have to pee.
And not in that sick bathroom, so--
O.K. There's a utility
sink in my lab.
Fine, wherever.
But no surprises.
Right.
Well. Except for the one.
Uh, is the surprise
that you're pirating cable?
No, no, Archer,
I've finally cracked it!
Wow, amazing, you can play YYZ.
First of all, it's Y-Y-Zed,
and second of all, no, I can't yet,
it's impossible.
Well --
And third of all, wrong thing!
Oh my God.
Krieger.
Is that...?
But how did...?
- I mean, at our wedding...
- I know.
- There was a lot of confusion...
- Noooooo!
Katyaaa!
No-ho-ho-hooooo!
Gross and/or ick, and is she...?
Alive?
Yeah, man.
Flick her titty.
Katya!
You're alive!
Well, on, technically.
Either way, you're welcome.
My sweet, beautiful Katya!
It's you!
My darlink Sterlink, you awake
me like the prince of Snow White!
I love you!
I... I love you!
Krieger thank you, this is the --
why do you have an erection?!
I'm happy.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Here they are!
God, geese at the trough.
What?
Are you - thanks for
startiar my sentence for me -
people standing around for?
It's Bear Claw Monday.
And almost nine-thirty,
Pam, in case you were thinking
about, I dunno, working.
Jeez, somebody's raring to go.
Because I burn clean, Cyril.
Because I don't glop up my
engine with bear claws.
And also because --
Hello, friends of ISIS!
- And also because Katya needs a W--
- Holy shitzombies!
I know, right?
Still crazy hot.
How --
Well for one thing, no bear claws.
is she even here?!
Wait, does this mean you and me --
Pam!
I swear to God, if you people
can't keep it down, this is the last
Bear Claw Mon --
Am I seeing things?!
- No, she's really here...
- Ow, ahh!
And if we don't file her
W-9 that first check will take,
like, eight weeks.
- I'm sorry, I'm a little confused...
- What, by the
dead woman standing here?!
Dressed like a whore?
Dead woman my
still-shapely ass.
She's obviously a double, carved up by
KGB plastic surgeons to look like Katya,
and --
How dare you?!
I'm sorry?
How dare you fail to recognize
my greatest accomplishment to date?!
You finally nailed YYZ?
It's zed!
And no, Neil Peart stands alone.
I was referring... to this!
Katya? On the flourish?
Is when --
Oh! Sorry, doktor...
Just like
the gypsy woman said!
You need to quit going to her.
And you need your head
examined if you think that
abomination is ever
going to work for ISIS!
Abomination?
Baby, come on,
you're not an abomination.
I mean, that's your
original skin, right?
Hobo.
What?
Yes.
See?
But --
Hang on, hang on.
Katya-person.
I'm still processing the
fact that you're a cyborg.
Yeah, way to bury the lead.
Who're you, Horace Greeley?
And also, was I not clear about that?
No!
- Although she does feel a bit clammy...
- Ow! Stop it!
You stop it!
Just because she's a cyborg
doesn't mean you can feel her up!
Da, I hef feelinks
just like all of you.
- I feel love, I leff, I sometimes cry...
- Albeit a
saline-lubricant solution.
Which reminds me, we need to talk about
other, um, internal lubricants like --
Stop!
That sounds like a private matter.
Yeah, that's what I'm talking ab--
And Katya!
My lovely lady.
Needs to go with Pam now
to do her stupid W-9.
But Ms. Archer said--
What, Pam?!
That she's so jealous of my love for
Katya, she won't hire a world-class spy
who also, spoiler alert, can do this?!
Babe, you wanna...?
- Oh! Sorry, darlink...
- Hey!
Wait, or do I mean sploosh?
Ya know, it's probably not the
worst idea in the world to have...
someone like her working at ISIS, since--
Since you wanna
screw affirmative action?
Since the KGB has
someone like Barry!
Barry!
Thet, thet --
Don't worry about Barry.
I'm never gonna let him
hurt you again, baby.
Ha!
It is Barry who should worry!
If I ever see thet zloi
mudak again, I --
Don't worry, you won't!
Yeah he never
calls, he never writes...
So just go with Pam
to do your paperwork --
And I'll go try
to convince Malory
that you'll be an asset to ISIS.
Thank you Lana, that's --
So not doing it for you.
So don't care.
So! Robocop!
Pro or con?
Neither!
I don't want her to be an ISIS agent,
and I certainly don't want her
and Sterling back together!
Well, I can
understand the latter --
I mean, who wears bangs?
-- but it can't hurt to
level the playing field,
now that --
Nikolai has been murdered.
By the new head of the KGB,
who is also a cyborg.
Just like
the gypsy woman said!
Oh for --!
- Oh, alright...
- Really?!
Katya can be an ISIS agent?!
Probationary.
But if I find out the KGB is behind this --
You won't!
They're not!
I'll part her out
and sell her for scrap.
And I thought you were
scared of robots!
I -- no, not
Katya, she's different!
Hmp.
Well don't come crying to me when
she breaks your heart again.
She didn't break my heart,
Mother, she was murdered.
Yes, and then you ran
away from home to, ugh,
grief-bang the entire Pacific Rim.
To what?
Nothing!
Oh please, I bet the
gene pool of Polynesia
is irreparably altered.
Darlink...?
Baby, I was
emotionally shattered.
Which, turns out, to be
kind of a pantydropper.
Is alright, darlink.
I understand this... how do you say?
Griff-bakink.
See?
Is she not something special?
Oh, is special occasion?
Well, the love of my
life, this smoking-hot woman,
was not only murdered and
then brought back to life,
she also just got a job today,
so yeah, pretty special.
- Uh...
- Shut up.
Babe? What're you hungry for?
I am thinking.
While she thinks, bring
me some soup dumplings.
No, no, I am thinking
about your mother.
God, don't waste the
ROM, or RAM, whatever.
Does she hate what I am?
What you are, meaning
"the one woman who can
free her child from the
psychological prison she's spent
a lifetime erecting?"
No, darlink, meaning a...
cyborg.
She'd hate you
no matter what you are.
Because I did not
ask to be this way...
Yeah, hey, me
either, vis a vis Mother.
And you?
Do you think I am a monster?
Baby, I don't care about
the chips and gears and...
I assume some hinges?
All I care about is what I see
when I look into those big green--
oh, I guess they're red now, huh?
Anyway, your eyes.
Da?
And what do you see in my eyes?
Mostly those insane boobs.
Check!
Ah.
Ooh.
Eee.
Unn.
Ahhhh.
Darlink?
Are you alright?
Yes, no, yes.
Yes.
Lot of feelings coming together,
just trying to process.
Not gonna lie, having
some dj vu here.
Ahh... Ahh... Ahh... ow!
Owwww!
Which, if I gave
it any real thought,
would probably explain a lot.
Try to relex, darlink.
You are, how do you say?
To push a rope?
Sorry, babe, I'll focus.
But could you close your eyes?
I kinda feel like I'm banging
tail-lights on a country road.
I swear to God, if I
went blind right this very
second I'd be okay with that.
Oh, dun't say that!
Mr. Sleepy Head!
Sleep?
I've been doing yogic breathing
work for two hours.
My balls are like cran-baisins.
What?
Cranberry raisins?
Craisins?
Whatever, yes, I
call them cran-baisins.
How are you this morning?
I em amazink!
Don't take this
the wrong way, but duh.
I mean our love, darlink.
It feels like...
what is a giant, unstoppable wave?
Wait, you know craisins,
but you don't know tsunami?
Da, then our
love is like tsunami.
Or the Mountain Everest.
An apt metaphor.
Because not only am I lightheaded,
certain parts of me are --
Nuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuumb!
- They are not coming back.
- Why?
In the sink?
Is your... vagina?!
Why?
Darlink, it was dirty.
The remedy for which,
miss, if you'll forgive
my boldness...?
Da, please, Woodhouse,
I think boldness is needed.
What do you suggest?
White vinegar,
mineral oil, and elbow grease.
Same thing we used in the RFC
to clean the engines on our
Sopwith Camels.
And so, with your permission,
while you breakfast on the
terrace I'll get that little
pleasure boat looking Bristol!
I took the liberty of
poaching you an egg.
Is not much of a liberty,
considerink thet you are going
to polish my vagina.
No.
No it isn't.
And when he woke
up from faint, boom!
He ren out of there fest like crezzy.
So.
You dated him.
What do you think?
I think... hang on.
I think if you're looking for
insight into why Archer is...
Archer, you need to jump in a
time machine and then go have
a treesome with Oedipus
and Sigmund Freud.
Thanks for nothing.
Well?!
I don't really have a roadmap
for my ex finding your
robo-gina in the sink.
In the sink, Cyril!
In the sink!
It was like a
transistor radio and a
veal cutlet had a baby!
Well gross and/or ick--
Right?!
-- but I don't see why
that means you have to drink my
Glengoolie Blue!
Because the liquor
stores aren't open yet,
and she made me pour out all
the booze at my house!
Holy shit, really?
Glengoolie Blue?
Yeah, and it's three
hundred a bottle...
I -- which I haven't even tasted yet!
Because I was saving it
for a special occasion!
Befitting a gift from my grandfather!
Who's dead!
Of course he is,
he'd be like, a hundred.
It's almost empty!
Just like my heart, Cyril --
Well, not your liver...
-- because she ripped
it out!
Wait, your liver?
My heart!
And threw it in the sink!
Wait, her vagina?
Ow! Ow!
- Oh for ---
The old man knew his scotch.
You are such an... asshole!
Wait, really?
Yes, really!
That was a gift to my grandfather!
From Frank!
Sinatra!
Well then I feel even worse,
because I'm probably gonna
puke it up in about five --
One minutes.
But I meant about Katya.
Yes!
You are an asshole about all things!
But, specifically,
now, about Katya.
Or...
could I hef done something wrung?
Besides leavin yer
cooch in the sink?
Pam! Pam!
What?
That just sounds considerate.
Is just, I know he hez
wery good reason to hate...
people like me.
Who, whores?
And that's twice, sorry,
ignore me, my whole thing is
I just crave attention.
But I mean, Barry
did murder her -- ungh!
And my possible father -- ungh!
And more importantly,
tried to murder me!
Unngh!
Because Barry!
Is a psychopath!
That doesn't mean all
cyborgs are like that!
But Cyril, machines...
can hurt people.
Waaaaaaghhhh!
Well you lost me there,
thankfully, but -- Give me that!
What, was that Peter Lawford's?
No, it was -- Oh shut up,
do you wanna learn something?
- Probably not...
- Because did you
know that in Chinese, the
words for crisis and
opportunity are the sathme word?
And... point?
Hello?!
Actually I have no idea.
They just used to say
that in the hospital.
While they made us fold those
pointy goddamn paper birds.
I think what Cheryl's--
Bawk bawk!
Therapy cranes!
Bawk!
I think what she's trying
to say is you can either think
- of this as a crisis...
- Or an opportunity!
To get closer!
- Hooray...
- By marrying her?!
That actually
was Peter Lawford's.
And why not, you were
gonna marry her before!
Before she wasn't a cyborg.
She's still kind,
smart, insanely hot...
Yeah, and even
though it's detachable,
that vagina is like, mind-shattering.
Oh yeah?
What, does it vibrate, or -- Ow!
Ow! Dammit You started it!
That's my fiance
you're talking about!
Really?
I can look past
our differences, Cyril,
I'm a much bigger man than you think.
Plus it'll drive Mother crazy.
Plus yes, it vibrates.
Really?!
Yes, really, and... Krieger?
Today?
Hm?
Oh! Sorry.
Little thing
called timing, Krieger.
And the erection's
really not appropriate.
I'm still happy!
Katya?
Baby?
Oh yes, yes, a
thousand times yes!
When's the wedding,
when's the wedding?!
I can actually
marry y'all right here.
Oh for God's sake!
Get it over with!
Brett!
Aaagh!
Wait, do you want me to be a groomsman?
No!
Go to the liquor store
and buy a case of --
three cases of champagne!
Sure, I'll just
limp on down there.
Don't limp, Brett!
Run!
We're having a wedding
in a few short minutes!
And it's a win-win.
Plus it vibrates.
Okay, bride and groom, check.
Bridesmaids, check.
Best man --
Well, best available.
Oh for -- name one,
name one friend of yours.
Shut up.
Ray, don't you have like,
a priest outfit, or...?
No, I wore it to Fetish Night
at The Snug, and it's covered in --
Okay! Ugh.
Red wine, ass.
And who gives this woman to
be wed in holy matrimony?
I do!
And no mother of the groom, so --
Yes! Right here!
Mother! You came!
Phrasing, boom!
Ahem.
Inappropriate.
Alrighty!
So unless anyone - besides Mommie
Dearest - objects to this union --
Uh, I think other Barry might.
Wh-?
Barry?!
Yeah, and I brought bubbly!
You.. . Mudak!
Whoa!
You kiss your mother-board
with that mouth?
And also, is anybody
gonna ask how and why
I knew to show up here?
Is...?
Okay, I'll bite.
By tracking the satellite
signal from Katya's internal
hard drive, which Doctor Dipshit
over there, bought from the KGB!
Wh-?!
Krieger!
- Yeah, but the savings...
- Like,
eighty bucks you saved.
But nobody's gonna save you, Archer.
Don't you have
that backwards?!
Archer don't!
Everybody down.
Why do I always
forget you're -- ungh!
Darlink!
- Really super-strong...
- Yeah,
walk that off while I kill
your girlfriend again.
Then we do the dance.
Actually, I don't think
I'm in any shape to dance,
right now Barry.
The dance of death, idiot.
But first let's me and you cut a rug.
How you say... come et me, bro.
Rrrrrraaarrrrgh!
Ow.
Is thet the best you got?
Ungh!
Obviously not.
But this is -- oof!
Katyaaa!
Jesus somebody, a little help?!
We are if you'd shut up!
It's pound!
That is pound!
Pound six, pound five two!
I'm confused, what're we --
Here!
Still confused.
Ray, now!
Oh.
Their CPU's are powered
by photovoltaic cells!
Without exposure to a light-source
they'll slowly lose power!
Like vampires?
I -- no, nothing
like vampires, idiot!
Well I'm sorry, Ira Flatow!
From Newton's Apple.
Will you shut up?!
If Barry gets weak enough,
maybe you can overpower him!
I was just gonna say that!
Move!
Sterling, be careful!
Shut up.
Pam!
- It'll spoil...
- God damn it.
Barryyyyy!
Polo!
Will you shut up?!
Polo.
Beset, on all
sides, by idiots...
Brett?!
I thought you were dead!
No, just hurt
really really badly.
Although not nearly as
badly as I am now.
You better not be
bleeding on my carpet!
No, pretty sure
I'm all out of blood.
Well serves you
right, for -- Oh Barry,
- I am coming for you...
- Phrasing, boom.
Brett!
Polo!
And after I kill you, and
defile your cyborg-y corpse,
I'm gonna -- wh-?!
Oh for shit's sake!
Really?!
Woooooo!
Darlink, I ken explen!
Ray, turn the lights on!
Archer no, the photovoltaics!
Turn on the goddamn lights!
Gaaaagh!
Why do I always forget that?!
And how can you explain that?!
What were they, having sex?!
Think so, yeah.
Called it!
As we fought, it became
more like, like dancing.
Bone dancing!
Shut up!
Katya, how could you do this?
I'm sorry I hurt you, but
I realized thet even though
you tried to see past what I
em, Barry and I are the same.
Inside and out.
Except her insides vibrate.
Rrrragh!
Ka-
Always with the forgetting...
We are like two mermaids.
We will swim together.
So, I won't ask you to forgive me...
But could you at least be happy for me?
Because I have finally found a soulmate.
No.
Or whatever...
Yes. Yes.
Thank you, darling.
You will always have
a special place in my...
Well, I guess my C-drive.
Well, other Barry and I...
are in her other special place.
Which, again,
vibrates.
Later, tator.
Well, mother, go ahead and say it.
Oh, Sterling.
You just had your heart broken.
And you don't need a smug
"I told you so" from me.
And smug it would be, because tell you
I most certainly did.
Just like that Electrolux all over again.
So...
- I know that sucked...
- Vacuum cleaner ponds?
Now?
Really?
No idea thankfully about any of that,
but
if you really did love Katya
you gotta be happy that she's happy.
Yeah...
She did look pretty happy, huh?
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com