All right, Mabel,
today is the big day.
Big day!
Soos finally
fixed up the laptop.
If this thing works,
we could learn the identity
of the author
and unravel the greatest
mysteries of Gravity Falls.
You ready?
Oh, I'm ready, baby.
Ma-ma.
This is it.
( chuckles )
BOTH: blip, blap,
bloobity bloop, twins.
( alarm )
Ugh!
Of course, a password.
Don't you worry,
bro bro.
With your brains
and my laser focus,
there is literally nothing
that can distract us from...
( piano music playing )
Did you hear that?
♪ All my life
I've been dreaming ♪
♪ Of a love
that's right for me ♪
♪ And now I finally
know her name ♪
♪ And it's...
sing it with me kids ♪
♪ Literacy
I finally understand
what all the buzz is about.
Reading.
Give me some
of that honey.
( kissing )
Ba bump.
Oh, boy.
( laughter and applause )
Thank you.
Just when I was getting
over Mermando,
of course, you show up
at my doorstep.
Oh, yeah, I forgot
about Mermando.
Did not care
for Mermandooo.
Okay,
this cryptology book says
there's 7.2 million
8-letter words.
I'll type, you read.
Okay, Mabel?
Mabel?
♪ And that's why we don't
stick our hands in... ♪
♪ Other people's
mouths ♪
Hey, I'm Gabe Benson,
y'all.
Goodnight.
( indistinct chatter )
Hey, good job today,
you guys.
You were late
on your cue.
What?
Hey, hey.
Be good to each other.
We're all stars.
Hey!
Guess who's Mabel?
Care to learn more?
I bet you do.
You like to learn.
( chuckles )
( screams )
Oh, hey, I'm Gabe,
master of puppets.
Nice to meet you.
You're amazing
with those puppets.
A lot of people
think puppets are dumb
or just for kids
or something.
Are you kidding me?
I'm puppet crazy.
People call me
"puppet crazy Mabel".
People used to call me
"puppet crazy Gabe".
So when's your
next puppet show?
if you're not throwing
puppet shows, right.
Yeah, I mean I'm totally
working on a puppet show.
Oh,
what are the details?
There are
so many details.
( sighs )
Dipper, how hard
do you think it would be
to write and compose
a sock puppet rock opera
and live pyrotechnics
by Friday?
( beeping )
What?
Mabel, are you serious?
I don't know
what happened.
I got lost in his eyes
and his ponytail
and I'm going to be
so embarrassed on Friday
if I don't have
anything.
But what about cracking
this password?
You know,
mystery twins?
If you help me with this
for just a couple of days,
I promise I'll help you
with the password.
Please.
Pretty please.
It's for love, Dipper.
All right, okay.
Yes!
Thank you.
This guy,
he's number one!
Okay.
Okay, okay, okay.
Man, I can't wait to get to
the bottom of this laptop.
We're close
to something big here.
I can feel it.
Ugh!
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
Come on.
All right, the play
is going to be called
"Glove Story-
A Sock Opera."
Just a warning,
people's eyes will get wet,
'cause they'll be crying
from laughing,
from how tragic it is.
Yeah, that...
that sounds great.
( coughs )
you just got to roll
with Mabel's craziness.
It's what makes
life worth living.
♪ Puppet boy,
puppet boy ♪
♪ You're the boy I...
ALL: ♪ Love
Not even gonna ask.
Goodnight, my babies.
Wack, wack, wack, muaah.
Soon, Gabe Benson.
( beeping )
Ugh, wrong password.
Wrong. Wrong! Ugh!
Don't stay up
all night, Dipper.
Last time you got
this sleep deprived
you tried to eat
your own shirt.
Bleh.
Just a few more tries.
( beeping )
Ugh!
I can't take that sound anymore.
I hate you sound.
There has to be
some shortcut or clue.
Who would know
about secret codes?
I think I know a guy.
Well, well, well,
you're awfully persistent,
Pine Tree.
Hats off to you.
( Dipper whimpering )
You again!
Did you miss me?
Admit it, you missed me.
Hardly.
You worked with Gideon.
You tried to destroy
my uncle's mind.
It was just a job, kid.
No hard feelings.
I've been keeping
an eye on you
since then and I must say,
I'm impressed.
Really?
You deserve a prize.
Here, have a head
that's always screaming.
( screams )
( Bill laughs )
The point is,
I like you.
How's about you let me
give you a hint, huh?
I only ask
for a small favor in return.
I'd never do
a favor for you.
Don't forget who defeated
you last time.
Right,
you defeated me.
Well, if you ever
change your mind,
I'll be here for you
ready to make a deal.
Hey, want to hear my impression
of you in about 3 seconds.
( screaming )
Hey,
I'm puppet Stan.
Still ignoring this.
Hey, Mabel.
( yawns )
Whoa, bag check
for Dipper's eyes.
Nobody?
Dipper, I told you to get
some sleep last night.
Here, wake up
with some Mabel juice.
It has plastic
dinosaurs in it.
It's like if coffee
and nightmares had a baby.
Last night I had
a dream with Bill in it.
Wait, hold up.
The triangle guy?
He said he'd give me
the code of the laptop
if I gave him
something.
Like I'd actually
trust Bill, right?
Don't worry, bro.
that the mystery twins
are back in action.
I'll help you
crack that code.
I just got to hand
off my puppet stuff
to my production crew.
Production crew?
We read the script.
Very emotional.
I cried, like,
eight times.
GABE: Hey, ladies.
Gabe!
Helps me dry out my ponytail
after a shower.
Aah. Aah.
Hoppity boppity.
( speaking
in foreign language )
I was just working on the
world's greatest puppet show.
It has puppets.
Your passion
is so refreshing, Mabel,
unlike the girl from
last night's puppet show.
Single-stitch on one puppet
and cross-stitch on the other?
I was like, uh-huh.
Cross... huh?
Naturally I deleted her off
my cell phone contacts list.
Naturally.
( nervous giggle )
I know you won't
let me down though.
Based on what you
said the other day,
you must be
a puppet expert.
You know, Gabe,
you look pretty sweaty.
You should really
take your shirt off.
Right?
Aren't we all
thinking that?
Later, ladies.
Bah!
We got to up
our game, girls.
Did you hear that thing
he said about the stitches?
Don't worry, Mabel,
your crew can handle it.
( grunts )
How many eyes does
a face have again?
I got it. I got it. Oh!
( alarm wailing )
I'm not okay.
Ah!
Okay, I'm back on fabrication.
Get me my lint roller.
Dipper, this sock crisis just
bumped up to a code argyle.
The laptop can wait.
Mabel,
do you seriously think
that your random
crush of the week
is more important
than uncovering
the mysteries
of this town?
You're obsessed.
I'm obsessed?
Look at you.
You look like a vampire.
But you said you were
gonna help me today.
Well, I can help
you with tickles.
( laughter )
Okay, fine.
You know what?
I'll do it on my own.
Passwords, passwords.
Mabel is useless.
( yawns )
Oh, man.
COMPUTER: Too many
failed entries.
Huh?
Initiate data erase
in 5 minutes.
( beeping )
I'm gonna lose everything?
I only have one more try?
Well, well, well.
Someone's looking
desperate.
I thought I told you
to leave me alone.
I can help you, kid.
You just need to hear
out my demands.
Ugh!
What crazy thing do
you want, anyway?
To eat my soul?
To rip out my teeth?
Are you gonna replace my eyes
with baby heads or something?
Yeesh, kid, relax.
All I want is a puppet.
A puppet?
What are you playing at?
Everyone loves puppets.
And it looks to me like
you've got a surplus.
I don't know, man.
Mabel worked
really hard on these.
Seems to me one little puppet
is a small price to pay
to learn all the secrets
of the universe.
Besides, what's your sister
done for you lately?
How many times have you
sacrificed for her, huh?
And when has she ever
returned the favor?
( beeping )
Tick tock, kid.
Just one puppet?
Fine.
So what puppet are
you gonna pick anyway?
Hmm, let's see.
Eenie meenie mynee...
You.
What?
This can't be happening.
What did you
do to my body?
Sorry, kid, but
you're my puppet now.
( evil laughter )
Oh, my gosh.
This can't be happening.
Wh-whoa.
( laughing )
Man, it's been so long
since I've inhabited a body.
Ooh! Ooh!
( chuckles )
Pain is hilarious.
And two eyes?
This thing's deluxe.
Why are you doing this?
I thought we had a deal.
Look, kid, you've been getting
way too close to figuring out
some major answers.
I've got big plans coming
and I don't need you
getting in my way.
Destroying that laptop
was a cinch.
Now I just need to
destroy your journal.
Race you to the bottom
of the stairs.
Hey.
Human soda.
I'm gonna drink
it like a person.
So where do you keep
that journal anyway?
It's got to be around
here somewhere.
Boy, these arms are durable.
you'll never find it
in a million years.
I borrowed your journal
to use as a prop in the show.
I'm gonna go before you
process this sentence.
Okay, bye!
Sure, sounds great, sister.
I'll see you at the show.
Wait.
No, Mabel, don't listen to him.
That's not me.
You've got to hear me.
No, no. Wait. Stop!
Ha, welcome
to the mindscape, kid.
Without a vessel to possess,
you're basically a ghost.
Oh, hi, Dipper.
There you are.
What up, dude?
Soos. Wendy.
Help me.
We're headed
to the theater.
Need a ride, Dipper?
( chuckles )
BILL: Anything for you, Red.
I'm gonna stop you, Bill.
I'm gonna find that
journal before you do
and I'm gonna stop you!
But how can you stop
me if you don't exist?
( evil laughter )
Bill?
Bill!
Got to get my body back before
he does something crazy with it.
Ah, nothing like
the theater, huh, toots?
Hey, Soos, want to hear
the exact time and date
of your death?
( chuckles )
Okay.
Hey, guys,
you all made it.
I would never miss
whatever this is.
By the by, Mabel, where'd
you put my journal again?
I used it as a prop
for the big wedding scene.
I still need
a reverend though.
Hey, what if I play
the reverend?
I mean, someone's got to
hold that journal, right?
Great. Let's go.
Oh, no, wait.
Mabel!
GRENDA:
The show is about to begin.
Please turn off
your cell phones,
unless
you're texting me, cuties.
Gather around
and let us sing
about a girl who had
almost everything.
Look, it's Mabel.
Hey there.
Did you say stable?
No, he said Mabel.
Okay, hit it, boys!
♪ Who's that girl
with the pig and the braces? ♪
♪ She put smiles
on everyone's faces ♪
♪ When she's around,
no, you're never bored ♪
♪ I'm a mayor
♪ I'm here for an award
♪ Thank you, mayor
♪ It's true, I'm great
♪ But the perfect girl
needs the perfect mate ♪
Hey, what's up?
I'm Gabe.
So, hey, Grendo,
where's that book prop I'm
using for the wedding scene?
It's up in the wedding cake.
But that doesn't come
down until Act 3.
So hold your horses.
Oh, I'll hold my horses.
I'll hold them.
You monster.
Hey, listen.
Have you seen Mabel?
Hmm.
What did Bill say?
I can't be heard
without a vessel?
Where would I find a...
Finally we're together.
I'm sorry, Mabel, but I have
to go fight in the war.
( screaming )
( growling )
( gunshots )
I'll wait for you, Gabe.
I'll wait for you.
GRENDA: Our intermission
has begun.
Mill about.
( crowd murmurs )
Ooh!
Okay, you can do this, Mabel.
Only 36 more musical numbers.
Psst.
Mabel.
The puppet books
didn't warn me about this.
Mabel, it's me, Dipper.
You need to help me.
Wait, what?
Dipper?
But you're so much more
of a sock than usual.
Mabel, you have to listen.
Bill tricked me.
He stole my body and now
he's after the journal.
You have to find the journal
before Bill destroys it.
It's the only hope
to get me back in my body.
But my cue's
coming up any minute.
Hey, Mabel,
do you have a moment?
Gabe!
( giggles )
Ow!
Mabel.
Mabel, it's clear to me now
that you really love puppets.
I mean you went whole hog.
And if you stick
the ending, well,
maybe later you could
join me for a biscotti?
( gasps )
You drive a biscotti?
I'll be waiting.
Did you hear that?
He loves it!
This play
has to be flawless.
Can't we wait
until after the show?
Mabel, you want me to be
a sock puppet forever?
( laughing )
I'm sorry.
It looks funny
when you're mad.
( grunting )
Just take over for me until
I get back with the book.
Little puppet face.
Gabe, you're back
from the war.
Want to kiss and sing
at the same time?
Okay.
Seriously?
Come on.
I hope this kiss never ends.
( exhaling )
There must be a way to
get Dipper's body back.
Oh-oh, but why would
you want to do that?
( gaps )
Bill-Dipper!
Bipper.
Shh.
You wouldn't
want to ruin the show.
Whoops.
( screaming )
It's slipping.
How's about you
hand that book over?
No way.
This is Dipper's.
I'd never give it away.
Hmm.
You didn't seem
to have a problem
taking it for your own play.
Or ditching him
when he needed you.
So come to your senses.
Give me the book
or your play is ruined.
( sighs )
There it is.
I mean, who would
sacrifice everything
they've worked for just
for their dumb sibling?
Dipper would.
Eh?
Oh!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
I'm giving you away.
You are a woman now.
Waddles, the rings.
Wait, what?
Oh, no.
Get out of my brother's body,
you evil triangle!
Whoa!
Children fighting.
I can sell this.
Aah!
You can't stop me.
I am a being of pure energy
with no weakness.
True, but you're
in Dipper's body.
And I know
all his weaknesses.
What do you mean
"his--?"
Tickle, tickle.
( laughing )
Aah!
Body spasms.
What are these?
A little note
about the human body.
You haven't slept
in over 24 hours.
Also,
I got a full night's sleep
and I'm on four
mega shots of Mabel juice.
( panting )
What is this feeling?
My body is burning.
I can't move
these stupid noodle legs.
Curse you,
useless flesh sticks.
Body shutting down,
must scratch,
mosquito bites.
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Whoa! Hey!
What?
Yes!
I'm in my own body
and it's just as
underwhelming as I remember.
( groans )
Everything hurts.
( evil laughter )
This isn't the last
you'll hear of me.
Big things are coming.
You can't stop me.
I'm sorry, Gabe.
( opera music playing )
Don't worry.
I've seen enough movies
to know this is the part
it was all part of the show
and loves it.
Cue applause!
( crowd booing )
Gabe!
Stick around
for the wrap party?
We got mini quiches.
Don't speak to me, Mabel.
You've made a mockery
of my art form.
Let's go, my loves.
( kissing )
Did he just make out
with his puppets?
I might have dodged
a bullet there.
( speaking in
foreign language )
Oof!
Mabel,
I'm sorry about all this.
It's my fault
your puppets got ruined.
Well,
one of them survived.
And she has something
to say to you.
I'm sorry, Dipper.
I spent all week
obsessing over a dumb guy.
But the dumb guy I should
have cared about was you.
Bah!
Mystery twins.
Ow!
What did
Bill do to my hand?
Aah!
Nothing
a little sleep can't fix.
Come on, bro bro,
let's go home.
Seriously, I need to
go to the hospital.
Hey, Dipper.
What did one sock puppet say
to the other sock puppet?
I don't know, Mabel.
What?
You look like
you could use a hand.
( laughing )
That joke
was really something.
Yeah, something terrible.
( laughing )
( screaming )