Ahh!
Morning, Dipper.
Guess who.
Oh, what joy.
If it isn't
Mr. Upsidedownington.
How long has it been?
Third grade maybe?
That's right, and I'm here
to deliver you
an Upsidedownington-tastic
message!
Is it the message that we're
getting too old for this sort of thing?
Um, kinda, actually.
It's that we're exactly
one week away
from our 13th birthday!
Whoa! Our birthday's
coming up already?
Soon we're gonna be
actual teenagers!
Finally I can stop reading
pre-teen magazines,
and start reading
post-pre-teen magazines.
PG-13 movies,
here I come.
And just one more year
until high school.
High school, Dipper!
Where girls
become women,
and they teach us
stuff about...
you know what.
Trigonometry?
Oh, yeah, baby.
That's not the only
good news coming up.
In one week, my senior
citizen ponytail kit
is coming in the mail.
I'm... I'm kinda going
through some things.
In one week,
my grandma is finally letting me
eat crackers
on my bed.
The future is coming
for us all, dudes.
- The future.
The future!
I'm sorry, I can't
take you seriously
with that face
on your chin.
What face, Dipper?
You're doing the voice,
so you obviously know what I'm talking about.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
There is something
wrong with you.
There's something wrong
with both of us.
All right,
party planners.
In one week,
we become teenagers,
and our summer vacation
winds to an end,
so we need to throw
the greatest party of all time!
I'm talkin' piñatas
with tinier piñatas inside.
Boom, dreams comin' true.
I'm talkin' inviting
everyone in town.
Let's see.
Where do we stand
with the gnomes?
Not so fast,
goofus and girl goofus.
After that
zombie incident,
no one's throwing
another party at my house.
I keep finding little
bits of the undead in the couch cushions.
But Grunkle Stan,
we need some roof to raise.
Dude, you can rent out
the Gravity Falls high school gym,
and have your party there.
That place is empty
all summer long.
The gym's
a great idea, Soos.
To the high school!
Dipper, my face
is on fire!
I'll just be
a second.
Hey, Uncle Ford,
are you okay?
Oh, yes, I'm fine.
I just said that
to make sure you'd come in here quickly.
But your face
is  on fire.
Yes. It's much faster
than shaving.
Now listen, Dipper.
I have a very important
mission, and you are
the only one
who can help me.
Remember the rift in
dimensional space-time I showed you?
It's cracking.
This is what Bill
has been waiting for.
If it breaks, it'll cause
reality as we know it
to completely unravel.
A hypothetical
and catastrophic event
I call Weirdmageddon.
Bill is out there,
and he'd use any trick
from deception to
outright possession
to make this happen.
But for the sake of humanity,
we mustn't let it.
- What do we do?
- We patch the rift.
I'll explain on the way.
- Wait. What about Mabel?
- It's okay, Dipper.
You should totally
go with Grunkle Ford
to save the world
or whatever.
Are you sure?
We're gonna be doing
birthday junk all week.
Plus, I packed
those walkie-talkies.
Here's one for
my party mission,
and one for
your smarty mission.
Ahem. I did mention
that the fate of the universe
is at stake,
didn't I?
Hurry! We haven't
much time.
Okay, Dipper, it's your first
big mission with Ford,
a chance to prove yourself.
Don't mess this up.
Ow! Ha ha.
I'm all right.
Whoa, Soos, I thought
you said this place was empty.
My dogs, what up?
Wendy, what are
you doing here?
Ugh. High school registration.
Oh! You know, I'm only
a year away
from high school
myself.
Would you say
your experience
is more rom-com
or wacky romp?
More like
teen horror movie.
High school
is the worst.
Classes get
super hard,
your body just
flat-out turns against you,
and worst of all,
everybody hates you.
Can't do it.
Can't do another year.
My hormones are like
a sweaty cage.
Why aren't they singing
about following their dreams?
TV taught me that
high school is like some sort of musical.
TV lied, man.
If you can avoid
growing up, do it.
I'd give anything
to be 12 again.
Anyway, what are
you guys doing here?
Just looking for a place
to have my 13th
birthday party.
Wendy Borduroy?
I mean Corduroy.
Corduroy.
See what I mean?
Master Mabel
to Dippity Dog.
We can have our party
at the gym,
but we gotta talk
about high school.
I'm starting to think
it might not be
the awesome future
we were expecting. Over.
I'm going through
a bad patch, Mabel.
We'll talk when
I get back... .
Dipper? Come in,
come in?
Hey, I know what will
make you feel better.
Let's deliver some invites
to your friends, huh?
Yeah!
Mabel?
Mabel, you there?
Listen, Dipper,
in order to seal the rift for good,
it's going to take an adhesive
stronger than anything on earth.
Something...
extraterrestrial in origin.
What do you mean?
Dipper, look at
the peculiar shape
made by those cliffs.
Does it remind you
of anything?
Hmm...
Shut... up.
According to my research,
the entire valley
of Gravity Falls was formed
when an extraterrestrial object
crash landed here
millions of years ago.
Did this craft cause
the town's strange properties?
Or, did the town's
strange properties
attract the craft?
The answer is
still unknown.
But that's crazy!
Where did the saucer go?
Sometimes, the strangest
things in the world
are right under
our noses.
And our feet, in this
particular instance.
Now, you might want
to stand back.
This magnet gun could
rip the fillings
out of a man's mouth
from a hundred feet.
I used to raid this thing
for parts for years.
Where do you think
I got the materials
to build my portal?
You-- I... words,
not working from mouth.
Now, come.
And take this.
Whoa, whoa!
Don't worry, I've been
down here countless times,
all the aliens have been dead
for millions of years.
Probably.
I can't believe there's been
a giant UFO
under the town
this whole time.
I wish my mind could be where
yours is right now, Dipper.
When confirmation
of extraterrestrials
still had that punch.
Now it's just sort of, meh.
McGucket and I used to
come down here all the time
to raid their tech
ad study their language.
This is so cool!
The substance we need
so seal the rift
is an alien adhesive,
strong enough to
keep the hull
of a spacecraft together.
Just one dollop of this adhesive
should be enough
to seal a crack in space-time.
Also, if it touches you,
it will seal up
all the orifices
in your face,
so try so avoid that.
Now, use your magnet gun
and follow me!
- Hup!
- Great Uncle Ford!
Your turn!
Say "hup". It helps!
Okay, just put on magnet,
leap down hole.
Turn on.
Come on already!
Magnet!
Hunh!
Aah!
A little help?
Oh, hi, Mabel.
You're just in time
for our one o'clock boy talk.
If you think that's good,
boom!
Me and Dipper's
13th birthday jam!
Oh, man, your birthday's
on the last day of summer.
I'm not gonna be here.
What?
Marius is flying me
out to Austria
to hang out at his castle
or whatever that week.
He's co clingy!
You're gonna be
out of town for my birthday?
But at least you can come,
right, Candy?
Sorry, Mabel, my parents
send me to music camp
this time of year.
There is no escape
from music camp.
So neither of you are
gonna be at my birthday party?
And you won't be able
to wish me good-bye
at the end of the summer?
I'm sorry, Mabel.
Summer happens so fast.
Ugh, Marius,
now's not the time!
I think I need to radio
for emotional backup.
Dipper, please come in.
Our party mission is
going down in flames.
Over.
Oh...
This is their
storage facility.
This place would have
been heavily guarded,
but now everything's defunct.
go ahead, flip any switch.
They've all been busted
for millions of years.
Clara, did you eat
my farm?
The glue should
be around here somewhere,
so keep your eyes peeled.
Dipper, let me ask you
something.
Have you thought much
about your future?
No, not really.
I mean, beyond graduating
high school with a high GPA
so I can get accepted
to a good technical college
with a photography
and media production minor
to start my own
ghost hunting show.
Ha ha ha!
It's like talking to
a younger version of myself.
If you're so sure of
what you want out of life, why wait?
Why put up
with the drudgery of school?
Huh, trust me, I'd love
to fast forward the whole thing, but
it's not like I have a choice.
Dipper, I've been thinking.
I'm getting too old
to investigate
Gravity Falls
on my own.
I need to train an apprentice
to help me fight monsters,
solve mysteries,
and protect this town.
And I think I'd like
to keep it in the family.
What are you saying?
I've read your additions
to my journal,
and I'm impressed
with your potential.
What would you say to
staying in Gravity Falls
after the summer ends
and becoming my apprentice?
What about school?
Dipper, I have 12 PhDs.
Your parents would be thrilled
I could give you such an advanced education.
There's also Mabel.
She'd be all alone
in California.
Mabel will be fine
on her own.
She has a magnetic
personality.
I watched her
become pen pals
with the pizza
delivery man
in the 60 seconds
he was at the door.
Gosh, we've never really
been apart before.
And isn't it suffocating?
Dipper, can you honestly
tell me
you never felt like you were
meant for something more?
I hav--
I don't know.
Sounds like
a dream come true,
but I'm not sure I have
what it takes.
I was tricked by Bill,
I was wrong about
Stan's portal.
Heck, I can't even operate
this magnet gun right.
Ha! Yes.
Dipper, you found
the adhesive!
- I did?
- Oh-ho, you really did it, kid.
Huddle in, let's get
a picture of this.
Uh, Uncle Ford, you said
everything down here
is dead, right?
Yes, unless somehow we
reactivated the...
security system!
What do we do?
Listen to me
very carefully.
I've studied these.
They're security droids,
and they detect
adrenaline.
You simply have to
not feel any fear,
and they won't see you.
- What?
It's okay.
I've done it before.
Just take a deep breath,
focus on your intellect,
and control your fear.
Wh-wh-what?
that's crazy! I--
Follow my lead!
Great Uncle ford...
Focus, Dipper!
I, uh...
I-I-
- I can't!
- Get down!
Aah! No!
Nooooo...
Wait! No!
Stay back!
It's too dangerous!
Sealing the rift is
what's important now.
Take this!
You're gonna have to
do it without me.
Use the adhesive.
Fix the rift!
Save the universe,
Dipper.
Great Uncle Ford!
Hang on,
I'm coming for you.
Don't worry,
I'll get you out of there!
Where's that thing
taking you?
It's an automated
prison droid.
And wherever it's going,
I'm not coming back.
What?
No, no, no.
Don't worry,
I'll think of something.
Dipper, what on earth
are you doing?
Hold on,
Great Uncle Ford.
I'm getting you out of this
one way or another.
Oh, no!
Come on, come on!
Aah...
Let go of my uncle!
Ohh. Aah!
Aah...
Oh, no. Aah!
Great Uncle Ford!
Okay, let's try magna-pulse.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no!
Come on, wake up, man.
We gotta get out of here
before--
Hey, I'm warning you!
I have a magnet gun!
Oh, yeah?
You think you can scare me?
Do your worst!
Nothing in this universe is
gonna take away my uncle.
So go ahead,
give me what you got.
I thought I was a goner, kid.
Are you all right?
what happened?
The orb didn't detect
any chemical signs of fear.
It assumed the threat
was neutralized
and then self-disassembled.
- Heh heh heh.
- I-- I did it?
You did it.
This is what I was
talking about.
How many other
12-year-olds
do you think are capable
of doing what you've just done?
Hey, everything
all right, pumpkin?
I just can't believe
the summer's almost over.
And now that I know how awful
high school's going to be,
I'm in no hurry
to start that train wreck.
Nobody likes getting older.
But just because
you're growing up
doesn't mean you have
to grow up, you know?
I mean, look at me.
I'm pushing 70,
and I still eat
ice cream for dinner.
But I don't want to say
good-bye to Gravity Falls.
Hey, at least whatever happens
after this summer,
you'll still have your brother
along with you
through thick and thin.
Not everyone can
say that, you know.
Yeah. At least
when I go home
I'll always have Dipper.
Good old reliable old...
Are you okay?
Let's get you out of there.
Listen to me, Dipper,
this town is a magnet
for things
that are special.
And that includes
you and me.
It brought both of us here
for a purpose.
Stay here with me, Dipper.
Become my apprentice.
Don't let anyone
hold you--
I'll do it.
I'm gonna stay.
Excellent.
Now, who wants to save
the world, apprentice?
Mabel, I just had
the best day of my life.
UFOs are real, and
there's one under the town,
and I saved
Great Uncle Ford's life and--
Hey, are you okay?
Tell me it's not true,
Dipper.
Tell me you were
joking.
- Ford's apprentice?
- Seriously?
Look, I was thinking,
and this is
a huge opportunity for me.
Well, it's a horrible
opportunity for me!
I had the worst day
of my life.
When we turn 13,
the summer ends,
and I have to leave
everything behind.
You're the only person
I could count on,
and now you're
leaving me, too?
Look, I've been
thinking about it.
I won't be gone
forever, okay?
I'll still
visit you at home
and we'll chat online--
we'll make it work.
I don't want it to work.
I just wish summer
could last forever.
But it can't, Mabel.
Look, things aren't gonna
stay frozen this way.
It's part of growing up.
Things change.
Summer ends.
- Ugh!
- Unh!
Mabel, wait!
I didn't mean it like that.
Mabel, come back!
Only party chocolate
can cheer me up now.
Nerd bucks?
Chewed up pens?
Ugh, wrong backpack.
It's not fair.
I just wish summer
could last forever.
That might be possible.
Sweater Town is not accepting
incoming calls right now.
M-M-Mabel, it's me.
What?
Who said that?
I can help.
The time travel guy?
What are you doing here?
You said you don't want
summer to end, right?
Did I hear that right?
Yeah.
Why are you
asking?
Look, maybe it's
against the rules,
but you once did
a favor for me, so
I thought I could
help you out.
It's called a time bubble,
and it prevents time
from going forward.
Summer in Gravity Falls can last
as long as you want it to.
Really?
But how does it work?
I just need you to get
a little gizmo for me from your uncle.
Something small-- he won't
even know it's missing.
Huh, maybe Dipper has
something like that in his nerd bag.
Let me guess.
Mabel didn't take it well?
I--I don't know.
Maybe I'm making
the wrong decision.
I need to think about this.
Dipper, right now we need
to focus on the mission.
Now, come on.
I've got the glue.
Hand me the rift
and let's make history.
What?
Oh, no, the rift!
Huh.
That's odd.
- Is this it?
- Yes, that's it!
Just hand it over and
I'll do my thing.
Unless you're ready
to leave Gravity Falls.
Just a little more summer.
Oops!
What?
Oh, no!
Wait, wait, wait!
Oh...
At last.
At long, long last!
The gate between worlds
is open!
The event one billion
years prophesized
has come to pass!
The day has come.
The world is finally mine!
What's going on?
What is that?
We're too late.
It's the end of the world.