Preston, I must say,
the guest list for
this year's party
has so much diversity.
Yes, a nice mix of
millionaires and billionaires.
Put the oyster fork
at an angle.
We're not animals, man.
Now where the devil is...
Pacifica!
What did I tell you
about that dress?
The theme is sea foam green,
not lake foam green.
- Go change.
- But I kind of like it.
Mind your mother,
Pacifica.
- But--
- [bell clangs]
Yes, Father.
[loud rumbling]
[gasping]
Oh, no, it's...
happening.
Yes, you are
my possessions.
Obey me!
[yells]
This is a disaster.
The party's in
just 24 hours.
Surely there's someone
who could handle this
sort of nonsense.
And I think I know
just the person.
[man]  You asked for it,
you got it.
An entire 48-hour
marathon of  Ghost Harassers.
on the Used To Be About
History Channel.
Be strong, bladder.
We're not gonna move
till sunset.
We interrupt this program
to bring you breaking news.
- Oh, what?
- It's starting!
- Turn it up.
- Make room for Grenda.
Tonight's the night, but I've
been out here for days.
The Northwest
family's annual
high-society
shindig ball soiree is here.
And even though common folk
aren't let in,
that won't stop us from
camping out
for a peek at
the fanciness.
[all] Ooh!
Okay, can someone
please explain
why people care about this?
Um, it's pretty much
the best party of all time.
Rich food, richer boys.
They say each gift basket
has a live quail inside.
Give me your life, Pacifica.
Guys, in case you've
already forgotten,
Pacifica Northwest
is the worst.
[knocking on door]
And that's not just
jealousy talking.
I'd say that
to her face.
I need your help.
You're the worst.
[all gasping]
- See?
- [knocking]
Look, you think
it's easy for me
to come here?
I don't wanna be seen
in this hovel.
But there's something
haunting Northwest Manor.
If you don't help me,
the party could be ruined.
And why should
I trust you?
All you've ever done
is try to humiliate
me and Mabel.
Just name
your price, okay?
I'll give you
anything.
Hi, Pacifica.
Excuse us.
Dipper, don't you see
what this means?
If you help Pacifica,
you could get us invites
to the greatest party
of all time.
What? Mabel, this is
Pacifica we're talking about.
But it's Candy
and Grenda's dream.
[both] Dream!
[sighs] Fine.
I'll bust your ghost.
But, in exchange,
I'll need three
tickets to the party.
[growls]
You're just lucky
I'm desperate.
[all] Whoo! Desperate,
desperate, desperate!
Grenda, get the glue gun.
We're making dresses.
Welcome to Northwest
Manor, dorks.
Try not to touch
anything.
[all exclaiming]
Everything's so fancy.
Fancy floors,
fancy plants.
[gasps]
Fancy man.
Yes. Very good, miss.
The rumors were true.
Ah, if it isn't
the man of the hour.
Hopefully, you can help us
with our little... situation
- before the guests
arrive in an hour.
- I'll do my best.
Splendid. Pacifica,
take our guests to
the problem room,
and, uh... he's not
wearing that, is he?
[teeth squeaking]
I'm on it.
It's like this collar
is strangling me.
Who do you guys think you're
impressing with this stuff?
Um, everyone.
You  wouldn't understand.
High standards are what make
the Northwest family great.
Funny, I thought it was
lying about founding the town.
Don't touch that.
Oh, wow, guys,
it's the guest list.
Whoa!
Check out this hottie.
Marius von Fundshauser.
He's a baron
from Austria.
Forget the quail.
I'm putting him in
my guest basket.
Hold up, ladies. I can't believe
I'm gonna say this,
but I think this boy
is out of our league.
Grenda's right.
He's a white whale.
Hunting him
will destroy us.
There are tons of
cute boys coming.
Let's swear a sisters'
truce not to waste
time on Marius.
Deal.
- Deal.
[all laughing]
Whoa.
[Pacifica] This is the main room
where it's been happening.
Yep, this looks like
the kind of room
that would be
haunted, all right.
I wouldn't be worried, though.
Ghosts fall under
a ten-category scale.
Falling plates sound like
a category one.
So what? Are you going
to bore him back into
the afterlife
by reading from
this book?
Just gotta splash
this sucker with
some anointed water,
and he should be out of
your probably-fake blonde hair.
What was that
about my hair?
Sh. I'm picking
something up.
Come on, stupid thing.
There we go.
- Uh, Pacifica?
- [screams]
Ancient sins.
[chanting continues]
Dipper, what is this?
It's a category ten.
[both screaming]
Ancient blood
and blackened skies.
The forest dark
once more shall rise.
What do we do,
what do we do?
Don't worry.
It can't get
worse than this.
I smell a Northwest.
Come out.
Come out,
wherever you are.
Hurry. Read through
your dumb book already.
I'm looking,
and it's not dumb, okay?
This book is gonna
save our lives.
All right, here we go.
Advice.
Oh, seriously?
You shouldn't
have come here.
This way. Hurry!
Welcome, dukes
and duchesses.
Sultans
and sportsmen.
Yo, what up, Presto?
And reclusive
102-year-old mayor
of Gravity Falls,
Mayor Befufftlefumpter.
[birds cawing]
It's okay.
They're with me.
Tonight, we will enjoy
only the finest of tastes
and only the snootiest
of laughter.
[fawning laughter]
That's the ticket.
Cheese, chocolate.
Candy, listen
to me carefully.
You're caught in
a sweet-savory loop.
Put the fondue fork down.
- I want to, but I can't.
- [tapping sound]
Introducing
Baron Marius von Fundshauser.
[fanfare plays]
Guten tag.
Guten  take me now!
Mabel, we had a truce.
Yes, yes,
yes, a truce.
Grenda, can you go
fetch us some
fancy napkins?
Wow. Okay.
Listen, Mabel,
I don't know if
I can follow this truce.
- He is too adorable.
- Me, too, Candy.
But what do we do?
He's unattainable.
What if we flirt
with him as a team?
With our cuteness combined,
one of us might have a chance.
It is the perfect plan.
But what about Grenda?
I love Grenda, Mabel,
but these boys are fancy.
Her aggressive flirting
style might scare them away.
Hey, what's on your shirt?
Ha! Gullible!
Loser!
Hurry. Through
the garden.
Watch out for peacocks.
Come on, come on.
I got it.
A haunted painting can only
be trapped in a silver mirror.
Look, there's
a silver mirror right there.
Wait. Don't
go in there.
This room has my parents'
favorite carpet pattern.
They'll lose it if we
track mud in there.
What? Are you serious?
- We'll find another way.
- [ghost wailing]
Pacifica, we don't
have time for this.
Let me through!
No. My parents
will kill me.
Why are you so afraid
of your parents?
You wouldn't
understand.
What is this place?
That's weird. I don't
even know where
this room is.
Hopefully, the ghost
doesn't either.
Yeah. Maybe we're safe.
- Pacifica! Watch out!
- [shrieks]
Your fate is sealed!
A silver mirror.
[ghost growling]
Prepare to die,
Northwest!
Did you get him?
Oh, free me!
[both]
Yes!
We did it!
[clears throat]
Can I pay you to pretend
that never happened?
Well, Pacifica, you really
found the right man for the job.
We can't
thank you enough.
That's enough.
Hey, just holdin' up
my end of the deal.
Wait. Leaving already?
You're at the world's
best party, dummy.
I'd love to stay,
but I've got
a category ten ghost
to dispose of.
Ha ha.
Category ten.
[both laughing]
Call me crazy,
but maybe she's not
that bad after all.
[ghost laughing]
What are you
laughing about, man?
I defeated you.
You've been had, boy.
- You remind me of me
150 years ago.
- What do you mean?
One hundred and fifty
years ago this day,
the Northwests asked
us lumber folk
to build them a mansion
atop the hill.
We were told it would be
a service to the town,
that once a year,
they would throw
a grand party, and all
would share in the bounty.
It took years of back-breaking
labor and sacrifice,
but when it was time
for the grand party
they promised the common
folk of the town,
they refused
to let us in.
You promised, Northwest.
With the trees gone,
the mudslides began.
While they partied
and laughed,
I was swept away
by the storm.
And so I said
with final breath,
150 years I'll return
from death.
And if the gate
still closed to town,
wealthy blood
will stain the ground.
A curse passed down
until this day.
So wait a minute.
The Northwests knew
this haunting was coming,
and they tricked me
into helping them
to avoid ghostly justice?
I'll be right back.
Thank you so much
for coming, mayor.
As a sign of our respect,
please take this chimp servant.
Keep him away from
bright lights.
He gets grabby.
[Dipper] Northwests!
You've got
some explaining to do.
Dipper, you came back.
You lied to me.
All of you did.
All you had to do
was let the townsfolk
into the party,
and you could've
broken the curse.
But you made me do
your dirty work instead.
Look at who you're
talking to, boy.
I'm hosting a party for
the most powerful people
in the world.
You think they'd come here
if they had to rub elbows
- with your kind?
- My kind?
I was right about you
all along.
You're just as bad
as your parents.
Another link in
the world's worst chain.
I'm sorry.
They made me.
- I should've
told you, but...
- [bell clangs]
Enjoy the party.
It's the last time
you and your kind
- will ever come.
- [chittering]
No, no!
Those aren't for him.
Stupid Northwests.
Making me do
their exorcism for them.
Exodus demonus,
spookus scarus,
aintafraidus
noghostus.
Dipper, please let me
get my vengeance on
the Northwests.
You hate them
as much as I.
Hey, I feel you.
It's just,
my sister's in there,
and you seem
a little unstable, man.
Very well, boy.
Then before you
banish my soul,
may these tired old
lumber eyes
gaze upon the trees
one final time?
Uh... I guess.
Go nuts, man.
[evil laughter]
What?
[screams]
Yes! Vengeance!
Oh, no. Mabel!
Hi. I'm Mabel.
So, Australia, huh?
Do you guys eat
kangaroo meat over there,
or are they
strictly pets?
I am from Austria.
[nervous laughter]
Tag, tag.
I am Candy.
I love the tiny hats
you wear on your shoulders.
If you were a boat,
do you know what kind you'd be?
A dreamboat.
That's what kind.
- You're tagged out.
- Tagged back in.
- You can't do that.
- I can tag myself.
It's allowed.
[arguing]
[Grenda] Ahem!
What exactly
was all that?
You were flirting with
Marius without me.
We're sorry, Grenda.
It's just...
Your flirting style
can come off as
a bit... intense.
Oh, I see.
You think I shouldn't
be myself
just because I'm in
this stupid mansion.
I thought you liked
my style.
We do, but these boys
might not.
Then I guess they wouldn't
like this either.
- Hey, Marius.
- Yeah?
You've got something
on your shirt.
[both gasping]
[all huffing]
Thank you all for coming.
I think we can all say
this party was
a rousing success.
I guess you could say
it was a slam dunk, Preston.
Yes, yes,
I guess, sure.
A toast...
to our family name.
What?!
Generations locked away.
My revenge
shall have its day.
Oh, the Grim Reaper.
I've been wondering
when you would arrive.
[ferocious growling]
Preston, what are
we going to do?
Prepare the panic room.
[screaming]
Please...
help me.
Whoa! That is messed up.
Just one way
to change your fates.
A Northwest must open
the party gates.
A Northwest?
Pacifica.
There you are.
The ghost is turning
everyone to wood,
and he just started
rhyming for some reason.
I need your help.
Pacifica?
Wanna know why
this room was locked up?
This is what I found
in here.
A painted record
of every horrible thing
that my family's
ever done.
Lying, cheating,
and then, there's me.
I lied to you just because
I'm too scared to talk back
to my stupid parents.
You were right about me.
I am just another link
in the world's worst chain.
Pacifica, I'm sorry
about what I said earlier,
but just because you're
your parents' daughter
doesn't mean you have
to be like them.
It's not too late.
- [ghost] It's too late!
- Oh, no!
- You are all wood!
- [screaming]
Dipper, wait.
All right, ghost.
Prepare to get...
No, wait!
No, no, no, no!
No, someone help.
Someone help!
A forest of death,
a lesson learned.
And now, the Northwest manor
will burn!
Hey, ugly.
Over here.
You want me to let in
the townsfolk?
'Cause I'll do it.
Just change everyone back.
You wish to prove yourself?
Pull that lever and open
the grand gate to the town.
Fulfill your ancestors'
promise.
Pacifica Elise Northwest,
stop this instant.
We can't let the town
see us like this.
We have a reputation
to uphold.
Now come into
the panic room.
There's enough mini sandwiches
and oxygen
to last you, me,
and a butler for a week.
[whispers]
We'll eat the butler.
- You dare disobey us?
- [bell clangs]
Dingly, dingly.
Is this bell broken?
Our family name
is broken,
- and I'm gonna fix it.
- [gasps]
Get it, get it.
[crowd clamoring]
Yes, yes,
it's happening.
My heart,
once as hard as oak,
now grows soft like more
of a birch or something.
[gasps]
Pacifica, you are not like
the other Northwests.
I feel lumber justice.
Oh, yes! Yeah!
Good Lord,
the riff-raff.
They're everywhere.
Ooh. Ha ha!
That's not how the fork
should be placed.
Ugh, man,
what happened?
Ahem!
Grenda, we are
so sorry.
We shouldn't have
left you behind.
It's okay.
Maybe I do need
to work on my flirting.
Come on, let's go dunk
our heads into cheese and
chocolate.
- Friends.
Wait! Don't go.
Grenda, was it?
I must speak with you.
There's something
about you.
I can't get you
out of my head.
You're so bold
and confident.
I know you're probably
out of my league,
but might I give you
mein  phone number?
I don't have a phone.
Write it on my face.
Whoa! Go, Grenda.
I guess we shouldn't
have sold her short.
I call bridesmaid.
What? I call
co-bridesmaids.
Man, if your family
hates you for this,
they're idiots.
This is great.
Enjoy it while it lasts.
Next year, I'm sure
they're just gonna
lock everyone out again.
Hey, guess what
we're standing on.
[gasps]
But seriously, I'd better go
find someone to clean this up.
Whoo! Scoobiddy doo!
Hornswaggle my goat knees!
Well, ho-ho,
what's up, McGucket?
Dipper, I been
lookin' for you.
I fixed the laptop.
I've been doin' calculations,
and I think
something terrible is comin'.
The apocalypse.
The end times.
[sighs]
You know what, McGucket.
How about we talk about
this stuff tomorrow?
It's a party.
Let's have some fun
for once, huh?
Oh, this is bad.
Somethin's comin'.
Somethin' big.
Quick, in here,
my darling.
A moment alone at last.
You can drop
the act, Trigger.
They're seeing
activity on the machine.
- It's go time.
- Roger that.
Where's my phone?
- I don't have it.
- Yes, you do.
It was in your purse.
So I'm just supposed to
hold onto everything for you?
I asked you when
we were in the car.
Why do we always
have to fight at parties?
Not even gonna ask.