>> CYRIL: And so, if I could
direct your attention to these
visual aids...
you will see that from our
initial supply of 1,000 kilos of
cocaine, we...
>> ARCHER: Hang on, dummy, we
had a ton of cocaine.
>> CYRIL: No, we... Well, we had
a tonne, T-O-N-N-E, also known
as a metric ton, but...
>> MALORY: (scoffs) Metric.
Who uses metric?
>> LANA: Every single country on
the planet except for us,
Liberia and Burma.
>> ARCHER: Wow, really?
>> ARCHER: 'Cause you never
think of those other two as
having their shit together.
>> CYRIL: Anyway, as you can
see...
>> MALORY: Why are they
thermometers?
>> PAM: I thought they were
>> ARCHER: Wait, they're not?
>> CYRIL: No... they... are...
not... cocks!
>> RON: Okay! Jesus, you people.
Next time, remind me to get shot
in the head.
>> ARCHER: Uh, Ron, next time,
get shot in the head.
>> MALORY: Sterling, shut up.
Cyril, continue.
>> CYRIL (sighs): So, as you can
see, we are already down to 125
kilos of cocaine, which was
worth about $6 million, so...
>> ARCHER: And, wait, how much
is that in pounds?
>> CYRIL: Forget pounds!
We're doing kilos!
>> ARCHER: No, I meant pounds...
>> MALORY: Sterling!
>> ARCHER: Exactly.
As in Doctor Who money.
>> MALORY: How do you stand
there and crack wise when this
is all your fault?
>> ARCHER: My fault?
I only lost 44.092 pounds of it,
mother.
It's Pam's fault we had to give
the Yakuza 100 kilos.
And this other five-- spoiler
alert-- she ate!
>> LANA: Yeah, and would now be
a good time to talk about Pam's
cocaine addiction?
>> PAM: Or the inspiring story
of her heroic struggle to
finally triumph over it?
>> LANA: What are you eating?
>> PAM (mouth full): Yogurt!
(grunting)
>> MALORY: Give me that!
>> PAM: Hey!
>> MALORY: Lick it.
>> ARCHER: (groans) Well, can't
unhear that.
Holy shit, yogurt is amazing!
Why have I never tried yogurt?!
>> LANA: How have you never
tried yogurt?
>> ARCHER: Mmm, I didn't know it
was that good.
>> MALORY: It's good because
it's cocaine!
>> ARCHER (gasps): Oh, my God.
And little kids eat it?
>> MALORY: Cyril, you said it
was locked up.
>> CYRIL: It is.
In the cage in the pantry.
>> MALORY: Then how did she get
it?
(Pam whistling)
That is it!
You're going to rehab.
>> PAM: What?! No, I can't!
And you can't make me!
>> ARCHER: Yeah, is that even
necessary?
I think she's in a pretty good
place.
>> MALORY: She's going and
that's final, and...
>> PAM: I swear to God, if you
send me to freakin' rehab, I'll
go right to the cops!
>> LANA: What?!
>> ARCHER: Oh, come on.
>> MALORY: You wouldn't dare.
>> PAM (laughing): Oh, yeah?!
Just try...
(clang)
>> LANA: Goddamn, Woodhouse.
>> WOODHOUSE: Only thing for a
grass, mum.
And, sir, I'm afraid your
breakfast will be four minutes
late.
>> ARCHER (groans): Typical.
>> ARCHER: What are you doing?
Come on. Tighter.
>> LANA: Oh, for the... That's
tight enough-- we're not making
tit bondage porn.
>> ARCHER: That's a thing?
>> CYRIL: Oh, yeah.
(Malory groans)
>> ARCHER: Ditto.
I just don't want her to escape.
You know how strong she is.
Might as well be green and
half-deaf.
>> LANA: What if we move the
coke and lock her in the cage
till she's clean?
>> ARCHER: Hey, yeah, sweat it
out, like Popeye Doyle.
How long would that take?
>> LANA: I don't know.
Couple of weeks?
>> MALORY: Try couple of never.
This is Pam we're talking about,
the poster child for addictive
personality.
What is wrong with you?
>> ARCHER (crying): I learned it
by watching you.
Oh, my God.
>> LANA: Yeah, spoiler alert.
So, what do you suggest we do?
>> MALORY (gasps): We throw her
a party.
With an enormous cake!
Cyril, can we spare another five
pounds of cocaine?
>> LANA: Malory!
>> MALORY: 2.27 kilograms, then!
Who are you, Thomas Corwin
Mendenhall?
>> ARCHER: Right?
>> LANA: We're not killing Pam!
>> CHERYL/CAROL: Wait, what?
>> RON: Jesus. Oh, come on in.
Make some more noise.
>> CHERYL/CAROL: Just 'cause
now you're the fat one?
>> LANA: Um, I said we were not
killing her.
>> CHERYL/CAROL: Oh.
>> LANA: And, also, this is a
baby.
>> CHERYL/CAROL: Ew!
>> LANA: A baby, by the way,
that I did not eat but to which
I will give birth.
>> CHERYL/CAROL: Ew!
>> ARCHER (chuckles): Right?
>> MALORY: Well, if she won't go
to rehab and you won't let her
die with dignity...
>> LANA: From an overdose of
cocaine cake?!
>> MALORY: Oh, please.
Change the word "cocaine" to
"Cookie Puss" and that's how her
obituary was going to read
anyway.
>> LANA: What the...
>> KRIEGER: I may have a simply
elegant solution.
>> LANA: Krieger.
>> KRIEGER: Right?
This place is like a Habitrail--
there are secret passages
everywhere.
>> CHERYL/CAROL: I think that's
why the colored maids never felt
safe.
They'd be polishing a spittoon
or whatever and suddenly...
Grandpa.
(others gasp)
Yeah. And dressed up like a
ghost?
>> LANA: What is it with your
family wearing ghost costumes to
scare black people?
>> CHERYL/CAROL: What is it with
you people making tit bondage
pornos in my ancestral home?!
>> KRIEGER: Ah, einige
Tittenfreude, huh?
>> CYRIL: Ooh, ja.
>> MALORY: So what's all this
about a solution?
>> KRIEGER: Aha! Yes.
And what is on my finger, you
ask?
>> LANA: I promise you no one is
asking that.
>> KRIEGER: Well, they should
because this nearly microscopic,
wittle-bitty guy is my new and
improved mind control chip.
>> ARCHER: Improved?
On the one that made Len Trexler
think he was a giant lettuce?
>> MALORY (gasps): Len
Trexler...
>> RON: Who the hell is Len
Trexler?
>> MALORY: Never heard of him.
>> KRIEGER: It's way improved,
and look how tiny.
I don't even need a drill-- I
can inject it right through the
temple.
>> PAM: Wait, what are we doing?
>> ARCHER: Stabbing science into
your brain.
>> PAM: What?!
>> MALORY: It's for your own
good, dear.
>> ARCHER: Yeah, so you don't
wind up giving blow jobs in a
bus station toilet.
But for cocaine.
>> PAM: No! Let me go!
(growling)
>> MALORY: Krieger, do you think
a chip could cure someone of
stage fright?
>> CHERYL/CAROL (gasps): No way!
>> MALORY: But you could be
>> CHERYL/CAROL: I could be
>> MALORY: Now, you listen to
me, missy.
You are getting a brain chip,
and then you're going on the
Grand Old Opera, and I don't
care if it kills you be...
(screams)
(Pam roars)
>> LANA: Pam, honey, just calm
down!
(Pam growls)
>> MALORY: Somebody do
something!
>> CYRIL: Nobody do anything!
>> ARCHER: Lana...
(Pam growls)
Lana!
>> LANA: Krieger!
>> KRIEGER: Yeah, I'm on it.
>> MALORY: Ow!
Idiot.
(Cheryl/Carol screams)
(Pam growls)
>> LANA: Pam!
>> ARCHER: Lana...!
>> CHERYL/CAROL: This is only
somewhat like that old Gypsy
woman said...!
>> ARCHER: Lana.
>> LANA: What?!
God shit damn it, Archer, what?!
>> ARCHER: Um, never mind.
>> LANA: Archer, I s...
>> ARCHER: The last thing you
need right now is a big,
shit-eating "I told you so."
(Lana groans)
>> MALORY: But it's exactly what
you deserve.
And, Krieger, I hope you have a
lot more where this came from
because...
>> LANA: Super.
Hunting women to force them to
have surgery against their will.
>> MALORY: It's for Pam's own
good.
She'll die if she doesn't quit
eating cocaine.
>> LANA: And who's gonna die if
you don't get rich managing
Cheryl's singing career?
>> MALORY: Maybe you.
Now, get out there and have
some fun!
>> ARCHER: How could we not?
(Woodhouse clears throat)
Woodhouse, I swear to God, if
you tell me lunch is four
minutes late...
>> WOODHOUSE: No, sir.
There's a Mr. Holly here.
Sorry, an Agent Holly.
From the FBI.
(others gasp, groan)
>> ARCHER: But lunch is still
a firm twelve.
(chuckles)
Firm twelve.
You know, as in inches?
Jesus, .3048 meters.
Hi.
Welcome to Nazi Canada!
(gagging sounds)
Eh?
>> MALORY: Why is the FBI here?
>> CYRIL: Did he show you a
warrant?
>> WOODHOUSE: No, sir, he...
>> CYRIL: Then tell him to go
piss off-- he can't come inside
without a warrant.
>> WOODHOUSE: He...
>> CYRIL: Well, unless you
invite him in.
>> ARCHER (groans): He's not a
vampire, idiot.
>> ARCHER: Plus it's daytime.
>> CYRIL: If invited in, law
enforcement can enter your home
without a warrant.
Once inside, under the doctrine
of "plain view," anything
illegal-- say, a truckload of
cocaine in the kitchen-- can be
lawfully seized as evidence.
They can also enter a private
residence under any number of
exigent circumstances, like
providing emergency assistance
to an occupant, say, if they
heard someone screaming...
(Malory screams)
(others gasp)
>> HOLLY: Good morning.
>> CYRIL: No, sir, good day.
I insist that you leave
immediately, as you have entered
this residence unlawfully.
>> HOLLY: Uh, you want to jump
in here, Yoda's dad?
>> WOODHOUSE: I invited him in.
>> MALORY: Woodhouse!
>> HOLLY: And once you do that,
you know, we are in.
Not unlike vampires.
>> ARCHER: See?
>> MALORY: Be that as it may,
why are you here?
>> HOLLY: Oh, just checking in,
making sure you folks aren't
engaging in treason, espionage
or anything else illegal.
>> MALORY: Well, I can assure
you...
>> HOLLY: Like drugs.
>> MALORY: Hmm?
>> HOLLY: Cocaine?
>> MALORY: Nope.
>> HOLLY: Yakuza?
>> MALORY: Mm-mm.
>> HOLLY: Shootout?
>> HOLLY: No one here was shot
>> MALORY (chuckling): Well, I
think we'd remember that.
>> HOLLY: Then what's his
problem?
>> LANA: Vasectomy.
>> CYRIL: Piles.
>> ARCHER: Gout.
>> CYRIL: Mumps.
>> KRIEGER: Progeria! (sniffles)
He's just a little boy.
>> CYRIL: But whatever is wrong
with him...
>> ARCHER: Goutmumps.
>> CYRIL: ...is none of your
business, and since nothing in
plain view would lead a
reasonable person to suspect
illegal activity, I demand that
you...
(Gillette screams)
>> HOLLY: Nobody move!
>> MALORY: Well?!
>> CYRIL (sighs): They can also
do what's known as a...
>> HOLLY: Protective sweep...!
>> CYRIL: Case law regarding
search-and-seizure is actually
quite interesting...
>> MALORY: What... about... the
cocaine?
(Cyril speaking indistinctly)
>> CYRIL: ...admissible as
evidence but only if he sees
it.
>> MALORY: So we have to
keep him out of the kitchen.
All right, fan out!
Agent Holly is the prime target,
but...
>> LANA: So, just so we're
clear, you want us to
tranquilize a federal agent.
>> MALORY: Do you have a better
idea?
>> LANA: I do not.
>> MALORY: Then we just slap
some panties and rouge on him,
pose him with Gillette-- whose
fault this is!-- make some
glossy 8x10s...
>> KRIEGER: I'll do it!
I have a camera! Dibs!
>> MALORY: And then I doubt
we'll be hearing from Agent
Holly in the future.
>> CYRIL: Or you could pose him
with Woodhouse.
>> WOODHOUSE: What?
>> KRIEGER (chuckles): God
knows he's a little GILF.
(others groan)
>> ARCHER: That's a thing?!
>> CYRIL: How do you not know
the different kinds of porn?
>> ARCHER: Because I have sex
with actual women, Cyril!
My girlfriend's not equal parts
the Internet, a tube of Kentucky
jelly, self-loathing and a sock!
>> MALORY: Tell that to your
cellmate!
Now, go!
>> GILLETTE (slurred): You
scared the shit out of me!
>> CHERYL/CAROL (groans): What,
literally?
>> PAM: Seriously, dude, what is
up with you?
>> GILLETTE (sniffles): I could
walk, and now I can't, and ain't
nobody loves ol' Ray no more.
(crying)
>> CHERYL/CAROL: Well, yeah,
you're disgusting.
But, you, I am totally digging
this whole Queen Kong vibe.
(Pam growls)
(Gillette sobbing)
>> HOLLY: My God, are they...
torturing a woman?
Hang on, ma'am!
I'm a federal agent, and I'm
coming!
By God, I am coming!
>> LANA: Okay, you three head
upstairs...
>> ARCHER: Hang on.
>> LANA: I'm going to the
kitchen to make sure he doesn't
stumble onto the coke.
>> ARCHER: Hang on.
>> LANA: What?
>> ARCHER: Question.
>> ARCHER: Are we not saying
"phrasing" anymore?
Which, that's fine, whatever,
but if we're doing a new thing
and nobody told me-- that I'd
have a problem with.
>> HOLLY: Oh, screw me!
>> ARCHER: Said Ripley to the
android Bishop.
Wait, hang on. Um...
Goddamn it!
What was wrong with "phrasing"?!
>> GILLETTE: Nothing!
I'm fine.
Just get out, leave me alone!
>> HOLLY: I just need to be sure
you're not being held here
against your...
That is a federal offense!
>> GILLETTE: I said, get out...!
>> KRIEGER: Oh, hey, remind me
to reboot the CPU in Ray's spine
so he can walk again.
>> CYRIL: What?
A reboot-- that's all it takes?!
>> KRIEGER: Beep boop.
>> CYRIL: He's been paralyzed
for months.
What the hell have you been
waiting for?!
>> KRIEGER: Yeah, but think how
much happier he'll be now.
>> LANA: Or-- and I'm just
spitballin' here-- I find Holly
first, show him the coke, get
immunity, testify against them,
then you and I go into witness
protection and spend the rest of
our miserable lives on the run,
hounded by the fact that we
betrayed our friends.
Ugh!
Or I get arrested and give birth
in a supermax prison and...
Oh, wait.
Does the baby grow up in prison,
or...?
>> WOODHOUSE: Oh.
Hello, old friend.
>> LANA: What the shit, Archer?!
>> ARCHER: Hang on.
I knew you'd shoot without
looking.
>> LANA: Oh, really, you know me
that well?!
>> ARCHER: Uh, well enough to
know you're down here wondering
if witness protection ever sends
people to the Virgin Islands.
>> LANA: Well, in case you'd
forgotten, I have an unborn
child to think about!
>> ARCHER: Jesus Christ, Lana,
who can forget?
It's baby this, baby that.
>> LANA: Aw, Baby Archer, who's
a jeawous baby?
>> ARCHER: What?!
Holy shit, do you have anemia?
>> LANA: No, I...
>> ARCHER: Uh, edema,
hypertension, preeclampsia,
Braxton-Hicks contractions,
pica?!
>> LANA: I...
>> ARCHER: GERD?!
Lana, do you have GERD?!
(Lana clears her throat)
>> LANA: How do you know about
the various possible
complications of pregnancy?
Archer?
>> ARCHER: Maybe I looked it up.
>> LANA: Why?
>> ARCHER: I was concerned about
you.
Blow me!
>> LANA: Just making sure you're
not into preggo porn.
>> ARCHER: Oh, goddamn it!
That can't be a thing!
>> LANA: It is absolutely a
thing, and do you just not have
the Internet, or...?
>> ARCHER: I have Minitel, okay?
>> LANA: A: not the Internet,
B: only works in...
>> ARCHER: France, Lana.
Oui, maintenant je sais!
>> LANA: Okay, um, thanks for
your concern, and I don't know
what you think you heard about
witness protection, but...
>> ARCHER: They don't make
babies grow up in prison, Lana.
>> LANA: Yeah, right?
>> ARCHER: They take them away
the minute they're born and send
them to an orphanage.
>> LANA: No, not the minute
they're...
>> ARCHER: That very minute,
Lana!
They don't even dry them off!
(Lana cries)
So if I were you, I'd run out
that door while I still had a
chance.
>> LANA: But-but, Archer, I...
>> ARCHER: I'd also waste five
precious minutes of my head
start in the race to freedom
giving that swell guy Archer a
combination good-bye/thank-you
blow job.
(Lana cries)
(Lana laughs)
>> LANA: Asshole.
>> ARCHER: Yeah, or a rim job.
What do you care?
You're never gonna see him
again.
>> LANA: I can't.
>> ARCHER: I know.
I was kidding, stupid.
>> LANA: I mean I can't leave
you, stupid!
(loud knocking)
>> HOLLY: This is the FBI!
Open this door!
>> ARCHER: Well, not now...
stupid.
And so, wait.
Where did we land on that
blow job?
Sorry, rim job.
>> HOLLY: Do you hear me?!
Open this door!
Obstructing... a federal
agent... is a felony...
punishable...
Ow!
...by up to 20 years
imprisonment, if said
obstruction results in the
bodily injury of said agent,
which I think may have just
happened to said agent's-- ow!--
rotator cuff.
Aah!
>> LANA: 20 years?!
>> ARCHER: Lana, look at all
that coke!
20 years is just gonna be the
Bac-Os on our prison salad.
Besides, technically, Woodhouse
is the one obstructing.
>> LANA: Archer!
>> ARCHER: Relax. They don't
send people that old to prison.
It costs, like, two grand a day
just to keep them alive.
>> LANA: I'm talking about us!
>> ARCHER: Hmm. I don't know.
A hundred bucks?
Depends who you ask, Lana.
Liberals say this much,
conservatives say this much...
>> LANA: So, now you're just
dicking around?
>> ARCHER: Yes.
>> LANA: Between the FBI and a
ton of cocaine.
>> ARCHER: Yes.
>> LANA: So, can I assume you
have a plan?
>> ARCHER: Yes.
I mean, I don't, but you can
assu... Ow! Ow!
(Holly grunts)
Ow! Ow! Ow!
(Holly groans)
>> HOLLY: I'm coming!
>> ARCHER: Said Ripley to... Ow!
Goddamn it, woman!
>> CHERYL/CAROL: Come on!
Why are you slowing down?!
>> PAM: Need... got to...
More cocaine.
>> CHERYL/CAROL: So, please
don't take this the wrong way--
because I'm loving being your
Esmeralda-- but you may have a
problem.
And it sounds like the solution
is more cocaine, so turn left up
there.
>> MALORY: But why are you
leaving?
They can't compel a husband and
wife to testify against each
other!
>> RON: Oh, yeah?
They may not have to compel me.
(Malory gasps)
>> MALORY: And what is that
supposed to mean?!
>> RON: Oh, why don't you ask
that guy you never heard of,
Len Trexler?
>> MALORY: How can I?
I've never heard of him.
>> RON: You wouldn't know the
truth if it bit you on the ass
and held on, would you?
>> MALORY: Ron, wait!
>> RON: What?!
>> MALORY: Well, if you insist
on being an ass, I can't stop
you, but there is the small
matter of my putting the deed
to my apartment in your name.
(Ron laughs)
>> RON: Ah, it's your loss!
I'll mail you your furs.
(Malory gasps)
>> MALORY: Don't you dare!
At the very least, I insist on a
bonded courier!
Ron?!
(Holly grunts)
>> ARCHER: Ow!
Lana, cut it... Ow! Ow!
(Holly groans)
>> ARCHER: Ow! Ow!
>> HOLLY: What's this door made
out of, mithril?
>> ARCHER: Ow!
>> LANA: Just once, why can't
you take...
>> ARCHER: Ow!
>> LANA: ...anything seriously
just once?
>> ARCHER: Ow! I was serious
about that rim jo... Ow!
Seriously, please stop hitting
me.
What the...?
>> CYRIL: Oh, thank God!
>> LANA: Cyril? Wait.
How did you...?
>> KRIEGER: This house is
insane.
>> CYRIL: And scary, and gross,
and I'm pretty sure I smelled a
skeleton.
>> KRIEGER: No, you definitely
smelled a skeleton.
>> LANA: Well, this is great!
>> CYRIL: How?!
I inhaled skeleton!
>> LANA: Because now the coke...
(loud sounds of eating)
...is getting eaten by Pam!
Quick, make the wall spin around
again!
>> CYRIL: It just kind of spun
by itself!
>> ARCHER: Jesus Christ, have
you people never even heard of
Scooby-Doo?
>> KRIEGER: Oh, come on!
>> LANA: Of course.
>> CHERYL/CAROL: Uh... Pam?
(Pam roaring)
>> PAM: Aw, crap.
(Pam grunting)
(Cheryl/Carol laughing loudly)
(gasps, sad roar)
>> ARCHER (laughing): Oh, my
God.
That's so freakin' unsafe.
>> LANA: Okay, Krieger, Cyril,
get in there, and we'll spin you
back around. Archer...
>> CYRIL: Why do I have to go
back in there?!
>> LANA: Because I said so!
>> KRIEGER: Yeah, plus
skeletons?
>> LANA: Archer?
>> ARCHER: Got it.
>> LANA: Oh! Goddamn it!
>> KRIEGER: Ooh!
>> CYRIL: Goddamn it.
>> ARCHER: Godspeed, you
meddling kids.
>> WOODHOUSE (moaning): And sir,
I'm afraid your breakfast will
be four minutes late.
>> ARCHER: Yeah, duh.
I already berated you.
>> LANA: Woodhouse, get away
from the door!
>> WOODHOUSE: Hmm? Oh!
>> HOLLY: Goddamn it!
Just what do you people think
the letters FBI stand for?
>> ARCHER: I bought a T-shirt
once where it stood for "Female
Body Inspector."
God, is Myrtle Beach not the
best?
>> HOLLY: Pull a stunt like this
again, you'll never make it back
to Myrtle Beach.
>> ARCHER: I probably wasn't
going to anyway.
Turns out it's actually not the
best.
>> LANA: And you actually have
no right to search this house.
As you can see, there's nothing
illegal going on.
>> HOLLY: Maybe not now, but I
know you still have a lot of
international contacts from your
ISIS days.
Mexico, Colombia, the Orient.
I bet it wouldn't be too hard to
get set up in the drug trade.
>> ARCHER (laughing): Well,
you'd be surp... Oh!
>> LANA: We're not drug dealers,
Agent Holly.
>> HOLLY: Good, because I'll be
watching you... like a hawk
that's been bred with an eagle
to produce some sort of...
eagle-eyed superhawk... with a
badge.
>> LANA: So, am I crazy, or is
he super weird?
>> ARCHER: Oh, well, I'm torn,
Lana, I really am.
I want to say "both," but I also
don't want you to stop my heart
again, so...
>> LANA: Who's da widdle baby?
Who's da widdle baby?
Yes, he is, widdle, little baby!
>> CYRIL: Wait. The brain chip
is in there?
>> KRIEGER: I told you it was
small.
>> CYRIL: Said Ripley to the...
No, doesn't work there.
>> KRIEGER: Yeah, it's crap.
Okay, I actually only have one
brain chip, so... who's our
lucky winner?
>> CYRIL: Hmm. I guess we have
to decide if we want regular
lame Cheryl and a Pam who's not
gonna overdose on cocaine and
die, or potentially famous
country singer Cheryl and a Pam
who... tits.
>> KRIEGER: Flip a coin?
>> CYRIL: No.
>> LANA: And, yeah, he's a
weirdo, but I think Agent
Holly's right.
We do have a lot of
international connections.
>> ARCHER: So, I'm thinking I
should take a trip down old
Mexico way, maybe Colombia, or
even Southeast Asia, or...
Hey, where's Ron?
>> MALORY: Never heard of him.
>> LANA: Um...
>> ARCHER: Lana, let it go.
Jesus.
>> MALORY: But maybe we should
try to sell out to an
international cartel.
But let me be clear.
You won't be gallivanting around
under the pretense of work just
to visit the fleshpots of the
world.
This isn't ISIS.
>> ARCHER: No, I...
>> MALORY: And it definitely
isn't your semester abroad.
>> ARCHER: What?!
Come on, that's...
Hey, I don't think we need to go
into all the...
>> MALORY: Cobra whiskey and
ladyboys. I mean...
>> LANA: Ha!
>> ARCHER: Shut up.
>> MALORY: You shut up!
And Krieger?
I trust the brain-chip implant
was a success?
>> KRIEGER: I think. I mean,
it's in there, and she's alive.
Now we just have to see if there
were any adverse side effects.
(loud yawning)
>> LANA: Uh... Cheryl?
>> CHERYL/CAROL: Nah, Cheryl's
gone.
I'm Cherlene now.
And if somebody don't fry me six
goddamn eggs and some Carolina
fries, I would personally be
shocked-- shocked, I tell you--
if by mornin' this place ain't
burnt to the ground.
(loud yawning)
>> KRIEGER: And I'm not a
I mean, I'm definitely a doctor,
so... no, I think we're good.
Yup, yup, yup.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> MAN: Made... in Georgia.