LOUDSPEAKER: Allaaaaaaaahu akbaaaaaaaaaar...
LANA (O.S.): Noooo...
LANA: Ugh, no wonder Morocco Mole was
so inept, he never got any damn sleep.
[brrrrrpt]
LANA: Unlike some people!
ARCHER: Wuzzat?! Oh. G'morning.
LANA: Don't "g'morning" me!
ARCHER: What's your problem?
LANA: Besides that
frickin air raid siren?
ARCHER: It's the muezzin
chanting the adhan, Lana. God,
be open to other cultures.
LANA: I am! What I'm not open
to is not sleeping on the
floor, listening to your drunk
ass fart and snore all night in
the only bed, which I'm sure
is why you wanted this room!
ARCHER: If I may rebut,
point by point?
LANA: No, you may -
ARCHER: A, pretty sure I offered
to share the bed, B, I
wasn't that drunk...
LANA: Really.
ARCHER: Lana, this is me we're talking about.
And okay yeah,
maybe I smoked just a teeny bit
too much hashish, but that's
only because I didn't
want to be rude.
LANA: To who, the creepy old Moroccan dude?
Or those Dutch high school girls?
ARCHER: Both, the latter of
whom were college juniors, and
C, Lana we had to take this room,
Beat history was made here!
LANA: Says who, the manager?!
ARCHER: Wh-? Why would he lie?!
HOTEL MANAGER: You
are American, yes?
ARCHER: Uh, yes?
HOTEL MANAGER: Then you know
Allen Ginsberg, author of the
poem Howl, "I saw the best
minds of my generation
destroyed by madness,
starving hysterical naked..."
ARCHER: Yes.
HOTEL MANAGER: So for extra one
thousand American, you can
have room where he wrote-
ARCHER: Yes!
LANA: Archer, Morocco.
ARCHER: Yeah, hang on. Is this really the
room where Allen Ginsberg wrote Howl?
HOTEL MANAGER: Why not.
ARCHER: Yeah why not? And just
so we're clear, you're mad at
all that stuff, and not just being
weird because we had sex last night.
LANA: Are you -- we
didn't have sex!
ARCHER: Good, because I lied, I was drunk.
Want some? Make ya feel better.
LANA: What will make me feel
better, is to get out of shit-
reeking Tangier, which we can
only do after we extract -
agent what's his name, Kazak -
who, why the hell hasn't he
activated his GPS beacon, and
while we're on the subject,
where the hell is our GPS?
ARCHER: Oh. Promise
you won't get mad?
LANA: Uh, no?
Noooo...
ARCHER: I know, right? It's loud as balls.
LANA: When did it
start going off?!
ARCHER: I dunno, like... before the
muezzin, but after the Dutch co-eds left.
LANA: You brought
them up to the room?!
ARCHER: Aha, busted! You
did get some sleep!
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
ARCHER: How can you not love this place?
The sights, the sounds, the smells...
LANA: No, Archer, just one smell, singular,
which would knock a possum over.
ARCHER: Didelphis virginiana! My second
favorite animal with a prehensile -
LANA: Tail.
ARCHER: Thanks, Brett
Somers, yes, a tail.
LANA: You have one.
ARCHER: I wish, then I'd be like my first
favorite prehensile-tailed animal -
LANA: Archer?
ARCHER: Nightcrawler! AKA-
LANA: Archer.
ARCHER: Kurt Wagner, Lana.
Although he can teleport, so
the prehensile tail is -
LANA: Goddammit we're
being followed!
ARCHER: When were you
planning to tell me?!
LANA: I -- whooaaa!
LANA: Look ooouuut!
SCOOTER GUY (O.S.):
[shouting insults]
ARCHER: Oh yeah?! Well -- damn, I had
something in Arabic for this...
LANA: Wow, that
accidentally worked.
ARCHER: Accidentally?
LANA: Just drive.
There, take that left.
ARCHER: Hang on, I'm
swinging back around.
LANA: No you're not, why?
ARCHER: Because look in here and
tell me the Arabic phrase for
"your mother is a whore and
a goatherd is her pimp".
LANA: Oh, right, absolutely.
ARCHER: Oh for -- nice,
real mature, Lana!
LANA: Look, obviously Morrocan
intelligence isn't as stoked about
Kazak coming over to ISIS as your
mother is so can you please
quit dicking around!
ARCHER: Who's dicking around?!
Me, who's driving this clown
car like Parnelli Frickin
Jones, or you, Lana Litterbug!
LANA: Archer, I am seriously not in the
mood for your bullshit right n-owww!
LANA: Ahem ARCHER: Oh.
Hold on, I'm stopping.
LANA: Why.
ARCHER: Because according
to this we're here.
LANA: Are you coming?
ARCHER: No, but I'm
breathing fast.
[door slam]
ARCHER: Get it? Lana,
did you get it? Lana?
Or were you just trying not to laugh
because you're cranky for some reason.
LANA: I'm cranky because I didn't sleep-
ARCHER: Inaccurate.
LANA: -- and now I can't sleep, because
I'm pretty sure I have a concussion!
ARCHER: Wait, seriously?
LANA: Yes, Archer, my
head totally kills.
ARCHER: Well that's not good-
LANA: Wait, seriously?
ARCHER: -- because Tangier's totally awesome-
LANA: Wildly inaccurate.
ARCHER: -- but it's probably not the
best place to receive medical treatment.
LANA: So what say we grab this Kazak guy
and get out of this flyblown shithole.
ARCHER: Okay, but you're
missing out on all the great
things Tangier has to offer.
LANA: Name one.
ARCHER: Chee- LANA: Besides cheap hash
and a repulsingly low age of consent.
ARCHER: Rugs?
- Okay... - Shooting me's not gonna
change the unbeatableness
of their rug prices.
LANA: It might change my mood-
ARCHER: To remorseful?
LANA: -- but I drew because we don't know
what's waiting for us behind this -
Door. Ya know...
DOG (O.S.): Grrowwrrrgrrl!
LANA: Ungh!
ARCHER: Lana!
LANA: Archer?
DOG: Grrrrrrrr...
ARCHER: How ya dooin, buddy?
LANA: I'll be better
when you shoot him.
ARCHER: I was talking to hiiim, stupid...
LANA: Great, then I'll shoo -
DOG: Grrowwoofwoofwoofrowwrr!
ARCHER: I don't think he likes guuuuns...
LANA: Okay, that's -- stop,
c'mon, cut it -Archer get
the damn dog off my tits!
ARCHER: Here boy! C'mon buddy!
Uh, heel? I don't think
he speaks English.
LANA: Well what's
"get off" in Arabic?!
ARCHER: She asked, regretfully, remembering
that just moments earlier she'd
thrown away his
eleven-dollar phrasebook.
LANA: Oh for the -- grrrrt off!
ARCHER: Oof! Who's a good boy?
Who's a good boy? Who's a
good boy good boy good boy?
LANA: Ugh, I thought
you hated dogs.
ARCHER: I love dogs, Lana.
Except Mother's dog.
Hated that dog.
LANA: Because she loved
it more than you?
ARCHER: Ha ha, very funny.
Although, she never forgot the dog's birthday...
[enchanting music]
LANA: Can we please
just do this?
DOG: Grrowwoofwoofwoofrowwrr!
LANA: Aagh!
ARCHER: What're you--
Lana put it away!
LANA: Alright okay
okay alright already!
ARCHER: See? He really doesn't like guns,
Lana, he can't stress that enough.
LANA: Well what are we supposed to do
if Kazak doesn't wanna come with us?
ARCHER: Feed him to Cujo here,
he can poop him out when we get
home. Who's a poopy
boy, who's a poopy boy?
LANA: Shit-breath slobberin-ass mutt...
ARCHER: Don't listen to her,
she's-
Wow, but you could use a tic-tac.
LANA: Kazak? Hello? Kazak.
Kazak!
DOG: Woowoowoowoowoof!
LANA: Get away from me,
what're you doing?!
ARCHER: What're you doing?!
Lana, you can't beckon
him and then rebuff him!
LANA: Beckon and rebuff whom.
ARCHER: Kazak.
DOG: Woof?
LANA: Noooo, he's not--
he cannot be Kazak.
ARCHER: He can according
to his nametag.
LANA: Son of a... bitch!
KAZAK: Woowoowoowoowoof!
ARCHER: Well, technically she's right.
Who's a sonuvabitch? Are you a
sonuvabitch?
KAZAK: Woof!
ARCHER: Lana, look! He
thinks he's people!
LANA: Nooo, no, no, no no, nooo.
I did not sign on to be a dogsitter
for -- who's frickin dog is this?!
ARCHER: Who gives a shit, Lana, he's
like the Pl of, lemme finish, fetch!
KAZAK (O.S.): Woof!
ARCHER: Well I will if you bring it here!
I can't throw it
if it's in your mouth!
KAZAK (O.S.): Woowoowoof!
LANA: Why didn't
you become a vet?
ARCHER: Honestly?
Didn't have the grades.
LANA: No shit.
ARCHER: Why would I lie about that?
And who're you calling?
LANA: Who do you think.
ARCHER: Ask her if
we can keep him.
CHERYL/CAROL (O.S.): Ms.
Archer, Lana for you, line one.
MALORY: I'm not here.
CHERYL/CAROL: Ooohhhh!
Then... how...?
MALORY: Oh for the love,
obviously I am here--
CHERYL/CAROL: Whew...
MALORY: -- I just don't
wish to speak to her!
CHERYL/CAROL: But you are here...
MALORY: Aht! If you walk over
here and touch me, you'll spend
your lunch hour being fitted
for a prosthetic hand.
CHERYL/CAROL: I only get forty-five minutes.
But I'll tell her
you're not here. But
you are, right?
MALORY: Out!
CHERYL/CAROL: Ahh!
MALORY: I assume Lana's mad
because Sterling's pushing her
buttons. What a surprise.
- Speaking of... - You finally saved
enough money for a sex change.
PAM: No. I'm actually broker than usual...
REFEREE: Nine...!
Ten...! She's out!
[ding, ding, ding]
PAM: Uht? Pungash bishiz...
PAM: But I'm very comfortable
in my own body, thank you very much, and-
MALORY: Don't thank me, thank -
PAM: And before you say-
MALORY: May I finish?! Archer
Daniels Midland, now what do
you want, I'm extremely busy.
PAM: To be a field agent!
MALORY: I'm sorry?
LANA (O.S.): You should be!
ARCHER: How was I supposed to know
it was gonna make him do that?!
[fweet]
LANA: Stuffing him full
of street kebabs?!
ARCHER: A, it was kufta, and bee-
elzebub's asshole, Kazak!
Bad dog! Bad dog!
KAZAK: [whine]
ARCHER: Sorry buddy, I didn't mean that, I-
LANA: I did! It's bad enough
your mother sends me on this
bullshit mission, but now she
won't even take my call?!
ARCHER: Lana, New York's five hours behind,
maybe she's not in the office yet.
LANA: Oh please,
she's totally there!
MALORY: Wh-?
Out!
CHERYL/CAROL: Just checking!
God!
MALORY: Idiot. As I was saying...
ARCHER: I'm! Sorry! And I'm sure I - [fweet]
ARCHER: -- ugh, also speak for Kazak,
who, by the way, is the real victim here.
LANA: How is he the victim?!
ARCHER: Lana, his nose is like a jillion
times more sensitive than ours!
[fweet]
ARCHER: Gotta be killing him...
LANA: Well before I kill him,
and you, just get us to the port.
Hopefully the stupid boat
to Spain has aspirin.
ARCHER: What boat?
LANA: What what boat,
the boat boat!
ARCHER: Wow, you might actually
be concussed, because
that was not a real sentence.
LANA: Archer?
ARCHER: And the boat's not a
boat, Lana, it's a frickin
hovercraft! Woohoohoohoooo!
KAZAK:
Woowoowoowooowoowooowooo!
ARCHER: Woohoo... oh. But, boat or not-boat...
We won't be getting on it.
LANA: A... roadblock?!
ARCHER: So, guess we're driving
through the desert to
the backup extraction point.
KAZAK: Rrowrf.
[sploosh]
LANA: uhh, uhh.
ARCHER: Sorry. I know you had your
heart set on that hovercraft ride.
MALORY: But why on earth do you
think you're qualified to
be an ISIS field agent?!
PAM: Uh, besides Cyril's one?
CYRIL: Hey...
PAM: Cyril? Ya wanna fresh one?
CYRIL: I do not, no.
PAM: Then shut your fist-hole, and show
Ms. Archer how I did on the IFAAB.
MALORY: The ISIS Field Agent
Aptitude Battery? You took it?
You aced it?! No, but --
this can't -- you cheated!
PAM: How?! Everybody watched me take it!
Under sterile conditions, by the way!
CYRIL: Well... [fweet]
PAM: What. Punkass bitches...
CYRIL: Sterile test conditions, anyway.
But I can promise she didn't cheat.
MALORY: Be that as it -- hm.
Hmm. Hmmmm? This means nothing,
My God, a perfect score on the
IFAAB merely indicates that a person
is a candidate for field agent
status, it can't determine if
they're suited for actual
field work. I mean, what if she
had to subdue an enemy agent?
PAM: Cue sad trombone, aaaaaaaaaaaand-Go!
EVERYBODY: Aaaaaagh!
MALORY: Pam! What the
hell did you -- waagh!
- My God... - And it goes on like that,
for another thirty-eight
soul-cleaving minutes.
GILLETTE: Of which you
were there for two.
KRIEGER: Three! I was scared,
I ran away, sue me. And then
sue me for this! Smoke bomb!
MALORY: So you aced the test and
beat up a nazi, a nerd, and
queen of the robots-
GILLETTE/CYRIL: Heeyyy!
MALORY: If the saddle oxford and/or
ruby slipper fits! Mister and/or
missy! What makes you think
I need another field agent?
LANA: I quit.
ARCHER: Lana believe me, nobody wanted
to ride a hovercraft more than me, but -
LANA: Stop the car! I'm serious, I'm-
ARCHER: I'm serious, calm the
hell down! Here, hit this
hashbrown, that creepy old dude
put his lips on it, but-
LANA: Archer stop the goddamn car!
ARCHER: Lana put the gun down, he's gonna-
KAZAK: Yipe!
ARCHER: Stoppin the caaar, buuuddies...
LANA: Sorry about that,
furface. Wouldn't have shot
you for a gazillion bucks.
KAZAK: Rrowr?
LANA: You, not so much.
ARCHER: Lana c'mon, we both know you're-
LANA: Quitting, Archer, yes, exactly.
ARCHER: Oh. I was gonna
say "not quitting."
LANA: Wildlier inaccurate.
ARCHER: "Wildlier" isn't a real word, by the way.
At least not in English.
KAZAK: Rrowr?
ARCHER: I dunno, she threw away my phraseboo-
[fweet]
ARCHER: Almost kind of
wishing she'd shot you.
KAZAK: Roowr.
ARCHER: No, no, no, I'm kidding
Who's my stinky boy, huh?
Who's my... [fweet]
ARCHER: So hey, I know we kid
around a lot, but I think you
might have dog cancer.
ARCHER: No way, I'm not going back for her.
You're new here,
but Lana cries wolf on quitting
ISIS like twice a week.
KAZAK: Rowr.
ARCHER: She'll be fine.
She's got... oh.
I was gonna say GPS, gun, sat-phone,
and canteen full of lifesaving water.
KAZAK: Rowr.
ARCHER: Well?! She's the one who
stormed off into the desert
with no GPS, no gun, no sat-
phone and no lifesaving water,
and why the hell are you taking her
side, she jammed a gun in your -
KAZAK: Rrowrf.
[sploosh]
ARCHER: So, were you whining
about Lana being an idiot or
about you being carsick?
KAZAK: Rrf.
ARCHER: How much frickin
kufta did you eat?!
KAZAK: Ruff!
ARCHER: Well? Whose fault is that?!
Okay, so maybe I egged
you on to eat five orders of it, and...
maybe I push Lana's
buttons on purpose, and just
generally make her life hell...
Which maybe I do, possibly, if
I'm being completely honest,
because I still have some pretty strong-
Ah, God damn, dude. Okay,
we'll go back for her. But
not because you said so!
LANA (O.S.): Because you let him,
you let him push your buttons.
That's why you stormed off with no
GPS, gun, phone, or lifesaving water.
And that's why you died in the desert.
Holy shit I'm
gonna die in the desert. Just
like Cheryl's gypsy woman said!
LANA: How. Would I ever.
Die in a dessert.
LANA: Well, pretty close. And
you're not gonna die out here,
because any minute now... aha!
Haaa!
Archer's gonna come crawling back to
you, tail between his legs, from - From
the wrong direction. Oh, shit.
Oh, shit.
ARCHER: Wait wait wait, shut up, what?
What are you talking about?!
CHERYL/CAROL: I dunno, like maybe a
gigantic chocolate mousse, or -
ARCHER (O.S.): I said desert!
CHERYL/CAROL: Oh.
Still pretty close.
ARCHER: Will you put
Mother on the damn phone?!
CHERYL/CAROL (O.S.):
What's the magic woooord?
ARCHER: Oh for the --please!
CHERYL/CAROL: No,
they changed it.
ARCHER: Cheryl, you
stupid [beeeeeeeeeeeep]
CHERYL/CAROL: Lucky guess.
PAM: Plus I'm a quick learner
plus you've seen me drive I'm
an amazing driver plus I almost
never get sick plus I already
bought three pantsuits plus-
MALORY: Alright! I'll think about it!
PAM: Is that a real you'll
think about it, or a "Pam if
your pig Leon wins a blue ribbon
at the county fair maybe
we won't kill him and eat him
for Easter dinner and render
what's left into soap"
you'll think about it?
MALORY: It's-
PAM: Because I never really got over that.
MALORY: It's a real one-
PAM: Yaaaaaay!
MALORY: -- but thank you for that glimpse
into your bleak, farmy childhood.
PAM: It was actually pretty awesome.
And if I'm being honest, so was Leon.
MALORY: Get out. What.
ARCHER (O.S.): Mother? Mother
it's Sterling, don't talk just...
MALORY: Ohhhh no!
ARCHER: Guess I had that coming.
MALORY: You must really think I'm an idiot...
ARCHER: Well, your
words Mother, but my
voicemail doesn't call you.
MALORY: Oh right. What's going on, did
you get Kazak, are you on the boat yet?
ARCHER: Okay, in order, I'll
get to that, yes, no, and
it's not a boat, it's a-
MALORY: Hovercraft, whatever,
why aren't you people on it?!
ARCHER: Well for starters, some of us
aren't people! But they think they
are! Yes they do! Yes they do!
Yes they -
MALORY: Sterling!
ARCHER: Oh, so anyway, Lana quit, and-
MALORY: She -- what'd you do this time?!
ARCHER: Nothing! She quit
because you made us fly to
Morocco, coach, by the way, and
don't even get me started on
that! For a dog! You know how
insulting that is?! A stupid dog?!
MALORY: Wh-? Is this about
the carriage ride?!
ARCHER: The -- I mean, I'd be lying
if I said it wasn't a factor! But -
MALORY: Let me tell you
something about that so-called
"stupid" dog, mister man...
ARCHER: Are you -- that's all
we were after?! Well?! You
could've told us, Mother! Oh!
And you could've told me you
just took her to the stupid vet!
MALORY: Whoooo just had a lovely birthday
carriage ride through Central Paaark?
DUCHESS: Woof!
MALORY: Yes she did!
Yes she did!
DUCHESS: Grrrrrrrr...
ARCHER: Whatever, look, we're
not gonna make it to the backup
extraction point, so get a fix
on my signal and reroute the
chopper to those coordinates!
MALORY: Okay, rerouting
now, ETA ten minutes.
ARCHER: Whenever, we'll be here...
One way or the other.
So hey, how you
doin on the kufta?
KAZAK: Rrf.
ARCHER: Yeah good, get it all out now.
Because this next part's gonna suck.
PASSENGER AGENT: [yelling]
LANA: Archerrrr!
ARCHER: See?! That's why I said scrooch down!
Lana! Lana scrooch down!
LANA: No no no, Archer don't
Are you out of your mind?!
ARCHER: No!
Although I am out of ammo. Okay
buddy, so here's the deal!
A, scrooch down! And B,
normally in this situation I
do a a pit maneuver, but if I
do that the truck will flip,
and if Lana doesn't die, best
case she's a quadriplegic and I
marry her out of guilt but
after a few years of feeding
tubes and colostomy bags I
start to resent her and the
night nurse is like,
Brazilian and twenty?
KAZAK (O.S.): Grrrr...
ARCHER: Don't judge me! I have
needs, man! The point is, and
it might be a kinda shitty
plan, but I'm gonna jump on the
truck, so I need you to take the -
KAZAK (O.S.): Grrowwrrrgrrl!
ARCHER: -- wheel, exactly, so...
Kazak?
AGENTS (O.S.): Aaaggghhhh!
KAZAK: Grrowwrrghhh!
ARCHER: Lana, look! He
thinks he's vampires!
KAZAK: Grrowwrrgh!
ARCHER: Lana look ooouuut!
Kazaaaaaaaak!
AGENT: Ungh,
ARCHER: Nah, guys probably got
nine wives and a jillion
kids and.. holy shit, that's racist
Archer, what is wrong with you?
LANA (O.S.): Seriously...
ARCHER: Lana!
LANA: Archer, thank-
ARCHER: God is he hit, tell me he's not hit!
LANA: He's fine.
KAZAK: Woof!
LANA: As am I, not that you
give a shit.
ARCHER: Shhh. Lana, don't ruin the moment...
LANA: What moment, what're you
-- ahhh.
What're you doing, what is that?
ARCHER: Microfilm. It was on
his collar the whole time,
something about nukes in
Pakistan or -- one of the
akistans, I forget
which one. Owwww!
My point is sometimes we do good work.
So promise me you'll never quit again.
LANA: Only if you promise you'll
quit being such a colossal asshole.
ARCHER: Mmmm.
I can't.
LANA: Ya know...
KAZAK: Woowoowoowoowoowoowoof!
LANA: What.
[fweet]
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com