♪♪
So, uh...
Shut up, everybody!
And what do you mean,
Mother killed Woodhouse?
- Me?
- Yes, you!
- Yeah.
- Duh.
Well, not, you know,
not her personally,
it was probably
that golem of hers.
(Low, contented rumbling)
- (Mother::) Mr. Zerk.
- (Growl)
It's obvious that Archer's
bungled this whole thing,
which means we need to do
a little... housekeeping.
- Rgh?
- Mm-hmm.
And don't bring back
a dirty shovel.
Rrrgh...
(Big yawn)
Oh, my God, if someone
doesn't bring me toast
I will literally die.
(Archer:)
And how do you know about this?
Oh, come on, everybody knows.
Your partner got in too deep
on his dope bill,
so she had that ape whack him.
If I find out
you're lying to me...
Why would I lie?
That bitch...
(Chuckling)
Well, you know what they say,
you lie down with dogs,
you wake up with fl...
(breaks squeal) (Poovey:) Jesus!
(Lana:)
What! What's the big idea?
The big idea is
we're going to Dreamland,
and you're all
gonna stay tied up
until I find out the truth.
Who keeps this much rope
in their trunk?
Besides rapists?
Uh, mountain climbers?
Yeah, climbing up to their
mountaintop rape-shed.
- Their what?
- How would that even work?
Are the victims already
up there, or... (Gunshot)
(Short, startled reactions) And
the next person who talks...
(Long ahem)
Son of a... what?
No, I was... gonna say
rope salesmen.
(Tires squealing)
(Poovey:) Oh, God!
Anybody have a joke about socks?
No? Okay, I got one.
Um, "sock sock."
And then you say "who's there?"
(Chuckles) Okay, then,
I guess just pout.
I... I-I don't understand.
Are you a cop?
(Laughs)
Uh, do I look like a cop?
N-no...
And yet!
(Startled yelp)
I'm commandeering this vehicle!
(Groans)
(Screams)
(Chuckling)
So listen... uh, I don't wanna
tell you how to live your life,
but if I were you, I'd just
go ahead and jump out.
(Terrified whimper/sob)
And I'd do it sooner rather
than... (Opens the door)
(Scream,
cut short by impact sound)
(Chuckling)
Later!
♪ ♪
♪♪
*ARCHER*
Season 08 Episode 08
"Archer Dreamland: Auflösung"
♪ ♪
Double double,
toil and trouble...
Although if I'm being honest,
it's really no trouble.
I love my work.
Not as much as you do,
obviously.
Alright, once my patient
arrives...
(Door creaks)
Well, speak of the devil.
I was just... oh, damn it,
what do you want?
Rrrrgh!
What?
Rgh.
(Annoyed sigh)
- Well, don't bring it back dirty.
- Rrgh!
_(Speaks German)
Because it ruins it.
(Archer:)
Now sit down!
Come on, I don't have
all Goddamn day!
I mean I do, but...
(through sock:)
Mm mmmf! Mmf mmfff mmf!
- What? (In agreement):
- Mmff! Mmf mmf! Rrmmfmf!
I can't understand a word
you're saying.
Mm mmmf! Mmf mmfff mmf!
Oh, my God.
- What?
- Pfft, pfft.
I don't know, I didn't really
have anything, I was just...
- Mmf mmmf!
(Groans)
- Pfft, pfft! Ptuh! Pbbb!
- There! Happy?
(Mother:)
What the hell
is going on here?
- Aha!
- Aha what?
Aha, um, hang on...
Trexler?
Why the hell are you here?
- I...
- Aha! Okay, I got it now. Sit down.
I beg your pardon?
Sit down!
Well, somebody likes to chew
his cabbage twice...
- Both of you!
- All right!
Rudolph
the rude-nosed Reindeer...
Now then, would you mind
telling me
what it is you think
you're doing?
I think it might be some kinda
Hercule Poirot-type deal,
where he gathers everybody
in the parlor.
- Have you lost your mind?
- (Chewing pills)
Actually maybe, I dunno,
I haven't slept in like a week
and I've been eating dexedrine
like candy, so...
(gasps)
Are you seeing tracers yet?
- I... no, shut up.
- What is this all about?
It's about you,
killing my partner!
What? Who told you that?
Trexler!
Wh... trexler, you dirty liar!
Well, now, technically I said
your goon killed him, but...
We had nothing to do with it!
Oh, and I'm just supposed
to take your word?
- You took his!
- Well?
- Why would I have him killed?
- Because he owed you money!
Okay, well think
about that statement.
- Strangely illogical.
- Yeah.
It's not like
he was walking around
with the money in his belly.
Then why'd you send me
down to long beach
the night my office was robbed?
- Burgled.
- Whatevered!
- To spy on Trexler! We're competitors!
- I...
Which is why, you idiot,
he's trying
to frame me for killing your partner!
(Trexler:) (Gasps)
Slander!
- Sue me!
- I got a half a mind to!
You've got half a mind, period.
And all the burns.
And if I could, I'd sue you
for hijacking my truckload
of whores!
- That wasn't me, either!
- Yeah, Poovey took 'em.
- Godddammit.
- What?
- Yeah, what?
- Oh, don't play dumb, Figgis!
I'm not! I had no idea!
- Or did he?
- Oh, you son of a bitch!
Why ya throwin' me
under the bus?
I am gonna go buy a bus, and
literally throw you under it,
and then drive it back
and forth on your face!
See?
Spoken like a true killer!
Oh, like you're one to talk!
I got three men in the morgue!
(Chuckling)
Again, that was Poovey.
- What?
- Goddammit! I mean...
(Poovey:) Well, some
people need to get shot!
- Case in point!
- Rrgh?
(Explosion, startled reactions
to the noise)
(Panting)
Whoo! Hey, gang!
(Chuckling)
What's happening?
(Reactions to Dutch's being
here) Are you kidding me?
How are you here?
Commandeered a vehicle.
I mean how are you still alive?
I dunno,
I guess just clean livin'!
A-and how did you know
we were here?
I didn't! No, no, this is just
an almost
unbelievable coincidence.
No, I'm actually just here
for my blue stuff.
- Your what?
- Um...
So this is a little awkward.
But he's actually my patient.
(Confused reactions)
- I don't care what he is...
- He's a Goddamn robot!
- Actually...
- Nobody smashes up my club!
(Whistles)
(Groans)
Mr. Zerk!
Grrrrghh...
(Chuckling)
Okay, but we gotta
make this quick...
Rarrrghh!
(Groans)
(Startled/impressed reactions)
'Cause I'm about a quart low.
A quart low on what?
This! He has to have it to live!
Yeah, so come on, doc,
fill 'er up.
Will somebody...
Archer, shoot him!
- What? No, he's my life's work!
- Yeah.
Plus it doesn't do any good.
Look.
Owww!
(Archer and Dutch chuckle)
Dammit, Archer!
You did that on purpose!
- Come on.
- Poovey: Seriously?
- What're you doing?
- Gettin' the hell outta here.
- Wh...? No, you're not!
- Well, ya say that...
Come on, man, jam it in there
so I can start killing
these shitheads.
(Angry/fearful reactions)
What?
No, no, that's not what I...
- Jam it!
- No!
I won't have you become
just another
mindless killing machine!
How, could you possibly think
you're the boss of me?
I'll show ya who's boss!
(Groans)
How ya like that?
Meh.
Well, then how about this!
- Oof!
- (Dutch:) Woooooo!
Come on, come on, come on,
come on, come on...
I'm going as fast as I can!
- What about me?
- What about you?
Get me outta here
alive, all right?
And the ransom money,
- we'll call it even.
- Yeah.
That's what you told Archer.
And look what good it did him!
- Wait, wait, wait, wait...
- Rrrraagghhh!
Ungh! Oh, my God,
that really hurt.
(Chuckling) Look at you, whining
like your little buddy.
My what?
Yeah. The little limey
dope-fiend.
When I gut-shot him
and left him for dead.
What?
(Murmured reactions)
Aha! Probably
on Trexler's orders!
What, no! I didn't...
He didn't tell me to do it.
Ow.
I did it just to see
his light go out.
Goddamn.
Rrrraaaagh!
Ungh!
Plus he cut me off in traffic.
You...
Rrrnnnngh!
- I'm sorry, what was that?
- Grrnk!
I couldn't hear you over
the sound of your Adam's apple
grinding against your spine.
- Grrnk...
- No, still nothin'.
Hurry up!
Jesus, you people would stand
in a bread line
and ask for toast.
Wait, there's toast?
- What?
- Why would there be toast?
- Why wouldn't there be?
- (Krieger:) Stop it!
Stop it! Don't you see?
You're better than this!
You don't have to be a killer!
You can use your power
for the good of all mankind!
Yeah, I could.
But I was a murderer before you
turned me into a freak,
so, I don't know why you thought
- this was gonna have a happy ending.
- But...
Now go make me some blue stuff!
Ngh!
Is... is that your final answer?
(Gagging) Not if I have
to come over there.
(Sighs) Well, I'm very
sorry to hear that.
Aktion!
(Dogs barking and growling)
- Oh, God!
- What is that?
What-what is that?
Sweet Mother of God!
(Panicked reactions)
Wait, what is this?
(Screams)
(Dogs snarling)
Rrnk! Goddamn... rrnk!
(Dogs snarling and gnashing)
Ugh. Now I don't even know
if I want toast.
Aaghhh! No, no, no!
Wait, wait, wait! Stop it! No!
(Chuckling) Holy shit. Glad
I don't have a flashback for that.
Down! Down! Down! Goddammit, do
these muttz even speak engl...
God!
Jesus Christ!
(Sniffs)
Achtung! Hunden! Aus! Aus!
- Krieger?
- I don't... hunden! Aus!
- Oh, for the...
- Rrrrgh!
(Startled yips)
(Low menacing growls)
(Tiny whispered
terrified reactions)
Why on earth would you do that?
They were ruining toast!
(Low menacing growls)
Somebody do something.
(Weary sigh) Well, I already
threw a chair, so...
Then you go do something!
(Startled yelp)
Archer, shoot them!
No! They're all I have left!
(Cat meows)
You don't count!
Rrrrghh!
(Barking and growling)
Rrrrrrghh!
Aus! Aus!
Rrrghh! Grrghh!
(Snarling and gnashing)
(Assorted reactions
to the fight)
(Chuckling) Man, I don't
know who to root against.
They saved your life!
Still though.
(Horrified reactions)
Nooooo!
Rrrghh! Grrghh!
(Dog snarling and gnashing)
(Horrified reactions)
Rrgh.
(A wail, followed by sobbing)
(Crying)
You, you saved my life!
Rrgh...
And was it...
Was it because you love me?
Rrrgh.
Oh, my God.
That is... without a doubt,
the saddest thing
I have ever heard.
Rgh?
I mean, in what kind
of crazy dream-world
could we ever possibly
be together?
(Archer chuckling)
Jesus Christ.
- Should've shot her when I had the chance.
- Okay, well,
everything seems under control
here, so we'll just, um...
Uh, where do you think
you're going?
- Yeah. With my money!
- With my money!
Well, thanks a lot, T-man!
- What?
- Drop the bag.
What did you call her?
- T-man...
- Oh, hey, uh...
- But-But it's not what you think...
- Hey!
- It-It means Treasury Agent...
Oh. Although right about now I'm
guessing she wishes it didn't.
- Son of a...
- Treasury agent?
- Look...
- No, you look!
(Tense/wary reactions)
Hey, be careful, it's got a...
- Zip it!
- I...
- I can explain!
- Yes.
Please explain
what you've been doing
in my bar for the past year.
Because either you were
moonlighting as a singer
just to make ends meet
on a government salary,
or you were working undercover
to bring me down!
Or both!
Dun-dun-dun!
- Not helping!
- But if I were undercover,
obviously my agency would
be in the know,
and so if anything
happened to me, you'd...
(gunshot)
(Groans)
Lana! What the shit, Mother?
I, I didn't mean to! This damn
thing's got a hair trigger!
That's what I was trying
to tell you! When?
Before!
Hair trigger my ass, gimme that!
(Gunshot)
Oh, shit!
(Groans)
Lana!
Man, that is a hair trigger.
Goddammit, Poovey!
How was that my fault?
- La-Lana!
- Archer?
Shhh. You're gonna be okay.
Somebody call an ambulance!
Ugh. I already threw a chair.
Archer...
I'm sorry.
Why-why-why are you sorry?
I got blood on you.
Well, I blew a load
on your dress, so...
(gunshot) Ungh! Poovey!
I'm sorry! I...
(Gunshot)
(Startled/annoyed reactions)
Poovey!
Goddammit! I...
(Gunshot)
- Drop the Goddamn gun!
- Okay! (Gunshot)
(Angry reactions)
(Long, weary sigh)
(Scared whisper)
Is she...
Yes! (Big exhale) Whew!
- What?
- What? I was asking if she's okay.
(Irritated reactions)
No, Poovey, she is the exact
opposite of okay! She's dead!
Because she got shot seven times
and nobody could possibly
survive that!
Not even in a parallel universe!
What the hell
are you looking at?
No, just...
Okay, so she's dead.
Yes! She's dead!
Forever and ever!
On infinite (Bleep) Earths!
_(Speaks German)
Shut up!
And gimme that!
- Poovey, I'm giving you half.
- Of the money?
- Wait a minute!
- Are you nuts?
But you have to promise to set
those Chinese ladies
up in business.
Oh, my God,
I've got so many ideas!
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
who says you get to decide
who gets the money?
John Moses Browning.
Well, news flash,
mister tough and smart guy,
you're out of ammo!
Wh... get him!
Duh-huh.
(Weary sigh)
Goddammit.
What?
What is it?
There's no money.
Just these weird German nudie
mags about sports and...
Implied incest.
(Cecil:)
There's no incest!
They're all just
really happy to be together,
- and outside, and...
- (Trinette:) Naked.
Well, and healthy. As a family.
Whatever.
Now is not the time.
Oh, right.
Sorry, father. Please continue.
(Clears throat)
And do you, Cecil,
take Trinette to be your
lawfully wedded wife?
Mmmmmm...
Ow! I do!
(Weary sigh)
So, I guess I'll see you around.
And so that's pretty much that,
I guess. Vengeance-wise.
And I, I don't know
if you feel avenged,
or... if that even matters to you.
Tell you what I do know,
is robot dogs? Jesus Christ.
And I know the case took a long
time, but like you always said,
I have a tendency to get
sidetracked.
Which, honestly,
was kinda shitty of you.
And the smart thing would've
been to read your envelope
full of clues and then start
rampaging, but... holy shit,
I wonder if that was your will.
Although I can't imagine
you having anything
that I would possibly want.
I mean, I'll swing
by your apartment
and take a look
around, but uh...
What else, what else?
Oh, I brought you some heroin.
Hopefully some kids won't
walk by and eat it.
Oh, and also, uh, a rock.
I didn't know
if you were Jewish.
We never talked about that.
I guess mainly because you were
so weirdly private.
But even so, Woodhouse.
Oh, I'm gonna miss
the shit outta you.
(Deep sigh)
All right, I'll see ya.
I dunno, next week, or...
Uh, you know what,
let's play it by ear.
What the...
Hello?
Hey, where the hell
are you guys?
Hello? Hello?
Wait, what's this?
(Low mumbling)
(Explosive sob)
♪♪
Synchronized by srjanapala
Made in Georgia.