This is it, dudes:
my favourite place in Gravity Falls
Everything I know I learned right here
A frog told me how to cross a street
When my house was haunted,
I learned how to eat ghosts
And this thing taught me how to dance
I've been jigging for 7 days straight!
Soos?..
Let him have this
Congratulations!
You win!
Oh! Watch out!
Ooh, cutscene
Dr. Karate, you killed my father
Dr. Karate, you killed my father again!
You take that baaack!
Fight!
Yeah yeah yeah! Go go!
Our winner Rumble McSkirmish
Winners don't lose!
What? You cheated
You'll take that baaack!
Round 2
I'm gonna punch them rough
Fight!
Let's gang up on them
Wendy! What's up babe?
Just putting up some flyers for my band
I'm leading guitar. No biggie
Are you wearing mascara?
Um, it's eye-paint for men
Robbie, Dipper was just showing me this great game
Ah, yeah, sweet, sweet
How's about you sit this one out, kid champ?
But... We just started this round
Hey, relax, man
I'm just trying to spend a little time
with my girlfriend, all right?
It'll just be one round
Round 3. Fight!
I'm going camping tomorrow with my dad,
so I won't be around
Ah, cool, cool. Watch out!
King me!
It's not fair!
She doesn't even know what we're playing!
Go fish?
Dude. I think I'm picking up
a radio station inside my head
Try blinking to see if you can change the channel
We-endy-y!..
Sounds like Robbie
Robbie?
Is he that jerky twerp I see making
goo-goo eyes at Wendy all the time?
He called me big dude once. I mean,
I am a big dude, but it kinda hurt
Should I sick Waddles on him again?
Easy, tiger!
I'll handle it
O-o-oh!
Ha-ha, conflict
Wendy, Wendy-Wendy, Wendy!
Come on out, girl! Come on down!
You realize she's not here, right?
Pssh. Yes.
What?
She's out camping with her family today
Maybe if you listened to her for once, you'd know that
What was that?
I just said she's not here
No-no-no. You wanna get into it, huh?
Who wants get into it, kid?
You think I don't know what's been going on, huh?
It's obvious, you've gotta thing for my girlfriend,
Don't you? Don't you?
What? No! Come on, man!
Yeah. I'm sure she's just dying to ask out 12 year old kid
who wears the exact same shorts every day
Hey, here's an idea.
Why don't I call her right now and see
if she wants to go out on a date with you
Hey! Look! Don't... You don't have to!
Don't, please, man!..
What are you gonna do, huh?
What? What? (Hello?)
My phone!
I'll buy you a new one
Oh no. You're not getting off that easy!
Hey, I know a fight when I see one
Stay right there!
You, me, Circle Park, 3 o'clock
We finish this!
Oh, he's gone
I was just gonna call the boys over to place a few bets
The smart money's on skinny jeans
What was I thinking? I can't fight!
I've never been in a fight before
Look at these noodle arms!
Just bonk him over the head
It's nature's snooze button
Boys!
Why can't you learn to hate each other in secret?
Like girls do
Sure, listen to your sister
Maybe you can share dresses too
Ha-ha-ha Boom!
Maybe he'll just forget about it?
Maybe it'll all blow over
I don't know Dipper. Teenagers are dangerous
Those hormones turn them into killing machines
Really?
Oh yeah dude. My cousin Reggie got in a fight with teen once
The guy broke like...
All his arms... All his legs...
I think he killed him or something, I don't know
Me and Reggie were just talking about it
I can't stay here. What if Robbie comes back?
I gotta hide!
Look kid. You've got yourself a choice here
You could either go face him like a man
or you can hide indoors, like a wimp
What will it be?
Wimp it is
Come on, Soos. Robbie is twice my size!
I mean, what would getting myself killed accomplish?
I just need to hide here until 3 o'clock passes
This day will never end
Relax, Dipper. Just try not to think about Robbie
Girl, why you ackin' so cray-cray?
"Why you ackin' so cray-cray" will be back in a moment
Poor Dipper
Hiding from Robbie, unable to face his fears
Fears are for chumps. That's why I don't have any
You want me to go get a ladder?
— We don't have one
— What?
You know, study shows that keeping a ladder inside the house
is more dangerous than a loaded gun
That's why I own ten guns:
in case some maniac tries to sneak in a ladder
Grunkle Stan! Why you ackin' so cray-cray?
You're the one who's ackin' cray-cray!
I gotta go now
Why would Grunkle Stan be so weirded out by ladders?
Of course!
I think he has a secret fear of heights!
We'll have to test him to be sure
Or we could leave well enough alone
Na-a-ah!
I wonder what it's gonna be like
to go inside a video game for real
I should have thought of this years ago!
Stupid Robbie, such a jerk
Round 4. Fight!
K.O.
Continue?
A winner never runs away from a fight!
That's easy for you to say
You have more than one life!
I wish one of these guys could fight Robbie for me
"To unleash ultimate power?"
I do like things that are ultimate
Back, back, hold, forward, back, forward,
down, hold, quarter, circle forward, triple punch!
I guess it didn't work
Uh... Soos?
Select your character!
Uh... Rumble McSkirmish?
You're real?
High five!
Ow! Your pixels are really sharp!
Greetings child boy!
I'm Rumble McSkirmish from a USA!
Punch Kick Punch Kick!
Ow! Cool!
Change machine! Change me into a powerful wolf!
With Rumble around Robbie will be so scared
I won't even need to fight him
I've got the world's greatest fighter to be my bodyguard!
I need power-ups!
This is so amazing! I've got to show Soos!
Soos?
Help! I'm trapped in a game!
It was cool in theory but in practice it was really boring
It's not just a game anymore
Alright Waddles. It's time to begin
Operation Get Stan Over His Fear Of Heights!
I came up with that name
Happy Great Uncle's Day!
There's a Great Uncle's Day?
Of course it's not a day I've made up
High heels! You shouldn't have
Seriously. What... What is this?
What's wrong?
Are you saying these heels are too high?
Do they make you uncomfortable?
— Maybe
— Admit it! Admit you have a fear of heights!
What? That's why you bought me these?
You should be ashamed of youself!
And on Great Uncle's Day no less!
But no, I don't have a fear of heights
We now return to world's most terrifying skydiving!
Ah! Ah! Ah! Turn if off!
So I have a fear of heights
Is that really so cray-cray?
We don't have any traditional power-ups
Turkey legs, pizza boxes or golden rings
How about half a taco?
Place it on the floor
I wish I could do that!
Now I must defeat the world's greatest fight fighters!
Take me to the Soviet Union!
That's gonna be tough. For a number of reasons
But I do know a fighter here in Gravity Falls
Maximum power?
His name is Robbie V. and he's kinda my archenemy
Did he kill your father?
Well, he's dating the girl I like
and he posts a really annoying amount of status updates
And then he killed your father!
Uh, sure
Anyway, I was hoping you could scare him off for me,
so I don't have to fight the guy?
Ha-ha-ha! Your question makes my shoulders bounce!
Fireball! Uppercut! Downercut! Bowl of punch!
So you'll protect me from Robbie?
Challenge accepted! Press Start!
Oh-oh. I think I hear my uncle
Stay perfectly still
I said stay still
This is as still as I can stay
How I'm gonna get Grunkle Stan over his fear of heights?
Hey Mable. Have you met Rumble yet?
He's my new bodyguard
The child gave me a taco!
Wow! He's got a crazy voice!
Here, say these words
Effervescent!
Applefritter!
Riboflavin!
Mabel, he's not a toy, he's a fighting machine
I'm gonna get him to defend me from Robbie
Isn't that kinda like cheating?
I guess so
Well, I'll see you after the fight
Poop! Poppenbuts!
Tell me my opponent's special moves
Don't worry. As soon as he sees you,
he's gonna wet his pants
His wet pants will be no match for this!
Woah! Where did that come from?
I punched an oil drum!
Trust me, you won't need that. Just give him a good scare
Yes!
With this!
This street has really dangerous litter
Hey Grunkle Stan!
How would you like to go take a walk
nowhere in particular while wearing a blindfold?
Huh! Beats just sitting around being old
Wait a minute!
You're not planning on taking me
somewhere super high up, are you?
Grunkle Stan! I would never!
Scout's honour!
All right. Let's go
Hee-hee-hee
Well-well-well, look who decided to show up
I thought you chickened out
You ready to settle this like men?
Look dude, I don't think you wanna fight me
Let's just call this thing off before someone gets hurt
You're scared, huh? Is that it?
Ok dude. You asked for it
Who's your friend? And why is he blurry?
This happens to be the greatest warrior that ever lived
Yeah, right. Hey eyepatch, what have the kid promised you
more tate for your forearms?
How can you laugh when you killed this boy's father?!
Wait, what?
I'm giving you one last chance: back down,
or this guy is gonna go nuts
How about you back down, kid!
You asked for it. Rumble, go!
What the?..
Wha... What is happening?
I didn't want to do this, man, but you gave me no choice
Maybe now you won't mess with me
Woah! Rumble, you can stop! I think Robbie's had enough!
Rumble Throw!
Stop! I said stop!
What the? That guy is crazy!
Fireball!
What the heck was that?
You're only supposed to scare him, you almost killed him!
I will not rest until the man who dishonoured you
is DESTROYED!
Punch!
This isn't good
Something told me this would be his first stop
Chill out man!
Please, Rumble, you gotta stop!
Rumble, wait!
Punch-punch-punch!
You don't have to do this
At least pace yourself
You might get a cramp
I love you dad!
Oh! My car!
We'll just buy another one
I love being rich
All you can hit!
Hi dude!
Soos! Where have you been?
Long story, man.
Dude, did you see that video game guy
destroying everything in sight?
That's crazy!
Yeah, I kinda sorta brought him to life to be my bodyguard
But now I have to stop him before he kills Robbie!
You need an amiable sidekick with a pickup truck?
You know I do!
Take off your blindfold NOW!
Yeah, that's pretty much what I was expecting
You're doing better than I thought!
Now look over the handrail
Nope
Hey, do you smell anger and hormones?
Finally, I'm safe
Hey, Robbie, get your own water tower!
Shh, keep it down, he'll find us!
Challenger sighted!
On to save the day, dude
You can hide, but you cannot hide!
Rumble, this has to stop, please, listen to me!
Kick!
What was that?
Oh boy
We're safe, right?
Of course not! This thing is on stills!
High, high up!
Punch!
Finish him!
No no no! Don't! Don't finish me!
Rumble!
Rumble, I have something to tell you
Robbie...
Robbie didn't kill my father
Then who did?
What?
No one did, I lied to you
Then you're actually a...
bad guy!
I guess I kinda am...
My entire journey —
A lie. My honour has been insulted
Sensei warned me not to join the path of evil
The boy has led me astray from my teachings
If Robbie V. is not the last stage,
then it must be...
YOOOUUUUUUUUUUU!
Dude!
Don't fight him, man
That guy's got like the black belt
wrapped around his black belt
You could get killed
I have to
I started all this, and I've got to at least try to stop it
You're sure you wouldn't rather hide like a wimp?
Fight like a man it is
Ready!
Fight!
Fireball and lightning ball through
Fire!
Ha ha ha! You fight like a girl!
Who was also a baby!
Oh no
That was worth a shot
No. I have no looking up
...animation!
What should I do? Roll him up and put him on my wall?
Dude! We should rock paper scissors for him
FIST
FIST PUNCH
FIST PUNCH RAIN!!!
Never underestimate that I have punches!
SUPER
SUPER POWER
SUPER POWER NINJA
SUPER POWER NINJA TURBO
SUPER POWER NINJA TURBO NEO
SUPER POWER NINJA TURBO NEO ULTRA
SUPER POWER NINJA TURBO NEO ULTRA HYPER
MEGA
MEGA MULTI
SUPER POWER NINJA TURBO NEO ULTRA HYPER
MEGA MULTI ALPHA
MEGA MULTI ALPHA META
SUPER POWER NINJA TURBO NEO ULTRA HYPER
MEGA MULTI ALPHA META EXTRA
MEGA MULTI ALPHA META EXTRA UBER
SUPER POWER NINJA TURBO NEO ULTRA HYPER
MEGA MULTI ALPHA META EXTRA UBER PREFIX
COMBO!!!
You sir truly are the champion of champions
Rumble wins!
Winners don't lose!
I wouldn't be too sure about that, man
Game Over!
What? No! No!
Noooooooo!
Game over, old friend
Ha-ha, nice one, dude
I'm sorry, Grunkle Stan
I thought this would help but I was wrong
So wrong!
I... I survived!
I survived and I feel great!
Wait. Let me do a cocky dance just to be sure
Ha-ha! Deal with it, world!
Stan Pines is cured of his fear of heights!
— You're coming kid?
— Uh-huh
What's the matter? You've got a fear of heights now?
Oh-oh
What? Who was that guy?
Why is it that whenever you're around,
there's always ghosts and monsters and whatever?!
I don't know, man
That guy almost broke my neck.
You know how mad I am right now?
So I guess you and I have to fight now, huh
Go ahead, man. Do your worst.
I just wanna get this over with
Oh man, I'm so gonna enjoy this
— Aren't you gonna run?
— Nope
Are you sure?
Pfft. It's not ever worth it
Playing lead guitar, so I'm gonna save my hands
Hey guys, I heard some crazy screaming out here
— Wendy?!
— Wendy?! You're back!
Yeah, man. Oh. What the heck happened here?
Freak tornado or something?
Uhh... Well...
And why are your faces all jacked up?
You guys weren't fighting each other, were you?
I hate it when guys fight
No, fighting? No, why would we? Never!
We actually fell down trying to stop
two other guys from fighting each other
Cool. Really makes me happy to see my two boys hanging out
I've got some unpacking to do
I'll text you guys later
Did you hear that? She called my one of her two boys!
She was looking at me though
Look, Robbie. If we stay at each other's
throats, we'll both lose Wendy
We need to make a cold war pact
Ok. What's that?
We need to learn to just hate each other in silence
You mean, like...
What girls do?
Yeah, exactly. What girls do
So then I told Thompson:
"Hey! Save some for the rest of us!"
Good one, Wendy!
Oh, man. Just a second
So as I was saying
Yeah, I know, you're the best!
[Subtitles by Ilya Zverev, for addic7ed.com]
I'm Dipper. I have shorts and determination!
It's-a me, a-Mabel!
I'm slower, but I jump higher!
Pick me or whatever
Yum-yum-yum-nom-nom-yum-yum
Alas, 'twas not but a dream
Om-nom-nom-nom
Eating my friends
Om-nom