( siren wailing )
( panting )
Halt!
I've got to hand it
to this perp.
No one's broken out
of the Infinetentiary before.
He's either the bravest
time-convict I've ever seen
or the dumbest.
Ow! Ohh!
My time-knee!
Oh, time-dang it!
Definitely the dumbest.
Freeze!
You're surrounded
by the Time Paradox Avoidance
Enforcement Squadron.
Anything you say
can and already has been used
against you in future court.
This is it, Blendin.
End of the timeline.
Any last words?
Uh-uh-uh-uh-uh...
I-I-I-I...
I invoke Globnar!
Globnar!!!
( murmuring )
Very well, speak the name
and century of those accused.
The two kids
that ruined my life,
Dipper and Mabel Pines,
21st century.
So be it.
May Time Baby
have mercy on their souls.
Candy! Candy!
Candy! Candy.
Candy--
No!
It's trapped!
Everything
is terrible forever!
Psst.
Hey, dudes.
You want to know a trick?
Boppity-boop-womp!
This just in.
Weather stations are calling
for a candy blizzard!
Forget taking
off the wrappers.
I'm eating these now!
Soos, you are
the greatest human ever to live.
( coughing )
That was a mistake!
Hey, no sweat, dude.
I'd do anything
for the Pines family.
STAN: Soos!
I need to scratch myself
in two places at once.
And I mean  anything.
Coming, Mr. Pines!
Whoa, better make sure
he gets his wallet back.
Wait, I've never seen
Soos's wallet before.
Don't you want to learn
some Soos secrets?
I don't know if we should be--
Whoa!
Soos has a membership
to laser tag?
I didn't know they let
grown-ups in there.
And look,
emergency salami.
Soos, my respect
for you has grown.
Jesus Esperaminguo Ramirez,
organ donor,
birthday: July 13th.
Wait a minute.
That's today.
Whoa.
That's weird.
I wonder
why he didn't tell anyone.
Uh, duh.
It's probably because
he wants someone
to throw him
a surprise party.
I've been waiting for
a surprise party my whole life.
Surprise!
Too little, too late, Chiu.
Ohh.
More exclamation points!
More, I say!
Wow, you guys
thought of everything.
Grenda, twins are born
birthday experts.
We've shared
every birthday together
so we know
how to make them perfect.
( noisemakers toot )
Hey, places, everyone.
I hear footsteps.
GRENDA: Everyone, be quiet!
All right, you promised
a giant hummingbird,
so I'm expecting to see
a giant hummingbird.
CANDY: Three, two, one...
Huh?
ALL: Surprise!
Happy birthday,
you king on earth.
We got everything you love.
Cake-flavored pizza.
Pizza-flavored cake.
And one more treat.
Razzle dazzle, friends.
It's me, the Razz Dazzler.
This is what
my life has become.
I...I...
Quick,
everyone pose
for the Birthday Smiles
Memory Album.
♪ Razzly-dazzly-doo
Soos, what's wrong?
It's, uh, it's nothing.
I, uh...
I gotta go fix a pipe
or something.
Whoa,
did you guys see Soos?
What happened to--
Oh, no.
Oh, no, no, no.
Okay, you guys didn't know,
so it's not your fault,
but Soos hates
his birthday.
BOTH: What?
It's a total mystery.
I guess he's been like this
since he was a kid.
Some weird personal biz.
There's gotta be
something we can do.
We've tried everything.
I even petitioned
the government
to have this day removed
from calendars.
Now I'm not allowed
on airplanes.
( sighs )
I don't know, guys,
maybe we should just
leave him alone, you know?
No one should be alone
on their birthday.
There's got to be a way
to cheer him up.
We just need to try harder.
You're right,
Dipper!
It's time for us
to bring out the big guns.
All right, guys,
blindfold me once,
shame on you,
blindfold me twice--
Wait a minute.
( sniffs )
Hot dog smell?
Sticky floors?
Future sounds?
Laser tag?
I love laser tag.
We definitely didn't rifle
through your wallet.
( nervous chuckle )
Welcome to the year 8,000.
Society?
Collapsed.
Fog machines?
Everywhere.
Are these walls just mattresses
spray-painted purple?
I think this place
used to be a mattress store.
I don't know, guys,
I'm not sure
I'm up for this today.
As soon as you start
playing with us,
you're gonna have
a great time.
We promise,
no matter what happens
we won't leave your side.
Well, I guess,
I could give it a shot.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Prepare for laser battle
in three, two...
( klaxon blares )
( all cheering )
Uh-oh.
Better tie down
these cowboys.
Whoa! This is even cooler
than I imagined.
Look how real
these laser guys are.
( grunts )
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Kick deflected.
Thank you for buying digicod,
the smart codpiece.
Wait, what?
( gasps )
Oh, no.
Soos!
Mabel? Dipper?
Dudes?
Soos!
Nice try, but that's
solid timetanium, kid.
There's only one way
out of here.
MAN: Through me!
Oh, uh, sorry.
Come on.
Through me!
if I'd just gotten it right
the very first chance,
but it still is effective.
( both gasp )
The time traveler guy!
What did you say
your name was again?
Blendo?
Blondin?
BlarBlar.
There it is.
It's Blendin!
Blendin Blenjamin Blendin.
How could you not know my name
after you ruined my life?!
Initiate flashback!
It was after you
stole my time device
to win your stupid pig.
I was cast out of
the time anomaly removal crew--
my whole life's purpose.
And then I was given
ten squared life sentences
in time prison.
I've spent every day since then
planning my vengeance.
And now finally,
it has come!
Look, we're sorry
about all that,
but we're in the middle
of something
really important
right now.
It's our friend's
birthday today,
and we promised
we wouldn't leave his side.
What?! You think some dumb
birthday matters right now?
Do you know where you are?
Welcome to Globnar!
MABEL:
Is this a reality show?
Are we in Japan?
BLENDIN:
It's gladiatorial time combat!
( grunts )
BLENDIN: The winner gets
a precious time wish
and then decides
the loser's fate.
N-n-no!
Please!
( screaming )
And the two of you
are officially challenged.
Dundgren!
Get me my war paint.
Dipper, we need a way
out of here.
But how?
I have an idea.
Hang in there, Soos,
we're coming for you.
Dipper?
Mabel?
Requesting back-up.
Ah! Ah!
Oh! Ah!
Oh, no.
( chuckles )
Laser Robbie.
Dudes?
( bell rings )
( Mabel clearing throat )
Oh, my stars.
Could it be my little, um...
Lolphy!
Your great-great-great-great-
great-great-great grandmother
from the past times.
Gam-Gam?
Yeah, neon green is good.
This is a good color for me.
It's fierce--
Huh?
What?
No!
You can't let them escape!
Stop there!
Gam-Gam, how could you?
I ain't no one's Gam-Gam,
sucka!
You just got time tricked!
No!
Hurry!
Back to Soos' birthday.
Okay.
I think I've got it.
( screaming )
Uhh. Are we back?
Oh, no! Look!
Mable, the Laser place
is a mattress store.
We went too far
in the past.
Time travel.
Man, why you gotta be
so complicated?
Huh?!
Looks like they overshot
their destination by 10 years.
I don't see them.
You better find those kids!
You'll get your justice,
Blendin.
I'm gonna keep stammering
until you find them.
I-I-I-I...
I hate that guy.
Let's move.
Yeah!
Okay, we just got
to go forward 10 years.
We can be back before Soos
even realizes we were gone.
Oh, no!
The timey thing.
It's busted.
Can you fix it?
Maybe.
I'll need some tools.
And I think I know
where to get some.
Let's try to lay low.
We don't want to change
the future.
Or  cause  the future.
I forget how this works
exactly.
Wow, 10 years in the past.
Everything is samey
but also differenty.
♪ Doppity-doppity-doo
Yeah!
Look out Broadway,
here I come.
This dream goes nowhere,
Toby!
Aww, marbles.
Whoa.
Oops. Sorry.
( whispering )
My friend thinks you're cute.
Oh, my gosh.
Tambry, shut up.
Ow! Hey!
( chuckles )
Thank you.
I mean you're super young,
so this is weird.
Now you know
how  she  feels, creep.
( chuckles )
Yeah, I... Huh.
Wow.
STAN: Schlep right up,
ladies and gentlemen,
to see my latest attraction.
All right, the coast is clear.
Now is our chance.
Ha!
Bingo!
All right, let's see.
BOY: Aw, come on, candy.
Fall. Fall.
Allow me.
You just need to know
a guy on the inside.
Bippity-boop-womp!
Jackpot!
( gasps )
Thanks, dawg.
You must be
some kind of genius
All right, I think
I've got this thing working
Dipper, Dipper, look.
No way.
Mi precioso,
you keep wandering off.
You don't want to be
late for your big day.
Sorry, Abuelita.
Big day?
This could be
the birthday
where that personal biz
went down.
We could finally find out
why Soos hates his birthday.
All right,
but let's be quick.
KID: I want a piece
of birthday cake!
( kids giggling )
Who's a handsome birthday boy?
(sing-song) It's you!
( giggles ) Soos, you are
such a ladies' man.
They're my cousins,
Grandma. Gross.
I got you a race car cake.
Man, I don't know
why Soos hates his birthdays.
This looks great.
Sorry, dude,
but could you move seats?
That's the seat of honor.
Uh, who's it for?
Oh. Heh.
It's for my dad, actually.
I haven't seen him in, like,
8 years, but he's coming today.
( door bell rings )
That must be him!
(inhales, exhales)
All right, Soos,
today's the big day.
Be cool.
Postcard for...
Soos.
( Soos reading aloud )
"See you next year for sure.
Dad."
Hey, don't sweat it, cuz.
You'll see him next year.
Ha. Yeah, next year.
I'm gonna go lay down.
You party without me,
dudes.
Wait, what about
your presents?
TOY:  Yay-uh.
So that's why
Soos hates his birthday.
It's the day he realized
his dad wasn't coming back.
So how much partying
can fix that?
( giggles )
Dorks.
Young Robbie.
Ay, Soos' father
is a dead-beat.
( speaking Spanish )
( clears throat )
Soos, I made you cookies
shaped like dinosaurs.
I don't want cookies.
I want to see Dad again.
And he wants to see you.
He's just...busy.
Busy in New Orleans?
Ay. Yes.
Trust me,
you will feel better one day.
Ohh, this is awful.
We promised Soos
a happy birthday,
but how can we
give him that now?
This goes beyond anything
we know how to fix.
BLENDIN: This way!
Mabel, hide!
They've got to be
around here somewhere.
I think I heard them!
( bird chirping )
Freeze!
( crying )
Trace their chrono-signatures.
Man, the sooner I defeat
those kids in Globnar,
the sooner
I can win my time wish.
Tell you what I'd do
if I had a time wish.
Retire early,
spend more time with the kids.
Nyah-nyah-nyah-nyah
with the kids?!
Don't you know a time wish
can literally do anything?
Any impossible problem solved,
just like that.
I mean,
imagine the possibilities.
Wait, Mabel, that's it,
the time wish.
If we defeat Blendin
in that space battle--
Then we can wish
that Soos' dad
came to his 12th birthday.
And Soos' birthdays
would be fixed forever--
But do you really think
we can win Globnar?
It's the only chance we have.
Besides, it's for Soos.
He would do the same for us.
Here we are, Blendin.
We surrender.
It's them!
Freeze!
They might have powder muskets
or slap bracelets.
Look, guys,
no tricks this time.
We're ready to challenge you,
okay?
Yes!
Let the Globnar begin.
Prepare for Globnar!!!
( silence )
Hey, turns out
I can mute him.
Man, I wish
we'd known that earlier.
Initializing.
( crowd cheering )
Globnar! Globnar!
Silence!
Whoo!
Oh, yeah!
That is one big baby.
Welcome, Globnar tributes.
I have
a very important nap to get to,
so let's make this quick.
You each have a chance
to settle your time-feud
through gladiatorial combat.
ROBOT: You will have
until time baby finishes
drinking the cosmic sand
in this hourglass.
No!
Come on.
It's good for you.
Waah!
Get ready, kids.
When I get that time wish,
you'll wish you were never born.
Or rather,
you'll wish you  were  born,
because I'm gonna wish
you were never born!
Dream on!
There's two of us.
And  we have hair!
Oh--oh, yeah?
Well, I have training!
What do you think I did
in prison all that time?
Uh-oh.
Let the Globnar begin!
( crowd cheers )
( buzzer )
( roars )
( grunting )
Yeah!
( roaring )
Globnar!
Very good.
You have escaped
the Cyclocks.
Yes!
Blendin for the almost-win!
There is only one
final challenge for Globnar.
An ancient game,
thousands of years old,
chosen for its exemplification
of pure strategy.
The ancient art of laser tag!
The one who touches
the victory orb first will win.
Laser tag?
Seriously?
Oh, I know it doesn't seem
that challenging now,
but just wait until they
turn on that fog machine.
You'll be done for.
You just wait until you--
MACHINE: Hit.
Hit, hit, hit, hit.
Oh, man.
Mabel, grab the orb!
Got it.
It is finished!
( burps )
( cheering )
( buzzer )
No!
No! No!
Yes!
You have made victory
in Globnar.
Before I give you
your time wish,
tell us what fate
do you decide for the loser?
Oh, jeez.
Death!
Mabel.
Sorry.
Got carried away.
So Blendin did try
to wish us out of existence,
but it was kind of our fault
for ruining his life.
Yeah, and he's kind of too sad
to be a real bad guy.
Maybe if we treat him right
in the present,
he'll turn out better
in the future.
Okay, as long as you keep
an eye on him,
we'd like to set Blendin free
and restore his position
at the Time Anomaly
Correction Unit.
And give him pretty hair.
So be it.
What?
You'd do that for me?
I got my job back!
I feel like hugging somebody.
I can kill you
in eight different ways.
Yes, sir.
Now, children, what is it that
you want for your time wish?
Thank you,
but the wish isn't for us.
Not you?
But then who?
Who is worthy
to receive such power?
Dipper?
Mabel?
Ah, who am I kidding?
I'm not up for this.
Heads, I stay.
Tails, I go make myself
some dinosaur shaped cookies.
( laughter slows down )
Huh. That's unconventional.
BOTH: Soos!
Guys!
We're so sorry
we left you hanging, dude.
We got caught up
in this time travel junk.
And there was a time Cyclops.
And don't forget
about the
time race.
Time race.
But the point is, Soos,
we think we know
how to fix your birthday.
Whoa. Really?
Wait, you guys did
all of that for me?
And that's not all.
Behold your time wish,
the power to alter time,
paradox-free,
in any way you choose.
We think the only thing
that can make you happy
is meeting your dad.
But the choice is yours.
You mean, I can finally see
my dad by touching this thing?
And you guys battled
through time and space
just to get this for me?
What are you waiting for,
Soos?
All right.
Here goes nothing.
( gasps )
Wait, what?
What the...
Bam!
Fixed you up.
But, Soos, what about
meeting your dad?
Well, birthdays
are supposed to be spent
with the people
who care about you.
But you know what?
That dude didn't care about me
enough to visit me once,
let alone fight monsters through
time and space like you dudes.
I mean, you had
a gladiator fight
just to make me happy.
I've been being ridiculous
this whole time.
Whoever my dad was,
he could take a hike.
I know who my family is now,
and it's you dudes.
Thanks for giving me
the best birthday ever.
Are you kidding me?!
Do you have any idea
what you've just wasted?
Do you know how many
have died to get a time wish?
The wars
that were started?
I also wished for
the slice of infinite pizza.
Watch.
And it can do that for,
like, infinity.
( indistinct )
Phew!
That's a good time wish.
There's still 10 minutes
before laser tag closes.
You dudes want to play?
Yeah.
( giggling )
DIPPER & MABEL:
Happy birthday, Soos.
Whoa.
Thought I heard an explosion.
Whoa, what's this?
Mystery Shack?
That is it!
You are single-handedly
the worst handyman
I've ever seen.
Uh, hey, excuse me, sir.
Hey you, gumdrop,
think you can fix a golf cart?
Well, I don't know if I--
Boom, you're hired.
One size fits all.
Step right up
to the Mystery Shack, folks.
Step right up.