Gravity Falls  S01E19  Dreamscaperers
I'm gonna say b-five.
Miss!
I don't think you're playing this right.
Kids! Come quick!
I need you to laugh at this with me!
Who's cute as a button, and always your friend?
'Lil G-I-D to the E-O-N!
Wink!
Lil' Gideon.
Ugh, Gideon.
Remember when I wouldn't date him,
And he tried to destroy us?
He's always trying to trick me into losing the Mystery Shack!
One time, I caught him stealing my moisturizer.
And yet, our mutual hatred for him bonds us together.
Come on down to
'Lil Gideon's tent of telepathy.
Opening soon at this location.
Uh, should we be worried about that?
Please. The only way Gideon's taking over this shack
is by breaking in and stealing my deed.
You mean like right now?
Uh, thirty-eight?
Forty-one? Oh, heavens to Betsy!
Gideon!
Well, well, Stanford!
My arch nemesis.
We seem to have entered
a dangerous game of cat and mouse.
But the question remains,
Who is the cat, and who is the--
Soos, broom.
Oh, no, not the broom!
You mark my words, Stanford!
One day I'm gonna get that combination!
And once I steal that deed
You'll never see the Mystery Shack again!
Good luck, bucko!
Ha! The combo to this safe is in the one place
he'll never find it, my brain!
Your brain isn't as safe as you might think, Stanford Pines!
This is the last straw.
It's time to unlock the journal's greatest secret.
He put the "old" in old west.
They call him... Grandpa the Kid!
I'm tired during the day.
I can relate to this.
Grunkle Stan, why can't we watch a movie
that we'll all enjoy? Dream Boy High!
Where love is on your permanent record.
Boo!
You'll learn to like it.
Dudes! There's a bat in the kitchen!
It tried to touch me with its weird little bat fingers.
Don't worry, I got this under control.
Dipper, take care of it.
Yes!
What? Why can't Mabel do it?
'Cause life ain't fair.
Now go fight a bat so we can watch tv.
No way, Grunkle Stan.
You always make me do dumb chores.
I'm putting my foot down this time.
I said, do it, kid! Now!
Okay, I'll do it!
Stupid chores.
Remember, bats are more afraid of you than you are of them.
Maybe I'm thinking of ducklings.
Ducklings. Quack, quack.
Quack, quack, quack.
Swabbin' on disinfectant. Doo-do-doo.
Why does Grunkle Stan always pick on me?
Think about it, the more painful or difficult the chore is,
The more likely it is I'll have to do it.
Why doesn't he pick on you guys?
Dipper, Stan's personality is one of life's great mysteries.
Like whether or not it's possible to lick your own elbow.
- I bet you can't.
- I bet I can.
Lick it! Lick it!
Lick it!
Sometimes I feel like Stan hates me.
The sink's clogged!
Dipper, get in here and fix it!
You think that combination's safe in your mind, Stanford?
We'll see what my new minion has to say about that.
"Triangulum. Entangulum.
"Veneforis dominus ventium.
Veneforis venetisarium!"
Lick that elbow! Lick that elbow!
Like the infinite horizon, it eludes my grasp.
Is that who I think it is?
Oh! Oh! Gravity Falls, it is good to be back!
Name's Bill Cipher.
And I take it you're some kind
of living ventriloquist dummy?
I'm just kidding,
I know who you are, Gideon.
What-- what are you?
H-- how do you know my name?
Oh, I know lot of things.
Lots of things.
Hey, look what I can do.
Deer teeth, for you, kid!
You're insane!
Sure, I am! What's your point?
Listen to me, demon!
I have a job for you!
I need you to enter the mind of Stanford Pines
And steal the code to his safe!
Wait.
Stan Pines.
You know what, kid, you've convinced me.
I'm sold!
I'll help you with this, and in return,
You can help me with something I've been working on.
We'll work out the details later.
Deal.
Well, time to invade Stan's mind.
This should be fun!
Remember, reality is an illusion,
The universe is a hologram, buy gold!
Bye!
It worked!
No. Sorry.
What is going on in that guy's head?
Dipper!
We've gotta help Stan!
Wait, what?
This evil triangle guy
said he's gonna break into Stan's mind,
And steal the combination to his safe!
Also, we stopped for snacks on the way here.
Triangle guy?
I feel like I've seen something like this before in the journal.
"Beware Bill.
"The most powerful and dangerous creature
"I've ever encountered.
Whatever you do, never let him into your mind."
Grunkle Stan!
"It is possible to follow the demon
"Into a person's mind and prevent his chaos.
One must simply recite this incantation."
This is just great.
I spend all day cleaning sinks and fighting bats for Stan,
And now I have to save him from some crazy brain demon?
But if we don't do anything,
Gideon might steal the shack, or worse!
Fine.
Get ready, guys. We're about to journey
into the most horrifying, disturbing place
any of us have ever been.
Our uncle's mind.
You think I can take these burrito bites into Stan's brain?
Thumbs up, thumbs down?
You know what? I'm just gonna bring them.
Okay, guys.
In order to save our uncle,
we're gonna have to follow that dream demon into his mind.
I wonder what Stan's thinking about right now.
I love Soos like a son.
Soos! This is serious!
Sowee.
Let's do this!
"Fidentus omnium.
"Magis omentium.
"Magnesuim adharminum.
"Magnum opus.
"Habeas corpus.
"Inceptus Nolanus overratus.
"Magis tremensium. Magis tremensium.
Magis tremensium!"
Oh, wow! Whoa!
Oh, what the--
Whoa! This is Stan's mind?
Huh. Figured there would be a lot more hot old ladies.
Remember, everyone,
We've got to look out for the triangle guy.
Yeah, look out for the triangle guy!
It's him! It's the guy!
You leave our uncle's brain alone,
You isosceles monster!
Gotcha!
Wait. What?
Ah, Stan's family, we meet at last.
Question mark, shooting star, pine tree,
I had a hunch I might bump into you.
Mabel!
What do you want with our uncle's mind anyway?
Oh, just the code to the old man's safe!
Inside the shack is a maze of a thousand doors
representing your uncle's memories.
Behind one of them is a memory of him inputting the code.
I just need to find it
and Gideon will pay me handsomely!
Not if we stop you!
Ha! Fat chance!
I'm the master of the mind.
I even know what you're thinking right now.
That's impossible!
No one can guess what I'm thinking!
Whoa! Where are we, bro?
We must be in heaven, 'cause I just saw an angel.
I'm never letting go of your leg!
You're out of your league, kids.
Turn around now, before you see something you might regret.
Later, suckers!
We're going in.
Mabel, can we leave those guys out here?
Looking at them hurts my eyes.
No! They can help us!
Totally! Arm throne!
Dude, arm throne!
- Arm throne!
- Ah!
- Whoa!
- Neato!
- Radical!
- I also think it's radical!
No refunds! No refunds!
Whoa, look! All of Stan's memories.
Great, sure there's plenty of memories
of Stan bossing me around.
Can't wait to see more of that!
Come on, Dipper.
We've gotta find the code before Bill does.
Mabel is talking!
So rad!
Let's get searching!
Jorge, Rico,
You're the two best Colombian prison friends
a fella could make.
Nope.
Sir, would you like to buy a Stan Vac vacuum?
Stan Vac. It sucks more than anything.
Gotta work on that.
Nope.
Whoa! It's Stan on a date!
So, your, uh, your eye is weird.
Let's, let's talk about that.
This is going terrible.
I can't think of anything to say,
And she looks weird up close.
Think of a way out.
Non-specific excuse!
Yeesh!
Look, guys. Memories about me.
That doesn't seem like a good idea.
I just want to know what the old guy really thinks of me.
We already know how Stan feels about us,
He loves us! We're great.
Yeah, let's just keep moving.
More moving? Yes!
I love motion!
Okay, just a quick peek.
Dipper, my back itches, can you scratch it?
Dipper, clean the boiler!
No buts!
Now go chop that firewood already!
Dude, Stan, I been meaning to ask you.
Why are you so hard on Dipper all the time?
Look, Soos, I'm gonna let you in on something.
You wanna know what I really think?
The kid's a loser. He's weak.
He's an utter embarrassment.
I just want to get rid of him.
Hello, code to Stan's safe, where are you?
Opening and closing doors is fun.
I can do it also!
If only people knew the truth.
That hidden behind this vending machine,
- I secretly have a
- boring!
All right, guys,
I have a good feeling about this door.
Hey, mr. Tummy.
Hey, mr. Stan!
Are you hungry?
Yes.
- Eat your crackers!
- Ugh!
Sweet sally.
Oh, we've been searching forever.
What if the triangle guy finds the memory before we do?
If we wanna find Stan's memory, we gotta think like Stan.
He's always hiding stuff, right?
Yeah, like how he hides his arrest warrants
under that rug in the gift shop?
Soos, that's it! Look!
There ya go.
And now to input the code.
Thirteen, forty-four, and finally--
Dude, we found it! Yeah!
But what do we do now?
Jinx!
Um, um, let's just destroy the door
Before bill can find it.
Wait! Maybe I should do it!
My big fat arms are great at destroying stuff.
Oh, okay.
Hey, guys!
I just saw a memory of Stan
roller skating and wearing short-shorts!
Didn't look--didn't look half bad.
Hey, something weird is going on here.
Boy, you kids sure are gullible!
I knew you'd lead me straight to the code!
It's funny how dumb you are.
The combination to Stan's safe!
Boy, that was even easier than I thought.
Oh, yeah?
Well, you're a...
A stink-face!
Awesome comeback, Mabel!
Don't treat me like a child, Xyler.
Later, suckers!
Come on, we've got to save Stan!
What's the point?
Why should I save him, huh?
I work for stan day and night,
And all he does in return is say he wants to get rid of me.
Dipper, I'm sure that's not true.
I saw it with my own eyes in one of his memories, Mabel!
He's always picked on me and now I know why!
Stan hates me!
Dipper, it doesn't matter what you saw.
If we don't stop Bill, we'll lose the shack!
No, you know what? Not this time.
For once, this is one of Stan's problems I'm not gonna fix.
Fine! Come on, Soos.
We'll save Stan ourselves!
Dipper, you're a cool dude, but this isn't cool, dude.
Let's go, Xyler!
All right, Craz!
Those are our names!
- Yello?
- Bill!
Did you find the memory with the combination yet?
Relax, shortstack, I got it right here.
Perfect!
Now give it to me
And I'll fulfill my end of the bargain.
Finally! It's-- you got a pen there?
It's thirteen, forty-four--
Ah! No, no, wait! No!
None more bottomless than the bottomless pit.
Which, as you can see here, is bottomless.
Whoo! Whatever that was, it's gone forever.
Ha ha! Boom!
Mabel did it!
The shack is safe!
The deal's off!
Wait. No! Wait!
I'm switching to plan b!
You!
You can't even imagine what you just cost me!
Do you have any idea what I'm like
when I'm mad?
So I guess he gets really mad when he gets mad.
Eat nightmares!
How do I get out of this place?
Exit? Hello?
Ah, this again?
He's a loser. He's weak.
I just want to get rid of him.
Yeah, those are all things people said about me when I was a boy.
Huh?
It was terrible.
I was the biggest wimp on the playground.
So one summer my pop signs me up for boxing lessons.
And it was even worse than the schoolyard!
Left hook!
You know, at the time, I thought my pop was trying to torture me.
But wouldn't you know it?
The old man was doin' me a favor all along.
Give me that bag!
Help! My purse!
- Help!
- Left hook!
So you see?
That's why I'm hard on Dipper.
To toughen him up,
So when the world fights, he fights back.
Do you think it's actually working?
I, I did it!
Yes!
He's really comin' along.
When push comes to shove, I'm actually proud of him.
Just don't ever tell him that.
His head's big enough as it is.
That's true.
Whoa, kid, what are you doin' here?
Nice hole in your chest, by the way.
Let's fix that up.
W-- what the-- how did you do that?
Word to the wise, kid, we're in the mind.
You could do whatever you can imagine in here.
Well, how about that.
No! Make it stop!
Help! Someone, please!
Oh, my gosh, what am I doing?
I gotta stop Bill!
Huh. Fightin' back.
One nightmare, coming up!
Nightmare?
Hope he doesn't mean that British dog-man
I'm always dreaming about.
'Ello, 'ello, 'ello!
Who's crike for a shdig in the pudding?
Ah! It's everything I ever feared!
You!
Ahh! My cuteness!
What did you do to my cuteness--
You're next!
Cool, we're next!
My dream boys!
And now to finish you off, for once and for all!
No! No!
Dude, no!
Hey, Bill!
What!
Nice bowtie!
- Dipper!
- Dude!
Guys! I just learned that you can conjure
whatever you can conceive in Grunkle Stan's mindscape!
Huh?
Just think of cool fighting stuff and it'll happen!
Like this.
He's dead now.
What? Who told you that?
Don't listen to him!
We can do anything?
Like have kittens for fists?
Well, hello, friends!
Anything, huh?
Soos loves stomach beam stare!
Enough games!
Hamster ball shields, activate!
Activate!
Ah, my eye!
Rise, Xyler! Rise, Craz!
No! Synthesized music!
It hurts!
And now to imagine your worst nightmare!
A portal out of Stan's mind!
Out of Stan's mind!
Mabel! Everyone!
Together!
No, no, no!
Enough!
You know, I'm impressed with you guys.
You're a lot more clever than you look.
Especially the fat one.
He's talking about you.
So I'm gonna let you kids off the hook.
You might come in handy later.
But know this.
A darkness approaches,
A day will come in the future
when everything you care about will change.
Until then, I'll be watching you.
I'll be watching you.
He's gone, we did it!
Wha--
Stan must be waking up.
Will I ever see you guys again?
In your dreams.
Good one, bro. Good one.
We did it!
What? Did what?
What are you all doing here?
And why was I dreaming of
two brightly colored and radical young men?
Grunkle Stan! You're okay!
What is this, a hug?
Nope.
It's a choke hold.
Not bad, kid. Not bad.
I'm just glad Gideon didn't get into the safe.
I really love this old shack.
Group hug!
No?
I never know the right time!
Hey, do you guys feel a--
Oh, I'm sorry, Pines family, did I wake you?
But we defeated Bill.
Bill failed me!
So I switched to plan b.
Dynamite.
What? Bill?
Who-- wh-- what are you guys talking about?
Spoiler alert, Stanford. I've got the deed!
The mystery shack belongs to me!
So, get off my property!
Daddy?
Bring it around the front.
Don't worry, guys.
It's just part of the dream.
We're going to wake up any second now.
Right? Right?
Someone, pinch me, dude.