¶
>> ARCHER: Oh, come on, how long
are you guys gonna stay mad at
me?
>> CYRIL: What, for getting us
all arrested for smuggling
cocaine into Colombia?
>> RAY: Probably the rest
of our damn lives.
>> CYRIL: Well, shouldn't be
very long, since we're headed to
La Culebra, the most dangerous
prison in South America.
(chuckles)
>> ARCHER: Well, Cyril, when we
get there and I join the
toughest gang, don't hold your
breath for a bid.
>> RAY: A bid?
>> CYRIL: They're prison gangs,
not frats!
>> ARCHER: And don't call a
fraternity a frat!
>> COP: ¡Callate!
(Archer grunts, groans)
(cops laughing)
>> ARCHER: No, I'm fine.
Don't worry about me.
>> COP: And don't worry about
La Culebra, gringos.
You are not going there.
>> CYRIL: Oh, well, that's good.
Is that good?
It doesn't sound very good.
Why does that sound really,
really, really bad?
>> ARCHER (sighs): Because
they're gonna kill us.
>> CYRIL: What?!
(cops laughing)
>> COP: Unless you got maybe
$100,000 U.S. on you.
>> ARCHER: Well, not on me,
on me, but...
(cops guffawing)
>> CYRIL: Hey, but when we're
digging out own graves, they're
gonna get cocky, and then we
whang 'em with our shovels,
right?
>> ARCHER: Cyril, this isn't an
episode of B.J. and the Bear.
>> RAY: That was?
>> ARCHER: It's the jungle--
nobody digs graves; they just
kneel you down by a ditch and
put a bullet in your...
>> CYRIL: Cow!
>> ARCHER: Why would they shoot
your... cow!
(yelling, grunting, gasping)
(birds chirping)
>> ARCHER: God...
(crashing)
(birds chirping)
>> ARCHER: ...damn.
(Archer groaning, chuckling)
>> ARCHER: Well, now I'm almost
afraid to say any--
(Archer groans)
Eat a dick, jungle.
>> CYRIL: Easy, easy.
Careful!
>> ARCHER: Cyril, for the love
of Christ, man!
>> CYRIL: Sorry.
>> ARCHER: You have to shut up.
>> CYRIL: I am.
Starting now.
Starting... now.
>> ARCHER: Cyril...
>> CYRIL: Sorry. (gasps)
(animal growls in distance)
What was that?
>> ARCHER: Probably a jaguar
excited about being magnificent
and crepuscular.
But I need you to focus on me,
because if, by some miracle, I
get the keys...
(Cyril gasps)
...and then, by some other even
bigger miracle, get us out of
these cuffs...
(Cyril sneezes)
I am gonna beat the shit out of
you, Cyril!
>> RAY: I'm gonna beat the
shit of both of y'all.
>> CYRIL: Oh, my God, Ray!
>> ARCHER: You're alive?!
>> RAY: What, did y'all
think I was dead?
>> CYRIL: Well, I just assumed.
>> ARCHER: Yeah, I totally did.
>> RAY: And you didn't
even take a moment?!
>> ARCHER: I mean...
>> RAY: Oh, screw you guys!
>> ARCHER: W-Wait.
What is in your mouth?
>> GILLETTE (muffled): Nothing.
>> ARCHER: It's the keys!
>> CYRIL: He's eating the keys?
>> ARCHER: Ray, don't you eat
those keys!
>> RAY: I'm not eating the
goddamn keys.
>> CYRIL: Waagh!
>> RAY: Ow!
>> CYRIL: What are you doing
down there?
>> RAY: What do you think
I'm doing?
(chain rattles)
>> CYRIL: Oh. (chuckles) sorry.
>> ARCHER: Do me! Do me, do me,
do me, do me, do me! Ray, do me!
>> RAY: Ow! Ow! Ow!
>> ARCHER: Sorry. Do me, please.
>> RAY: First, promise you
won't be mad at me.
>> ARCHER: I... Wait.
Why would I be mad at you?
>> RAY: Because you're an
asshole!
>> MALORY: I beg your pardon?!
>> LANA: Since Cyril's not here,
I'm helping Cherlene redline her
record contract, and I think we
should move on.
They're not gonna let you
kill a guy.
>> CHERLENE: What about a dwarf?
>> MALORY: What about Sterling?!
>> CHERLENE: Wait, he's a dwarf
now?
>> MALORY: He's missing!
With God knows how much of our
dwindling cocaine, and no one's
doing anything to find him!
>> LANA: If he calls here, my
plan, in its entirety, is to ask
him where he is.
>> PAM: It has a simple
elegance.
>> MALORY: Well, have you tried
calling him?
(auto-dial beeping)
>> MALLORY: What?
(techno music playing)
>> PAM: Yaaaayyyyy!
>> CHERLENE: Wooooooooo!
>> FEMALE VOICE: The mailbox
of...
>> ARCHER: ...Ar-Ar-Archer...
>> FEMALE VOICE: ...is full.
Leave it.
>> MALLORY: All right!
Turn it off! Turn it off!
(voicemail message repeating)
>> LANA: I can't! It's...
>> ARCHER: Ar-Ar-Archer. Archer.
>> KRIEGER: Rrgh! Rrgh! Rrgh!
>> ARCHER: (voice slows):
Archer... Archer...
>> PAM & CHERLENE: Aw.
>> KRIEGER: Okay, so he forwards
his phone here.
That's easy.
Then he taps the phone line into
the intercom.
They're both low-voltage.
No big deal, but that's patched
into the actual house wiring,
obviously one-ten AC, which
means he must have wired a
transformer in the circuit
somewhere, but he's got all
these fake wires in here that
don't connect to any...
(Malory sobs)
>> MALORY: Is this all just a
game to you people?!
My God, I'm broke, my husband
kicked me out of my own home,
we're running out of cocaine,
and on top of all that, my son
is missing!
>> LANA: Um, okay, if Archer
calls, I'll...
>> MALORY: No, please don't
disturb me.
I think I'm getting a migraine.
(whistle blows)
>> CHERLENE: Outlaw country!
Wooooooooooooooo!
>> MALORY: I honestly don't know
how much more I can take!
(Cherlene chuckles)
>> LANA: Wow. I think she
seriously might be, like,
nearing the end of her rope.
>> PAM: Hey, speaking of rope...
>> LANA: You want cocaine?
>> PAM: Yay!
>> ARCHER: Goddamn it!
>> RAY: How is this my
fault?
>> ARCHER: Because why do you
always get paralyzed?!
>> RAY: Because why do you
always crash every goddamn
vehicle I get in?!
>> ARCHER: I didn't crash it!
That crooked idiot, drunk
murdering cop did!
>> CYRIL: Uh, yeah, speaking
of, these guys don't look too
good.
(cop coughs very weakly)
>> ARCHER: Well, they're gonna
look even worse when they're
jaguar poop!
>> CYRIL: What? We can't just
leave them here.
>> ARCHER: As opposed to what,
Cyril?!
You and I sling them over our
shoulders and climb 200 feet
straight up a cliff without
a goddamn rope?!
>> CYRIL: I...
>> RAY: Wait. Where am I in
that scenario?!
>> ARCHER: I guess getting
pooped out of a jaguar!
>> CYRIL: Well, we definitely
can't leave Ray!
>> ARCHER: We have to!
Ray, I'm sorry.
>> RAY: No, you're not!
>> ARCHER: I am, actually,
which, whatever, but...
(gun cocks)
>> CYRIL: We are not leaving
Ray!
>> ARCHER: What do you even
think you're doing?
>> CYRIL: I am taking command!
(Archer and Cyril laugh)
>> CYRIL: Hey, I'm serious!
>> ARCHER: Oh, my God.
Okay.
Oh, that's really funny.
Thanks, Cyril.
I-I think we needed that.
>> RAY: We did.
We really did.
>> ARCHER: Oh, man.
Now give me the goddamn weapon.
>> ARCHER: You nut!
(Cyril laughs)
>> CYRIL: Thought you were gonna
hit me with it.
>> ARCHER: I was.
Okay, so how do we get Ray and
his useless legs out of here?
>> RAY: Well, now, I
actually have some thoughts on
that.
>> ARCHER (sighing): Goddamn it.
>> RAY: I think it's a
pretty good plan, y'all.
>> ARCHER: No, it isn't!
We might as well slather
ourselves with whatever it is
crocodiles eat, and swim down!
>> CYRIL: What do crocodiles
eat?
>> ARCHER: Everything!
They eat everything!
And fear is their bacon bits.
>> CHERLENE: I don't understand
what you're saying.
>> LANA: Damn it!
Look, I think Malory is
genuinely going through a really
hard time right now, so I think
we should do something nice for
her.
>> CHERLENE: I don't understand
what you're say...
>> LANA: Goddamn it!
>> PAM: I'm with you, Lana.
It freaked me out seeing her cry
like that.
It was like seeing my dad cry.
>> LANA: Crying because...?
>> PAM: (splutters) Name it.
He's a gigantic pussy.
Oh, my God, when my mom died?
Hey, and speaking of pussies...
>> LANA: A Long Island Iced Tea?
I'm not even supposed to drink
regular iced tea.
>> PAM: Yeah, this is a Long
Island.
>> CHERLENE: Yeah, stupid!
Your words.
>> LANA: Shut up!
And, okay, so what would cheer
Malory up?
What does she like?
>> PAM: Archer and money and
liquor.
>> LANA: Besides that.
>> CHERLENE: Some different
liquor.
>> PAM: You know what always
cheers me up...
>> LANA: We're not giving her
cocaine.
>> PAM: I was gonna say cock.
>> CHERLENE: Yeah, stup... Ow!
>> LANA: You done?
>> CHERLENE: I am. Thank you.
>> LANA: Ass. And Pam, that's
not a bad idea.
>> PAM: Hmm. I don't know if I'd
be comfortable with that.
I mean, even for me, it's...
>> LANA: Let me stop you before
you say what it is you think I'm
talking about.
>> PAM: Getting shitty drunk on
two different kinds of liquor,
dressing up like Mr. Archer,
and banging the old lady with
a strap...
Ow!
>> LANA: That's not what I had
in mind.
>> PAM: Okay, good, 'cause the
the dressing up like Mr. Archer
part makes it kind of weird.
>> LANA: I...
>> PAM: I'd have to be super
drunk, like so drunk I bet I
wouldn't even enjoy...! Ow!
(Pam clears her throat)
Okay, so what's your plan?
>> CYRIL: Well, eventually, we
have to come to a village or
whatever, and maybe we can
barter with them for a ride,
or...
>> ARCHER: Barter with what,
Cyril?
>> CYRIL: I don't know.
Maybe the gun, or...
>> ARCHER (laughing): Yes!
Great idea, yeah, Cyril.
Let's give an M-16 to a bunch of
wild Indians!
>> CYRIL: Whoa, whoa, whoa, hey!
>> RAY: Goddamn,
Huckleberry Finn!
>> ARCHER: What?! I don't think
it's racist to assume that a
previously uncontacted tribe of
indigenous peoples might react
unpredictably, perhaps even
wildly, to a bunch of white guys
who walk up and hand 'em a
goddamn M-16!
>> CYRIL: Oh, okay.
I didn't know in your scenario
the indigenous people were
uncontacted.
>> RAY: Totally different
scenario.
>> CYRIL: In which, no, you
obviously wouldn't just want to
hand them an M-16.
>> RAY: 'Cause they'd be,
like, "What?!"
Or whatever their word for that
is.
>> MALORY: What?
>> LANA: A spa day!
>> MALORY: What? No.
I can't go out like this.
>> LANA: No, no, no!
That's the best part.
It's here!
>> MALORY: Then it's not a spa
day.
It's just a bath!
I want to go back to sleep!
>> LANA: Well, after this,
you'll be so relaxed.
>> MALORY: I took three Valium!
If I get any more relaxed,
I will literally die.
>> LANA: Okay, well, that's also
good... because you may not
actually find this to be all
that relaxing.
>> MALORY: What the...?
Why are they dressed like that?
>> LANA (sighing): That was the
only way they'd do it.
>> CHERLENE: Strip!
>> PAM: Yay!
>> CYRIL: Wait. What?
>> ARCHER: Crocodylus acutus!
And maybe even...
Are we in the Orinoco drainage
basin?
>> CYRIL: How should I know?
>> ARCHER: Okay, so maybe
Crocodylus intermedius is in
play!
Not to mention four kinds of
caiman, including the Black
Caiman, which can grow up to
22 feet!
>> RAY: Is that why you're
up on those goddamn cans?
>> ARCHER: Yeah, if a big bull
croc slithers up on the raft,
I'm gonna pour a ring of gas
around me and set it on fire.
>> CYRIL: Why...?
>> ARCHER: Cyril, they can't
chomp through fire.
Although, I have no reason to
think that.
>> CYRIL: Why are you so scared
of crocodiles?
>> ARCHER: Gee, I don't know,
Cyril.
Maybe deep down, I'm afraid of
any apex predator that lived
through the K-T extinction.
>> CYRIL: The...?
>> ARCHER: Physically unchanged
for 100 million years, because
it's the perfect killing
machine-- a half-ton of
cold-blooded fury, with a bite
force of 20,000 Newtons, and
stomach acid so strong, it can
dissolve bones and hooves.
And now we're surrounded, those
snake-eyes are watching from the
shadows, waiting for the night.
>> RAY: ¶ Waiting
For the night! ¶
>> ARCHER: Damn it, Ray!
>> RAY: ¶ Ooh-hoo!
>> ARCHER: Keep your voice down!
>> RAY: Why?!
Crocodiles don't have ears!
>> ARCHER: They absolutely have
ears, shit head!
>> RAY: Well, so do I, and
you just talked yourself out of
a hat!
(all yelling)
>> CYRIL: Jeezy Pete's!
>> ARCHER: Way to go, Ray.
Now he's got a taste for...
(yelling)
>> RAY: Oh, my God!
>> CYRIL: Shoot it! Shoot it!
Shoot it!
>> ARCHER: Uh, I can't!
>> RAY: Sweet Jesus God,
then at least shoot out my eyes
so I don't have to see!
(yelling)
Oh, my God!
>> CYRIL: What is happening?
(yelling)
Oh, God!
>> RAY: Oh, boy.
(groaning and crying)
No.
(Archer groans)
(Gillette and Cyril crying)
(growling)
>> ARCHER: Huh.
(Cyril and Gillette whimpering)
I thought that was gonna be way
more... epic-fireball-y.
(Gillette whimpers)
>> CYRIL: Wuh-wuh, wuh-wuh,
wuh-wuh...
>> ARCHER: Come on, Cyril.
Pick one.
Either have a stroke, or spit it
out.
>> CYRIL: W-w-were you g-g-gonna
say, "A taste for human flesh?"
>> ARCHER: No, I was gonna say,
"Hat," but now it's not funny.
Well, not as funny.
>> RAY: It's all your
fault.
It's all your fault.
>> ARCHER: Which part, Ray?!
The part where I flipped our
jeep down a cliff about 90
goddamn times, because I got
drunk to cope with the fact I
was about to murder us in the
jungle?!
>> RAY: Well, it-it... it's
your fault we're in this stupid
jungle in the first place!
>> ARCHER: Well, if we're gonna
go back to the beginning of
time, Mother's the one who got
us arrested for treason, and
then bought a ton of goddamn
cocaine!
>> CYRIL: I thought you b-bought
it.
>> LANA: Wait. What?
>> MALORY: Up! Up!
Hands off the goods, mister!
>> PAM: Aw.
>> MALORY: I said that's
ridiculous.
Where would I get 2,000 pounds
of cocaine?
>> LANA: But if you didn't...
Okay, so, where would Archer get
that much coke?
>> MALORY: Well, who knows with
him?
Maybe wherever he got that new
kind of VD none of the doctors
had ever seen before.
>> LANA: Wha?! When was that?!
>> PAM: Yeah, when was that?
>> CHERLENE: Seriously, was...
>> MALORY: Trust me, if you had
it, you'd know.
>> CHERLENE & PAM: Phew!
>> LANA: Ugh. I loathe knowing
that I had sex with the same
person as you two.
>> PAM: What? You had sex with
me!
>> LANA: No, I... (gasps)
Oh, my God, that's right.
>> MALORY: Ha!
>> PAM: What are you laughing
at?
>> MALORY: Oh, my God, that's
right.
>> ARCHER: So if you dicks want
to blame somebody for our
current predicament, blame...
>> RAY: You! I blame you!
Archer! I blame you!
J'accuse!
(flames whoosh, all yelling)
>> ARCHER: What was that, Ray?!
(whistling)
(laughs): Sorry.
I genuinely couldn't hear you.
(Cyril and Gillette crying)
>> ARCHER: Jesus, what is wrong
with you two?
>> CYRIL: What's wrong?!
What's wrong is we're about to
be on fire!
>> RAY: Do something!
>> ARCHER: Uh, no?
>> RAY: Archer!
>> ARCHER: Not until you
apologize.
>> RAY: For what?!
>> CYRIL: Ray, goddamn it, just
apologize!
>> RAY: I... Jesus Christ,
I'm sorry!
>> ARCHER: There, was that so
hard?
Okay!
(Gillette coughing, sputtering)
>> CYRIL: What the hell are
you... (coughing)
>> ARCHER: Crocodile repellent!
>> CYRIL (coughing): What?!
>> ARCHER: We got to swim for
it-- on three.
>> CYRIL: No, no, n... (grunts)
Archer!
>> ARCHER: Sorry, three!
Kick, Cyril, kick!
(Cyril coughing)
(Gillette retching, coughing)
It's okay, stupid, I forgive
you.
>> RAY: F...
>> ARCHER: Forgive, yes.
Cannonball!
Woooooo!!
(Cyril retching)
(Gillette moaning)
>> ARCHER (chuckling): Oh...
>> CYRIL: Oh, God, I think I
swallowed a leech.
>> ARCHER: Well, the gas ought
to kill that.
>> RAY: (coughs) You
asshole, you could've killed us!
(Cyril clears throat)
Well?!
>> CYRIL: Well, you did set the
raft on fire.
>> RAY: Oh, my God, you
always take his side!
>> CYRIL: I never, ever, ever
take his side.
>> ARCHER: Blah, blah, blah,
some joke about you two having
vaginas.
Come on, let's go.
>> CYRIL: Go where?
>> ARCHER: Well, long-term, I
was thinking home.
Short-term, I... Here, hold
this.
(grunts)
>> RAY: Go herd.
>> ARCHER: Short-term, somewhere
that's not the crocodile version
of a drive-through.
(crocodile snarls)
>> CYRIL: Sounds good!
Here we go!
>> ARCHER: Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh.
>> CYRIL: I got it. (grunting)
>> ARCHER: Cyril.
>> CYRIL: What if I need a gun?
>> ARCHER: Um...
here.
>> CYRIL: Oh, come on.
>> ARCHER: The only limit is
your imagination.
Pyoo! Pyoo!
(Cyril sighs)
>> PAM: Aw, look, she's almost
not terrifying.
>> LANA: (sighs) Thanks, you
guys.
I think the spa day took her
mind off Archer being missing,
even if it almost got weird.
>> CHERLENE: She made it weird.
>> LANA: No, you did.
Nobody wants an enema.
>> CHERLENE: Some people...
>> LANA: Not with yogurt.
>> PAM: So... you think those
guys are okay?
>> LANA: I don't know.
I mean, if it were anybody else,
I'd say no, but this is Archer
we're talking about so...
probably not.
>> CYRIL: Oh, for... Can you not
give it a rest?
>> RAY: Not until he admits
he's been half-assing this
entire cocaine debacle from
the get-go.
>> ARCHER: That's only because I
thought it was gonna be way
easier.
>> RAY: You think
everything's gonna be easy!
>> ARCHER: It almost always is!
>> RAY: Aha! See?
That's what I resent.
>> ARCHER: What do you resent,
Ray, my muscly shoulders poking
into your tum-tum?
>> RAY: I resent how you
never take anything seriously
because you just assume
everything's gonna work out for
you.
>> ARCHER: It almost always
does!
(Cyril sighs)
Case in point.
>> CYRIL: What the...
>> RAY: Goddamn it.
>> CYRIL (quietly): Hey, do you
think those guys are Doctors
Without Borders?
>> ARCHER: Yes, Cyril, I do.
I bet those assault rifles shoot
polio vaccine.
They're narcos, dummy.
And that plane's probably loaded
with coke.
Okay, here's the plan...
>> CYRIL: What? Are you crazy?
>> RAY: You're out of your
mind.
>> ARCHER: We have to get out of
the country, so we can either
walk out-- which, no, no, we
can't-- or we can fly out in an
airplane full of cocaine.
>> CYRIL: Ray is paralyzed.
Who's gonna fly it?
>> ARCHER: Don't... That...
Why would you worry about that
before you need to?
>> CYRIL: What?
>> ARCHER: Why clog your brain
with a bunch of hypothetical
maybe-what-if bullshit?
>> CYRIL: Because...
>> ARCHER: Shut up.
This is what we're doing.
So, Cyril, lock and load that
stick.
(indistinct chatter)
(Gillette stifles a sneeze)
>> ARCHER (quietly): Manos
arriba.
>> GILLETTE (whispering): Nice.
>> ARCHER: You want to...
>> RAY: Oh, right.
(cocks gun)
>> BOSS NARCO: Bueno pues,
cuando está cargado...
>> RAY: Manos...
Um...
Wait, what was it?
>> ARCHER: Arriba! Goddamn it.
¡Manos arriba!
(weapons cocking)
>> BOSS NARCO: (chuckles) I
don't think so, gringo.
>> ARCHER: Drop your weapons!
I'm serious.
I will shoot this guy right in
the...
>> BOSS NARCO: (laughs) What the
hell is that?
>> ARCHER: Pyoo! Pyoo!
(narcos laughing)
>> CYRIL: Suppressing fiiiiiire!
(narcos shouting)
>> ARCHER: Okay, okay!
(moans)
Goddamn it, Cyril!
>> CYRIL: Woooooo!! (chuckles)
Oh, geez, oh, geez, oh, geez!
Sorry.
>> ARCHER: That's why I wanted
you to be stick.
>> RAY: Uh-uh!
>> ARCHER: Yeah, come on.
It's been a long day.
>> BOSS NARCO: Do you have any
idea who we are?
>> ARCHER: Mmm... nope.
Do you know who we are?
>> BOSS NARCO: No.
(Archer burps)
>> ARCHER: Then blow me.
Cyril, make sure it's good and
tight.
(Archer chuckles)
Why are we not still doing
phrasing?
>> CYRIL: Why are we still not
worrying about who's gonna fly
the damn plane?!
>> ARCHER: Oh, right.
¡Oye, pendejos!
¿Quién es el piloto?
(narcos snicker)
(narco speaks Spanish)
>> CYRIL: Oh, you are kidding.
>> ARCHER: Okay, Ray, ballpark,
how long will it take you to
teach me how to fly a plane?
>> RAY: What... How long?
>> CYRIL: I flew the space
shuttle.
>> ARCHER: Cyril, hush.
Big guys.
Ray, how long...
>> RAY: How long will it take
you, Archer, to admit you dick
around every time we're in
danger just to screw with
everybody because of your
complete... no, your utter
contempt for your own mortality?
>> ARCHER: I mean...
Yeah, duh.
>> RAY: That's all I wanted.
(grunts)
>> CYRIL: (gasps) What?
You could walk this whole time?!
(Archer laughs)
>> ARCHER: No, Cyril, of course
I'm not mad.
I think what Ray did was
awesome.
>> CYRIL: Okay, well, then you
are an idiot.
>> ARCHER: Your words.
>> CYRIL: Which, I guess,
so am I, since I just realized
we can't land anywhere with
all this cocaine onboard.
Oh, my God, you guys, where are
we gonna land?!
>> RAY: Jesus Christ, woman,
calm down.
We got five hours of fuel.
We'll worry about that when we
have to.
>> ARCHER: Guess I'm rubbing off
on you, Ray.
Goddamn it!
>> BOTH: What?!
>> ARCHER: Why are we not doing
"phrasing"?
>> CHERLENE: ¶ Now I'm coming
Now I'm coming
¶ I'm coming home to you...
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> MAN: Made... in Georgia.