PAM: Oh for the --
We're already late, what'd
ya go and start that for?
CHERYL/CAROL: I didn't!
PAM: So, it just
spontaneously combusted.
CHERYL/CAROL: So creepy...
look, I've got goosebumps.
PAM: I'm sure you do.
MALORY: What is --
is something burning?!
CHERYL/CAROL: No!
Maybe you're having a stroke!
MALORY: I'm not having a stroke!
ARCHER: That's great, Mother, keep
those periodic updates coming!
MALORY: Oh shut up.
ARCHER: Hey, Friday happy
hour, you guys in?
PAM: Gimme that.
ARCHER: No no no no no that's not --
CHERYL/CAROL: [delighted squeal, giggle]
-- water.
PAM: Well what the hell was it?!
ARCHER: Grappa.
- Aww...
- No shit, that was like twenty bucks' worth.
PAM: Who drinks a
pint of grappa?!
ARCHER: Well nobody
now, Wendy Wasteful.
So you can buy my first
couple of rounds.
PAM: Nah, I can't, we --
ARCHER: No, you can.
I'm allowing you.
PAM: Oh my God, thank you
ARCHER: You're welcome.
PAM: -- but we've got dates.
ARCHER: Meaning the
fruit of the date palm?
PAM: Muh-huh.
Date dates, dingdong.
ARCHER: With who?
CHERYL/CAROL: Oh, just some
handsome firemen I met.
At a warehouse fire.
PAM: So c'mon, let's go already!
My cooch has cobwebs on it.
ARCHER: Ew.
Krieger, hey, wanna get a drink?
KRIEGER: Oooooooooooooh, no.
- It's mushi night, movie and sushi
- With... oh.
Meaning that's tentacle porn.
KRIEGER: "Fisherman's Wife"
and "Fisherman's Wife Two:"
"The Re-Tentacling."
HOLOGRAM: [embarrassed giggle]
ARCHER: Mother, hey,
wanna go get a drink?
MALORY: You know, as a
matter of fact, I do.
- Oh, okay, uh --
- And as another matter of fact, I am.
With Ron, in the bar
at The Tuntmore.
And if he plays his cards right, he'll
be wetting a lot more than his --
[TWEEEEEEEEEEEET!]
MALORY: Oww!
What is wrong with you?!
ARCHER: Well for one
thing, tinnitus!
Which... Yeah, I think
it's getting worse.
And how do they all have dates,
these aren't people you date,
I'm who should have a date, I'm the...
best at dates.
Hmm, I wonder if
Lana has a date.
LANA: Yes!
ARCHER: Lana?
ARCHER: You heard that?
LANA: Yes!
ARCHER: Who're you,
Jaime Sommers?
LANA: Yes!
ARCHER: No seriously, I can barely hear
me, are my ears really that messed up?
LANA: Yes! Yes! Yes!
ARCHER: Okay, Jesus, I'm not deaf,
I'm just -- Going to vomit.
I am going to vomit.
MALORY: Not on my
carpet, you're not!
I -- Oh for God's
sake, get a room!
LANA: We did.
♪ ♪
Sync & corrections by Alice
www.addic7ed.com
LANA: Shut up, because first of all...
I don't have to explain myself to you,
of all people, and --
[TWEET.]
LANA: -- and if you blow that
thing again the next time you
hear it'll be when some whore
is giving you a blow job.
ARCHER: Doesn't even make sense.
CYRIL: I think she means she'll
shove it up your -- [TWEEEEEEET.]
LANA: Dickhole, and where
did you get that?!
ARCHER: Rape prevention class.
Which, turns out, is a
not-good place to meet women.
LANA: No shit.
ARCHER: Yeah, it's like their guard is
so up, it's -- Cyril, scotch, where?!
CYRIL: Well if you mean my
grandfather's Glengoolie Blue,
you drank it and then puked
it into my trash can!
ARCHER: Oh my God, Lana I get,
she wants to make me jealous,
but are you seriously just
getting me back for the scotch?!
LANA: Do you even hear yourself?
ARCHER: It honestly
kinda comes and goes.
LANA: Well, since thanks to you I didn't
do the former, now we're doing the latter.
Cyril, go start the car.
CYRIL: Are you not going -
LANA: Cyril?
Remember the ground
rules for this?
So carefully negotiated?
CYRIL: I will go start the car.
LANA: And before you say it --
ARCHER: How long's it been since you got laid, Lana?
LANA: That's not why I'm
dating Cyril again!
ARCHER: Uh-huh, so two --
LANA: No! Not two years!
Ass.
Fourteen months.
So go ahead, laugh.
ARCHER: At what?
I was gonna say two weeks.
Two years is... Lana, that's the --
third saddest thing I've heard today.
Pam told me about a little girl who
drowned trying to save a puppy.
LANA: Jesus... what was
the second saddest?
ARCHER: The puppy drowned too.
But it's a close third, I mean don't do this,
Lana, c'mon, I'd be happy to bang you.
LANA: Me and anybody who
could fog a mirror.
ARCHER: Well before, maybe, but I
really think I've changed, Ya know!
And-or matured!
LANA: Ha.
ARCHER: No, I'm serious, with the cancer,
and my possible father dying, and um...
oh my God, the tinnitus?!
LANA: Archer...
ARCHER: Hang on, should we get that?
LANA: Get what?
ARCHER: Is the phone not...?
Damn you, tinnitus,
you're a cruel mistress!
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
But seriously, do
you not hear that?
LANA: Yes, now!
It's your phone!
ARCHER: Oh. Duh.
Wait please, Lana, c'mon, you can't
deny we're attracted to each other!
LANA: So?!
ARCHER: So what if all that
stuff really has matured me?
I know I'm not perfect, but
you have to admit I'm better!
LANA: Than?
ARCHER: Than I was!
And also than Cyril
could ever be.
- First of all, Cyril --
- Cheated on you as much as I did, Lana,
- and I'm ten times handsomer than
him, so...   -  They're the same!
ARCHER: Lana, be
honest with yourself.
LANA: It was actually
about ten times worse.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
What happened to your
idiot voicemail?!
ARCHER: I'm doing this new thing, where
now it just rings, drives people crazy.
LANA: Oh my God, you have matured...
ARCHER: Lana, I have!
Just let me prove it!
LANA: If.
In some crazy parallel
universe I agreed to that.
How would you.
ARCHER: By -- Jesus, hang on, Woodhouse
might be trapped in the dumbwaiter again.
He was in there two
days last time.
LANA: Your apartment's one level,
how do you have a dumbwaiter?
ARCHER: Goes sideways.
Mmmmmmmmyello?
Speaking.
Uh-huh.
Okay, bye.
Yes!
Okay, Lana, check you later.
LANA: What?
What about all that just now?
ARCHER: All what just now?
LANA: About how much you've matured,
and how you want to get back together?
ARCHER: That's what you heard?
Wow, your ears are
even worse than mine.
LANA: Wait, was that
even Woodhouse?
ARCHER: Nooop!
LANA: Then who was it?!
[CRYING]
KATYA: Yes, my dear
Sterling, come for me.
Phrezzing, boom.
[WHISTLING]
MAN: Hey, asshole!
ARCHER: [AHEMS]
ARCHER: Thanks.
And oh, my name is Cyril Figgis.
ARCHER: Hey, how's it going?
KATYA: Thenk you,
they are beautiful.
ARCHER: Sorry about the chocolate, I
didn't know you were allergic or whatever.
KATYA: The alkaloids.
They can make a problem
with my bioelectronics.
ARCHER: Oh. Right.
Because you have those.
KATYA: And I'm sorry
if you misunderstood.
I did not call you
for the romance.
ARCHER: I -- yeah I mean yeah,
no, duh, and besides I wouldn't
be interested, I have
a girlfriend, so.
KATYA: Oh.
ARCHER: Yeah, an actress.
Of stage and screen.
KATYA: Oh.
Well, I hope she
makes you happy.
Is funny, you don't
ask where is Barry.
ARCHER: What do you mean where is
Barry, he's -- Yeah, where is Barry?
KATYA: I... I don't know!
And only one week after, well, you
know, when I left you for him,
he said he must go
for work, to London.
ARCHER: Wow, that was months ago...
KATYA: And since then, nothing!
Not a word!
What could have
happened to him?!
ARCHER: Uhhh...
BARRY: Noooooooooooooooooooo!
KATYA: He is on space station?!
But why?!
ARCHER: Well, ya know, I hate to say
this, but obviously he met someone else.
KATYA: Sterling. Pliz.
ARCHER: Yeah, that was the -- third
dumbest thing I've ever said.
KATYA: Wait, what
were the first two?
ARCHER: Buddy, you
just sold a timeshare!
Make that two timeshares!
- Goddamn maintenance fees...
- Sterling, will you please help me find him?
ARCHER: How?
That office was just a trailer.
KATYA: Barry.
ARCHER: Oh. Barry, right.
KATYA: Pliz, Sterling.
If you ever truly loved me, you
will help Barry to come home to me.
ARCHER: 'kay.
PAM: Okay, lemme get this straight...
You wanna help psycho
cyborg supervillain Barry, who's trapped
in space like General frickin Zod,
get back to earth so
she'll dump him for you?
ARCHER: Right?
When Barry gets back she'll
realize what a dick he is,
so she'll need somebody to talk to, so enter
Sterling Archer, the sensitive friend!
CHERYL/CAROL: What is
this, Opposite World?
PAM: Yeah, right?
Oh for -- this is
not Opposite World.
- I think in her mind that mean
- God, okay!
This is Opposite World!
CHERYL/CAROL: Whew!
ARCHER: Um, okay, and since
certain people around
here may not see how
brilliant my plan is,
- they're gonna need to be --
PAM: Convinced?
ARCHER: I'm sorry, did
you say incapacitated?
- Because, Krieger, I can't have the--
KRIEGER: Responsible people?
ARCHER: Naysayers!
Walk in on you while you're
helping Barry build a rocket!
KRIEGER: Barry The
Unstoppable Psycho-Cyborg.
ARCHER: He's not
unstoppable anymore!
Ray's got bionic legs!
But if you don't wanna see two
robots smashing each other with
cop cars and shit as they fight to the
death through the streets of Manhattan...
KRIEGER: Bup bup bup bup bup!
Stop.
My penis can only get so erect.
HOLOGRAM: Honntou ne...
[Very true...]
KRIEGER: I was tired!
ARCHER: Ew.
[WHISTLING]
ARCHER: Cyril?
CYRIL: What.
[TRANQUILIZER DART]
ARCHER: Ew.
ARCHER: Ray?
GILLETTE: What.
[TRANQUILIZER DART]
ARCHER: Seriously, how
is that even a genre?
And is this just
jackoff central?
PAM: Ugh, not with all
this damn racket!
ARCHER: Wh-? Why aren't
you in position?!
PAM: I am, this is how I do it!
ARCHER: Wh-? Ewww!
I meant with Mother!
PAM: Oh.
I put Cheryl on that.
ARCHER: Great, Miss
Opposite World?!
CHERYL/CAROL: You heard
me, do not go in there.
LANA: Why, what are
you hiding this time?
MALORY: Probably another one of
her so-called mystery fires.
CHERYL/CAROL: Lana, I said no!
LANA: Okay, so where's
the... fire.
MALORY: [DEEPLY WEARY SIGH]
CHERYL/CAROL: Worst. Day. Evah!
ARCHER: Okay status report!
Mother in there?
CHERYL/CAROL: No.
MALORY: Carol, open
this damn door!
- Um, okay, now I just need to find
LANA: Cheryl!
CHERYL/CAROL: And
neither is Lana.
ARCHER: Nice!
Hey excellent job, seriously--
Ow! I mean... totally shit job?
LANA: Cheryl!
CHERYL/CAROL: Thank you.
PAM: So when I said this is Opposite World --
CHERYL/CAROL: Pam.
The important thing
is that I'm happy.
Try not to overthink it.
KRIEGER: I just wanna help you finish
your new spaceship, why is that weird?
BARRY: Why is that weird -- Because my
sworn purpose in life is to murder your
little buddy Archer?
KRIEGER: Archer?
No way man, I hate that guy!
BARRY: Since when?
KRIEGER: Since, um, he
slept with my girlfriend!
HOLOGRAM: Dattara iinoni...
[I wish.]
KRIEGER: Keep it up.
BARRY: God, that is
just classic Archer!
KRIEGER: Right?
I mean, not a huge surprise,
from a self-centered alcoholic
who feels compelled to
sleep with every woman
he meets because
that's the only way to
fill the emptiness inside where
his mother's love should -- ow!
BARRY: Do what?
KRIEGER: One sec?
ARCHER: What the shit?!
KRIEGER: What, you said be convin--
ARCHER: Convincing!
Not deliberately hurtful!
KRIEGER: Well?!
BARRY: Yo, asshole!
What're we doing here?
KRIEGER: Fixing that
spaceship, buddy!
Looks like it's just
about done, huh?
BARRY: Yeah, those scientists
were pretty resourceful.
Until they all died.
KRIEGER: And how did
they, um, all die?
BARRY: Oh... different ways.
KRIEGER: 'kay.
MALORY: Swift and severe.
The punishment will
be swift and severe.
I mean it, Lana, that
girl is out of here.
LANA: Aww, and right when she was gonna
invest ten million dollars in ISIS.
MALORY: She said that?!
Oh my God, that phony
prospectus must've worked!
Do you think the
money's in here?!
Come on, help me
look in these boxes!
LANA: Malory!
MALORY: What?!
Oh.
Dammit.
ARCHER: So yeah... Krieger's helping
Barry finish his rocketship,
and when he gets home he can...
tell you about the other woman.
KATYA: The what?!
ARCHER: Wait, how'd we
get to another woman?
KATYA: Oh my God, do you
have proof of this?!
ARCHER: No, I -- can probably get some...
KATYA: Oh, Sterling!
- If Barry really is cheating on me...
ARCHER: And also if I prove it somehow...
KATYA: Then he will
be dead to me!
Because I will kill him
with my bare hands!
ARCHER: Yeah, or not, since then there's
no reason for him to come home at all!
KATYA: What's that?
ARCHER: Nothing, what?
Oh, you mean that?
Sorry, that's... just
a sympathy boner.
[WHISTLING]
MAN: Oww!
ARCHER: Woooo!
Cyril Figgis strikes again!
ARCHER: Status report!
CHERYL/CAROL: Terrible!
ARCHER: Wait, what
hap -- goddammit!
CHERYL/CAROL: What?!
Dude, assimilate!
ARCHER: Are Mother and
Lana still in the vault?
CHERYL/CAROL: No.
ARCHER: I -- rrgh!
MALORY: A situation, by the way,
for which I blame you entirely.
LANA: How is this my fault?!
You were the -- holy shit, there really
are nerve gas canisters up here!
I thought that was a joke!
MALORY: How is that funny?
ARCHER: Because I said so.
KRIEGER: What's this
even written on?
ARCHER: A bar bill,
and just do it.
Forget about actually
fixing the rocket.
KRIEGER: But what about
the robot fight?!
And why are you
beating on shit?!
BARRY: Because shit is stuck!
KRIEGER: Dude!
It's not a frickin tractor!
BARRY: Yeah, that's what all the
space-nerds up here kept saying.
Until Other Barry just
couldn't stand it anymore.
KRIEGER: I --
ARCHER: Krieger!
Forget the robot fight and
just read the damn script!
Then upload the audio
to the mainframe!
KRIEGER: Okay, either Barry!
I need you to find a female
co-ax bus connector.
BARRY: What's a female...
whatever look like?
ARCHER: Pam!
Pam!
Paaaaaam!
PAM: Whaaat?!
ARCHER: C'mon, I need your help on --
wait, what were you doing in there?
PAM: Nothin.
But don't go in there!
ARCHER: No, huh-uh!
That's how Mother and Lana
wound up locked in the vault!
- A situation, by the way, for which--
LANA: I heard you!
ARCHER: C'mon!
You're still into all that
stupid AV stuff, right?
PAM: Uh... Not reeeally...
KRIEGER: Okay, so screw those in...
BARRY: Wait... all of 'em?
KRIEGER: Dammit
man, I said screw!
BARRY: I am screwing!
KRIEGER: Wow, this
might actually work.
PAM: What's that?
ARCHER: I said why
not use this one.
PAM: No! Gimme that!
ARCHER: Why, what's on here?
PAM: Nothing! Jesus!
CYRIL: Christ, Ray!
Is it too much to ask?!
Just once?!
To be unconscious in a bathroom without
being sexually assaulted by -- you, um...
...have a dart in your neck.
GILLETTE: Oh. So do you.
CYRIL: Oh.
- Sorry I accused you of, um...
GILLETTE: It's okay.
C'mon, let's find our --
CYRIL: Noooooooooooooooooooo!
GILLETTE: Noooooooooooooooooooo!
PAM: Yes... owww!
ARCHER: Will you focus?!
PAM: That's as good
as I can get it!
Dicknuts!
ARCHER: Shut up, okay, then that'll have
to do, so make a tape or whatever, and --
CHERYL/CAROL: So, just a quick heads up,
Ms. Archer and Lana are still in the vault.
ARCHER: Wh-?
Then why are you bothering--
MALORY: Carol!
LANA: Cheryl!
CHERYL/CAROL: [startled yelp]
MALORY: Pam you better
not be making pornos!
PAM: 'kay!
ARCHER: Tape, woman, tape!
PAM: Okay, here!
Dicknuts!
ARCHER: I'm afraid I
have some bad news.
Now, the audio's a little rough, ya
know, it's from outer space, but --
KATYA: Sterling, pliz!
I want to hear it.
ARCHER: Well, Katya, you say that...
ARCHER ON TAPE: Barry?
Barry it's me, Archer.
ARCHER: That's not me,
talking to Barry.
KATYA: Shh!
BARRY: Classic Archer!
ARCHER: That's Barry, talking to--
KATYA: Shhhhh!
ARCHER: Yeah so listen, Katya
asked me to call you...
BARRY: Shit.
ARCHER: She's wondering
why you left.
BARRY: Because couldn't
stand it anymore.
KATYA: [small gasp]
ARCHER: So you lied
to her about being on
- the space station because--
BARRY: Archer.
I am screwing!
Female.
Scientists up here all of 'em?
KATYA: [medium gasp]
ARCHER: Oh, I was
gonna ask which one but--
BARRY: All of 'em?
All of 'em?
All of --
ARCHER: Okay Barry, I --
BARRY: Different ways.
Like?
In.
Asshole!
KATYA: [huge gasp]
ARCHER: Okay, Barry!
Jesus, have some--
KATYA: [almost feral [sobbing/screaming]
ARCHER: Katya, baby, don't!
C'mon, you'll -- wait, does
that even hurt your hands?
KATYA: The only thing
that hurts is my heart!
And when Barry gets back, his heart
will hurt, because I will rip it out!
ARCHER: What if... Barry
wasn't coming back?
KATYA: But you said Krieger
was fixing rocket.
ARCHER: Yeah, but only because he wanted
to see an epic robot fi -- oh, shit!
Will you excuse me?
For a sec?
ARCHER: No no no no no no no no!
BARRY: Yes!
I think that's got 'er, dude!
KRIEGER: Told you it was
the viscous coupling!
BARRY: Well goody,
you win space camp.
So tell Archer I'm coming for him,
phrasing, boom, and both Barrys out!
ARCHER: Krieger!
Why is Barry rocket-shipping away
from the frickin space station?!
KRIEGER: Because Newton's
Third Law of Motion?
ARCHER: Hey thanks,
Neil deGrasse Tyson!
HOLOGRAM: Oooooh,
deGrasse Tyson-san...
ARCHER: How the hell
did you fix his ship?!
I gave you a bunch of gibberish!
KRIEGER: I may have gone
a teeny bit off script?
ARCHER: Wh-?
What is wrong with you?!
KRIEGER: With me?
Dude, robot fight.
- Oh, and Barry said tell you he's--
ARCHER: I heard him!
Okay, I'll tell Katya to pack
a bag and we'll move to,
Alaska or somewhere else snowy,
where he can't track us!
KRIEGER: Doesn't
even make sense.
ARCHER: You know what
doesn't make sense?!
OPERATOR: The number you have dialed
has been disconnected or is --
ARCHER: Nooooooooooooooooooo!
OPERATOR: -- longer in service.
Goodbye.
[PHONE RINGING]
BARRY: Hey, punkin pie!
KATYA: Dun't give me your pie of pumpkin,
Barry, you are in the big trouble!
BARRY: I --
KATYA: I told you!
I said dun't try to kill
Sterling and what do you do?!
BARRY: Um, that.
KATYA: Da.
But I do what you ask me.
To repair your rocket, I use Sterling,
and once again break his heart, so --
BARRY: Archer? Please.
KATYA: No. You pliz, he loves me.
You should have heard
thet pathetic tape.
BARRY: Well whatever, look --
KATYA: You look.
When you get home you are going
to hev some new ground rules.
BARRY: Okay, hon?
Look, I'm sorry I lied, but,
ya know, I make the rules.
- I mean, I am the head of the KGB, so--
KATYA: Hello?
Darling, you are breaking up.
KATYA: Now who do I hev to screw
to get a drink around here?
BORIS: Nobody, ma'am.
Unless you wunt.
And if you do wunt,
I ken be buttum.
No problum there.
Sync & corrections by Alice
www.addic7ed.com