ARCHER: Rat Patrol!
God, that was killing me.
So yeah, these exact same jeeps,
only with fifty-cal machine guns
on the back, and the Rat
Patrol just tore ass all over
North Africa, hassling Rommel.
How did you never see that show?
GILLETTE: I was probably here,
digging this goddamn jeep outta
this goddamn sand!
ARCHER: Hey don't yell at me, I'm
not the idiot who got us stuck!
CYRIL: You were driving!
So yes, you are exactly the
idiot who got us stuck!
ARCHER: Well whatever, the Rat Patrol
drove through way deeper sand than this.
GILLETTE: Ya know...
ARCHER: Although I think one guy's backstory
was that he'd been like, a bootlegger?
But Kentucky's not all sand-duney, so--
CYRIL: Can you at least get out
of the jeep?!
ARCHER: Yes.
GILLETTE: Well?!
ARCHER: Hang on?
[BELCHES]
But only because taking a dump on
Turkmenistan is on my bucket list.
CYRIL: A true citizen of the world.
ARCHER: Right?
I mean shut up?
Is... damn.
Okay, I guess this'll have to do.
GILLETTE: Noooop!
CYRIL: You're not using the map for that!
ARCHER: Hey, I'm not the idiot
who didn't -- I mean, I also
didn't think to bring toilet
paper, but I'm not, ya know...
GILLETTE: An idiot.
ARCHER: Exactly.
CYRIL: Right, because an idiot wouldn't
wipe his ass with our only map.
ARCHER: No, an idiot would wipe
his ass with our only compass.
GILLETTE: Wait, which is where?!
ARCHER: Who am I, Lewis and-or Clark?
CYRIL: Archer.
ARCHER: Well the last time I saw
it was on the bar in the Athens
airport, but --
GILLETTE: God damn it!
ARCHER: Yeah, I doubt it's still there.
CYRIL: [annoyed sigh]
ARCHER: A sticky-fingered
people, the Greeks.
GILLETTE: Well you're not! Using the map!
ARCHER: Okay!
Jesus...
CYRIL: Wh-?
Noooo no no no no!
ARCHER: Well it's this or the map, so...
GILLETTE: Great, we'll just tell
him his money's out in the
desert covered with shit.
ARCHER: There's still
ninety-five grand in the bag!
And if what's-his-name...
CYRIL: Gorbagun Gorbanguly.
ARCHER: Really?
CYRIL: Yes, really.
And you can have a hundred.
ARCHER: What?
Cyril, since what, Monday, I've
had nothing but ouzo and lamb.
C'mon, I need at least a thousand.
CYRIL: Three hundred.
ARCHER: Oh for -- eight hundred!
CYRIL: Five.
ARCHER: Seven!
CYRIL: Seven, and you dig out the jeep.
ARCHER: Okay, deal.
But I take the map.
CYRIL: No! We just went over --
ARCHER: To read!
Now c'mon, hurry up!
The lambs are screaming!
CYRIL: Hey be careful,
there might be snakes!
ARCHER: Not even gonna swing at that one.
CYRIL: Ha ha.
I'm talking about cobras.
ARCHER: What do you know
about cobras, Cyril?
CYRIL: I know the Caspian
cobra, which is indigenous to
Turkmenistan, is often light
brown with darker ventral bands.
ARCHER: Well goody, you win...
cobra-knowing.
GILLETTE: Dukes, it's gonna be dark soon.
How far is it?
CYRIL: I dunno, I need to look
at the -- God damn it, Archer!
ARCHER: What, I said I needed a thousand!
Bet three hundred bucks seems pretty
cheap for a map right about nyowwww!
So hey, so yeah, did you say light
brown with darker whateveral bands?
CYRIL: Ventral bands, on -- wait, why?
ARCHER: Eh.
Just curious.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
MALORY: "Curious"
meaning what, exactly?
LANA: Uh, meaning odd or strange?
MALORY: First of all, Turkmenistan isn't--
LANA: Or how about just sexist
and stupi --
MALORY: Enough!
Please, we've talked about this,
it's not even eight-thirty.
Let me get settled before you clomp
in here in one of your jealous snits.
LANA: One of my -- wait, whoa, clomp?
MALORY: Yes, Lana, clomp, meaning--
LANA: I know what clomp means!
PAM: Your clompin' ass oughta know...
LANA: Wh-?
PAM: Seriously, I bet your
downstairs neighbors hate you.
LANA: For your information.
The Flatows are always
incredibly polite to me.
PAM: That's because the Flatows think
they live under a frickin AT-AT.
CHERYL/CAROL: Zhwizz-clonk!
Zhwizz-clonk!
Zhwizz --
LANA: Okay!
MALORY: Whereas this one, almost
impossibly light on her feet.
It's like... if you've ever
seen Jackie Gleason dance.
PAM: So, is that a compliment, or --
MALORY: I don't see how
it possibly could be.
PAM: Okay.
MALORY: Nor do I see how
you could possibly think
that you're at all suited to a
covert mission in Turkmenistan.
LANA: Why, because I'm black,
or because I'm a woman?
MALORY: Wh-?
Pick one!
I mean look, I don't want
to sound racist, but --
LANA: But you're gonna power through it.
MALORY: Not about you,
about Turkmenistan!
Lana, this is a Central Asian,
maledominated, xenophobic
puppet-state whose dictator
changed the words for bread and
Friday to his dog's name.
CHERYL/CAROL: Gurpgork.
MALORY: Yes, Gurpgor --
how did you know that?
CHERYL/CAROL: Oh my God
how did I know that?!
PAM: Okay.
MALORY: And all that crazy is
sitting on top of an ocean of
oil and natural gas.
Making this pipeline crucial
to the Russians, which is why
we're paying Gurbanguly to...
hinder construction.
LANA: Wh-? Wait, so now we're paying
people to blow up oil pipelines?!
MALORY: See? Another
reason I didn't send you.
LANA: What, the environment?!
MALORY: Of what, this litterbox?
Or Western Europe?
Because T-72 tanks aren't exactly
known for their low emissions.
LANA: I want it officially
on record that I am strongly
opposed to this mission.
MALORY: What record?
PAM: Aww, can I at least put
something in the newsletter?
MALORY: Wh-?
You're not still doing that?!
PAM: No?
ARCHER: Yes!
GILLETTE: No!
ARCHER: Please!
Just pretend I'm -- who's your
go-to movie star, ya know, for --
GILLETTE: Lorne Greene.
ARCHER: Wow.
GILLETTE: Yeah.
ARCHER: Bonanza or Battlestar?
GILLETTE: Duh.
So, I come to the Ponderosa
looking for ranch work, but my
chaps get torn and Hop Sing --
ARCHER: Ray?
Time's kind of a factor here.
GILLETTE: I am not. Ever.
Sucking your taint.
ARCHER: Okay, so Cyril...
Better chapstick it up, buddy.
CYRIL: First of all, not only
does sucking out the venom not
help the snakebite victim,
it can also envenom the --
ARCHER: Taint-sucker,
that's you, let's go.
CYRIL: And second of all, the
venom's not there anymore, it's
pumping through your veins
to your heart and brain.
ARCHER: My -- well put
a tourniquet on me!
GILLETTE: You can't tourniquet the taint.
ARCHER: But -- wait is
my dick gonna be okay?!
CYRIL: Well the danger there is cytotoxins,
which can cause severe necrosis.
ARCHER: Nec -- so my
dick's gonna fall off?!
CYRIL: Maybe.
ARCHER: Aaagh!
CYRIL: But the bigger danger
is the neuro and cardiotoxins,
which can cause respiratory
failure, cardiac arrest --
ARCHER: Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaagh!
CYRIL: So the most important
thing is for you to stay calm.
GILLETTE: Ew.
CYRIL: Oh boy...
ARCHER: What, that's good right?
If my body's throwing up the poison?
CYRIL: It might be.
If you had drunk it.
ARCHER: Jesus H. Thirst, speaking of...
Ray, back pocket down there, flask.
CYRIL: Wh-?
No, alcohol's a vasodilator!
It's the absolute worst possible
thing you can do for a snakebite!
ARCHER: Well maybe for regular people.
CYRIL: ...?!
ARCHER: Cyril, it's already full
of cobra venom, now's not the
time for any more chemical
changes to my blood!
CYRIL: Okay, give it to him.
ARCHER: Wh-? Gimme that!
GILLETTE: Here, baby.
ARCHER: It's half empty!
CYRIL: That's still way more than you--
ARCHER: Just shut up and -- Dig.
I'm not doing super great.
CYRIL: Well I could use some help!
ARCHER: I would, but I
can't feel my hands.
CYRIL: I meant Ray!
Who's just standing there...
Ray, dammit, on bionic legs!
GILLETTE: Oh right.
ARCHER: God damn it, Ray!
GILLETTE: I forgot!
ARCHER: How do you forget
you have bionic legs?!
GILLETTE: I, ya know, are you constantly
aware you have regular leg bones?!
No, you're --
ARCHER: Just pick up the goddamn jeep!
GILLETTE: He said, suddenly all...
pro-bionic.
Okay, on three.
One, two, threeaagh!
CYRIL: Ray?
ARCHER: What is that,
what're you doing?!
GILLETTE: My back my back my back my back...
ARCHER: Are you shitting me?!
Bionic legs, and you
lifted with your back?!
Cyril, my gun's in the gear bag,
could you hand it to me, please?
CYRIL: To... use as a signal?
ARCHER: Yeah, maybe.
If there's any bullets left
after I murder both of you.
CYRIL: Wh-?
Why me?!
ARCHER: It's number two
on my bucket list.
CYRIL: What's number one?
ARCHER: Going to one of those
things where they make some
record-breakingly huge kind of food, like
a frittata the size of a hockey rink.
And then eating a piece, and then
laughing, because I murdered you.
MALORY: Krieger, I need you
to -- Krieger, Krieger?
KRIEGER: Yep! Yep yep yep!
MALORY: Whatever unspeakable thing
you're doing back there can wait --
KRIEGER: Well, you say that...
MALORY: Yes I do, and I just
did, so come on, I need
you in the control room.
Because they should
have checked in by now.
So keep trying to reach them
on the sat-phone, and if that
doesn't work try to get satellite
photos on the next pass.
And not a word of this to
anyone, especially -- Lanaaa!
I thought I heard
self-righteous clomping.
Can I help you?
LANA: Funny, I was just
gonna ask you that.
MALORY: No, we're fine.
Aren't we, Krieger?
KRIEGER: Yes?
LANA: So, the mission?
Going as planned?
MALORY: Yes, as a matter of fact
they just this minute checked in.
All good.
LANA: Uh-huh.
MALORY: "Uh-huh."
Ugh, have you ever heard such
a superior, know-it-all tone?
KRIEGER: Oh, you're serious?
GILLETTE: Yes!
CYRIL: No!
GILLETTE: Cyril!
I can't move, Archer's... Oh.
Well, very nearly dead, so --
CYRIL: I'm not calling for an extraction!
GILLETTE: Look, just because
Lana makes you feel insecure in
your masculinity --
CYRIL: Mascu -- look who's talking!
GILLETTE: Oh for -- Cyril, when I
was ten years old I killed a bear.
CYRIL: Nuh-uh... really?
GILLETTE: With a bow.
And then Daddy made me take a
big ol' bite out of its heart.
CYRIL: Oh my God!
That is... horrible!
GILLETTE: No shit, I was
bawling my eyes out.
But he kept slapping me until I did it.
CYRIL: Jesus...
ARCHER: Seriously.
No wonder you're gay.
And Cyril if you call ISIS, I will
literally literally, murder you alright.
I'd rather die than sit through another
one of Lana's big "I told you so's."
At least you get to bang her.
GILLETTE: Well, you seem
to be feeling better.
ARCHER: Hang on.
Gay-vy Crockett, boom, nailed it.
But no, I'm pretty sure I'm dying.
GILLETTE: So since you're too pussy
to call for an extraction...
CYRIL: I'm digging, I'm digging!
ARCHER: Well wait, hang on.
Because unless I'm hallucinating...
There's a Landcruiser over there
flipping his highbeams at us.
BOTH: You're hallucinating.
ARCHER: Oh.
Well the good news is, we don't have
to worry about these alligators.
That's not actually good news, is it.
CYRIL: No.
No it is not.
ARCHER: Okay... later, gator!
JAMES MASON: No no no no no,
what is the meaning of this?!
ESCORT: I'm sorry, James Mason!
But he just won't stop
tooting that darn tooter!
JAMES MASON: Mr. Archer, I'm
afraid I must ask you to cease
your insufferable tooting--
This instant.
ARCHER: Fine by me.
I hate opera.
Almost as much as I hate hoodies,
what the hell's going on here?
JAMES MASON: Oh no, not hell,
Mr. Archer, this is --
ARCHER: Hey. Cut-rate James Mason.
I got kicked out of
Episcopal prep school.
Twice.
So if there is a heaven --
JAMES MASON: Oh, I'm sorry, nor is this heaven.
ARCHER: Well no, obviously it's not heaven --
JAMES MASON: No, it's a --
ARCHER: -- because Janis Joplin's
not giving me a rim job.
JAMES MASON: Way station,
I beg your pardon?
ARCHER: Right?
Sorry, a cobra bit my taint.
JAMES MASON: Yes.
ARCHER: I'm not myself.
JAMES MASON: Aren't you?
ARCHER: Are I?
JAMES MASON: Are you, indeed.
Would you like to know who
Sterling Archer really is?
ARCHER: No?
LANA: Why not?
Why won't you guys stand up to Malory
with me about blowing up the pipeline?
PAM: Mmmmmmmmmmmcuz we don't give a shit?
LANA: About the earth?!
CHERYL/CAROL: Oh please, if you
really cared you'd resign, but
there's no way you ever will
because you're just counting
the days until, her face bloated
and yellow from liver failure,
she calls you to her deathbed
and, in a croaky whisper,
explains that Mr. Archer is
totally incompetent and that
you, the long-suffering
Lana Kane, are the only one
qualified to run ISIS, and you
weep shameful tears, because
you know this terrible place is the
only true love you will ever know.
LANA: Excuse me.
PAM: Daaamn...
CHERYL/CAROL: What?
Oh my God, was I talking?
CYRIL: Who the... hell is he...
talking to?
ARCHER: James Mason...
CYRIL: Oh.
GILLETTE: Maybe that's his Lorne Greene.
ARCHER: James Mason, why
are we in Baltimore?!
JAMES MASON: I thought you might
like some insight into how you
became the man you are.
ARCHER: No, I would absolutely
not like some --
JAMES MASON: Sterling Archer,
age eighteen..
ARCHER: The most recruited
prep school lacrosse player in America...
JAMES MASON: Visiting
Baltimore for the weekend, to decide if
he will accept a full athletic
scholarship to Johns Hopkins.
ARCHER: Whooooo!
Yeah, so we don't need to see how...
JAMES MASON: At a stop on the
train ride from New York you
struck out the major league
homerun champion, Slammer Sloan.
ARCHER: Whooooo!
ARCHER: Well obviously, I was awesome, but I--
JAMES MASON: Drew the attention
of a beautiful woman named
Ruth Ann Litzenberger... Qui tait, vraiment,
une femme fatale.
And who followed you here, to
this very hotel in Baltimore,
and sent you a note, to come to her room...
ARCHER: Look, seriously -- Woooooo!
Wait, how did you know I was
staying -- What's going on here?
RUTH ANN: Sterling?
Will you be the best there
ever was in the game?
ARCHER: Wh-?!
YOUNG ARCHER: Uh...
ARCHER: Noooo!
YOUNG ARCHER: Duh.
ARCHER: Yeah, sooo... I don't know if
you're deaf or just an asshole or both,
but I'm pretty sure I said
I didn't wanna see this.
JAMES MASON: But Sterling, do
you not see how the actions of
a deeply disturbed woman have
profoundly influenced your life?
ARCHER: Well obviously!
I mean -- Oh, you mean my lacrosse
career ending because a crazy stalker
gut-shot me.
JAMES MASON: Do I?
ARCHER: I don't know, James Mason!
Do you?!
Besides, what freakin' movie is this?
What's next, Mr. Gower slaps me deaf?!
C'mon, you're all over the road here!
CYRIL: Well?!
ARCHER: Well what?!
CYRIL: I'm doing the best I can!
GILLETTE: If that's the
best you can do -- gaagh!
Just kill your -- gaagh!
Wh-?
Are you bouncing on purpose?!
CYRIL: No, I'm trying to get
Archer to whatever passes for a
doctor around here before it's too late!
ARCHER: Sounds like a plan, James Mason.
CYRIL: And maybe if you shut up I can
concentrate on the rowaaaghhhhh!
GILLETTE: Gaagh!
What the shit was that?!
CYRIL: A camel.
GILLETTE: Well great, now we've
both killed a large animal!
Drive around it!
CYRIL: I, uh... don't
think that's an option.
ARCHER: Hey check it out, Fred and Barney,
we're at the Water Buffalo Lodge!
MALORY: Krieger, any word from Sterling?
KRIEGER: Yep!
Yep yep yep!
MALORY: Well?
What did they say?
KRIEGER: Oh.
I mean nope. Nope nope nope.
MALORY: [annoyed sigh]
KRIEGER: But, ya know,
I'm sure they're fine.
CYRIL: Wait, no!
I had the right of way!
GILLETTE: Gaagh!
GILLETTE: Seriously, I get that
you're upset but I think I have
a pinched nnngghhh!
GILLETTE: Gaaagh!
CYRIL: Now just a darn minute!
We're Americ -- Hello...
GILLETTE: Yeah.
Way to not call it in.
JAMES MASON: I beg your pardon?
ARCHER: Yeah, you should.
And I'm outta here.
JAMES MASON: I'm afraid
that isn't possible.
ARCHER: Oh really?
And why is --
AMBULANCE DRIVER: Comin through!
C'mon, make a hole!
YOUNG ARCHER: Phrasing, boom.
ARCHER: Boom.
Scholarship to Johns Hopkins.
JAMES MASON: Mmm.
Bit of a moot point though,
really, given your SAT scores.
ARCHER: Goodbye, James Mason.
JAMES MASON: No, you -- Mr. Archer, wait!
CYRIL: Please, here!
Here's forty-three hundred dollars,
surely that's enough for a camel.
TURKMEN CHIEF: Ah, baksheesh!
CYRIL: Baksheesh, exactly, but our friend...
okay, snake is...
oh, okay, so "Our friend was bitten
by a snake" is... Ozum jora?
Bishlemek gurpgork?
TURKMEN CHIEF: Etmek bishlemek gurpgork.
CYRIL: Wh-?
No, no!
I mean... Yok,yok.
JAMES MASON: No, no!
JAMES MASON: Mr. Archer, please!
ARCHER: You please, cut-rate James Mason!
And then shut up, because I'm going...
ARCHER: Home.
Goddammit.
Or... what is it?
CYRIL: Gurpgork!
TURKMEN CHIEF: Ah!
Gowushmak eshek gurpgork!
CYRIL: Wh-?
No!
Yok!
Not that Gurpgork!
(Makes claw, growls) Rawr, rawr!
TURKMEN CHIEF: Ah, Gurpgork!
Patysha alabai!
TURKMENI: Ah, Gurpgork!
Hawa hawa! Gurpgork!
TURKMEN CHIEF: Gurpgork.
CYRIL: [deeply weary sigh]
GILLETTE: How's it the same word
for bread and snake and Friday
and that damn dog?!
CYRIL: How the hell should I know?!
MALORY: Because you have an entire satellite
array at your disposal, you idiot!
KRIEGER: Yeah, I don't actually
know how any of this works.
MALORY: But --
KRIEGER: That was the fat guy, you killed.
LANA: Oh, and just so you know?
I do know what true love is, so... yeah.
MALORY: What in God's
name was that about?
KRIEGER: She'd probably ruin the wedding.
ARCHER: Come on, what the hell is this?
JAMES MASON: I thought you'd
like to see something.
ARCHER: I've seen poverty, I've been to...
oh, how's it going in Turkmenistan?
JAMES MASON: Mmmmm, not great.
TURKMENI [excited chattering]
GILLETTE: Cyril, just draw a snake!
CYRIL: Oh right.
CYRIL: Okay, uh... doo doo doo...
elliptical head, oblique dorsal
scales, symmetric sub-caudal scalation,
darker ventral bands, obviously...
okay, here we go.
CYRIL: Wh-?
What is wrong with you people?!
GILLETTE: What's wrong with you?
Gimme that!
GILLETTE: Here! Tada. A Snake!
CYRIL: Oh that's crap...
TURKMENI [alarmed gasp]
TURKMEN CHIEF: Gurpgork?!
Dishlemek gurpgork?!
CYRIL: I -- wanna say duh, but...
ARCHER: What's the point?
ARCHER: C'mon, this is stupid, I don't
need to see this, I remember all of it.
JAMES MASON: Do you?
CHILD ARCHER: Yeah...
ARCHER: Yeah I mean, that's me, I'm like... Six.
I'm six today, it's my birthday.
JAMES MASON: And your
Mother isn't home, is she?
ARCHER: No, she had to -- look,
Guatemala's democratically
elected government wasn't
gonna overthrow itself.
JAMES MASON: Mmm.
And with Woodhouse, shall we
say, indisposed...
WOODHOUSE: [heroin-induced snoring]
JAMES MASON: There was no one
to give you a birthday present.
ARCHER: I... wait, no, yeah, I got...
TURKMEN CHIEF: Derman!
Derman gurpgork!
Derman gurpgork etmek!
GILLETTE: No, I don't think
he can keep bread down...
CYRIL: No, I think it's--
Derman is medicine!
TURKMEN CHIEF: Derman gurpgork!
CYRIL: I think it's antivenom! Gimme!
TURKMEN CHIEF: Yok, yok!
Kop kop kop baksheesh.
CYRIL: Oh.
He wants a lot lot lot of money.
GILLETTE: So?
We've got ninety-five grand!
CYRIL: But that's for the mission, to --
GILLETTE: Blow up a
frickin oil pipeline?
CYRIL: Wait, really?
GILLETTE: Cyril, what did you think
she meant by "hinder construction?"
CYRIL: Oh.
Do you ever think maybe we're
kinda not always a hundred
percent of the time
doing the right thing?
GILLETTE: Do you ever shut
up and give that man-bear
twenty-five grand so you and I
can split the other seventy?
CYRIL: Yes, yes I do.
ARCHER: I got a... yeah,
I got an alligator!
CHILD ARCHER: [tiny gasp]
MYSTERY MAN: Hello, Sterling.
MYSTERY MAN: Your mother doesn't
know I'm here, but I wanted to
bring you a birthday present.
I hope you like alligators.
CHILD ARCHER: I do...
ARCHER: I did...
CHILD ARCHER: Thank you, sir.
But... who are you?
MYSTERY MAN: Sterling, I...
am your real father.
CHILD ARCHER: [small gasp]
ARCHER: [huge gasp]
CYRIL: Archer?
ARCHER: Buck Henry?
Oh my God, Cyril! Ray! I know --
CYRIL: You're okay!
Hey, we gave you the antivenom.
Cyril, shut your dickhole.
Jesus, God.
I know who my real father was.
Well? Who was he?
He...was...ugh...
Now it's gone.
God dammit.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com