[snoring]
Aw, she looks so peaceful.
Think she's dreaming that
she's not overstaying her welcome?
When she got that wine delivered
to the house,
I thought that was her thank-you present,
that she was leaving,
-but then she just drank the wine.
-Five days ago.
-Morning, everybody.
-Aah! Kinko!
Another beautiful day
in the city of Brotherly Angels.
Todd, I don't recall
accidentally ingesting poison,
and yet here you are
trying to make me vomit.
You wanna go buy me a kite
and then fly a kite?
No. Kites are sky trash.
[groans]
Why is it so daytime right now?
Wanda?
[groaning]
Wanna go surf some cloud waves?
That's what I call wind.
Sorry. Some of us have jobs.
Not all of us. Just some of us.
Oh, yeah, my job.
-Morning.
-[J.D.] What?
I'm done with my sabbatical
and I'm ready to get back to work.
What sabbatical? I fired you.
Oh, I thought
when you said, "You're fired,"
that was just you
"giving me the business."
No, I was taking the "business"
away from you.
Oh.
Hey, Mr. Peanutbutter.
You wanna go fly a kite?
Put me down
for a supersized "sounds great."
But with an even larger main course
of "sadly, I cannot."
I am swamped here at work.
First, I gotta put my suit on.
Then I gotta go to hair and makeup.
Then we record the show.
And then I gotta take my suit off.
So, that's, like, the whole day. Sorry.
[groans]
Ah.
"Looking for a friend?"
Yes.
"Need direction?"
I'm listening.
"Try Scientology"?
-Huh.
-Excuse me? Sir?
-Huh?
-Have you ever thought
about trying improv comedy?
Improv comedy? I don't know...
Why not?
It's not like there's anything else to do.
Here on Mars.
We're on Mars?
Yes. And in a Martian ice cream shop.
Care for a butterscotch swirl?
Whoa!
The only limit is my imagination.
Why not come by our theater
and try a free class?
Okay!
Can I bring this food inside the theater?
Ha, good one.
-But no.
-Oh.
[♪♪]
"That's when I learned
that guns can blow a vato away.
But calculus?
Calculus can blow a mind away."
[Abe] Cut!
We got it!
That's the day, everybody.
[slurping]
-You sure we got it, Abe?
-Of course. You were phenomenal.
Really? Because that kid sneezed
in the middle of my monologue.
-We can fix that in post.
-Abe, I'm supposed to tell you
the boom mike fell into the last shot.
You sure you don't wanna get another take?
Just for safety?
What am I, Kubrick?
We can fix all this stuff in post.
It's an easy scene.
Secretariat's a nice guy,
the Spanish kids learn a lesson.
Boom. Bam! Done!
But Secretariat never actually taught math
in South Central.
I don't know what Secretariat did
or didn't do. I wasn't there.
-Yeah, but--
-Okay, so the studio wants gangbangers,
we'll give them gangbangers.
-We get paid either way, right?
-I guess.
I can't wait to get home.
I got a coq au vin in the slow cooker.
You like coq au vin?
I think so. Is that the move
where a French girl pours soup in--
Come over for dinner, okay?
-You'll love it.
-Okay.
Chin up, big guy.
So, we ain't making Casablanca.
[slurping]
-BoJack. Shut up.
-Aah! What are you--?
No one can know I'm here.
-What?
-Shut your stupid mouth, you idiot.
As you know, you're my favorite client.
If I left Vigor,
would you follow me to a new agency?
Sure, but no one's gonna hire me
after this movie comes out.
The script turned into a piece of shit,
and the director is a total hack.
Good guy, total hack.
Let's get you something
before the movie comes out.
We got an offer in for this new play
off-Broadway.
Theater? That's what real actors do.
Yeah, I told them that,
but they said she wanted you.
-She?
-Yeah, this hot new playwright Jill Pill.
-She came out of nowhere.
-Jill Pill?
New York Magazine called her
the enfant terrible
of the immersive theater world,
and then later clarified
that that's a compliment.
It sounds like the kind of thing
I should be doing now.
-Something artistic and bold.
-Rehearsals start in two weeks.
Are you ready to go to New York
for six months?
New York's a great city to live in
for six months
and not a second longer and only
if you're insanely wealthy. I can't wait!
Now, that's a lot of apple sauce.
[all] Apple sauce!
Oh-ho!
That was so funny.
Which one of you guys
wrote all those funny jokes?
No, Todd, here at Shenanigags,
we make things up on the spot.
-Let's try it. Give me a suggestion.
-Uh... I don't know.
Suggestions?
[all laughing]
Your suggestion was "suggestions."
-Way to break the fourth wall.
-That wasn't that funny.
My name's Bryan
and you haven't won me over yet.
-Oh, Bryan.
-Todd, in improv,
we get suggestions from an audience
then make up scenes based on them.
There are just a few simple rules.
You don't ask questions. You don't say no.
No matter what. When someone makes a
suggestion, you always try to build on it.
We call that "yes, and..."
Yes, and if you mess up, that's okay.
It's all part of the fun.
Is it really that simple?
Ugh! It's incredibly complicated
and requires years of training.
Oh, Bryan.
[all laughing]
But improv isn't just about a constant
clamoring for attention and validation.
It's about community.
I've always wanted to be part
of a community.
Well, you are now.
Your first class is $200.
I thought you said it was free.
Oh, that was just me doing an improv.
I am so proud of you.
Every day I'm telling people all about
the great stuff you're doing there.
-Yeah, I don't know--
-And they say, "Wow, she sounds amazing."
And I say, "I'm here to confirm
she is an incredible woman."
-Well--
-You know, the sound guy's wife
works with at-risk teens.
And I was like, "Yeah, that's okay,
but compared to what my wife is doing,
-your wife is bullshit!"
-Oh.
And he had to agree with me.
-Um--
-Because I am his boss.
-Listen--
-Let me talk to one of the locals.
I wanna hear someone else talk
about how what a selfless hero my wife is.
-Oh, uh...
-Ah, now come on.
-Most refugees got their tongues cut out.
-Find one with a tongue.
-I don't think--
-Indulge me.
Okay.
[in softer voice]
Hello. I am refugee from village.
Hey, what's your name, Superstar?
Uh, my name is...
Coffee Maker.
[groans]
Ah. Kofi Makir.
Am I pronouncing that right?
Hey, Todd, you had some killer provs
in class today.
Yes, and that zombie dentist scene
was so innovative.
Eh...
-Oh, Bryan.
-Guys, look.
It's Copernicus.
[all gasp]
-Who's that?
-What are you, new?
Yes, I am new.
Copernicus is the founder of Shenanigags.
That guy is the Jan-Ove Waldner
of modern improv.
-Who is Jan-Ove Waldner?
-The Michael Jordan of table tennis.
Oh.
-Let's go talk to him.
-Are you kidding?
You can't just go up and talk
to Copernicus.
Man, Todd, you don't know shit.
You're just a tourist.
No, I'm not.
If you're one of us, prove it.
Go improv that lady over there.
Freestyle.
No audience, no net.
-I don't know...
-Hey, if you're down with the prov,
you gotta prove that prov.
All right. I'll do it.
-Hello, old ma'am.
-Oh, hello.
I'm just waiting for my friend Doris.
Have you seen her?
Yes,
and she exploded?
Doris exploded?
-You just got prov'd!
-In your face, lady!
The streets are ours!
-Hurray, improv! I did it!
-You have briefly won me over.
Poor Doris...
That is not what I thought coq au vin was.
But it's great.
Well, I'm no Emeril Lagasse,
but we do get by.
-Oh, stop. [laughs]
-Bam!
Like Emeril? Ha, remember that?
He said "bam."
I don't know who Emeril is,
but he sounds delightful.
Hey, should I give him a sitcom?
BoJack, Abe tells me
you guys are almost done with the movie.
One week left!
You two lovebirds gonna do
any traveling or anything?
I'll be traveling back and forth
to New York for the next few months
because BoJack's doing a play there
after you finish.
-Oh, I love plays.
-A play.
That's my favorite place
to eat crinkly candies.
Yeah, I can't wait to finally work
on something good, you know?
Oh?
Although I gotta hand it to your husband.
It has been a really painless shoot,
even though the movie's gonna be
a piece of shit, right?
-What?
-Oh, you said "piece of ship," right?
Like shipshape? [giggles]
Anyway, what were we talking about?
Who knows?
-Okay, moving on.
-Hey, it's fine.
Abe knows what we're making.
Right?
[Abe slurps]
-Wanda, would you help me with dessert?
-Uh, okay.
Yeah.
New York is so great in the summer,
but I don't think
we're going to be done in time.
We're looking at a ton of reshoots.
-Are you kidding?
-Well, you know,
because the movie's such a piece of shit
and all.
Did that hurt your feelings?
I mean, you're the one who said
we're not making Casablanca.
Right, because Casablanca is a movie
about a club owner named Rick.
This movie's about Secretariat,
a racehorse.
Wait, you literally meant we're not making
the actual movie Casablanca?
That movie already exists.
Why would we make Casablanca?
-This is a different movie.
-I think there was a misunderstanding.
Wrong, boy-o.
There was a mister-understanding.
And that mister is me
understanding you just fine.
You come into my home
and you call my work shit?
-You know what I think? You're shit.
-What?
You think I don't get enough takes?
I'll get more takes.
Just wait, see how many takes I can get.
Well, don't go.
We haven't had dessert yet.
Shirley's lemon meringue? Mwah.
I mean, it's no banana cream pie.
Because it's a different kind of pie?
[slurs] That's right.
Why did you have to antagonize him?
I wasn't trying to antagonize him.
-He said, "It's no Casablanca."
-Well, what's done is done.
You're happy.
You didn't want me to go to New York.
Lucky me, I get to stay here
and work on this movie
that's gonna ruin my career.
There's no reason to sulk about it, right?
Or you could sulk about it.
Diane does raise some good points.
No, she doesn't.
Besides, I don't think Diane's the person
you wanna be going to for life advice now.
Why? Just because I've been drinking
myself to sleep on your deck chairs
and lying to my husband for the last week?
Hey, there's a Cheez-It on the shelf.
I knew I kept these things around
for a reason.
-I just had the most amazing prov sesh.
-No one cares, Todd.
Hey, you guys wanna help me practice?
Make a suggestion.
-Stop.
-Aah. Sorry, officer,
I didn't see that stop sign.
Yes.
And my car runs on farts.
-[Todd mimics farting]
-[Wanda] Ugh!
-Stop. No, stop it.
-Please stop.
Not a suggestion.
[mimics farting]
Okay.
I just hope I impress the elder council.
I want to become a Level Two,
so I can finally achieve clarity
on the Mainstage with the chosen ones.
Oh, shit, Todd's in a cult.
What? No, improv is not a cult.
It's just a dogmatic school of thought
taught by a for-profit organization
with the promise of social
and professional opportunities.
-Ahh.
-It's a cult. And I know.
I learned a little about cults
during that year I was a Scientologist.
Coincidentally during that year,
I read a book about cults.
Wait, are you saying
Scientology is a cult?
No, Scientology is not a cult.
Improv is a cult.
I wanna be very clear.
This is about improv.
-I really don't think it's that bad, guys.
-Why does anything matter, right?
Love is an illusion,
and happiness is fleeting,
no such thing as God, and all your
favorite musicians beat their wives.
Allegedly.
Would you talk to her?
[sighs] Yes.
Yes, and I am a Nazi Kardashian.
Heyyy... Hitler.
Please stop.
[panting]
President Lohan!
Get away from that fire hose!
[all] Fire hose!
[grunts] Sorry I'm late, guys!
Todd, we take tardiness seriously here
at Shenanigags.
-If you miss one more class, you're out.
-I'm sorry. But, wait, Bryan isn't here.
-He's later than I am.
-Bryan's not gonna be at practice anymore.
He's been negative, so Copernicus thought
he could benefit from some time away.
He's been reassigned to the Shenanigags
comedy cruise line, the Giggleship.
-Is that a reward or a punishment?
-That's up to Bryan.
Let's have no more questions
about the Giggleship.
Oh, uh, all right.
Well, you know,
I was actually talking to my best friend,
and he said improv is a cult.
I mean, that's crazy, right?
[all laughing]
[coughs]
If you think Shenanigags is a cult,
you're free to go, Todd.
Oh, no. I don't wanna go.
I love this place.
My friend just doesn't know
how great you guys are.
It sounds like your friend's
not yes-and'ing you.
Invite him to your graduation show.
If he's too negative to support you,
you should take a good hard think
about if that's the kind of energy
you want in your life.
[groans] I hate good hard thinks.
I love you, too, Mr. Peanutbutter.
But I-- I gotta go.
I'm--
Yeah, I'm building a school for deaf kids.
The kids get jealous
if I'm talking on the phone.
Uh, okay, bye.
So, hey, hi.
How long are you thinking of staying here?
Just for my own reference.
Oh, shit.
Is Wanda making you get rid of me?
No one is making me do anything.
Except keep acting in this movie you hate.
Well, yeah.
I really thought I could do it. I thought
I could go far away and help people
and be this best possible version
of myself.
And what happened?
I couldn't.
I wasn't the person I thought I was.
I'd love to stay and wallow with you,
but I gotta head out.
Today we're filming what used to be the
scene where Secretariat commits suicide,
but is now a scene where he swims
in a fishing hole
-with his girlfriend "Susie Side."
-Yeesh.
If you wanna blow off work,
I'm probably just gonna sit on the couch,
drink beer, and watch old episodes
of Horsin' Around.
Hmm.
[audience laughs]
And if I hear one more peep out of you--
-[crashing]
-[audience laughs]
-Sabrina!
-[Sabrina] What? I didn't peep!
Oh!
[audience applauding]
Sabrina was such a little bitch.
She was an orphan. She had a tough life.
Hey, Diane, you're still here.
And BoJack is here.
Did you go to work today?
I was gonna, but then I remembered
everything is garbage,
so why bother doing anything?
-True story.
-Okay.
[the horse] Oh, you didn't.
[audience laughing]
Oh, you did.
[sitcom theme plays over TV]
-Hello.
-Hey, could you get the door?
-Whoa.
-Mm.
The property's gonna be ready in June.
Gives us two months
to get everything we need
out of this place.
Mm. Perfect.
Just so you know, I had to register
the corporation in your name.
-What?
-Just until the divorce is finalized.
Katie's lawyers are watching me closely
right now.
They're hawks.
I mean, not literally.
Well, one literally.
Know what, actually, he might be a falcon.
Rutabaga, this is too--
This is a temporary technicality,
I promise.
I'm not gonna leave you holding the bag.
Okay?
Mm. Mm.
Hey, your assistant wasn't out there,
so I just-- Ooh.
-Oh, hello.
-Look at this urn.
What's going on in here?
Mr. Peanutbutter, shut the door.
Rutabaga and I are starting a new agency,
and we want you to come with us.
Well, well, well, what delicious irony.
It appears the cat is chasing the dog.
Are you in or out?
Are you kidding?
You're the agent who got me
Hollywoo Stars and Celebrities.
-Well--
-What do they know?
-Right, so--
-Do they know things?
-Okay--
-Let's find out.
-Right--
-Big fan.
I like you guys.
I like your hustle
and I like your matching lipstick.
-Well, um--
-I am in.
Mm-hm.
Go home, Goober.
Yeah! Go home, Goober!
[coughs] Goober sucks.
Why doesn't he ever go home?
Yeah, Goober's the one who should go home.
-You suck, Goober!
-Hey, Goober! Get murdered!
Go sit on a sharp dick, you piece of shit.
-Hey, guys.
-Shut up, Todd.
BoJack, listen, I-- Oh!
-Hey, whoa!
-Boo! Party foul!
-You knocked over Bucking-can Palace.
-Come on!
Uh, sorry, I'll clean that up later.
Listen to this guy, "clean it up later."
Hasn't picked up his shit in years.
Clean up your shit, Todd.
BoJack, I wanted to invite you
to my graduation show tomorrow night.
-What?
-Look, I know you think
it's just a dumb cult,
but you're my best friend
and it would really mean a lot
if you came.
[groans] I'm gonna go down to the basement
to practice my space work.
And here I am going downstairs.
[cell phone ringing]
Hello?
-What kind of pants are you wearing now?
-What? I don't know. The normal kind.
Yeah? Mm. Are they comfy?
A comfy pair of pants?
I guess. Why?
Just wondering
what kind of hit you're gonna take
when the studio sues the pants off you
for breach of contract.
They're suing me?
Also, are you wearing comfortable shoes?
Because that was a long road to walk
to get to that punch line.
-This is serious.
-We're not just doing bits?
You started it with the pants thing.
You need to go back to set.
You can't just not go to work.
[sighs]
Remember, you wanted this.
Are you saying you're finally ready
to settle down with yours truly?
Darn tootin'.
I may be a professional racehorse,
but I'm tired of running in circles.
[Abe] Cut!
Perfect.
But let's get that last part again.
-Anything you want me to do differently?
-No, I just think we should get it again.
You know, for safety.
-Action!
-I'm tired of running in circles.
[slurps] And again?
I'm tired of running in circles.
Why don't we get it like five more times?
[Abe] Let's get it ten more times.
[sighs]
-Ta-da!
-We did it.
-What now?
-We die, have our guts ripped out
through our noses,
and get enshrined inside of it. Duh.
Hey, BoJack,
can I talk to you for a minute?
Ooh...
Alone, please?
Oh...
So, good news. We're gonna go on a trip.
-Right now. You and me.
-What?
I booked us a room for the weekend.
Pack your bags, let's go.
Where? Why?
Less asking, more basking.
In the sun, that is. Santa Barbara.
-I'm not really in the mood for--
-I think some time away
could be really good for us, as a couple.
Oh.
I know you've been really bummed out
about the movie,
but I don't think moping around the house
with Diane all day is healthy.
All I've ever wanted
was to be in this movie,
and you just want me
to put on a happy face--
Yes. There are lots of people
who don't like their jobs.
Doesn't mean
they have to bring it home with--
-Yeah, that's easy for you to say.
-What is that supposed to mean?
Well, come on.
You're a network executive.
You don't give a shit about work.
I actually have a lot of pride
in what I do.
What? You have a lot of pride?
Your job is to pump out garbage every year
hoping some of the garbage
stinks less than the rest
so you can quietly renew that garbage
and keep failing sideways
until you retire
to a three-point-five bedroom garbage
in Beverly Garbage
and spend the rest of your life
-watching your former assistant's garbage.
-I don't know where this is coming from.
Every good thing
that ever happened to you happened
because of network executives like me.
That show you spend all day watching,
your house, your career--
Great house, great career, great life!
Must be why I'm so happy all the time!
-You don't know--
-I don't?
My life was ruined
by a network executive like you.
Well, I'm sorry
that things have been so hard for you,
but that doesn't give you the right to be
shitty to me. I can't be around someone
who's just fueled
by bitterness and negativity.
Well then, what are you doing here?
What happened, BoJack?
Same thing that always happens.
You didn't know me.
Then you fell in love with me.
And now you know me.
You know, it's funny. When you look
at someone through rose-colored glasses,
all the red flags just look like flags.
-So, Wanda's moving out.
-Oh, shit. Because of me?
No. Because of me.
I'm sorry. You wanna watch another episode
of Horsin' Around?
Where Olivia does the school project
where she pretends an egg is a baby.
Spoiler alert:
Ethan needs to make an omelet.
Why won't you go home?
I should. I know I should.
I wish I could just go home right now
and crawl into bed
and not have to talk about anything
or explain anything.
He would just say, "How was your day?"
And then he would say,
"Hey, did you know the monorail
was invented by George Monorail?"
And I would say,
"I don't think that's true."
And he would say, "Well, if he didn't
invent it, he certainly perfected it."
And I wouldn't have to say,
"I'm sorry I left.
I'm sorry I made things so difficult.
I'm sorry I'm not the person
I thought I was."
I would just say, "My day was good."
And he would say, "I love you."
The longer you keep lying to him,
the harder it's gonna get.
Can I ask you something?
That play in New York,
would that really have made you happy?
Yeah. I mean, for a little bit.
And if Kelsey didn't get fired,
and you got to make the movie
you wanted to make,
would that have made you happy?
For a little bit.
But then...
Probably...
So, what does it matter?
But there has to be more.
Well, when's the last time
you were actually happy?
You microchipped my penis? Check, please!
[all] Microchip.
[laughs]
Ah.
[audience applauding]
[sighs]
[doorbell rings]
Oh.
[all] Todd!
-[Todd groans]
-[all laughing]
[laughs] Yeah.
Oh.
Hey, Mr. Peanutbutter.
Hey. How are you?
I can't do this anymore.
You can't do what anymore?
I can't talk to you on the phone
all the time.
It's too hard.
Uh, have you tried Bluetooth?
I think maybe we should stop
calling each other, for a little bit.
I'm sorry. I just miss you too much.
But listen, I love you. Okay?
Mr. Peanutbutter?
Uh, yeah. Uh, okay.
I love you, Diane.
-Where is he?
-I don't know, sir.
Can't do this to me. Where the hell is he?
♪ If you come to find out who you are ♪
♪ And may you find out
May you find out who you are ♪
♪ And if you come to search
For what is love ♪
♪ Then may you find it
May you find it at any cost ♪
♪ Go now
You'll go, but don't just hide ♪
♪ Never leave this
Never leave this town ♪
♪ Of the parade ♪
Boxer versus raptor.
Na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na.