For tonight's final llusion
we have incredible sack of mystery.
When you put your money in
it mysteriously dissapears.
Well, of course! That makes perfect sense!
What a nice man! That was totaly worth a try!
The tiger was badly injured in the explosion
but we repaired him
with a fist.
Woo! Yeah! That tiger is our hero!
Tiger fist! will return after these messages.
Hey look! It's that commercial
I've been telling you guys about.
Are you completely miserable?
Yeees!
Then you need to meet Gideooon..
- Gideon?
- What makes him so special?
He's a psychic!
So don't waste your time with other
so called man of mystery.
at Gideon's tent of telepathy!
I'm getting all curiosy inside.
Well don't get too curiosy,
Ever since that monster Gideon
rolled in town, I've had nothing but trouble.
Gideon!
- Well, is he realy psychic?
- I think we should go and find out!
Never! You're forbiden from patronizing the competition!
Noone that lives under my roof
is allowed under that Gideon's roof.
- Do tents have roofs?
- I think we just found our loophole. Literaly.
So come down soon, folks.
Gideon is expecting you.
Gravity Falls
Episode 4 - The hand that rocks Mabel
Get right here folks!
Put your money in Gideon's psychick sack!
Oh sure! Wow!
That makes perfect sense!
Aww, this is like a bizzaro version of a Mystery shack.
They even have their own Soos.
It's starting, it's starting!
Let's see what this monster looks like.
Hello America!
My name is lil' Gideon!
That's Stan's mortal enemy?
Like.. he's so.. widdle.
Ladies and gentlemen, it is such a gift
to have you here tonight.
Such a gift.
I have a vision.
I predict, you'll soon all say..
- It came true!
- What? I'm not impresed.
You're impresed!
Hit it dad!
♪Oh I can see,
what others can't see!♪
♪It ain't some such old trick,
it's an natability.♪
♪Where others are blind,
I am futurely inclined.♪
♪and you too could see
the view that's widdle lil me!♪
Come on everybody! Round up!
I want you all to keep it going!
- What? How did he?
- Keep it going!
♪- You wish your son would call you more!♪
- I'm leaving everything to my cats!
♪- I sense that you've been here before!♪
- What gave it away?
Come oon.
♪I'll read your mind if I'm able♪
♪- Something tells me your name Mabel.♪
- How he do that?
♪So welcome all yeeee
to the tent of telepathy♪
♪and thanks for visiting
widdle ol' meee♪
Man, this kid is even
bigger fraud than Stan.
- No wonder our uncle is jealous.
- Oh come on, his dance moves were adorable
And did you see his hair? It was like wooosh.
- You're too easily impressed
- Yeah, yeah.
Check it out Dipper!
I succesfuly bezappled my face!
- Is that permanent?
- I'm on apreciating my time.
- Somebody answer that door!
- I'll get it!
- Howdy?
- It's widdle old you!
Yeah, my song is quite catchy.
I know we haven't formaly met.
but after yesterday's perfomance,
I just couldn't get your laugh out of my head.
You mean this one?
Aw, what a delight. And when I saw you in the
audience, I said to myself
now, there is a kindred spirit. Someone
who apreciates sparkly things of laugh.
That's totaly me!
Enchanting. Utterly enchanting.
- Who's at the door?
- Noone grunkle Stan!
I apreciate your discretion,
that Stan is no fan of mine.
I don't know how a lemon so sour
could be related to a peach so sweet.
- Gideon!
- What do you say, we step
away from here and chat a bit more.
Perhaps in my dressing room?
Makeovers!
Do you see something you like?
Cos I do..
What?
Hey Dipper! What's going oon?
Where have you been? And
what's going on with
those finger nails, you
look like a wolverine.
I know, right? Waaa!
I'm hanging out with my new pal Gideon.
He's one dapper little man.
Mabel, I don't trust anyone
who's hair is bigger than their head.
Aw, leave him alone. You never
wanna do girly stuff with me.
You and Soos could do
boy stuff all the time.
- What do you mean?
- Hey dude.
- You ready to blow up these hotdogs
in a microwave one by one?
- Am I?
One at a time! One at a time!
Wow! The view from your family
factory is nuts!
Good thing we both brought our
Operate glasses!
Mabel, when I'm up here
looking down on all them lil old people.
I feel like I'm king of all I survey.
- And guess that makes you my queen!
- What?
You've being so nice to me right now.
Quit it!
I can't quit it.
I'm speaking from my heart.
- From the where now?
- Mabel, I've never felt this close to anyone.
So..so close.
Look Gideon, I am ..
I like you a lot but let's
just be friends.
At least give me a chance.
Mabel, will you do me the honour
- of going on a date with me?
- A play date?
A shopping date?
It will just be one lil old date.
I swear with my lucky bolo tie.
Okay, then. I guess.
Mable Pines, you have made me
the happiest boy in the world.
Are you sniffing my hair?
It's not a date, Dip,
it's just, you know
I didn't want to hurt his feelings.
Until he figured it, I'd throw him a bone.
Mabel, guys don't work that way.
He's gonna fall in love with you.
Pff, yeah, right.
I'm not THAT lovable.
- Kaboom! Yes!
- Okay, at least we agree on something here.
A night of enchantment awaits, my lady.
Oh boy.
I can't believe they'd let us bring
horse in here.
Well, people have hard time saying
'no' to me.
Ah! Monsieur Gideon!
The feet on the table!
An excellent choice!
- Jean-Luc, what have we discused about our contac?
- Yes, yes. Very good.
I've never seen so many forks.
And water with bubbles in it?
Oh, ulala, weewee.
Oh, parlez-vous français ?
I have no idea what you're saying.
Hey, hey! What the jackal is Mabel doing
in the paper next to that crazy pitpocket Gideon?
Oh, yeah. That's like a big deal.
Everybody's talking about Gideon
and Mabel's big date tonight.
What? That little shyster is dating my great niece?
I wonder what the new name will be for the
power couple?
Mabidion? Gidiable? Magidbelion!
I didn't know! I didn't hear about it!
And plus, I told her not to!
Yeah, well it ends tonight.
I'm going right down to that little scug's house.
This is gonna stop right now.
Dude, woudn't it be funny if that was a closet?
And he had to come back again and
walk through the real door?
Nope, real door.
Gideon, you little punk!
Open up!
I will pardon nothing!
Why! Stan Pines!
- What a delight!
- Out of the way, bud.
- I'm looking for Gideon.
- Well, I haven't seen the boy around, but since you're here.
You simply must come in for coffee.
- Bu but I came..
- It's imported. All the way from Columbia.
I went to jail there once.
Some digs you got here.
Oh, this. This is beautiful.
Now, I hear your niece
and my Gideon are well,
they are singing in harmony
lately, so to speak.
Yeah, and I'm against it.
No, no, no. I see it as a fantastic
business oportunity.
Yes, the Mystery Shack and
the Tent of Telepathy.
We'd been at each other's throats for far..
Let me get that.
At each others throats for far too long,
yes we have.
This is our big chance to brush aside
our rivalry
and pull our collective profit, you see.
I'm listening.
Autograph your own head, shot lady!
Mabel, tonight's date was a complete success.
And tomorrow date promisses to top
this one in every way!
Woah, woah. You said just one date
and this was it.
What a surprise! A red-crested
south american rainbow maco!
Two.. three.. four..
Mabel! Will! You!
Accompany! Gideon!
To! The ballroom! Dance!
This! Thurpsday!
Thursday!
- Oh so adorable.
- Gideon got a girlfriend.
They're expecting us, please say you'll go.
Gideon, I'm sorry but I'm gonna have to say..
- I'm on the edge of my seat
- This is gonna be adorable.
If she says no, I'll die from sadness.
I can verify that will indeed happen.
Hey! How did it go?
I don't know..
I have a lobster now..
Well, at least it's over and you will never
have to go out with him again.
Mabel, it's over, right?
Mabel?
He asked me out again and I didn't
know how to say NO!
Like this - NO
It's not that easy, Dipper.
I do like Gideon, as a friend/little sister.
So I didn't want to hurt his feelings.
I just need to get things back where they used to be.
You know, friends.
Boat midnight, boat midnight.
You know, I thought dancing would be the end
of the evening, right?
Don't you want this evening to last my sweet?
NO! I mean, yes.
I mean, I'm always happy hanging with a friend.
Buddy, pal, chump, other word for friend.
- Pal?
- I already said pal. A mate?
How about soulmate?
Well, you can't say no to that.
He's so nice, but I
can't keep doing this.
But I can't break his heart.
Aaah! I have no way out!
- What in the heck happened on that date?
- I don't know. I was in the friend-zone
and then before I knew what was happening,
he pulled me into romance zone!
It was like quicksand! Geopardy quicksand!
Mabel, come on. It's not like
you'll have to marry Gideon.
Great news, Mabel.
You have to marry Gideon.
- What?
- It's all a part of my long-term deal with buddy Gleafall.
There's a lot of cash tied up in this thin,
plus I got this shirt.
I am fat.
Bodies change, honey!
Bodies change.
- Oh no, Mabel.
- Mabel's not here.
- She's in sweater town.
- Are you gonna come out of sweater town?
All right. Enough is enough.
- If you can't break up with Gideon, than I'll do it for you.
- You will?
- Oh thank you, thank you, thank you
- Allright, allright.
Hello! Dipper Pines, how are you?
- You look good, you look good.
- Thanks, you are..
Look, Gideon. We've gotta talk.
Mabel isn't joining you tonight.
She doesn't want to see you anymore.
She's kinda weirded out by you,
no offense.
So what you're saying is..
- You've come between us.
- You're not gonna like
freak out or anything, are you?
Of course not. This things happen.
So, okay cool. Well, then again, sorry man,
but uh..
Hey, thumbs up!
Thumbs up, indeed my friend.
How did it go? Was he mad?
Did he try to read your mind with his psychic powers?
Don't worry Mable, he's just a kid.
He doesn't have any powers.
Dipper Pines, you don't know what you've done.
You've just made the biggest mistake of your life.
Gideon Charles Gleafall, clean up
your room this instant.
I can buy and sell you old man!
Fair enough.
Hit me dude!
- Feels good.
- I'm so glad everything's back to normal.
- Your turn.
- Your tur.. Aw, man.
- Hello?
- Toby Determined, Gravity Falls Gossiper.
Oh, hey man. Sorry for acusing you of murder last week.
Water under the bridge. Saay..
We want to interview you about
whether you've seen anything
unusual in tihs hiertown
ever since you've arrived.
Oh! Finally! I thought nobody would ever ask!
I have notes and theories! Aha..
412 Gopher road. Tonight?
- Got it.
- There! I did your dirty work.
Now it's time to pay your end of the bargain.
Sandra Himeneses phone number!
Bless you, lil Gideon!
Hello!
Hello friend.
- Gideon.
- Dipper Pines.
How long have you been lining in
this town? Week? Two?
You like it here? Enjoying the scenery?
- What do you want from me, man?
- Listen carefully boy.
This town has secrets you couldn't begin
to comprehend.
Is this about Mabel?
I told you, she's not into you.
Liar! You turned her agains me!
She was my peach dumpling!
Are you okay man?
Howdy!
Reading minds isn't all I can do.
But..but you're a fake..
Oh, tell me Dipper. Is this fake?
How's your hair tasting buddy?
Wendy, I need some advice.
- You've broken up with guys, right?
- Oh yeah.
Russ Toram, Elay Hall, Stoney Davidson.
I don't know what's
wrong with me.
I thought everytrhing was back to
normal, but I still feel all gross.
Flake Wurly,  Nate Halls, oh, the guy with the tattoos.
Maybe letting Dipper do it for me was a mistake.
Gideon deserves an honest break up
Deanny Feldman, Mark Epstin, oh.
Oh man, I'm not sure I actualy broke up with him.
No wonder he keeps calling me.
I know what I gotta do.
Thatnls for talking to me, Wendy.
Ignore.
Grunkle Stan was right about you!
You are a monster!
Your sister will be mine!
- Who's the cute little guy? You are!
- No you are!
- She's never gonna date you, man!
- That's a lie!
And I'm gonna make sure you never lie to me
again, friend.
Gideon! We have to talk!
Mabel! My marshmallow!
What are you doing here?
I'm sorry Gideon, but I can't be your marshmallow.
I am here to be honest and tell you that myself.
I..I don't understand.
Mabel, this probably isn't the best time
to be brutaly honest with him!
Hey, but we can still be makeover buddies, right?
- Woudn't you like that?
- Really?
No! Not really!
- You were like attacking my brother! What the heck?
My tie! Give it back!
Not so powerfull without this, are you?
Dipper!
Listen Gideon. It's over.
I will never ever date you.
Yeah!
My powers!
Oh, this isn't over. This isn't the last you'll
see of lil..ol..me.
This is living brother.
From now on, it's all named brand foods and
clown paintings.
-  Well hehey Gideon, look what..
- Stanpher Pines!
I rebuke thee!
Rebuke? Is that a word?
The entire Pines family
have invoked my fury!
You will all pay recompense
for you transgressions!
What, you got like a
word-a-day calendar or something?
B-but-but but sunshine, what about our
arrangement with Mable and..
Silence!
Well, I see he's taking one of
his rages again.
Sorry, Stan. I'll have to stand with
Gideon on this one.
Okay, okay. I can see when
I'm not wanted.
Stan, I'm sorry, but I'm gonna need
that painting back, Staaan!
Stan!
Try and catch me, suckers!
I could've had it all.
What the heck happened to you two?
- Gideon.
Gideon.
Yeah, the little mutant swore vengeance
on the whole family.
I guess he's gonna nibble my anckles
or something.
Oh yeah. Yeah! How is he gonna
destroy us now, huh?
Try to think what number we're thinking of?
He'll never guess what
number I'm thinking of.
Negative 8! Noone would guess a negative number!
Oh, look out! Somebody's
planning our destruction right now.
Gideon, I still love you.
If only my family weren't in the way.
Look at me.
I'm old and I'm smelly.
Hey, what are you going to do without
your precious amulet?
Oh, you'll see boy.
You'll see.
- You're done.
- Not yet.
- How about now?
- Almost.
And.. there.
Let's do this.
You're all fired.
Два парня и корыто