Because this is what
was there, lana!
There where?
Outside a clown college?
They have those here? I don't know!
Archer, look out!
Ugh! We'll never catch
him in this thing.
Maybe you should've thought
about that before you
Blew the damn drop.
I blew jack shit!
Name dropper.
And if you weren't so busy
trying to bang that waitress...
Oh, for --...You would've noticed
that odin had agents in play.
She was the hostess!
If you weren't blinded by jealousy.
Okay, yes, I'm jealous.
First step's admitting it.
Jealous that odin's
gonna beat us again...
Odin!Thanks to your
epic poonhoundery.
First of all, lana --
Great. Good job. Shut up!
Odin doesn't beat sterling archer.
Only sterling archer beats --
Did you want to
finish that thought?
Did you want to finish
shutting your big, fat,
Negative, wordsy mouth?
Whose fat mouth told the stupid
waitress he was an isis agent?
Hostess!
And I had a plan.
What? To get laid in the walk-in?
Also, because I'm
not an ant, lana...
...I happen to see the big picture.
Oh, really? Well, then, where's...
...Kasparov?
Okay, that was a fluke.
Yeah, a fluke of nature
because I happen to have
Perfect situational
awareness, lana...
Archer....Which cannot be taught,
by the way...
Archer....Like a poet's...
Mind for...
Archer....To make the perfect word.
Archer! God damn it!
I'm relishing --
Way to go, lana. Nice warning.
Nice relishing. Ow.
Think that was odin? Nah,
it's only you that beats you, buddy.
Ha ha ha.
Hey, gang.
Barry.
Gee, thanks for helping
us catch kasparov.
Odin appreciates the assist. Yeah.
And if you ever get tired
of playing j.V. Ball,
You know where to find us.
Oh, yeah? Uh, where's that?
Uh, dicktown?
Jesus, even their cards are nice.
Lana, look at this -
it's embossed.
Oh, okay.
Then, I guess just pout.
Oui.
Oui, je sais, mais --
Oui. Au revoir.
That was the mayor of paris.
Name dropper.
Who is just as eager as I
am to know why isis agents
Were terrorizing paris!
So, I crashed a few cop cars,
ran over a few mimes.
So, I don't play by the rules,
mother, but I get results.
Well, as long as you got kasparov.
Oh, uh, yeah, about that.
That's why she can't
have nice things.
either that, or I steal them. Hmm?
what? What's that?
what? What do you want, pam?
'cause I'm a little
busy for chit-chat.
Busy trying to turn that thing on?
look at this! O-n -- nothing!
Well, just keep at it.
you're not my supervisor.
I'm sorry -- what?!
He sort of offered
me a job at odin.
Barry dillon? Barry "We
have this whole huge
History together" Dillon?
We don't have this
whole huge history.
Oh, my god.
Barry. Sweet, huh?
Using a mirror to reflect the
laser beam back into the laser?
Yeah. Oh, my god.
Sorry it took so long.
And that I'm
accidentally inside you.
Not a problem.
I-I just want to keep my options
Open, so you can't breathe a
Word of this to malory.
You know how she gets.
Odin?! Well, since I'm
not appreciated here.
What's to appreciate? Exactly.
I mean, that's indicative of
Your whole attitude, mother.
Sterling malory archer, you are...
Of course free to
pursue your options.
Wait, hang on.
And if odin made you a
better offer, what kind of
Mother would I be if I stood
in the way of your happiness?
Uh...Wait, what just happened here?
Fine! She thinks I won't go?!
Well, guess what! I don't need her!
I, however, do need your keycard.
Yeah, hi. Barry dillon, ease.
Yes, I'll hold!
Oh, d just wait till I get to odin.
I will! Keycard?
Oh. Here! God!
They are the
stuff-throng-est family.
okay, so, after I
call your vase guy...
Freeze every one of his accounts!
And then get me woodhouse.Am
And we'll just see how tough
Sterling is when he
can't suckle at my teat!
Woodhouse, she froze my accounts,
and I need to get
In my safe, so open the
goddamn door already!
I'm afraid I can't,
since isis actually pays
The rent on the -- damn it!
En did we get a bulletproof door?!
After the popeye incident, sir.
Oh, right.
Wait, so you kick me
out of e own house?!
Yes, sir.
Although it pains me dearly.
I'm gonna pain you dearly,
woodhouse, when I peel
All your skin off with a
Flensing knife, sew it into
Woodhouse pajamas, and then
Set those pajamas on fire!
Hello?
It's just you and me now, reggie.
So be a lad? Put on some mingus?
Hi, barry dillon, please?
Yes, it's sterling arch--
Ohh. Yes, I'll hold!
Oh! Come on.
We've got mi6 in the semis on
Sunday, and I am slicing
it like a butcher.
Just keep at it. trexler:
I think it's this new grip.
So, listen, remember
How you wanted me to float that
Job offer to lana kane?
Love her! Yeah!
When does she start?
That's the thing.
See, I think sterling archer
Thought I was talking to him.
Archer?! You're kidding.
Yeah, I wish.
Mean, obviously the guy's
great in the field.
You would know.
Now see? Why do you do that?
Why do you softball
'em in like that?
I'm sorry. How's the leg?
Hurts when it rains...
And when I think about archer,
and so I blew him off.
No, no, no, no, barry,
you blow him on!
"On" As in hire him? As in here?
Yes.
It'll drive his mother crazy.Ob
Gotta be the grip.
And you froze all of
sterling's accounts?
Domestic and foreign?
even the one on the isle of man.
Oh, my god, and is that like
Whore island for women? Nope.
Then you just watch.
In no time, he'll be begging
me to take him back.
He hasn't called, has he? Nope.
How ya holdin' up, mama bird?
Well, except for your grossly
over-familiar tone, I
Couldn't be happier!
even if mr.
Archer gets a job at odin?
Please! Odin won't hire him.
After the stunt he
pulled in berlin?
Well, whose fault is that?
Yours! You bust in,
shoot two perfectly
Good double agents --
And you think an appropriate
response is to ruin my suit?
Oh, and my shirt! I'm sorry.
So, will you please
just help me up?!
No.
...For which I am
pretty genuinely sorry.
Nothing two steel rods
And 16 titanium
screws couldn't fix.
Ah, come on, don't be shitty.
Yeah, barry. trexler:
It's water under the bridge.
Get over it. Because he
is part of the family now.
So go put his stuff in his office.
Yeah, barry.
Barry, hi!
So, I was wondering if your
tempting offer was still open.
No, you silly man!
About the job.
No, just...Keeping my options open.
Definitely come in.
I mean, we did kind of
fill the position, but...
I don't know if it's
gonna be a good fit.
I just don't see why you need this.
Because this is a huge
Opportunity for me, and I need
To feel confident.
In the interview.
Oh, that looks great!
Yeah, it feels pretty Good.
Come on, already. Take a cut.
What, like, out the window?
Don't worry about it -
I get a deal on those.
90 cents a ball.
Uh, okay.
God, you're a natural!
Bet it's all that lacrosse
at boarding school, huh?
Yeah, 13 years' worth.
13 years?!
What, did she ship you
off in kindergarten?!
Gosh, that must've been tough.
No, I-I-I loved it.
Uh...Made a lot of good friends.
Family, almost, is what they were.
Speaking of --
How's your mother taking all this?
Oh, please. I bet she
doesn't even miss me.
Because he'll be back,
crying for his mommy!
Just like that christmas break
When I moved and forgot to give
My new address to his
stupid boarding school.
I mean, he rode the train into
The city all by himself.
He couldn't pick up a phone book?
9 years old, and bawling in
That police station
like a little girl!
Ha! What's that tell you?
kind of a lot, actually.
Oh, shut up.
I bet you're barren.
My god. On christmas?
Well, christmas eve, technically.
Well, the lovely framboise
From h.R. Has some
paperwork for you to sign.
'allo! 'allo.
why don't you follow her on down to
Your big new corner office...
Okay. trexler:...Where the
sofa is soaked in scotchgard.
If you know what I'm -- yeah,
I think I do.
It's resistant to stains.
Right, right, i got it.
Super! 'cause we're one big family.
Why do you make that sound?
Gee, let's see.
You're off to interview with
Odin, ho oy f barr a"Oh, I
Forgot to mention the whole
Naked laser thing" Dillon!
Odin isn't some co-ed
Freshman dorm where everyone
Runs around screwing!
I'm sorry, framboise. It's not you.
I mean, it's not me, either.
Obviously.
But in the office?
You don't sex on the women at isis?
Constantly!
But it's not allowed, and
Actually, it's probably illegal.
But here -- framboise:
Here we are one big famille.
Yeah, and the, uh,
famille thing actually makes
This borderline creepy.
Perhaps if you tried
it from behind?
Yeah, let's try that.
Don't get any on that snappy suit.
Don't you have better things to
Do than mince around and gawk?!
About a million.
But cheryl was scared to come in
Here, so I took time out of my
Busy "Mincing schedule" To tell
You that you have a phone call.
Is it sterling?!
I am sure I don't know.
Do you know you're a little bitch?
Will you remember
this conversation?
Probably not, no.
Well, then... Off.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
with the language!
You kiss your mother
with that mouth?
You leave bub out of this!
And how dare you steal
my son away from me!
Steal him? You cut him loose.
You cut him loose! trexler: What?
I want you to fire
him this instant.
I can't do that. He's happy here.
He's making new friends.
God damn it, archer!
What, barry? I said,
"Don't come in here."
Framboise, what'd I say?
He said do not come in.
Yeah, barry.
I don't care if he's happy!
Well, that's obvious.
Meaning what?!
Meaning who leaves a
9-year-old kid in a police
Station on christmas?! Eve!
And he told you about that?
Oh, we've have such great talks.
Fire him! trexler: Join him!
Come work for me!
Have you lost your mind?!
Every time I see you.
Fire him. trexler: Can't do it.
Can't or won't?
Either? Fine.
Then go check your telex.
Oh, my god. Look at that.
A burn notice?
"Isis disavows agent sterling archer,
a.K.A. Duchess..."
Man, she loved that dog.
"...Who is to be considered
an unreliable asset
And security risk."
Oh, it must've killed
her to do this.
And I'm smirking.
No, you don't smirk
At a mother's suffering, barry,
You asshole! Ow!
It's just with the shattered
Femur and the gunshot wound
And -- I don't know if you knew
This -- but framboise and
I were kind of engaged.
I did not know that!
Yeah. trexler: And I served
her up like a pudding.
Well, engaged to be engaged.
Ow!
Ass! If you love it,
put a ring on it.
Okay, so -- okay, you go fix this.
You know, I'm not
even sure I want to.
She was obviously into him.
Ugh! Come on!
Ass! Not framboise! Archer!
The burn notice?
His mother obviously
just sent that to --
To every agency on the planet.
Look at this -- c.I.
A., mi6, interpol.
We can't keep him now, barry!
Oh, so...
So you take him to the basement.
You put one in his ear.
Can you do that?
Oh, my god!
That framboise is a freak,
huh? Yeah.
No, as a matter of fact,
I don't have barry on speed dial.
Well, gee,
that's rather surprising.
You know what's surprising?
Kissing you goodbye at the
Airport, dozing off in first
Class, and then seeing you on my
Flight when I get up to pee!
That, to me, is rather surprising.
And really expensive, turns out.
Just --
Seriously.
I mean, I don't want to sound
Like a jerk, but that framboise
Chick must've been a prostitute
Before she got this gig.
In, like, bangkok.
I was almost embarrassed for her.
Where we going, anyway?
We're headed down to
sub-basement 3 for a minute.
Is there a shower down there?
'cause I bet I just reek of her.
One second. Dillon.
Barry, you getting that?
Really? Yeah.
I'm brushing it your way, pal.
No, I'm actually at
the lobby right now.
O s.Secondba wait,
where are we on that shower?
Maybe head on back
up to your office.
'cause there's actually, like, a
Private bathroom in there.
Oh, good, 'cause like
I said, I bet I just reek.
Yeah, you've mentioned that.
But I -- no!
Baby, I am putting you in the
Corner, where you will sit quietly.
Hey, you! Hey, you!
And who are you?
Cyril figgis,
isis comptroller and...
...Very eager to sit here
quietly in the corner
Because he is so tired. Um, so...
I'll just be here, then.
Yep? Yep!
No! No! No!
Who put out a burn
notice on sterling?!
That would be you. What?!
Holy shit, the look on your face.
But I would never!
Not in a million -- get a mirror.
Oh, dear god.
Did I drink absinthe?
That bottle and most of this one.
Until we wrestled it away from you.
'cause you don't know
how to share, biotch!
Easy, tough guy.
I don't remember any of that.
Absinthe makes me black out.
All right, ya yellow sons
of bitches, let's dance!
It also makes you incredibly mean.
and ugly!
Seriously. biotch.
Danger zone.
Well, don't just sit there!
Undo this!
Ooh. "Ooh" What?!
We can't, ms. Archer.
It's too late.
I'm sorry, so --
What are you saying?
Uh -- can you not
give me a minute?!
No! You fire me, I take my things!
Take all the things!
Here, take this!
Go staple my heart back together!
Ton coeur?! Tu n'as pas un coeur!
How am I the bad guy in this?!
So, barry...
That was framboise,
our head of h.R.
With whom I guess I
won't be meeting?
No, she's gone.
And so, remember how I said
we'd just hired someone?
Yes. And so,
remember sterling archer?
Wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait!
Barry, if you touch me,
I swear to god I will
put you in the ground.
That was before his
Mother put out a
burn notice on him.
Wha--?! Malory burned archer?
Worldwide. Holy shit.
Yeah, so he's gone. Already?!
Like literally gone?!
Oh, my god.
I liked her better mean. He's gone!
I killed my baby boy,
and now my baby is gone!
Oh, now.
You can always... Always what?!
Well, I was gonna say you
can have another baby,
But...You're all dried up in there.
No, no, no.
Like, figuratively gone.
Unlike framboise, whose car
should be blowing up any minute.
Uh, excusez-moi, mademoelle.
'allo! May I help you...
Avec your box?
So archer's still here?
Yeah, he's in that corner office.
And once facilities cleans his
Brains out of it,
it can be your office.
Really? Yeah, I don't think
The regular cleaning
staff does brains.
No, I mean, you shoot
Him, and I get an office
And the bank where
You'll drive your new company
Car to deposit your insane
Paychecks, and maybe, if you
Stand on those tiptoes,
your huge apartment.
"Huge" As in...?
As in you won't see
Your live-in servants
unless you really want to.
All right, let me
go shoot this prick.
Wait. Let me do it.
Really? 'cause I would
kind of love to.
Not as much as I would.
You guys kind of
have a history, huh?
Yeah. You could say that.
Knock yourself out.
So, hey, these servants -
if I did see them,
Would they curtsy meekly?
Well, otherwise, I mean,
what's the point?
Archer! Oh, come on.
Lana, why the hell are --
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Lana, no!
Barry, does this make
up for framboise?
It does, other barry.
It sure does.
Barry?
I guess go ahead and call
facilities or whatever.
Because there is lamp everywhere.Co
God, lana!
Get on with your life already!
Argh! Telex! You got one in here?!
Why, so you can smash that, too?
No. 'cause I'm pretty
Sure I'm financially responsible
For the furnishings!
So I can send a telex
From odin to make the burn
Notice from your mother look
Like an odin black flag!
Mother burned me? lana: Apparently.
Oh, my god, that's Classic her.
You're both classic her.
Now shut up, get dressed, and
Grab the keys to that company car.
We've got about two minutes
Before some odin dick sees this
And seals the exits.
Any way we can bump that to five?
I seriously need a shower.
Archer! archer: Okay, god!
Climb down off that rag.
Oh, my god.
Looks like jonestown in here.
Yes, pam, get me some
Poison, because I am
already dead inside.
Too dead inside to read good news?
Is it my obituary?
Well, it's not that good.
Give me that, you oaf!
"All agencies, disregard isis
Burn notice on agent archer, a.
K.A. Duchess --"
An odin black flag operation!
Pam, he's alive!
My sterling is alive!
Aw, and look at happy
little mama bird!
Well, the blowback on odin
for this will be huge,
And I saw it coming. Uh-huh.
I knew it.
Just like I knew sterling would
Come crying back to mommy,
Wiping his snotty nose on his
Sleeve like a scared
little boy on christmas.
Uh-huh. malory: Eve.
It was only christmas eve. I know.
Good to have you back.
malory: And? And?
And do you just plan
To loom over me all day,
like some sort of...Henge?
Okay.
You see? This is why.
This is why we can't have nice
Things, barry, you asshole!
How am I the bad guy in this?
Because I wanted this, archer.
I'm sick of you getting the best
Assignments st because
your mother's the boss.
Do you know what that's like?!
Besides awesome? lana: Rrr!
Hang on. I think my car's on p-2.
Well, I have to get cyril,
who's on...
Framboise. framboise: 'allo!
Hello? cyril: Hello.
Oh, man.
That's bad.
Yes, now! Let's talk this out.
Talk what out?!
How you ruined my
chance to work for odin?
Or -- ooh! -- Maybe how I just
Caught my boyfriend balls
deep in some french chick!
Ex-boyfriend, I bet.
lana: Ya think?!
Yeah, he's not coming back.
Archer.
Sorry, I know this is tough.
I mean cyril, whatever, but your
Feelings for me are
obviously conflicted.
You're right, archer.
I am conflicted. archer: Yeah.
Because if I had shot
You in the face, I'd be living
Here, getting curtsied
at by servants!
Yeah, but you couldn't do it.
maybe -- maybe we
both belong at isis,
You know? Maybe
that's our real home.
That's what mother said
about boarding school.
I'm really sorry about cyril.
Yeah, me too.
Even if you broug it on yourself.
Excuse me? archer: Oh, come on.
I don't recall ever seeing a
Welcome mat at your back door.
Archer. archer: But -- wait,
would that cheer you up?
Me and you, a little revenge anal?
Archer. archer: Yes?
You wearing a seat belt?
Uh, no, wh--
Lana-a-a-a!
So, uh, is that a yes?
Or a maybe or...?
What?
Oh, okay.
Then, I guess just pout.
Sync by YYeTs.net
Transcript by Addic7ed.com