>> summer: Bye, mom! Bye, dad!
>> morty: Drive carefully!
>> rick: Have fun, you two.
>> beth: Yes, we will have as
much fun as possible on our...
Titanic -themed getaway.
Much fun as possible on our...
>> jerry: Let's lose the 'tude,
Titanic -themed getaway.
please.
>> jerry: Let's lose the 'tude,
It's supposed to be romantic.
Please.
>> beth: Speaking of disasters,
It's supposed to be romantic.
dad, we are leaving you in
>> beth: Speaking of disasters,
charge, here.
Dad, we are leaving you in
>> rick: I know, c-can we wrap
Charge, here.
this up?
>> rick: I know, c-can we wrap
Morty and I [burps] have some
This up?
synthetic laser eels oxidizing
Morty and I [burps] have some
in the garage.
Synthetic laser eels oxidizing
>> beth: Hey, don't blow me off.
In the garage.
I am drawing a line, okay?
>> beth: Hey, don't blow me off.
Any damage to this house or
I am drawing a line, okay?
these children when we get back,
Any damage to this house or
and...N-no more adventures with
These children when we get back,
morty.
And...N-no more adventures with
>> morty: Aw, geez, rick.
Morty.
If my mom's the one who's saying
>> morty: Aw, geez, rick.
it, then you know it's pretty
If my mom's the one who's saying
serious this time.
It, then you know it's pretty
>> both: That's right.
Serious this time.
>> jerry: Wait. What?
>> both: That's right.
>> rick: Listen, you have my
>> jerry: Wait. What?
word as a caregiver,
>> rick: Listen, you have my
everything's gonna be fine.
Word as a caregiver,
And if not, like you say, no
Everything's gonna be fine.
more adventures or whatever.
And if not, like you say, no
It's like that old song "blomp
More adventures or whatever.
blomp-a noop noop a-noop noop
It's like that old song "blomp
noop."
Blomp-a noop noop a-noop noop
y-you guys know that song?
Noop."
From tiny rogerts?
Y-you guys know that song?
You never heard of it?
From tiny rogerts?
You know, the black effeminate
You never heard of it?
guy from the '50s?
You know, the black effeminate
No-nobody?
Guy from the '50s?
A-all right, whatever.
No-nobody?
Look, who cares?
A-all right, whatever.
Just go on your stupid trip.
Look, who cares?
>> jerry: Not one thing out of
Just go on your stupid trip.
place.
>> jerry: Not one thing out of
[ engine turns over ]
Place.
not a single thing.
[ bubbling, crackling ]
>> summer: Well, we're past the
point of no return.
I'm going to have a party.
I found jello.
Can you sneak your mom's vodka?
Yes, she does.
I saw it in your laundry room.
Listen, you can't both be in
denial about it.
Okay, bye.
Denial about it.
>> morty: Summer, you can't
Okay, bye.
throw a party!
>> morty: Summer, you can't
Remember what mom said?
Throw a party!
>> summer: Yeah, if anything
Remember what mom said?
gets messed up, you and
>> summer: Yeah, if anything
grandpa rick get punished.
Gets messed up, you and
I'm only a human being, morty.
Grandpa rick get punished.
>> morty: Rick, tell summer she
I'm only a human being, morty.
can't have a party!
>> morty: Rick, tell summer she
>> rick: Uh, summer, you can't
Can't have a party!
have a party.
>> rick: Uh, summer, you can't
>> summer: [ scoffs ]
Have a party.
>> rick: Because [burps] I'm
>> summer: [ scoffs ]
having a party, b-I-I-I-itch!
>> rick: Because [burps] I'm
>> morty: Oh, what?!
Having a party, b-I-I-I-itch!
Rick, you can't!
>> morty: Oh, what?!
>> summer: What do you mean
Rick, you can't!
you're having a party?
>> summer: What do you mean
Are some glip glops from the
You're having a party?
third dimension going to come
Are some glip glops from the
over and play cards or
Third dimension going to come
something?
Over and play cards or
>> rick: "glip glop?"
Something?
you're lucky a traflorkian
>> rick: "glip glop?"
doesn't hear you say that.
You're lucky a traflorkian
>> summer: Is that like their
Doesn't hear you say that.
n-word?
>> summer: Is that like their
>> rick: It's like the n-word
N-word?
and the c-word had a baby and it
>> rick: It's like the n-word
was raised by all the bad words
And the c-word had a baby and it
for jews.
Was raised by all the bad words
>> morty: Listen, I think the
For jews.
three of us could just, you
>> morty: Listen, I think the
know, have a nice time, like
Three of us could just, you
just hanging out, and, you know,
Know, have a nice time, like
doing a little bonding and --
Just hanging out, and, you know,
>> summer: Screw that.
Doing a little bonding and --
This is my chance to gain some
>> summer: Screw that.
footing with the cool kids.
This is my chance to gain some
>> rick: That's why you party?
Footing with the cool kids.
Boy, you really are 17.
>> rick: That's why you party?
>> summer: Why do you party?
Boy, you really are 17.
>> rick: To get [burps]
>> summer: Why do you party?
wr-wriggedy wriggedy wrecked,
>> rick: To get [burps]
son!
Wr-wriggedy wriggedy wrecked,
>> summer: Just keep your sci-fi
Son!
friends away from my awesome
>> summer: Just keep your sci-fi
ones.
Friends away from my awesome
>> rick: Yeah, and you keep your
Ones.
awesome friends away from my
>> rick: Yeah, and you keep your
canapes.
Awesome friends away from my
>> after dinner, titanic 2 will
Canapes.
attach to the rail system near
>> after dinner, titanic 2 will
our replica iceberg, and the
Attach to the rail system near
hydraulics encased in these
Our replica iceberg, and the
tubes will execute a controlled
Hydraulics encased in these
sink into the icy depths.
Tubes will execute a controlled
>> jerry: A rail system seems
Sink into the icy depths.
archaic for an attraction this
>> jerry: A rail system seems
impressive.
Archaic for an attraction this
Are you sure the ship will sink?
Impressive.
>> I can assure you the ship
Are you sure the ship will sink?
will sink, as it has a thousand
>> I can assure you the ship
times before.
Will sink, as it has a thousand
It is un-unsinkable.
Times before.
>> ooh!
It is un-unsinkable.
>> jerry: Look, it's the line
>> ooh!
for the bow!
>> jerry: Look, it's the line
>> beth: Jerry, I'd love to just
For the bow!
kick back with a margarita and
>> beth: Jerry, I'd love to just
read.
Kick back with a margarita and
Do you mind if I skip the whole
Read.
"king of the world" bit?
Do you mind if I skip the whole
>> jerry: Well, it's not the
"king of the world" bit?
"king of the world" bit.
>> jerry: Well, it's not the
That's jack and fabrizio.
"king of the world" bit.
This is where rose says, "I'm
That's jack and fabrizio.
flying, jack!"
This is where rose says, "I'm
but whatever.
Flying, jack!"
I can be the only one to do it
But whatever.
alone.
I can be the only one to do it
>> beth: Well, what about her?
Alone.
Excuse me, ma'am.
>> beth: Well, what about her?
Would you like to take my place
Excuse me, ma'am.
in line?
Would you like to take my place
>> I, uh -- I could get into
In line?
trouble.
>> I, uh -- I could get into
>> beth: We won't tell.
Trouble.
>> jerry: So...
>> beth: We won't tell.
You're a titanic fanatic?
>> jerry: So...
>> oh, yes.
You're a titanic fanatic?
I've worked here since it
>> oh, yes.
opened, but I've never been able
I've worked here since it
to participate.
Opened, but I've never been able
>> jerry: Happy to help...Rose.
To participate.
>> [ giggles ]
>> jerry: Happy to help...Rose.
>> I love watching bukkake.
>> [ giggles ]
I mean, like, I don't know if I
>> I love watching bukkake.
personally would ever do it...
I mean, like, I don't know if I
>> summer: Brad! Hey!
Personally would ever do it...
>> yo.
>> summer: Brad! Hey!
>> brad is here!
>> yo.
Quick, make my hair look drunk.
>> brad is here!
>> check it out.
Quick, make my hair look drunk.
Tammy's already drunk.
>> check it out.
Cool.
Tammy's already drunk.
>> the beacon was activated.
Cool.
Who is in danger?
>> the beacon was activated.
>> summer: Ugh! Grandpa!
Who is in danger?
>> rick: Birdperson!
>> summer: Ugh! Grandpa!
>> I am pleased there is no
>> rick: Birdperson!
emergency.
>> I am pleased there is no
>> rick: Oh, there's an
Emergency.
emergency, all right.
>> rick: Oh, there's an
A [bleep] emergency!
Emergency, all right.
When's the last time you got
A [bleep] emergency!
laid, 'pers?
When's the last time you got
>> it has been a...Challenging
Laid, 'pers?
mating season for birdperson.
>> it has been a...Challenging
>> rick: Then it's time to get
Mating season for birdperson.
your beak wet tonight, playah.
>> rick: Then it's time to get
Go have some fun out there
Your beak wet tonight, playah.
birdp-- bird-- birdperson.
Go have some fun out there
>> morty: Oh, man, how many
Birdp-- bird-- birdperson.
people did you invite, rick?
>> morty: Oh, man, how many
>> rick: Uh...People?
People did you invite, rick?
Mm, six.
>> rick: Uh...People?
>> rick: Yo! What up, my
Mm, six.
glip glops?!
>> rick: Yo! What up, my
>> morty: Oh, man!
Glip glops?!
[ electronic music plays ]
>> morty: Oh, man!
[ breathing heavily ]
[ electronic music plays ]
oh!
[ breathing heavily ]
Y-y-you know there's a garbage,
Oh!
right?
Y-y-you know there's a garbage,
Hey, uh, what the hell?!
Right?
>> ooh. That's why you never
Hey, uh, what the hell?!
invite a floopy doop and a
>> ooh. That's why you never
shmoopy doop to the same party.
Invite a floopy doop and a
[ bed springs squeaking ]
Shmoopy doop to the same party.
>> morty: Oh, oh, g--
[ bed springs squeaking ]
oh, that's disgusting!
>> morty: Oh, oh, g--
You guys are in my parents' bed!
Oh, that's disgusting!
>> oh. Sorry.
You guys are in my parents' bed!
I'm not feeling too well.
>> oh. Sorry.
I just needed to lie down for a
I'm not feeling too well.
bit.
I just needed to lie down for a
>> morty: Oh. Okay.
Bit.
S-s-sorry. [ chuckles ]
>> morty: Oh. Okay.
>> [ groans ]
S-s-sorry. [ chuckles ]
>> morty: Oh, my god!
>> [ groans ]
Are you kidding me?!
>> morty: Oh, my god!
>> the thing people don't
Are you kidding me?!
realize about the gear wars is
>> the thing people don't
that it was never really about
Realize about the gear wars is
the gears at all.
That it was never really about
>> rick: Uh-huh. Yeah.
The gears at all.
No, no, to-totally.
>> rick: Uh-huh. Yeah.
>> morty: Rick, you got to
No, no, to-totally.
stop --
>> morty: Rick, you got to
>> rick: Morty!
Stop --
Have you met gearhead?
>> rick: Morty!
>> morty: Hey, how's --
Have you met gearhead?
>> rick: Morty here, he -- he
>> morty: Hey, how's --
would love to hear all about the
>> rick: Morty here, he -- he
gear wars.
Would love to hear all about the
>> how familiar are you with the
Gear wars.
gear wars, exactly?
>> how familiar are you with the
>> morty: Uh...Not at all.
Gear wars, exactly?
>> oh, boy.
>> morty: Uh...Not at all.
I envy you.
>> oh, boy.
Okay, it was about 754 years
I envy you.
ago...
>> rick: Oh, hey, morty!
H-have you -- have you met my
buddy scropon?
>> morty: Not again, rick.
Buddy scropon?
That last guy droned on for
>> morty: Not again, rick.
20 minutes, you know?
That last guy droned on for
And meanwhile, the whole house
20 minutes, you know?
is being destroyed!
And meanwhile, the whole house
>> rick: Whoa, morty, this guy's
Is being destroyed!
entire planet was destroyed.
>> rick: Whoa, morty, this guy's
Have a little perspective.
Entire planet was destroyed.
>> hey, rick, squanchy party,
Have a little perspective.
bro!
>> hey, rick, squanchy party,
>> rick: Aw! Squanchy!
Bro!
>> is there a good place for me
>> rick: Aw! Squanchy!
to   squancaround here?
>> is there a good place for me
>> rick: Squanchy, you can
To   squancaround here?
squanch wherever you want, man.
>> rick: Squanchy, you can
Mi casa es su casa, dawg!
Squanch wherever you want, man.
>> all right!
Mi casa es su casa, dawg!
I like your squanch!
>> all right!
>> morty: Uh, rick, what exactly
I like your squanch!
is "squanching"?
>> morty: Uh, rick, what exactly
>> rick: Morty, listen -- we've
Is "squanching"?
had a lot of really cool
>> rick: Morty, listen -- we've
adventures over the last year,
Had a lot of really cool
but it's time to relax.
Adventures over the last year,
>> morty: Yeah, if I relax now,
But it's time to relax.
there might not even be any more
>> morty: Yeah, if I relax now,
adventures!
There might not even be any more
>> rick: Jesus, morty, you're
Adventures!
bumming me out.
>> rick: Jesus, morty, you're
Can't we just pretend like
Bumming me out.
everything's fine for a few
Can't we just pretend like
hours, enjoy ourselves, and then
Everything's fine for a few
worry about all this later?
Hours, enjoy ourselves, and then
>> morty: Yeah, that's easy for
Worry about all this later?
you to say, rick.
>> morty: Yeah, that's easy for
You know, you like not caring
You to say, rick.
about stuff.
You know, you like not caring
You know, wh-wh-what's in this
About stuff.
for me?
You know, wh-wh-what's in this
[ soft music plays ]
For me?
[ indistinct conversations ]
[ soft music plays ]
jessica.
[ indistinct conversations ]
>> rick: Knock it off,
Jessica.
slow mobius!
>> rick: Knock it off,
>> ha ha! Sorry, dude!
Slow mobius!
I'm just trying to show off my
>> ha ha! Sorry, dude!
powers, bro!
I'm just trying to show off my
>> morty: I can't believe she's
Powers, bro!
here.
>> morty: I can't believe she's
>> rick: Well, what are you
Here.
doing standing here, morty?
>> rick: Well, what are you
Go. Talk to her.
Doing standing here, morty?
Tonight, the only adventure
Go. Talk to her.
you're on is your cusping
Tonight, the only adventure
manhood.
You're on is your cusping
[ both laugh ]
Manhood.
>> jerry: Oh, rose.
[ both laugh ]
Whee!
>> jerry: Oh, rose.
Is that what I think it is?
Whee! Is that what I think it is?
>> yes, every couple gets to
Is that what I think it is?
re-create jack's drowning at the
>> yes, every couple gets to
end of the movie.
Re-create jack's drowning at the
It's so romantic.
End of the movie.
>> jerry: I can't wait to do
It's so romantic.
that with beth.
>> jerry: I can't wait to do
>> I don't know, jerry.
That with beth.
With all due respect, it seems
>> I don't know, jerry.
like your wife may not be that
With all due respect, it seems
interested.
Like your wife may not be that
>> jerry: [ gasps ] look!
Interested.
>> iceberg, right ahead!
>> jerry: [ gasps ] look!
The buffet is now closed.
>> iceberg, right ahead!
Iceberg, right ahead!
The buffet is now closed.
>> uh, sir?
There's not a problem.
>> what do you mean there's not
a problem?
>> the guidance system isn't
A problem?
putting us on a direct collision
>> the guidance system isn't
course.
Putting us on a direct collision
This ship is about to completely
Course.
miss the giant iceberg!
This ship is about to completely
>> well, do something!
Miss the giant iceberg!
Steer into it!
>> well, do something!
>> I'm trying!
Steer into it!
>> it's too late.
>> I'm trying!
Ladies and gentlemen...
>> it's too late.
Don't brace yourselves.
Ladies and gentlemen...
[ all gasping ]
Don't brace yourselves.
>> jerry: No! No!
[ all gasping ]
What happened?!
>> jerry: No! No!
>> their rail system must have
What happened?!
failed.
>> their rail system must have
>> oh, my god!
Failed.
We're not gonna sink!
>> oh, my god!
>> totally gonna get laid
We're not gonna sink!
tonight.
>> totally gonna get laid
>> I like your feathers.
Tonight.
>> they are designed to attract
>> I like your feathers.
the attention of the female.
>> they are designed to attract
>> it's working.
The attention of the female.
>> tammy, I should let you know
>> it's working.
I just got out of a highly
>> tammy, I should let you know
intense soul bond with my
I just got out of a highly
previous spirit mate.
Intense soul bond with my
>> I'm not looking to get into a
Previous spirit mate.
soul bond.
>> I'm not looking to get into a
I'm just looking for...
Soul bond.
>> I believe birdperson can
I'm just looking for...
arrange that.
>> I believe birdperson can
>> hey, summer, haven't seen you
Arrange that.
at flute practice in a while.
>> hey, summer, haven't seen you
>> summer, don't tell me you're
At flute practice in a while.
friends with her.
>> summer, don't tell me you're
>> summer: Are you kidding me?
Friends with her.
I don't even know what she's
>> summer: Are you kidding me?
doing here.
I don't even know what she's
>> rick: Whoa. Not cool, summer.
Doing here.
This is a party.
>> rick: Whoa. Not cool, summer.
Everybody should be welcome.
This is a party.
[ crashes ]
Everybody should be welcome.
oh, great.
[ crashes ]
Who invited abradolph lincoler?
Oh, great.
>> summer: I thought everyone
Who invited abradolph lincoler?
was welcome.
>> summer: I thought everyone
>> rick: It's not the same,
Was welcome.
summer.
>> rick: It's not the same,
Lincoler is a crazed maniac --
Summer.
just a misguided effort of mine
Lincoler is a crazed maniac --
to create a morally neutral
Just a misguided effort of mine
superleader by combining the
To create a morally neutral
dna of adolf hitler and
Superleader by combining the
abraham lincoln.
Dna of adolf hitler and
Turns out it [burps] just adds
Abraham lincoln.
up to a lame, weird loser.
Turns out it [burps] just adds
>> rick, you brought me into
Up to a lame, weird loser.
this world, a suffering
>> rick, you brought me into
abomination tortured by the
This world, a suffering
duality of its being.
Abomination tortured by the
But I shall finally know peace
Duality of its being.
when I watch the life drain from
But I shall finally know peace
your wretched body!
When I watch the life drain from
>> whoa. What's up, man?
Your wretched body!
>> I have no quarrel with you,
>> whoa. What's up, man?
boy.
>> I have no quarrel with you,
>> "boy"?
Boy.
What's that supposed to mean?
>> "boy"?
>> it's just -- l-look, I-I
What's that supposed to mean?
don't know how you thought I
>> it's just -- l-look, I-I
meant it, but...
Don't know how you thought I
>> rick: Don't look at me, dude.
Meant it, but...
>> look, I'm
>> rick: Don't look at me, dude.
half-abraham lincoln, so --
>> look, I'm
>> so I should get on my knees
Half-abraham lincoln, so --
and kiss your ass?!
>> so I should get on my knees
>> well, no, but...
And kiss your ass?!
You know?
>> well, no, but...
>> what do I know?
You know?
That the third reich will reign
>> what do I know?
for a thousand years?
That the third reich will reign
>> leave him alone, brad.
For a thousand years?
>> stay out of this, jessica!
>> leave him alone, brad.
>> rick: Kick his ass, brad!
>> stay out of this, jessica!
Kick his ass!
>> rick: Kick his ass, brad!
>> all: Kick his ass!
Kick his ass!
>> brad!
>> stupid! [ grunts ]
>> morty: Rick!
>> rick: I just did you a favor,
morty.
>> morty: Sorry about all that.
Morty.
Rick has some really strange
>> morty: Sorry about all that.
friends.
Rick has some really strange
>> ugh! Brad is such a jerk.
Friends.
He's always trying to prove what
>> ugh! Brad is such a jerk.
a man he is.
He's always trying to prove what
I just want to find somebody
A man he is.
nice and sweet.
I just want to find somebody
>> morty: Jessica, can I show
Nice and sweet.
you something?
>> morty: Jessica, can I show
>> wow! Look at all this stuff.
You something?
>> morty: Yeah.
>> wow! Look at all this stuff.
This is me and my grandpa rick's
>> morty: Yeah.
sci-fi workshop.
This is me and my grandpa rick's
Check this out.
Sci-fi workshop.
[ projector beeping ]
Check this out.
>> it's beautiful.
[ projector beeping ]
>> morty: You know, jessica,
>> it's beautiful.
there's something I've always
>> morty: You know, jessica,
wanted to tell you.
There's something I've always
>> what's that, morty?
Wanted to tell you.
>> I think that you're the
>> what's that, morty?
most --
>> I think that you're the
>> no, that -- those weird
Most --
sounds coming from the closet
>> no, that -- those weird
over there.
Sounds coming from the closet
[ closet rattling ]
Over there.
>> morty: Oh, my god!
[ closet rattling ]
>> aah!
>> morty: Oh, my god!
>> hey, I'm squanching in here!
>> aah!
>> morty: Oh, my god!
>> hey, I'm squanching in here!
Oh, that is so disgusting!
>> morty: Oh, my god!
Ow! Oh! Oh, crap!
Oh, that is so disgusting!
[ device warbling ]
[ warbling ]
[ all screaming ]
>> rick: Huh.
Big star in the sky.
[ inhales sharply ]
oxygen-rich atmosphere.
Giant testicle monsters.
Oxygen-rich atmosphere.
We'll be fine! Let's party!
Giant testicle monsters.
[ all cheering ]
>> ♪ just shake that ass, bitch,
and let me see whatcha got ♪
♪ just shake that ass...
>> summer: I swear to god,
morty, if it weren't for the
fact that everyone's still
Morty, if it weren't for the
having a blast in there, I would
Fact that everyone's still
be so furious with you right
Having a blast in there, I would
now.
Be so furious with you right
>> rick: Oh, man.
Now.
Y-you hear that, morty?
>> rick: Oh, man.
You really lucked out with
Y-you hear that, morty?
summer o-on that one.
You really lucked out with
>> morty: How are you guys not
Summer o-on that one.
freaking out right now?!
>> morty: How are you guys not
T-the whole house is sitting in
Freaking out right now?!
another dimension!
T-the whole house is sitting in
I-I mean, w-what the hell are we
Another dimension!
supposed to do?!
I-I mean, w-what the hell are we
M-m-mom and dad are gonna kill
Supposed to do?!
us!
M-m-mom and dad are gonna kill
I'm losing it here, rick!
Us!
>> rick: Relax, morty, relax!
I'm losing it here, rick!
It's gonna be fine.
>> rick: Relax, morty, relax!
All we have to do is go out and
It's gonna be fine.
find us some kalaxian crystals.
All we have to do is go out and
[ detector beeping ]
Find us some kalaxian crystals.
oh, shit, mother[bleep]
[ detector beeping ]
kalaxian crystals, morty, just a
Oh, shit, mother[bleep]
few miles south of here.
Kalaxian crystals, morty, just a
>> morty: Okay. Let's go, then.
Few miles south of here.
W-w-we got to go get those
>> morty: Okay. Let's go, then.
crystals right now, rick.
W-w-we got to go get those
>> rick: Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Crystals right now, rick.
Morty, morty, I-I can't go with
>> rick: Whoa, whoa, whoa.
you.
Morty, morty, I-I can't go with
I got to hang back and make sure
You.
everything stays cool here, you
I got to hang back and make sure
know?
Everything stays cool here, you
I mean, who knows what -- what
Know?
if somebody breaks something?
I mean, who knows what -- what
>> summer: Yeah. Me too.
If somebody breaks something?
I should stay.
>> summer: Yeah. Me too.
>> you guys have any aspirin?
I should stay.
>> rick: Oh, hey, morty, this is
>> you guys have any aspirin?
perfect!
>> rick: Oh, hey, morty, this is
You can take lincoler with you.
Perfect!
>> hey, man, I'm not going
You can take lincoler with you.
anywhere.
>> hey, man, I'm not going
I'm injured.
Anywhere.
>> rick: Shut up, lincoler.
I'm injured.
It's the [burps] least you can
>> rick: Shut up, lincoler.
do for wrecking the living room.
It's the [burps] least you can
>> summer: Yeah!
Do for wrecking the living room.
And, nancy, you should go, too.
>> summer: Yeah!
>> what? Why -- why me?
And, nancy, you should go, too.
>> summer: Because, uh,
>> what? Why -- why me?
you're -- you're so good at
>> summer: Because, uh,
playing the flute.
You're -- you're so good at
>> sorry for the inconvenience,
Playing the flute.
folks.
>> sorry for the inconvenience,
We should resume sinking
Folks.
shortly.
We should resume sinking
In the meantime, please, stay on
Shortly.
the ship and enjoy a
In the meantime, please, stay on
complimentary plate of
The ship and enjoy a
james cameronion rings.
Complimentary plate of
>> jerry: Great.
James cameronion rings.
Not only is the ship not
>> jerry: Great.
sinking, but now the fourth wall
Not only is the ship not
has been broken.
Sinking, but now the fourth wall
>> beth: [ sighs ]
Has been broken.
I am gonna go back to the room
>> beth: [ sighs ]
to finish my book.
I am gonna go back to the room
You should find that lucy woman.
To finish my book.
>> jerry: But -- but --
You should find that lucy woman.
>> [ clears throat ]
>> jerry: But -- but --
you see, jerry?
>> [ clears throat ]
May I show you something?
You see, jerry?
Had everything gone as planned,
May I show you something?
this entire area would be
Had everything gone as planned,
underwater.
This entire area would be
>> jerry: [ sighs ]
Underwater.
I would have liked to see it.
>> jerry: [ sighs ]
This trip has been a "titanic"
I would have liked to see it.
failure.
This trip has been a "titanic"
Get it?
Failure.
Ooh!
Get it?
>> draw me, jerry.
Ooh!
>> jerry: Oh, boy.
>> draw me, jerry.
Lucy, wow.
>> jerry: Oh, boy.
Uh, this isn't what I had in
Lucy, wow.
mind.
Uh, this isn't what I had in
>> but it's the perfect moment.
Mind.
We've been dreaming about this
>> but it's the perfect moment.
for 16 years.
We've been dreaming about this
>> jerry: Um, not like this.
For 16 years.
Not -- not with you.
>> jerry: Um, not like this.
[ chuckles nervously ]
Not -- not with you.
[ gun cocks ]
[ chuckles nervously ]
>> you are gonna draw me.
[ gun cocks ]
>> jerry: Aah!
>> you are gonna draw me.
>> then you're going to [bleep]
>> jerry: Aah!
me in that car over there.
>> then you're going to [bleep]
>> it's weird, 'cause I
Me in that car over there.
definitely think that all men
>> it's weird, 'cause I
are created equal.
Definitely think that all men
But, at the same time --
Are created equal.
>> morty: Okay!
But, at the same time --
Um, the crystals should be
>> morty: Okay!
really close.
Um, the crystals should be
>> there they are!
Really close.
[ detector beeps ]
>> there they are!
>> wait.
[ detector beeps ]
Something's not right.
>> wait.
[ creature growls ]
Something's not right.
>> [ screams ]
[ creature growls ]
[ creature roars ]
>> [ screams ]
>> get the crystals!
[ creature roars ]
I'll handle the beast!
>> get the crystals!
Prepare to be emancipated from
I'll handle the beast!
your own inferior genes!
Prepare to be emancipated from
[ grunting ]
Your own inferior genes!
>> [ gasps ]
[ grunting ]
summer's gonna like me again.
>> [ gasps ]
[ creature growling ]
Summer's gonna like me again.
>> [ grunts ]
[ creature growling ]
[ grunts ]
>> [ grunts ]
>> morty: Lincoler, come on!
[ grunts ]
Let's get out of here!
>> morty: Lincoler, come on!
>> mein journey is over, morty.
Let's get out of here!
[ groaning ] I have something
>> mein journey is over, morty.
important to tell you.
[ groaning ] I have something
>> ♪ and the gears, they turned
Important to tell you.
for a thousand years ♪
>> ♪ and the gears, they turned
♪ until the dark day that they
For a thousand years ♪
stopped ♪
♪ until the dark day that they
>> morty: [ gasps ]
Stopped ♪
rick, I got them!
>> morty: [ gasps ]
I got the crystals!
Rick, I got them!
>> rick: All right!
I got the crystals!
You did it, morty.
>> rick: All right!
>> morty: Rick, wait!
You did it, morty.
There's something you need to
>> morty: Rick, wait!
know.
There's something you need to
I couldn't have done it without
Know.
lincoler.
I couldn't have done it without
He said that he was really sorry
Lincoler.
and that he loves you like a
He said that he was really sorry
father.
And that he loves you like a
He only wanted you to accept
Father.
him, and he hopes that his final
He only wanted you to accept
act would redeem him in your
Him, and he hopes that his final
eyes.
Act would redeem him in your
He sacrificed himself to save
Eyes.
all of us, rick.
He sacrificed himself to save
He died.
All of us, rick.
>> rick: Well, at least he
He died.
didn't die in vain.
>> rick: Well, at least he
He got these crystals.
Didn't die in vain.
[ sniffs ]
He got these crystals.
and these babies just saved this
[ sniffs ]
lame-ass party!
And these babies just saved this
Wubba, lubba, dub, dub!
Lame-ass party!
Play something.
Wubba, lubba, dub, dub!
S-somebody, play something.
Play something.
[ clicks ]
S-somebody, play something.
>> morty: Wait a minute. What?
[ clicks ]
[ hip-hop music plays ]
>> morty: Wait a minute. What?
>> rick: ♪ put your right foot
[ hip-hop music plays ]
forward and your left foot
>> rick: ♪ put your right foot
back ♪
Forward and your left foot
♪ then slide around like on a
Back ♪
nordictrack ♪
♪ then slide around like on a
♪ move to the left
Nordictrack ♪
♪ step to the right
♪ move to the left
♪ wiggle your elbows, and look
♪ step to the right
up into the light ♪
♪ wiggle your elbows, and look
>> ♪ it's the, it's the
Up into the light ♪
♪ it's the rick dance
>> ♪ it's the, it's the
♪ it's the, it's the
♪ it's the rick dance
>> rick: Slow mobius, hit me
with the clock beam!
[ warbling ]
With the clock beam!
>> ♪ it's the, it's the
[ warbling ]
♪ it's the rick dance
>> ♪ it's the, it's the
>> rick: That's the rick dance!
♪ it's the rick dance
All right!
>> rick: That's the rick dance!
[ burps ] whoa, man!
All right!
[ all cheering ]
[ burps ] whoa, man!
>> morty: What the hell was
[ all cheering ]
that?!
>> morty: What the hell was
I thought those crystals were
That?!
supposed to help us get home or
I thought those crystals were
something!
Supposed to help us get home or
>> rick: What? No, no, no.
Something!
I can get us home whenever I
>> rick: What? No, no, no.
want to.
I can get us home whenever I
But, listen, speaking of those
Want to.
crystals, can I get the rest of
But, listen, speaking of those
them?
Crystals, can I get the rest of
I'm starting to come down,
Them?
morty.
I'm starting to come down,
Crystal kalaxian is a really
Morty.
strong, but fleeting high.
Crystal kalaxian is a really
[ door slides open ]
Strong, but fleeting high.
>> morty: [ grunts ]
[ door slides open ]
that's what I think of your
>> morty: [ grunts ]
crystals, rick!
That's what I think of your
>> rick: Oh, morty, you idiot!
Crystals, rick!
Does anybody else have any more
>> rick: Oh, morty, you idiot!
k-lax?
Does anybody else have any more
B-birdperson?
K-lax?
Uh, squanchy?
B-birdperson?
>> don't squaunch at me.
Uh, squanchy?
>> morty: All right, everybody,
>> don't squaunch at me.
party is officially over!
>> morty: All right, everybody,
Rick, take us home now.
Party is officially over!
>> rick: All right, all right,
Rick, take us home now.
fine, morty, you party pooper
>> rick: All right, all right,
buzzkill!
Fine, morty, you party pooper
Boo, boo! Morty sucks!
Buzzkill!
>> boo! You suck, whatever your
Boo, boo! Morty sucks!
name is.
>> boo! You suck, whatever your
>> rick: Boo!
Name is.
Morty, you're the worst, morty.
>> rick: Boo!
>> boo!
Morty, you're the worst, morty.
>> but these gears just started
>> boo!
turnin'.
>> but these gears just started
>> almost finished, jerry?
Turnin'.
>> jerry: Uh, almost.
>> almost finished, jerry?
I haven't quite captured your
>> jerry: Uh, almost.
beautiful eyes.
I haven't quite captured your
>> I'm sure it's good enough.
Beautiful eyes.
Move!
>> I'm sure it's good enough.
Every weekend, jacks and roses
Move!
have their titanic experience in
Every weekend, jacks and roses
this car, and I have to mop it
Have their titanic experience in
up.
This car, and I have to mop it
The floor drops out to make it
Up.
easier.
The floor drops out to make it
But now it's my turn.
Easier.
We're going to get it nice and
But now it's my turn.
steamy in there, and I'm going
We're going to get it nice and
to slam my hand on the steam and
Steamy in there, and I'm going
leave a nice handprint, and then
To slam my hand on the steam and
you're going to love inside of
Leave a nice handprint, and then
me.
You're going to love inside of
No mess. No clean.
Me.
>> beth: [ grunts ]
No mess. No clean.
>> jerry: Beth!
>> beth: [ grunts ]
>> beth: Bet you're glad I think
>> jerry: Beth!
kindles are dumb now.
>> beth: Bet you're glad I think
I can't help but feel a little
Kindles are dumb now.
guilty.
I can't help but feel a little
I didn't peg lucy for a rapist.
Guilty.
>> jerry: What does a rapist
I didn't peg lucy for a rapist.
look like exactly, beth?
>> jerry: What does a rapist
Is it a slavic man wearing a
Look like exactly, beth?
denim jacket with a patchy beard
Is it a slavic man wearing a
and the scent of cheap champagne
Denim jacket with a patchy beard
wafting over his blister-pocked
And the scent of cheap champagne
lips?
Wafting over his blister-pocked
>> beth: What?
Lips?
Well, at least you got all this
>> beth: What?
free stuff.
Well, at least you got all this
Should be enough to satisfy your
Free stuff.
titanic jones for a while.
Should be enough to satisfy your
>> jerry: [ grunts ]
Titanic jones for a while.
I'm not going to fit.
>> jerry: [ grunts ]
Beth, listen to me.
I'm not going to fit.
You're going to get out of here.
Beth, listen to me.
You're gonna go on, and --
You're going to get out of here.
>> beth: Jerry, just leave the
You're gonna go on, and --
door.
>> beth: Jerry, just leave the
>> jerry: It's not a door, beth.
Door.
It's debris.
>> jerry: It's not a door, beth.
>> beth: I don't care.
It's debris.
Just leave it.
>> beth: I don't care.
>> jerry: Yeah. Okay.
>> [ laughs evilly ]
"cape fear"!
I'm -- I'm doing -- I'm -- I'm
going to do like from
"cape fear."
Going to do like from
[ grunts, groans ]
"cape fear."
[ moaning, screaming ]
>> hey, squanchers!
The party's squanching on at my
place!
[ all cheering ]
Place!
>> summer: Cool.
[ all cheering ]
I'm coming, too.
>> summer: Cool.
>> uh, no.
I'm coming, too.
You're not squanchy enough for a
>> uh, no.
squanchy party.
You're not squanchy enough for a
>> summer: What?
Squanchy party.
>> nancy told us what a bitch
>> summer: What?
you are.
>> nancy told us what a bitch
>> summer: Guys, seriously.
You are.
Nancy?
>> summer: Guys, seriously.
>> summer, you're a bad person.
Nancy?
All you care about is having
>> summer, you're a bad person.
popular people like you.
All you care about is having
That's not what
Popular people like you.
abradolph lincoler stood for.
That's not what
Well, I-it was hard to pin down
Abradolph lincoler stood for.
what he stood for, but it's
Well, I-it was hard to pin down
certainly not what he died for.
>> summer: Next time I party,
I'm just gonna focus on getting
totally wrecked.
You're so wise.
Totally wrecked.
>> rick: [ mumbles ]
You're so wise.
>> may I assist you with that?
>> rick: [ mumbles ]
>> morty: Uh, sure, yeah.
>> may I assist you with that?
Thanks.
>> morty: Uh, sure, yeah.
>> morty, do you know what
Thanks.
"wubba lubba dub dub" means?
>> morty, do you know what
>> morty: Uh, that's just rick's
"wubba lubba dub dub" means?
stupid nonsense catchphrase.
>> morty: Uh, that's just rick's
>> it's not nonsense at all.
Stupid nonsense catchphrase.
In my people's tongue, it means,
>> it's not nonsense at all.
"I am in great pain.
In my people's tongue, it means,
Please help me."
"I am in great pain.
>> morty: Well, I got news for
Please help me."
you.
>> morty: Well, I got news for
He's saying it ironically.
You.
>> no, morty.
He's saying it ironically.
Your grandfather is, indeed, in
>> no, morty.
very deep pain.
Your grandfather is, indeed, in
That is why he must numb
Very deep pain.
himself.
That is why he must numb
>> morty: Come on, um...
Himself.
>> birdperson.
>> morty: Come on, um...
>> morty: Come on, birdperson.
>> birdperson.
Rick's not that complicated.
>> morty: Come on, birdperson.
He's just a huge asshole.
Rick's not that complicated.
>> then why do you care so much
He's just a huge asshole.
if you are no longer allowed to
>> then why do you care so much
continue on your adventures
If you are no longer allowed to
together?
Continue on your adventures
It appears fate has presented
Together?
you with an opportunity to free
It appears fate has presented
yourself of rick forever.
You with an opportunity to free
>> morty: You know what?
Yourself of rick forever.
You're right.
>> morty: You know what?
I shouldn't even care.
You're right.
This is probably the best thing
I shouldn't even care.
that could have happened to me.
This is probably the best thing
I'm sick of having adventures
That could have happened to me.
with rick.
I'm sick of having adventures
>> my people have another
With rick.
saying -- "gubba nub nub doo rah
>> my people have another
kah."
Saying -- "gubba nub nub doo rah
it means, "whatever lets you
Kah."
sleep at night."
It means, "whatever lets you
[ cellphone beeps ]
Sleep at night."
>> summer: Guys, mom and dad
[ cellphone beeps ]
are, like, right around the
>> summer: Guys, mom and dad
corner.
Are, like, right around the
>> this is your moment, morty.
Corner.
Choose wisely.
>> this is your moment, morty.
Tammy!
Choose wisely.
[ grunts ] caw!
>> summer: Wow.
We are so screwed.
>> morty: Rick, wake up.
>> rick: Huh? What? Wait? What?
What? Stop.
>> morty: Rick, you got to do
something quick.
My parents are home.
Something quick.
>> rick: [ groans ]
My parents are home.
uh, all -- all right.
>> rick: [ groans ]
All right. Hold -- hold on.
Uh, all -- all right.
[ gulping ]
All right. Hold -- hold on.
ahh! So good.
[ gulping ]
>> morty: Oh, my god.
Ahh! So good.
They're walking up the driveway.
>> morty: Oh, my god.
>> rick: Bring me the thing.
They're walking up the driveway.
>> morty: What -- what thing?
>> rick: Bring me the thing.
>> rick: The thing. The thing.
>> morty: What -- what thing?
The -- the -- it's got, like,
>> rick: The thing. The thing.
buttons on it and lights on it.
The -- the -- it's got, like,
It -- it -- it beeps.
Buttons on it and lights on it.
>> morty: Rick!
It -- it -- it beeps.
That describes everything in
>> morty: Rick!
your garage!
That describes everything in
>> summer: Do you mean this?
Your garage!
>> rick: Summer for [burps]
>> summer: Do you mean this?
for the win.
>> rick: Summer for [burps]
All right, that should do it.
For the win.
>> morty: Whoa!
All right, that should do it.
What did you do?
>> morty: Whoa!
>> rick: Uh, s-see for yourself.
What did you do?
>> summer: Whoa!
>> rick: Uh, s-see for yourself.
>> rick: Yeah, e-everything's
>> summer: Whoa!
frozen in time.
>> rick: Yeah, e-everything's
Yeah, and slow mobius thinks
Frozen in time.
he's all that.
Yeah, and slow mobius thinks
>> morty: For how long?
He's all that.
>> rick: I don't know.
>> morty: For how long?
How long do you guys want?
>> rick: I don't know.
A week? A month?
How long do you guys want?
>> summer: Can we start cleaning
A week? A month?
the house and see how we feel?
>> summer: Can we start cleaning
[ mid-tempo rock music plays ]
[  epic music plays]
>> rick: Worst movie ever.
>> summer: Dumb.
>> morty: Ooh, boy, what a waste
of time.
[ laughter ]
Of time.
get it?
[ laughter ]
You know, 'cause it's frozen.
Get it?
>> summer: This has been so much
You know, 'cause it's frozen.
fun.
>> summer: This has been so much
>> morty: Hey, rick.
Fun.
You know, this whole time, I
>> morty: Hey, rick.
haven't once heard you say that
You know, this whole time, I
"wubba lubba dub dub" thing that
Haven't once heard you say that
you usually say.
"wubba lubba dub dub" thing that
>> rick: Don't need to.
You usually say.
I have [burps] a new
>> rick: Don't need to.
catchphrase.
I have [burps] a new
>> morty: Oh, yeah?
Catchphrase.
What -- what's that, rick?
>> morty: Oh, yeah?
>> rick: I love my grandkids.
What -- what's that, rick?
>> both: Aww.
>> rick: I love my grandkids.
>> rick: Psych!
>> both: Aww.
Just kidding -- my new
>> rick: Psych!
catchphrase is, "I don't give a
Just kidding -- my new
[bleep]"
Catchphrase is, "I don't give a
♪ just shake that ass, bitch,
[bleep]"
and let me see whatcha got ♪
♪ just shake that ass, bitch,
And let me see whatcha got ♪
and let me see whatcha got ♪
♪ just shake that ass, bitch,
roll credits!
And let me see whatcha got ♪
♪ just shake that a--
Roll credits!
roll the credits! Go!
♪ just shake that a--
♪ just shake that ass
Roll the credits! Go!
that's the end of season one!
♪ just shake that ass
That's the end, mother[bleep]
That's the end of season one!
"I don't give a [bleep]" is my
That's the end, mother[bleep]
new catchphrase!
"I don't give a [bleep]" is my
[bleep] you!
New catchphrase!
That's season one! Boom!
[bleep] you!
Season one up in your face,
That's season one! Boom!
mother[bleep]
Season one up in your face,
yeah!
>> revenge.
What?!
>> party!
>> whoo, baby!
>> [ groans ] please, stop!
>> hey, brah!
>> I don't understand.
Are you enjoying this?
Do you like this?
>> yeah, you know it, dawg!
>> [ gags ]
>> whoo, baby!