Wait up.
Yeah, you should keep up.
I can keep up.
Whoa!
Neato!
Mysterious,
boarded-up cave.
It might be filled with
lost prehistoric life forms.
Or Mesoamerican gold.
Uh, ladies first.
[both giggling]
Ha ha! Good thing you've
got your smarts, Poindexter.
I've got the other thing.
What is it called?
Oh, right, punching.
Cool. Splinters.
Whoa! It's
so creepy in here.
Hey, don't worry, bro.
Wherever we go,
we go together.
Don't forget to leave
our names so they know
who owns the place.
Pines, Pines,
Pines, Pines.
Finally, after all
these long years of waiting,
you're actually here.
Brother!
Ow! What the heck
was that for?
This was an insanely
risky move,
restarting the portal.
Didn't you read
my warnings?
Warnings, schmarnings.
How's about maybe
a thanks for saving you
from what appears to be,
I don't know,
some kinda sci-fi
sideburn dimension.
Thank you? You really think
I'm gonna thank you
after what you did
30 years ago?
What I did?
Why, you ungrateful...
Don't expect me
to go easy on you
just because
you're family.
Hey, hi.
Mabel here.
Quick question.
What the heck
is going on here?
Stan, you didn't tell me
there were children down here.
And some sort of
large, hairless gopher.
Ha ha, I get that a lot.
They're your family,
Poindexter.
Shermy's grandkids.
I have a niece,
and a nephew?
Greetings. Do kids
still say greetings?
I haven't been in
this dimension for
a really long time.
Whoa, six-fingered
handshake.
It's a full finger
friendlier than normal.
Ha ha, I like this kid.
She's weird.
I... I can't believe it.
You're the author
of the journals.
You've read
my journals?
I haven't just read them.
I've lived them.
I've been waiting
for so long to meet you.
I don't know what to say.
I have so many questions.
[hyperventilating]
I think I'm gonna
throw up.
No, no, false alarm.
Just gotta ride it out.
Listen, there'll be time
for introductions later.
But first, tell me, Stan.
Are there any
security breaches?
Does anyone else
know about this portal?
No. Just us.
Also, maybe the entire
U.S. government.
The what?!
Fan out. We're not
going anywhere
till we find Stan Pines
and those kids.
Okay. It's all right.
We've got a while before
they find this room.
We just need to lay low
and think of a plan.
It looks like we're
stuck down here for a while.
Who wants to tell us their
entire mysterious backstory?
Yes, I have some questions
about all this myself, Stanley.
Stanley?
But your name
is Stanford.
Wait, you took my name?
What have you been
doing all these years,
you knucklehead?
Yeah, Grunkle Stan,
no more lies.
You owe us some answers.
What's the deal
with this portal?
Why did you keep
this a secret?
And what happened
between you and your brother?
I'm hoping all this aligns
exactly with my fan-fic, Stan.
If not, I will be
very disappointed.
Okay. Okay, okay.
I know I have
a lot of explaining to do.
It all started
a lifetime ago.
1960-something.
Glass Shard Beach,
New Jersey.
I lived with my ma and pa
in the Lead Paint district
above the family pawn shop.
Dad was a strict man.
Tough as a cinder block,
and not easily impressed.
I'm not impressed.
Mom was
a pathological liar,
which served her well
as a phone psychic.
That'll be 99 cents
an hour.
No, you're overpriced.
Yeah, I predicted
you were gonna hang up.
And then, there was
my nerdy twin brother Stanford.
As if his abnormally high
IQ wasn't enough,
he also had
a rare birth defect--
six fingers on each hand,
which might've explained
his obsession
with sci-fi
mystery weirdness.
As for me, I had what Mom
liked to call personality.
But as different
as we were,
we were the perfect team,
and every day,
we'd wander the beach,
looking for adventure.
Whoa!
A shipwrecked sailboat.
Possibly haunted by
pirate ghosts.
This is the greatest
thing I've ever seen.
And I once saw
a dead rat floating
in a bucket.
[laughing]
Ew. What's wrong with you?
Huh. You know what
this thing's missing?
Flags.
[both] Kings of New Jersey,
kings of New Jersey,
kings of New Jersey!
I dub thee
the  Stan O' War.
Ow! What the heck?
Well, well, if it ain't
the loser twins.
Nice boat. You get it
at the dump?
[giggles]
You would know,
Crampelter. Get lost!
Listen, dorks,
and listen good.
You're
a six-fingered freak,
and you're just
a dumber, sweatier
version of him.
And you're lucky
you have each other,
because neither of you
will ever make any friends.
[laughing]
Dorks
and losers.
Hey, don't let
those idiots get to you.
But I am a freak.
I just wonder if there's
anywhere in the world
where weirdos like me
fit in.
Hey, chin up, buddy.
Look.
One of these days,
you and me are gonna
sail away from
this dumb town.
We'll hunt for treasure,
get all the girls,
and be an unstoppable
team of adventurers.
You really mean it?
High six?
High six.
Those were the good times.
Those bullies may have
been right about us
not making many friends,
but when push comes to shove,
you only really need one.
Ford's brain seemed to get
more impressive every year.
So did our pet project.
Sure, I got in more than
my fair share of trouble,
but when your brother's
the smartest kid in school,
you've always got a leg up
on the competition.
The future was looking
bright for both of us,
till one day.
[  Woman over P.A.] Pines twins
to the principal's office.
Pines twins to
the principal's office.
Ah, great.
What is it this time?
Not you. Him.
Now, Mr. Pines, I'd like to
speak with you
very frankly,
if I may.
Very frankly
is the only way I speak.
You have two sons.
One of them
is incredibly gifted.
The other one is standing
outside this room,
and his name's Stanley.
What are you saying?
I'm saying your son
Stanford is a genius!
All of his teachers
are going bananas
over his science fair
experiment.
You ever heard of
West Coast Tech?
Best college
in the country.
Their graduates turn
science fiction
into science fact.
The admissions team
is visiting tomorrow
to check out
Stanford's experiment.
Your son may be
a future millionaire, Mr. Pines.
I'm impressed.
What about our little
free spirit Stanley?
That clown?
At this rate,
he'll be lucky
to graduate high school.
Look, there's a saltwater
taffy store on the dock,
and somebody's gotta
get paid to scrape
the barnacles off of it.
Stanford's going places, but
hey, look on the bright side.
At least you'll have one son
here in New Jersey forever.
Joke's on them
if they think
you wanna go to
some stuffy college
on the other side
of the country.
Once we get
the  Stan O' War  complete,
it's gonna be
beaches, babes,
and international
treasure hunting for us.
Look, Stan,
I can't pass up
a chance like this.
This school has
cutting-edge programs
and multi-dimensional
paradigm theory.
Be-boop. I am a nerd robot.
That's you.
That's what you sound like.
[chuckles]
Ah, well,
if the college board
isn't impressed with
my experiment tomorrow,
then okay, I'll do
the treasure hunting thing.
And if they are?
Well, then I guess
you better come visit me
on the other side
of the country.
Without Ford, I was just
half of a dynamic duo.
I couldn't make it
out there without him.
And now, thanks to
that dumb college,
I was gonna lose
my brother forever.
This is all your fault,
you dumb machine!
Oh, no. No, no, no.
What did I do?
There. All right.
Good as new.
Probably.
All right, kid,
show us what you got.
Okay. Well,
what would you say
if I told you
the future of technology
was beneath this sheet?
I'd say we wasted
a car trip.
What?
But it was stable yesterday.
A fuse must've blown
or something.
Kid, a perpetual motion
machine has one job--
to not stop.
I don't think you're
West Coast Tech material.
No, wait. Don't go!
I worked so hard.
One paddle paddle paddle,
two paddle paddle.
Man, that Jackie O.
What a fox.
Hey, what's the word,
sixer?
Can you explain
what this was doing
next to my broken
project?
Okay. I might've
accidentally been...
horsing around.
This was no accident, Stan.
You did this.
You did this because
you couldn't handle me
going to college
on my own.
Look, it was a mistake.
Although, if you
think about it,
maybe there's
a silver lining.
Huh? Treasure hunting?
Are you kidding me?
Why would I wanna do
anything with the person
who sabotaged
my entire future?
You did what,
you knucklehead?
Stanley, what's
going on in here?
Wait, no.
I can explain.
It was a mistake.
You ignoramus.
Your brother was gonna be
our ticket outta this dump.
All you ever do
is lie and cheat,
and ride on
your brother's coattails.
Well, this time,
you cost our family
potential millions.
And until you
make us a fortune,
you're not welcome
in this household.
What?! Stanford, tell him
he's being crazy.
Stanford? Don't
leave me hanging.
High six?
Fine! I can make it
on my own.
I don't need you,
I don't need anyone.
I'll make millions,
and you'll rue the day
you turned
your back on me.
Thanks to one dumb mistake,
I had no brother,
no home, no nothing.
But I had a plan
to fix everything.
Oh, this story's
so sad.
I know what you two
little broken teacups need.
To hug it out.
Hug it out.
Hug train
comin' in the station.
Hugapalooza 2000!
Kid, will you
knock that off?
I'm trying to tell
my life story here.
I had decided I wasn't
gonna show my face at home
till I proved I could
make something of myself.
Unfortunately,
the treasure hunting business
was slow going.
Apparently, gold is
some kind of rare metal.
Luckily, I struck
another kind of gold.
In sales.
Hi there.
I'm Stan Pines
of Stanco Enterprises.
Are you sick of this
always happening to you?
Then you need
the chamois of the future.
Made with the same material
astronauts use
to clean up cranberry
stains on the moon.
That's the Sham Total.
It's a total sham.
I had made my mark,
all right.
Unfortunately,
so did the chamois.
Apparently, the cheap dye
I used to color them
only made stains worse.
Customers weren't
crazy about that.
Luckily, they were
chasing me
with Stanco-brand
pitchforks.
Suckers!
I was officially banned
from New Jersey.
But with a quick name change,
Steve Pinington was ready
to take on Pennsylvania.
Hi. I'm Steve Pinington.
Are you sick of bandages
that are hard to remove?
Then what you need is
the Rip Off.
The Rip Off won't
give you rashes.
I repeat, it won't
It gave you rashes.
I traveled
the whole country,
sometimes
outside of it,
always one step ahead
of the law,
looking for something
that would be my big break.
Whoa. So that explains
all the fake ID's.
But wait,
what about you?
Did you end up going
to your dream school?
Not exactly.
All right, I know
Backupsmore
wasn't anyone's
first choice,
but what we lack in prestige
we make up for in
mostly bug-free dorms.
I'm sure your families
are proud.
More or less.
In a place like that,
I had to work twice as hard.
Luckily, that's what
I do best.
I went from undergrad
to PhD
three years ahead
of schedule,
wrote a thesis that was
nationally ranked,
and was awarded
an enormous grant
for my own
scientific research.
But what to study?
My whole life,
I'd been teased
for my six fingers.
But that got me thinking
about anomalies.
Things that were odd,
unusual,
statistically improbable.
And according to
my investigations,
there was one place with
a higher concentration
of these things
than anywhere else.
A small lumber town
in Roadkill County, Oregon.
Gravity Falls.
Meanwhile, your old
Uncle Stan was doing great.
I'd come up with
a sophisticated new
business strategy.
Come on. Owl, owl...
Football player
with an omelet?!
Gah!
I was in great shape,
living on my own,
and the best part was,
I didn't need help from nobody.
[line ringing]
Hello. This is
Stanford Pines.
I was heading out
on my own, as well.
I set to work
using my grant money
to investigate the strange
properties of this town.
But what would
I find here?
Bingo. I began
to investigate at once.
I knew I'd have to record
my findings.
I began to keep
a journal.
[shrieking]
The journals!
Sorry, sorry.
[clearing throat]
Got excited there
about the journals.
Keep talking.
I began to keep
a journal.
[shrieking]
I'm going
to ignore that.
There were anomalies
everywhere.
And the more I looked,
the more I saw.
Fascinating.
What did you say
your name was?
Shmebulock... senior.
It was finally a place
where I felt at home,
but something
nagged at me.
Where did it all
come from?
It seemed to me
the answer must lie
outside of our world,
a dimension of weirdness
leaking into ours.
I realized the only way
to understand Gravity Falls
would be to build
a gateway, a portal
to the source of
its weirdness.
But I couldn't
make it alone.
I decided to call up
my old college buddy,
Fiddleford McGucket,
a young but brilliant
mechanic
who was wasting his talent
trying to make
personal computers
in some garage in
Palo Alto.
[ringing]
Hello. Fiddleford
Computermajigs.
You say you're trying
to build
a trans-universal
poly-dimensional meta vortex?
Well, that's
mathematically feasible,
I reckon.
[spits]
Many long nights were spent
perfecting the machine.
It would be
the crowning achievement
of my studies,
an answer to the source
of this town's anomalies.
Get out, get out,
get out!
The time had come
to test it.
Ready?
And...
[yells]
What?
I got you, buddy.
What is it?
Is it working?
What did you see?
[speaking gibberish]
Fiddleford?
When Gravity Falls
and earth becomes sky,
fear the beast
with just one eye.
Fiddleford, get
a hold of yourself.
You're not making
any sense.
This machine
is dangerous.
You'll bring about
the end of the world with this.
Destroy it before
it destroys us all!
I can't destroy this.
It's my life's work.
I fear we've unleashed
a great danger on the world.
One I'd just
as soon forget.
I quit.
Fine. I'll do it
without you.
I don't need you,
I don't need anyone.
[eerie whispering]
What? Who said that?
I was in
over my head,
and feared I was
losing my sanity.
I needed help.
Someone I could trust.
[pounding on door]
Just give me a few more
days, Rico.
I'll pay your goons back,
I swear.
You haven't seen your brother
in over ten years.
It's okay. He's family.
He won't bite.
Who is it?
Have you come
to steal my eyes?
Well, I can always
count on you
for a warm welcome.
Stanley, did anyone
follow you, anyone at all?
Hello to you, too, pal.
Hey, what is this?
Sorry. I just had to
make sure you weren't...
uh, it's nothing.
Come in, come in.
Are you gonna explain
what's going on here?
You're acting like Mom
after her tenth cup of coffee.
Listen, there
isn't much time.
I've made huge mistakes,
and I don't know
who I can trust anymore.
Hey, easy there.
Let's talk this
through, okay?
I have something
to show you.
Something you won't believe.
I've been around
the world, okay?
Whatever it is,
I'll understand.
There is nothing
about this I understand.
It's a trans-universal
gateway,
a punched hole through
a weak spot in our dimension.
I created it to unlock
the mysteries of the universe.
But it could just as easily
be harnessed
for terrible destruction.
That's why I shut it down
and hid my journals
which explain
how to operate it.
There's only
one journal left.
You are the only person
I can trust to take it.
I have something
to ask of you.
Remember our plans
to sail around the world
on a boat?
Take this book,
get on a boat,
and sail as far away
as you can.
To the edge
of the earth.
Bury it where
no one can find it.
That's it?
You finally wanna see me
after ten years,
and it's to tell me to get as
far away from you as possible?
Stanley, you don't
understand what I'm up against.
What I've been through.
No, no, you don't understand
what I've been through.
I've been to prison
in three different countries.
I once had to chew my way
out of the trunk of a car.
You think you've
got problems?
I've got
a mullet, Stanford.
Meanwhile,
where have you been?
Living it up in
your fancy house
in the woods,
selfishly hoarding
your college money,
because you only
care about yourself.
I'm selfish?
Stanley, how can
you say that
after costing me
my dream school?
I'm giving you a chance
to do the first worthwhile
thing in your life,
and you won't
even listen.
Well, listen to this.
You want me to get rid
of this book?
Fine, I'll get rid of it
right now.
No! You don't understand.
You said you wanted
me to have it,
so I'll do what
I want with it.
My research!
Stanley, give it back.
You want it back,
you're gonna have to
try harder than that.
You left me behind,
you jerk.
It was supposed to be
us forever.
You ruined my life.
You ruined your own life.
Stanley. Oh, my gosh,
I'm so sorry.
Are you all right?
Some brother you
turned out to be.
You care more about
your dumb mysteries
than your family.
Then you can have 'em.
Whoa, whoa, hey.
What's going on?
Hey, Stanford...
Stanley, help me.
What do I do?
Stanley!
Stanley,
do something!
[screaming]
Stanford?
Stanford, come back.
I didn't mean it.
I just got him back.
I can't lose him again.
Come on!
[echoing]
Stanford!
I lost him.
I didn't know
if he was dead or alive
in some distant galaxy,
but I knew his journal
must have the answer
to getting him back...
somehow.
I didn't get
much sleep that night.
Or the night
after that.
I tried for weeks to turn
that dumb machine back on.
But without
the other two journals,
it was hopeless.
Finally,
I ran out of food.
I had no choice
but to go into town.
Just the bread then,
stranger?
That'll be 99 cents.
Hey, that's no stranger.
That must be
the mysterious science guy
that lives in the woods.
No, no, you got
the wrong guy.
I've heard strange stories
about that old shack.
Yeah, mysterious lights
and spooky experiments.
Gosh, I'd pay anything
to see what kind of
shenanigans you get
up to in there.
Me, too.
Do you ever give tours?
No, really, I...
[sighs]
Yes, I do give tours.
Ten... no, no,
15 bucks a person.
[cheering excitedly]
So what did you say
your name was,
you man of mystery?
Oh, Stan... ford.
Stanford Pines.
Step right up, folks,
to a world of
enchantment or whatever.
Behold the nerdy
science box.
[electricity zaps]
Ah! My eye!
Uh, I can assure you,
that is in no way permanent.
I paid $15 for this?
[people grumbling]
Uh, you're lucky you weren't
part of the last tour group.
They never made it
out alive.
[chuckles nervously]
Right?
[laughter]
Funny.
So I came up
with a plan.
I couldn't leave
my brother's house
until I figured out
how to save him.
But I needed to pay
his mortgage somehow.
For once in my life,
people were actually
buying what I was selling.
And so,
the Murder Hut was born.
Later renamed
the Mystery Shack.
Finally, I'd found
something I was good at.
For once, being
a liar and a cheat paid off.
The old me was dead.
And I faked a car crash
to prove it.
By day, I was Stanford Pines,
Mr. Mystery.
But by night, I was
down in the basement,
trying to bring
the real Stanford back.
I couldn't risk anyone
learning the truth
and sabotaging my mission.
So I lied to everyone.
The town, my family,
your parents.
Even you kids.
So all this time,
you were just trying
to save your brother.
Grunkle Stan, I'm so sorry
I didn't believe you.
That's okay, kid.
I probably wouldn't
have believed me either.
[man] I heard talking.
It was coming from downstairs.
We're too late.
The agents are
coming for us.
What'll we do?
Oh, man, I was so spellbound
by your dramatic tale,
I forgot all about
those dudes.
Wait. Forget.
That's it.
I think I know a way we might
be able to defeat those agents.
Of course.
I don't know how you
got a hold of one of these,
but this is perfect.
I can just amplify the signal
to a radio headset frequency.
There. Now everyone,
plug your ears!
Get down now!
Sir, looks like there's
a hidden door
behind the vending machines.
Excellent. Get me
Washington on line one.
I've been practicing making
sounds of excitement for
this very occasion.
Hey, do you hear that?
What? Where am I?
Why am I standing in
some sort of goofy,
fun knick-knack house?
Stand down, gentlemen.
I've been sent with the latest
intel from Washington.
According to this
very real report,
the power surges
in Gravity Falls
were actually
due to radiation
from an unreported
meteor shower.
A total embarrassment
for your whole department.
Luckily, I'm here to take
this mess off your hands.
I'll need all of your
floppy disks,
and, uh, eight tracks.
Right?
Uh, everything about
this case is contained
on this drive.
Well, what are you
waiting for?
A kiss on the cheek?
Get outta here before
I have your butts
court-martialed.
Uh, yes, sir.
Apologies, sir.
[whistles]
False alarm, everyone.
Whoa.
Great-uncle Stanford,
that was amazing.
Let's not go crazy.
It was serviceable.
Ha ha, thank you, kids.
But please, call me Ford.
Sure. Thanks,
great-uncle Ford.
So, uh, would you mind
if I asked you
a couple million questions
about Gravity Falls?
Um, well, I, uh...
All right, kids,
it's been a long day.
Me and my brother have
a lot to talk about.
Why don't you
hit the hay, huh?
But it's the author.
I've been waiting so long
to ask questions about--
I said, hit the hay!
I'll just let myself out.
[phone dialing]
Wendy, I've got something
amazing to tell you.
Clear the next
14 hours.
Look at us.
When did we become
old men?
You look like Dad.
Don't say that.
[both laughing]
[sighs]
Okay, Stanley,
here's the deal.
You can stay here for the summer
to watch the kids.
I'll stay down in
the basement
and try to contain
any remaining damage.
When the summer's over,
you give me
my house back,
my name back,
and this Mystery Shack
junk is over forever.
You got it?
You really aren't gonna
thank me, are you?
Fine. On one condition.
Stay away from the kids.
I don't want them
in danger.
'Cause as far as
I'm concerned,
they're the only family
I have left.
Did you hear
what they said?
I think Uncle Ford said
they're gonna buy us
puppies made of
ice cream.
Might be wishful
thinking, though.
I don't know if this
is good or bad.
I wanted to meet
the author, but...
Yeah. I liked the way
things were here before.
Just us and Stan,
and the occasional
goblin monster.
I'm sure they'll
work things out.
Dipper, you don't think
we'll turn out
like Stan and Ford,
do you?
What do you mean?
I mean, they used to be
best friends,
but then, they got
all stupid.
Can you promise me
you won't get stupid?
Not stupider than you,
dum-dum.
[giggles]
Good night, stupid.
[Soos] Okay, so it turns out
the second Stan,
the Stan
that we know,
was actually Stanley,
but the first Stan
was Stanford,
but we didn't know
until Stanford
came out of the portal,
which was built
by Stanford,
but then Stanley
pretending to be Stanford,
he did the portal
'cause he's Stan,
but he's not Stan.
Soos, it's 3:00
in the morning.
Okay, okay,
I understand.
Anyway, act two,
Stan started...
Aaaah!