[man] So you said let's do the show
about the horse,
- but this time without the horse.
- [woman] I know,
- [man] And I said, "That's a terrible idea."
- - [woman]  I'm sorry. I got...
And you said, "I got someone
even better." Hi guys.
- What's this asshole's name again?
- Vincent D'Onofrio.
- And here we are.
- [director] Okay. Action!
Hey, Zoe. Hey, Zelda.
- I forgot my boombox.
- And your deodorant.
- Pee-yew, mister.
- [audience laughs]
- Zoe, that's no way to get adopted.
- Adopted, by me?
Children, I'm a single
breakdancing instructor
who can barely take care of himself.
Plus, I'm too rad to be a dad.
[rhythmic grunting] Ooh!
And shake it up. Hah!
- [man coughs]
- Cut!
[klaxon blares]
It's fine, Katrina. If I didn't randomly
wander into doors all the time,
I never would have ended up
co-piloting the very plane
that brought me to Los Angeles.
Excuse me, didn't you see
the flashing red light outside the door?
Of course. That's why I stopped...
what I was doing to come inside.
[laughing]
Ooh, are you filming a sitcom?
I love sitcoms!
You should have a character say,
"Talk to the hand."
[laughter]
The hand! Not the face,
where the ears are.
- Newsflash: hands can't hear.
- [laughter and applause]
What do you mean the character
needs to be more likable?
They don't teach likability
at the American Stanislavski Theatre.
Look, this is not about your acting.
You don't want an actor,
you want a blank canvas
upon which to project your own
mawkish notions of goodness.
Some man for all seasons
up for a bit of anything...
Cheerful, optimistic, indomitable.
I assure you no such man exists.
But you're welcome to keep looking.
This D'Onofrio has had enoughfrio.
- Hah hah!
- Hmm.
But my favorite scenes
are when a character
is completely oblivious to something
really important going on behind him.
That, dear friends, is where the sit
truly hits the com.
- Excuse me.
- Kind of in the middle of something.
- He's yakking away, tension's building...
- Hey, you, sir.
The audience is like,
"Hey, turn around."
Maybe the person behind him
even interrupts him...
- Can we talk to you for a second?
- Just like that.
And then, when it would be ridiculous
to go on even one second longer...
- My name is David Chase.
- Do you mind?
Only then does he say,
exasperated,
"What? What do you want?"
I want your face on billboards,
you beautiful nonsensical clown prince.
- Doggie-doggie what now?
- [laughter and applause]
Kid, how'd you like to be the star of
"Untitled Horsin' Around Knockoff"?
Me, a star? But I have
no experience, no formal training.
Hey, you, you don't need
any of those things.
You got "it."
Ohh...
[theme music playing]
[Diane] Hey, BoJack, it's me again.
[yawns] Hmm?
[groans]
I haven't heard from you
in, like, three months,
so I'm calling again
to make sure you're okay.
[overlapping chatter]
What's new with me?
Well...
Monocle? No, I think
you're thinking of Mr. Peanut.
[Diane] I don't know if you heard
but Mr. Peanutbutter
is running for governor, kind of.
I want a comprehensive crisscross
of cold calls to Contra Costa County.
I mean, Christ, people, get me signatures.
First, they need to get Woodchuck
Coodchuck-Berkowitz recalled,
which is basically impossible.
So that actually makes it really easy
for me to be supportive.
- [smooching]
- [chuckles]
- How's the recall effort?
- Stupendous!
Uh, no. We're about 4,000 signatures shy
of stupendous,
and the deadline's in a week.
Even if you don't get all the signatures,
I'll still be proud of you.
Maybe even more so.
But when we do get
the signatures we need...
- Please note I said "when," not "if"...
- Noted.
Then the campaign will begin in...
oh, where did you say again, Katrina?
Earnest. When we get the signatures,
the campaign will begin in earnest.
Right. Earnest, California.
Earnest is not a city in Cal...
Why do I try?
Looks like you two
have everything worked out.
Just please note
that I am being supportive.
Noted!
[Diane] Most women wouldn't like
having their husband's ex-wife
hanging around all the time,
but I'm totally cool with it
because she makes me look
super chill by comparison.
Oh, uh... okay.
Anyway, call me back.
This is Diane, by the way.
Nguyen, obviously.
You sure you wouldn't rather
just play a governor
in a movie or TV show?
I could attach Tommy Schlamme
to direct.
Tommy Schlamme, shmommy Schlamme.
This is bigger than all that.
Don't you recall?
- Recall what?
- The governor. We need signatures.
Oh, sure.
Where do you stand on the issues?
Oh, he doesn't stand anywhere on issues
because he's not running for governor yet.
I'm mainly for people right now
and also for the future.
[groans]
Listen, I'm not feeling so hot.
Why don't you go get
signatures downstairs.
Jennifer Garner's in the lobby.
She'll sign on to anything.
Judah! Can I get your John Wilkes Hancock?
Oh, I never developed a signature.
I find them unnecessarily ostentatious.
But I can print my name legibly.
Thank you, Rain Man-bun.
That'll do nicely.
- Okay.
- [groaning]
Ralph dropped this off for you.
"I always make a beeline
to see my feline." Aww!
Also, you wanted me to remind you about
FX's American Dead Girl miniseries.
Oh, that's right! What train wreck
are we rubbernecking at this year?
They're doing the Sarah Lynn story
and they're looking
for someone to play BoJack.
Oh! [retching, coughing]
Well, as I was saying, FX is looking
for a BoJack Horseman...
[retching, clearing throat] Ugh!
- Horseman... Ho...
- [retching]
- [moaning]
- So, as we discussed earlier,
is this one of the moments
where you would want privacy?
You know what I'd do
if I had eight million dollars?
- Yeah, you'd give it to the waitress.
- Oh, no, no, no.
I mean, if I had
eight million dollars now,
I'd start a company that makes
remote-controlled drones.
But these drones have a seat
hanging from the bottom
so you can fly around in it.
A drone with a throne.
A drone throne.
But if you're in it, isn't it not a drone?
I feel like you're getting
really hung up on labels.
Well, anyways,
with my eight million dollars
I'm starting a new dating app
just for firemen
and redheaded women named Emily.
Aww, you don't need an app,
just hang out with me.
Todd, you're great.
What a way to end a sentence.
But I want a boyfriend who isn't asexual.
Whoa. Why did you call me that?
No, no, it's not bad.
I didn't mean it negatively.
- I was just, like, stating it.
- I'm not... that word doesn't describe...
Okay, okay, I'm sorry,
whatever you call yourself,
you're my friend and I support you.
But sometimes labels can be helpful.
Wow. Well, I would label
this conversation "rough".
Here's the check.
And this cow likes getting tipped.
[Diane] Hey, BoJack, it's me again,
voicemail number 17.
Did I tell you I'm working at a blog?
I wrote a story about
an all-girl refugee kickball league.
It didn't get as many clicks as Gillian's
story about how in certain pictures
you can see the outline
of Chris Hemsworth's penis
but, you know, we're all contributing
in our own ways.
Anyway, it's weird not having you around.
I hope you're okay, wherever you are.
"I'm so smitten
with my favorite little adult cat."
Oh! I love it.
I'm sorry I couldn't make it
to the Paul Blart 3: Till Death
Do Us Blart premiere last night.
I had a doctor's appointment.
- Whoa. Is everything okay?
- Yeah, yeah, it's fine.
I don't like not knowing where you are,
especially when we live three freeways
and an unprotected left turn
away from each other.
I was thinking, what if you move
somewhere closer to me,
like into my house?
Oh. [stammers] Wow!
Would you, could you, with a mouse?
I... I could, and I would,
but it's not a good time.
Oh, okay.
- I'm sorry.
- No, no, it's fine. There's no hurry.
- We're still young, right?
- Oh, yeah, I'm super young.
Blake Lively accidentally
called me Mommy yesterday,
but I'm sure she does that
to other young women all the time.
[moaning, slurping]
[doorbell rings]
[gasps] Churro-flavored waffles!
- [doorbell ringing]
- Huh?
[gasps]
Drone Throne.
Whoa, whoa!
Okay, Todd. Whoa!
Oh, God, today's the day.
I haven't been this nervous
since Diane was vacuuming
during a thunderstorm
on the Fourth of July,
I had to take a bath,
and there was a stranger in our yard.
There's no need to be nervous,
or calm for that matter
because you've already lost.
We're 1,600 signatures short
and the clock runs out at 9:00 AM.
So it's gonna take a miracle, huh?
[buzzer blaring]
Oh, no! It's over.
Everyone can get out of my house now.
Ooh, tough break, kid.
We're all in shock.
McG! Are you still looking for a star
for your transgender Teddy Roosevelt
Planes, Trains and Automobiles reboot,
Plans, Trans, A Man, A Canal, Panama?
Because someone just became available.
Whoa! Whoa!
I don't understand what happened.
Let me put it in terms
your dumb dog brain can comprehend.
All your life people have been
throwing you bones
because they like you,
but everyone has a ceiling
to their likability.
This is a bone you can't have,
because people just don't like you enough.
- I'm sorry, Mr. Peanutbutter.
- You know, it's funny.
Personally I like Woodchuck
and he's a fine governor,
but for some reason, even though
I have zero qualifications,
I honestly thought I would have made
an even better governor.
- Well, what matters is you tried.
- But I would have been good, right?
Now that there's no chance
you will ever be governor,
I can tell you honestly...
- Yes. You would have been great.
- [chuckles]
Stop. But seriously, though, elaborate.
You care about people,
you follow your heart.
Those are important qualities
you should never give up on.
So what you're saying is
I shouldn't give up?
- On those qualities.
- Yeah. Never concede.
- Stick it out, stay in the race.
- Uh... no...
Uh, maybe we should get
Katrina's two cents on this.
- Katrina?
- Race. That's it, Diane!
You diabolical Thin Mint.
You, and only you, are responsible
for the great thing I am about to do.
Katrina?
- [applause]
- [deep breath]
Thank you, thank you.
Moments ago I found myself
in what seemed to be a no-win situation.
But it turns out
it was a "Nguyen situation."
I'm referring of course
to my supportive wife Diane Nguyen,
- who told me to never give up!
- [groans]
And that's why I am challenging
Woodchuck Coodchuck-Berkowitz
- to a ski race down Devil's Mountain.
- What?
No more petitions
or fancy ballot initiatives,
just a mano a mano,
no-holds-barred slippery slalom
down an ice-covered peak.
Winner gets to be governor,
loser goes home.
Your move, Governor.
Mic drop!
- [feedback squeal]
- [cheers and applause]
- Aaah!
- [cheering]
[Woodchuck]
What the hell is he talking about?
It sounds like he's challenging you
to a ski race down Devil's Mountain.
What an absurd conceit.
Do I even need to respond to this?
No, sir.
Because I'd rather focus
on my drought relief optimization
using geohydration technology,
or DROUGHT plan.
If I know anything, this story
will go away in a couple of days.
Now Mr. Peanutbutter, you challenged
Woodchuck to a ski race a month ago.
Not just any ski race, a high-stakes dash
down Devil's Mountain
- for the governorship itself.
- But still no comment from the governor.
Why won't he race you?
That's what I want to know.
You and me both, friendo.
But this isn't an us-ocracy,
it's a dem-ocracy.
- [audience] Ooh!
- So let's ask "dem" what "dey" think.
- [cheers and applause]
- Any questions for the governor, folks?
[audience chants]
Why won't Woodchuck race?
So, to be clear, my DROUGHT plan
is actually a drought relief plan.
I see now how that's confusing.
Any other questions?
Are you going to race Mr. Peanutbutter?
Any questions about the DROUGHT plan?
To ski or not to ski?
That was the question
posed by William Shakespeare
and it's perhaps even more relevant today.
Of course, there are reasons
why a gubernatorial election
should not be decided by a ski race,
but are there also reasons
why it should?
For the sake of "fairness"
we've brought in two experts
with opposite opinions
who will now have equal time
to just say those opinions
because that's what news is.
You think they'll really race
down Devil's Mountain?
What do I care? As long as I've got
my giant bag of kettle corn,
that's the only thing that concerns me.
- [Todd grunts]
- [gasps]
- What the?
- Drone Throne strikes again! Ha ha!
Get back here with my kettle corn!
You can't call it a drone
if you're riding on it.
Suckers! Hooray!
Ha ha! Oh... oh, no!
Aw, man.
I was hoisted by my own petard,
the one petard I thought
would never hoist me.
[Woodchuck] Unprecedented poppycock.
This poppycock has no precedent.
Maybe it's time to make a statement.
Madeline, no.
This outlandish buffoonery
is beneath the office of the governor.
I can't defile the legacy
of my predecessors
who built the Golden Gate Bridge,
irrigated the Central Valley,
and played Mr. Freeze in a Batman movie.
Can't you see this thing
is eating you alive?
Do it for us, Woodcharles.
Do it for us.
[groans]
And so this ski race would be both
undemocratic and unconstitutional,
which is why I will not be racing
Mr. Peanutbutter down Devil's Mountain.
What if the state constitution
were changed to allow it?
- Then would you race Mr. Peanutbutter?
- I... [sighs]
Fine. If a state senator
wanted to waste everybody's time
by sponsoring an amendment
to the constitution,
and the motion got two-thirds majority
in both houses
so as to allow
a democratically-elected governor
to accept a ski race challenge
for his office,
then yes, I would race Mr. Peanutbutter.
Well, I guess that puts
that idea to bed, right?
- Hmm.
- Right?
- Hmm... [chuckles]
- Right?!
You want me to sponsor a ski race
amendment to the constitution?
Or you could sponsor the amendment
that has a hidden rider
doubling farm subsidies in your district.
- Inglewood could use some farms.
- That's right.
I do have these campaign donors...
Uh, I mean, constituents
who really care about babies' access
to vaping devices.
- [coughing]
- Uh-huh.
I've always wanted to drive across
a bridge to Hawaii.
- Can we do that?
- You got it.
Aloha! [giggles]
Hoo hoo hoo hoo! Whoo!
[chuckles] It tickles.
[sighs]
I'm astounded that it has come to this.
But since the exorbitantly expensive
and astonishingly titled I Love California
amendment is now law,
I formally accept Mr. Peanutbutter's
challenge to a ski race.
It happens that I'm an excellent skier
who won numerous medals in the sport
when I raced for Dartmouth
but, again, I am shocked
that fact is relevant
in the matter of selecting
our state's governor.
Mr. Peanutbutter, I will see you
on Devil's Mountain.
- Whoa!
- This is insane.
You could actually become governor
by winning a race.
Yeah. Wow.
You know, it's days like this
I wish I knew how to ski.
- You don't ski?
- Never really got into it, no.
Then why did you challenge the governor
to a ski race?
[chuckles] I didn't think
it would get this far.
You gotta admit, this is pretty out there.
Well, I guess that's it. Oh, well.
Tough break. Bye forever, Katrina.
No, this is not over.
This is just beginning.
Mr. Peanutbutter,
you're going to ski school.
Doggie-doggie what now?
[Diane] Hey, BoJack, it's me again.
Where are you, I'm worried,
hope you're not dead,
etc... you get it.
Anyway, things are even crazier
around here lately.
Don't know if you've seen the news,
but I really wish you were here for this.
Well, I'm off to ski school
so I can learn how to ski,
so I can become the governor.
[Diane] Y ou'd say something like,
"That's the dumbest thing
I've ever heard."
Sounds great, sweetheart.
But as the old saying goes,
that's politics.
[Diane] Then you'd probably say,
"A, that's not an old saying
and, B, that's not politics!
Nothing about that is politics."
This is so great!
Then you would be so overwhelmed
by the unbearable ludicrousness
of the situation
that you would get in your car
and drive to Hawaii,
which is also a thing you could do now
because of a new bill
that cost our state billions of dollars.
It's all so great!
[sighs] You know, it's funny,
because the last time I saw you
you told me that you needed me
in your life,
and then you just disappeared.
So how do you think
that makes me feel?
Well, wherever you are,
I hope you're happy.
I really do, BoJack.
Also, I haven't seen Todd in a while.
He's not with you, is he?
[munching]
Oh, simple kettle corn.
Between the worlds of the sweet
and the savory.
Not quite popcorn, not quite candy.
- What are we?
- [cawing]
Hey, get away! Get, get!
[gasping, choking]
Wow, my first day at ski academy.
What collegiate shenanigans
will befall me?
There will be no shenanigans
on my watch.
Professor Thistlethorpe,
the famously humorless yet somehow
also lovable ski instructor?
Peanutbutter, is it?
Everything about you disgusts me.
Uh...
And yet, there might be
something in you after all.
You really mean it?
This shall be my greatest challenge.
Meet me on the summit
tomorrow at daybreak.
Well, it is daybreak
and here we are at the summit.
First lesson, break your skis in half.
Oh, I don't have skis.
Was I supposed to bring skis?
- You didn't say that.
- No bother. They shan't be required.
Instead, read this book of poetry.
I'll see you in the classroom.
Ah, there you are.
Did you read the book of poetry?
No! I forgot to.
- Excellent.
- I'm sor... Excellent?
My assignment was a test.
Skiing isn't about reading old books.
- It's about speaking truth to power...
- Oh!
And you have spoken it eloquently.
You are my finest student.
I love you.
[coughing]
- Are you okay, professor?
- Just a cough.
I'm sure it's nothing. You can come by
tomorrow for your diploma.
I can't believe ski school
is already over.
Professor Thistlethorpe?
Professor Thistlethorpe!
[weakly] Remember everything
I taught you.
I will.
Also, if you have any tips for skiing,
that would be really helpful.
The most important part of skiing
is to keep your legs ben...
[sobbing]
Who's Ben?
Devil's Mountain is the place,
skiing is the sport.
I'm uncomfortable.
It's cold out.
Tell me, who do you think
will win today's bout
and what does it mean
for the future of California?
I hate winter sports.
I want to go inside and drink a cider.
- [starter's pistol firing]
- And they're off!
[grunts, yelling]
[Tom] Woodchuck, off to a great start.
Mr. Peanutbutter seems to be employing
some sort of awkwardly
falling down technique.
- Any sign of them?
- Nothing yet.
- Oh! I made you a card.
- You did?
[chuckles] Oh, wow, it's sparkly.
Sorry, I went a little overboard
with the glitter
and a little underboard with the glue.
[Ralph] "Let's move in together.
I think I'm ready now."
This is great.
Are you sure, though,
because last time you seemed
a little hesitant.
- No, I was just a little pregnant.
- Oh!
I was gonna tell you, really,
but then before I could tell you
there was nothing to tell you.
Oh.
I'm so sorry. I still wish
you would've told me.
I have a card for that. On the front
it says, "Life isn't fairage."
I'm sorry. I just felt dumb
because all my life I've wanted a family.
But I didn't want it to happen
just because I got pregnant by accident
- and then you got stuck with me.
- Okay, first of all,
if I get stuck to something,
you're the prettiest glue trap I ever saw.
- You know what I mean.
- Second, if that's how you feel,
maybe you shouldn't get pregnant
by accident.
- Well, I didn't try to!
- No.
I'm saying maybe we should
get you pregnant on purpose.
- Really?
- Yeah.
We love each other,
and we enjoy having sex with each other...
And we're good
at having sex with each other.
And also, I think you'd be
an amazing mother.
- [sighs]
- Even Blake Lively thinks so.
Ah, still got it.
Yes!
[grunting, yelling]
Whoa! Whoa-ho-ho!
Ohh! Get control.
Woodchuck in the lead,
still in the lead.
Woodchuck remains
very much in the lead.
Goodbye, dear friend.
You served me well.
[gasps] Okay, all right, here we go.
Mr. Peanutbutter?
Ohh! [yelling]
[grunting, gasping]
[yelling]
[gasping]
[panting]
I see Woodchuck!
Yes!
Go, Woodcharles!
Oh... whoa... [grunts] Whoa!
Oh, my God.
Todd forever!
Whaa!
- [crowd gasping]
- Ow, ow, ow, ow! [grunts]
- [crowd cheering]
- Invictus!
- [groaning, grunts]
- Ooh! Ooh.
- [moaning]
- Oh... ohh.
- Did I win?
- Come on, honey.
Let's go home.
- [applause]
- Well, I hope that settles it.
We can finally put an end
to this nonsense.
Sir, the rules are clear: the first person
to cross the finish line becomes governor,
and, well, a strange boy
fell out of the sky
and crossed the line first.
They're swearing him in now.
- So help me Todd.
- Congratulations, Governor Chavez.
[cheers and applause]
You know, ever since
I first became governor
I've thought,
"I don't want to be governor"
and that's where I am now.
So, can I not be governor?
[groaning and gasping]
You'd like to resign?
Yeah. I'm just really not
into labels right now.
Maybe after some soul searching
I'll be ready to really know what I am.
But for right now,
I think I speak for all Californians
when I say, "I ate too much kettle corn
while drifting through the sky
on an out of control drone throne."
Okay, is this charade over?
Can I be governor again?
Sir, we live in a society of laws.
When a governor resigns,
that triggers a special election.
Until which, the governor's seat
shall remain vacant.
- [all gasping]
- Election, you say?
Mr. Peanutbutter, will you run?
- You bet I will, and you know why?
- No, tell me.
Because this whole ski race was a joke.
Of course Woodchuck was gonna beat me.
He went to Dartmouth.
So where's the candidate
for regular schmoes like me,
- who went to Northwestern?
- Is he serious right now?
You know, Governor Woodchuck
Coodchuck-Berkowitz
thinks he's better than us,
but is he better than us?
- [crowd] No!
- Uh, if I could say a few words...
He thinks the race is over.
Well, I say it's just starting.
And he wants me to sit and stay
and roll over?
- No!
- I say California's tired of rolling over.
What do you say?
- [crowd] Yeah!
- [woman] I'm tired.
I say it's time for me
to stand up and speak.
- [cheering]
- Diane-Diane what now?
So loud as you can,
let me hear what you want.
[chanting] Peanutbutter!
Peanutbutter!
- Uh, citizens...
- I can't hear you!
Peanutbutter!
- Peanutbutter!
- [nervous chuckle]
- Friends, some decorum, please.
- Peanutbutter! Peanutbutter!
- [grunts] Ah! [panting]
Peanutbutter! Peanutbutter!
Peanutbutter!
[line ringing]
- [voicemail] The mailbox belonging to...
- BoJack Horsemack...
- Horseman... oh, wait, how do I...
- [voicemail]...is full. Goodbye.
♪ Back in the '90s
I was in a very famous TV show ♪
[laughing]
- ♪ I'm Mr. Peanutbutter ♪
- ♪ Ooh, yeah ♪
♪ Now tell me
How can I get no votes? ♪
♪ Yeah, I'm for the future
Yeah, everyone will get a free TV ♪
- ♪ All right! ♪
- ♪ I'll put my face on billboards ♪
♪ The entire world will see ♪
♪ Yeah, I promise peace and love
Across this broken land ♪
♪ Yeah, I'm your governor
Mr. Peanutbutter man ♪
♪ I'm tasty and good-lookin'
'Cause that's just who I am ♪
♪ Go vote! ♪
Boxer vs. Raptor,
♪ Na-na na-na na-na na-na! ♪