>> beth: So, dad, guess what
tomorrow is.
>> rick: Martin luther king
Tomorrow is.
jr.'s birthday.
>> rick: Martin luther king
>> beth: No.
Jr.'s birthday.
Well, it...Might be.
>> beth: No.
>> rick: It is.
Well, it...Might be.
>> beth: Fine.
>> rick: It is.
But also, tomorrow is your
>> beth: Fine.
one-year anniversary back in our
But also, tomorrow is your
lives.
One-year anniversary back in our
I'm gonna make you
Lives.
flying-saucer-shaped pancakes.
I'm gonna make you
>> rick: Oh, t-t-there's no need
Flying-saucer-shaped pancakes.
to do that, beth.
>> rick: Oh, t-t-there's no need
Regular pancakes are fine.
To do that, beth.
[ loud warble ]
[ all scream ]
>> morty: [ groans ]
>> jerry: Oh, my god!
Oh, what is happening?!
>> beth: Happy anniversary, dad.
>> rick: Oh, I get it.
Regular pancakes are already
shaped like flying saucers.
Mmm.
Shaped like flying saucers.
I-I should be making you
Mmm.
breakfast for putting up with
I-I should be making you
me.
Breakfast for putting up with
>> jerry: You should be making
Me.
us a whole restaurant.
>> jerry: You should be making
>> beth: Nonsense.
Us a whole restaurant.
We couldn't be happier to have
>> beth: Nonsense.
you around.
We couldn't be happier to have
I just wish I got to see more of
You around.
you.
I just wish I got to see more of
[ loud warble ]
You.
>> rick sanchez of earth
[ loud warble ]
dimension c-137, you are under
>> rick sanchez of earth
arrest for crimes against
Dimension c-137, you are under
alternate ricks by the authority
Arrest for crimes against
of the trans-dimensional council
Alternate ricks by the authority
of ricks.
Of the trans-dimensional council
>> jerry: Hey! What the heck?!
Of ricks.
>> neutralize the jerry.
>> jerry: Hey! What the heck?!
>> jerry: Wait! No! I'll --
>> neutralize the jerry.
>> summer: Dad!
>> jerry: Wait! No! I'll --
>> beth: Dad!
>> summer: Dad!
>> morty: Rick!
>> beth: Dad!
>> rick: Everybody, relax.
>> morty: Rick!
If I know these a-holes, and I
>> rick: Everybody, relax.
am these a-holes, they just
If I know these a-holes, and I
want to haul me to their stupid
Am these a-holes, they just
clubhouse and waste my time with
Want to haul me to their stupid
a bunch of questions.
Clubhouse and waste my time with
Let's get it over with.
A bunch of questions.
>> bring his [burps] morty.
Let's get it over with.
>> morty: Oh, man.
>> bring his [burps] morty.
>> rick: Leave my [burps] morty
>> morty: Oh, man.
out of this.
>> rick: Leave my [burps] morty
>> you lost the right to have a
Out of this.
say in these things when you
>> you lost the right to have a
refused to j-- [burps] join the
Say in these things when you
council.
Refused to j-- [burps] join the
>> beth: W-w-w-what about jerry?
Council.
>> rick: Will you at least
>> beth: W-w-w-what about jerry?
unfreeze my daughter's idiot?
>> rick: Will you at least
>> jerry: ...Give you anything!
Unfreeze my daughter's idiot?
I have a rare antique-coin
>> jerry: ...Give you anything!
collection!
I have a rare antique-coin
Just don't hurt me!
Okay, maybe not antique, but it
was a limited minting.
They have little r2-d2s instead
Was a limited minting.
of george washington.
They have little r2-d2s instead
>> beth: Our son's been
Of george washington.
abducted!
>> beth: Our son's been
>> jerry: You hate me for buying
Abducted!
those coins!
>> morty: Geez, rick, w-what is
this place?
>> rick: The citadel of ricks.
This place?
It's the secret headquarters for
>> rick: The citadel of ricks.
the council of ricks.
It's the secret headquarters for
>> morty: Council of ricks?
The council of ricks.
>> rick: As you know, morty,
>> morty: Council of ricks?
I've got a lot of enemies in the
>> rick: As you know, morty,
universe that consider my genius
I've got a lot of enemies in the
a threat -- galactic terrorists,
Universe that consider my genius
a few sub-galactic dictators,
A threat -- galactic terrorists,
most of the entire intergalactic
A few sub-galactic dictators,
government.
Most of the entire intergalactic
W-w-wherever you find people
Government.
with heads up their asses,
W-w-wherever you find people
someone wants a piece of your
With heads up their asses,
grandpa, and a lot of versions
Someone wants a piece of your
of me on different timelines had
Grandpa, and a lot of versions
the same problem, so a few
Of me on different timelines had
thousand versions of me had the
The same problem, so a few
ingenious idea of banding
Thousand versions of me had the
together like a herd of cattle
Ingenious idea of banding
or a school of fish or those
Together like a herd of cattle
people who answer questions on
Or a school of fish or those
yahoo! Answers.
People who answer questions on
>> morty: Hey! What do you know?
Yahoo! Answers.
It's a cowboy version of me.
>> morty: Hey! What do you know?
>> rick: Geez, you're easy to
It's a cowboy version of me.
impress.
>> rick: Geez, you're easy to
Yeah, most timelines have a
Impress.
rick, and most ricks have a
Yeah, most timelines have a
morty.
Rick, and most ricks have a
This place is a real who's who
Morty.
of who's you and me.
This place is a real who's who
>> turn your boring, old morty
Of who's you and me.
into a f-- hot fashion statement
>> turn your boring, old morty
with some morty dazzlers.
Into a f-- hot fashion statement
>> hey, check this out.
With some morty dazzlers.
>>   show me the morty.
>> hey, check this out.
>> rick: Dumb.
>>   show me the morty.
>> excuse me, sir, is your morty
>> rick: Dumb.
insured?
>> excuse me, sir, is your morty
You know, every year, hundreds
Insured?
of mortys are injured --
You know, every year, hundreds
>> rick: Back off!
Of mortys are injured --
Not my cup of tea, this place.
>> rick: Back off!
I say the point of being a rick
Not my cup of tea, this place.
is being a rick.
I say the point of being a rick
>> save your anti-rick speech
Is being a rick.
for the council of ricks,
>> save your anti-rick speech
terror-rick.
For the council of ricks,
>> rick: Hey, save your rick
Terror-rick.
rules for the [burps]
>> rick: Hey, save your rick
sheep-ricks, rick-pig.
Rules for the [burps]
>> [bleep] me, pal.
Sheep-ricks, rick-pig.
>> rick: [bleep] you?
>> [bleep] me, pal.
No, no, no, no, no.
>> rick: [bleep] you?
[bleep] me.
>> bring up the holograms.
27 ricks brutally murdered in
their own timelines -- an
unprecedented rick-icidal
Their own timelines -- an
epidemic.
Unprecedented rick-icidal
What say you, earth rick c-137?
Epidemic.
>> rick: You think I did this?
What say you, earth rick c-137?
Why am I the first rick you pull
>> rick: You think I did this?
in every time a rick stubs his
Why am I the first rick you pull
toe?
In every time a rick stubs his
>> you [burps] have a history of
Toe?
non-cooperation with the
>> you [burps] have a history of
council.
Non-cooperation with the
>> rick: Yeah, so does the
Council.
scientist formerly known as
>> rick: Yeah, so does the
rick.
Scientist formerly known as
W-w-w-w-w-why isn't he here in
Rick.
handcuffs?
W-w-w-w-w-why isn't he here in
>> because he's dead, too!
Handcuffs?
[ crowd gasping, groaning ]
>> because he's dead, too!
who else would you have us
[ crowd gasping, groaning ]
question?
Who else would you have us
You fit the profile.
Question?
Of all the ricks in the central
You fit the profile.
finite curve, you're the
Of all the ricks in the central
malcontent, the rogue.
Finite curve, you're the
>> rick: I'm the rick, and so
Malcontent, the rogue.
were the rest of you before you
>> rick: I'm the rick, and so
formed this stupid alliance.
Were the rest of you before you
You wanted to be safe from the
Formed this stupid alliance.
government, so you became a
You wanted to be safe from the
stupid government.
Government, so you became a
That makes every rick here less
Stupid government.
rick than me.
That makes every rick here less
[ crowd grumbling ]
Rick than me.
yeah, murmur it up, d-bags.
[ crowd grumbling ]
Now, if you'll excuse me, I've
Yeah, murmur it up, d-bags.
got pancakes back home with
Now, if you'll excuse me, I've
syrup on top of them.
Got pancakes back home with
They're about to hit that
Syrup on top of them.
critical point of syrup
They're about to hit that
absorption that turns the cakes
Critical point of syrup
into a gross paste, and I hate
Absorption that turns the cakes
to get all andy rooney about it,
Into a gross paste, and I hate
but I think we all like fluffy
To get all andy rooney about it,
disks of cake with syrup on top,
But I think we all like fluffy
and I think we also like to be
Disks of cake with syrup on top,
accused of crimes when there's
And I think we also like to be
evidence!
Accused of crimes when there's
So, as they say in canada,
Evidence!
peace oot!
So, as they say in canada,
>> evidence! Good idea.
Peace oot!
Scan his portal gun!
>> evidence! Good idea.
>> rick: Oh, come on.
Scan his portal gun!
Don't look at another man's
>> rick: Oh, come on.
portal-gun history.
Don't look at another man's
We -- we all go to weird places.
Portal-gun history.
>> yes, but it appears you alone
We -- we all go to weird places.
have been going to the exact
>> yes, but it appears you alone
timelines and locations in which
Have been going to the exact
the murders occurred.
Timelines and locations in which
[ crowd grumbling ]
The murders occurred.
>> rick: What?!
[ crowd grumbling ]
That's rick-diculous!
>> rick: What?!
I'm obviously being set up.
That's rick-diculous!
>> earth rick c-137, the council
I'm obviously being set up.
of ricks sentences you to the
>> earth rick c-137, the council
machine of unspeakable doom,
Of ricks sentences you to the
which swaps your conscious and
Machine of unspeakable doom,
unconscious minds, rendering
Which swaps your conscious and
your fantasies pointless while
Unconscious minds, rendering
everything you've known becomes
Your fantasies pointless while
impossible to grasp.
Everything you've known becomes
Also, every 10 seconds, it stabs
Impossible to grasp.
your balls.
Also, every 10 seconds, it stabs
>> rick: I've heard enough.
Your balls.
[ burps ]
>> rick: I've heard enough.
run, morty!
[ burps ]
>> morty: [ panting ]
Run, morty!
>> unh-unh. Not you.
>> morty: [ panting ]
aaaah!
>> [ screams ]
[ loud farting ]
[ steady farting in distance ]
>> morty: Oh! Oh!
[ dialing ]
>> yeah, I'd like to order one
large person with extra people,
please.
Large person with extra people,
>> white people.
Please.
No, no, no, no. Black people.
>> white people.
And hispanic on half.
No, no, no, no. Black people.
>> morty: [ panting ]
[ dialing ]
>> yes, I'd like to order one
large sofa chair with extra
chair, please.
Large sofa chair with extra
>> high chair.
Chair, please.
No, no, no, no. Recliner.
>> high chair.
And wheelchair on half.
No, no, no, no. Recliner.
>> morty: [ panting ]
And wheelchair on half.
[ all speaking gibberish ]
>> they could have gone into any
one of these.
>> [ groans ]
One of these.
son of a...
>> [ groans ]
>> oh, geez.
Son of a...
>> oh, man!
>> oh, geez.
>> we lost 'em.
>> oh, man!
>> yeah, I'd like to order one
>> we lost 'em.
large phone with extra phones,
>> yeah, I'd like to order one
please.
Large phone with extra phones,
>> cellphone.
Please.
No, no, no, no. Rotary.
>> cellphone.
And pay phone on half.
No, no, no, no. Rotary.
>> rick: That'll keep 'em
And pay phone on half.
[burps] busy for a while.
>> morty: Those guys were wrong,
right?
Y-y-y-you d-- you wouldn't kill
Right?
yourself -- y-y-yourselves.
Y-y-y-you d-- you wouldn't kill
>> rick: Of course not, morty.
Yourself -- y-y-yourselves.
How could that profit me?
>> rick: Of course not, morty.
But someone out there is killing
How could that profit me?
ricks, and the council ain't
But someone out there is killing
gonna stop thinking it's me
Ricks, and the council ain't
until we clear our names --
Gonna stop thinking it's me
by finding the real rick-killer.
Until we clear our names --
>> morty: I'm scared, rick.
By finding the real rick-killer.
Maybe we should go home and
>> morty: I'm scared, rick.
stockpile weapons, like that
Maybe we should go home and
show "doomsday preppers."
Stockpile weapons, like that
>> rick: Not really my style,
Show "doomsday preppers."
morty.
>> rick: Not really my style,
Besides, your home is most
Morty.
likely swarming with ricks by
Besides, your home is most
now.
>> all right, listen, jerry.
If rick calls, this device is
gonna trace his location.
You just got to keep him on the
Gonna trace his location.
phone for 30 seconds or longer.
You just got to keep him on the
>> beth: Who wants lemonade?
Phone for 30 seconds or longer.
>> oh, yeah.
>> beth: Who wants lemonade?
Mmm!
>> oh, yeah.
Oh! Delicious!
Mmm!
>> beth [belches] you're a
Oh! Delicious!
treasure.
>> beth [belches] you're a
>> I have a beth just like you
Treasure.
in my [belches] reality, except
>> I have a beth just like you
you know what?
In my [belches] reality, except
She's not as brilliant or
You know what?
[belches] attractive.
She's not as brilliant or
>> beth: Aw.
[belches] attractive.
Th[belches]ank you.
>> beth: Aw.
[ laughter ]
Th[belches]ank you.
>> oh! She did! She did it!
[ laughter ]
[ telephone rings ]
>> jerry: H-hello?
>> rick: Hey, jerry, it's rick.
>> jerry: Rick! Hey.
[ laughs nervously ]
what's -- what's up?
>> rick: So, listen, the heat's
What's -- what's up?
on, and there's nowhere left to
>> rick: So, listen, the heat's
turn, so morty and I are just
On, and there's nowhere left to
gonna fly my spaceship into a
Turn, so morty and I are just
black hole.
Gonna fly my spaceship into a
>> jerry: What?!
Black hole.
>> rick: Is that cool with you,
>> jerry: What?!
dawg?
>> rick: Is that cool with you,
>> jerry: Rick, no!
Dawg?
Morty!!
>> jerry: Rick, no!
>> we got it.
Morty!!
The call's coming from...
>> we got it.
♪ inside the house
The call's coming from...
>> look at his face!
♪ inside the house
>> you dummy!
>> look at his face!
>> ugh.
>> you dummy!
Can't believe our daughter
>> ugh.
married you.
Can't believe our daughter
>> too easy!
Married you.
[ laughter ]
>> too easy!
>> rick: The ricks are probably
[ laughter ]
gonna waste some time messing
>> rick: The ricks are probably
with jerry.
Gonna waste some time messing
They won't be able to help
With jerry.
themselves.
They won't be able to help
But as soon as they get bored,
Themselves.
they'll be onto us.
But as soon as they get bored,
>> phones à la clams and
They'll be onto us.
phonesghetti with phone balls.
>> phones à la clams and
Anything else?
Phonesghetti with phone balls.
>> rick: Yeah, more phone
Anything else?
sticks, please.
>> rick: Yeah, more phone
>> right away, sir.
Sticks, please.
>> morty: You know, rick, when I
>> right away, sir.
first saw all those ricks and
>> morty: You know, rick, when I
mortys, I thought, "gee, that
First saw all those ricks and
kind of devalues our bond."
Mortys, I thought, "gee, that
but then I realized it just
Kind of devalues our bond."
means that our relationship must
But then I realized it just
be pretty special to span over
Means that our relationship must
all those different timelines.
Be pretty special to span over
>> rick: Yeah, it's got to be
All those different timelines.
that way.
>> rick: Yeah, it's got to be
You're a camouflage.
That way.
>> morty: Camouflage?
You're a camouflage.
W-w-w-what are you talking
>> morty: Camouflage?
about, rick?
W-w-w-what are you talking
>> rick: Ricks have a very
About, rick?
distinctive and traceable
>> rick: Ricks have a very
brain wave due to our genius.
Distinctive and traceable
The best way to hide from an
Brain wave due to our genius.
enemy's radar is to stand near
The best way to hide from an
someone with complementary
Enemy's radar is to stand near
brain waves that make ours
Someone with complementary
invisible.
Brain waves that make ours
See, w-w-w-when a rick I-is with
Invisible.
a morty, the genius waves get
See, w-w-w-when a rick I-is with
canceled out by the, uh...
A morty, the genius waves get
[ clears throat ]
Canceled out by the, uh...
...Morty waves.
[ clears throat ]
>> morty: Um...Because o-our
...Morty waves.
personalities are so different?
>> morty: Um...Because o-our
[ portal gun beeping ]
Personalities are so different?
>> rick: Oh, shit, dawg.
[ portal gun beeping ]
My portal gun was hacked
>> rick: Oh, shit, dawg.
remotely, morty -- obviously by
My portal gun was hacked
the real killer, to frame me.
Remotely, morty -- obviously by
But I was able to trace the
The real killer, to frame me.
signal.
But I was able to trace the
Come on. Let's go.
Signal.
[ door bursts open ]
Come on. Let's go.
uh-oh.
[ door bursts open ]
>> excuse me.
Uh-oh.
We've tracked a pair of
>> excuse me.
dangerous criminals to this
We've tracked a pair of
exact location.
Dangerous criminals to this
They look exactly like us, so
Exact location.
in order to avoid confusion, I'm
They look exactly like us, so
gonna mark us each with a red
In order to avoid confusion, I'm
"x" right now.
Gonna mark us each with a red
That way, if someone has a gun
"x" right now.
and we both tell you to shoot
That way, if someone has a gun
the other one because they're
And we both tell you to shoot
the evil one, you'll know who's
The other one because they're
lying.
The evil one, you'll know who's
>> hey, check it out.
Lying.
>> damn it!
>> hey, you didn't pay your
bill!
>> t-the red "x"! Red "x"!
Bill!
>> rick: Hey, it's a good thing
>> t-the red "x"! Red "x"!
that space outlet had lab coats
>> rick: Hey, it's a good thing
and your favorite kind of shirt
That space outlet had lab coats
in stock, huh, morty?
And your favorite kind of shirt
>> morty: Yeah, rick, I-I heard
In stock, huh, morty?
you the first time.
>> morty: Yeah, rick, I-I heard
You don't have to keep saying it
You the first time.
over and over.
You don't have to keep saying it
>> rick: Man, this place is way
Over and over.
off the grid.
>> rick: Man, this place is way
This guy does not want to be
Off the grid.
found.
This guy does not want to be
>> morty: Well, if he's a rick,
Found.
doesn't he just have to stand by
>> morty: Well, if he's a rick,
a morty to hide?
Doesn't he just have to stand by
I mean, isn't that what mortys
A morty to hide?
are -- human cloaking devices?
I mean, isn't that what mortys
>> rick: Morty, you're making a
Are -- human cloaking devices?
bigger deal out of this than it
>> rick: Morty, you're making a
is.
Bigger deal out of this than it
[ groaning in distance ]
Is.
>> morty: Oh, my god, rick,
[ groaning in distance ]
look!
>> morty: Oh, my god, rick,
There's a bunch of people
Look!
strapped all over that building!
There's a bunch of people
>> rick: Not people, morty --
Strapped all over that building!
mortys.
>> rick: Not people, morty --
[ all groaning, screaming ]
>> morty: Oh, god!
W-w-why would somebody do this?
It's horrible!
>> rick: Well, one morty's
enough to hide from the
bureaucrats, but you get -- you
Enough to hide from the
get a whole matrix of mortys and
Bureaucrats, but you get -- you
put them in agonizing pain, that
Get a whole matrix of mortys and
creates a pattern that can hide
Put them in agonizing pain, that
even from other ricks [bleep]
Creates a pattern that can hide
I fiddled with a co[burps]ncept
Even from other ricks [bleep]
like this once.
I fiddled with a co[burps]ncept
On paper, morty. On paper.
Like this once.
I wouldn't do this.
On paper, morty. On paper.
It's barbaric overkill.
I wouldn't do this.
I mean, you could accomplish the
It's barbaric overkill.
same result with, like, five
I mean, you could accomplish the
mortys and a jumper cable.
Which I also wouldn't do!
I'm just saying, it's bad
craftsmanship.
>> beth: Coffee time!
Craftsmanship.
>> yeah!
>> beth: Coffee time!
>> yo, yo, yo, yo!
>> yeah!
>> that's what I like to hear!
>> yo, yo, yo, yo!
>> jerry: [ groans ]
>> that's what I like to hear!
>> hi, jerry.
>> jerry: [ groans ]
>> jerry: Leave me alone.
>> hi, jerry.
I'm working.
>> jerry: Leave me alone.
>> oh, you are?
I'm working.
W-w-w-what do you do?
>> oh, you are?
>> jerry: [ scoffs ]
W-w-w-what do you do?
I-I'm -- I'm in between
>> jerry: [ scoffs ]
advertising jobs.
I-I'm -- I'm in between
>> advertising? Wow!
Advertising jobs.
So, people need help figuring
>> advertising? Wow!
out what to buy, and then
So, people need help figuring
y-y-you help 'em?
Out what to buy, and then
>> jerry: [ laughing ] well,
Y-y-you help 'em?
it's a little more complicated
>> jerry: [ laughing ] well,
than that.
It's a little more complicated
>> well, I mean, you do it, and
Than that.
you seem like a guy who really
>> well, I mean, you do it, and
has it all together.
>> jerry: Dude, are you -- w--
you're being a dick, right?
>> oh, gosh, I-I hope not.
You're being a dick, right?
I-I-I-I-I-I wouldn't want to
>> oh, gosh, I-I hope not.
offend you in any way.
I-I-I-I-I-I wouldn't want to
>> jerry: You're really a rick?
Offend you in any way.
>> [ laughs ]
>> jerry: You're really a rick?
y-- of course I am -- just as
>> [ laughs ]
much as my morty's a morty.
Y-- of course I am -- just as
>> jerry: Hey, he looks a lot
Much as my morty's a morty.
like eric stoltz from the movie
>> jerry: Hey, he looks a lot
"mask."
Like eric stoltz from the movie
you know, the one with cher in
"mask."
it?
You know, the one with cher in
>> that's right, jerry!
It?
He -- he's from a reality where
>> that's right, jerry!
everyone is eric stoltz "mask"
He -- he's from a reality where
people.
Everyone is eric stoltz "mask"
He's eric stoltz mask morty.
People.
They assigned him to me because
He's eric stoltz mask morty.
I never had any kids of my own.
They assigned him to me because
But if I did, boy, I'd love them
I never had any kids of my own.
if they were as smart and as
But if I did, boy, I'd love them
successful as you are, jerry.
If they were as smart and as
>> hey, get a load of this.
Successful as you are, jerry.
Jerry's hanging out with
>> hey, get a load of this.
doofus rick.
Jerry's hanging out with
>> [ laughs ] this is perfect.
Doofus rick.
>> I'm not doofus rick!
>> [ laughs ] this is perfect.
I'm rick j19-zeta-7!
>> I'm not doofus rick!
>> oh, is that the timeline
I'm rick j19-zeta-7!
where everybody eats poop?
>> oh, is that the timeline
Jerry, you know this guy eats
Where everybody eats poop?
poop, right?
Jerry, you know this guy eats
>> hey, I don't eat poop!
Poop, right?
Y-you guys are always so mean to
>> hey, I don't eat poop!
me.
Y-you guys are always so mean to
[ both laugh ]
Me.
>> [ sobbing ]
[ both laugh ]
I guess it's only fair to tell
>> [ sobbing ]
you now, jerry.
I guess it's only fair to tell
I'm the worst rick of them all.
You now, jerry.
>> jerry: According to who --
I'm the worst rick of them all.
other versions of you?
>> jerry: According to who --
If I've learned one thing, it's
Other versions of you?
that before you get anywhere in
If I've learned one thing, it's
life, you got to stop listening
That before you get anywhere in
to yourself.
Life, you got to stop listening
>> wow.
To yourself.
You really are wise, jerry.
>> wow.
I-I-I guess that's why you work
You really are wise, jerry.
in advertising.
I-I-I guess that's why you work
>> jerry: The fact that you feel
In advertising.
that way makes you the best rick
>> jerry: The fact that you feel
of them all.
That way makes you the best rick
>> morty: You don't care about
Of them all.
me at all!
>> morty: You don't care about
I'm no different than that
Me at all!
jacket you've got on!
I'm no different than that
Y-y-y-- o-or your stupid portal
Jacket you've got on!
gun!
Y-y-y-- o-or your stupid portal
I'm just a tool!
Gun!
I-I-I'm just an object!
I'm just a tool!
>> rick: Hey, it's your choice
I-I-I'm just an object!
to take it personally, morty.
>> rick: Hey, it's your choice
Now, for the love of god, be
To take it personally, morty.
quiet.
Now, for the love of god, be
The point of this is to get the
Quiet.
drop on the guy.
The point of this is to get the
>> morty: You know what, rick?
Drop on the guy.
I'll tell you something!
>> morty: You know what, rick?
I'm more than a human shield!
I'll tell you something!
>> rick: Yeah, that's right.
I'm more than a human shield!
You    are.
>> rick: Yeah, that's right.
You're a perfect, impenetrable
You    are.
suit of human armor, morty,
You're a perfect, impenetrable
because you're as dumb as I am
Suit of human armor, morty,
smart, which is why when I say
Because you're as dumb as I am
[burps] "shut up," it's really
Smart, which is why when I say
good advice.
[burps] "shut up," it's really
[ whirring ]
Good advice.
great. Nice work, morty.
[ groans ]
[ hands clap slowly ]
>> ooh. Look at you, c-137.
You -- aren't you a tough
customer.
>> rick: The slow clap? Really?
Customer.
Kind of played out, dude.
>> rick: The slow clap? Really?
>> not in this dimension, it
Kind of played out, dude.
isn't.
>> not in this dimension, it
In fact [chuckles] I invented
Isn't.
it.
In fact [chuckles] I invented
Nobody else has ever even done
It.
it here before.
Nobody else has ever even done
>> rick: Well, la-di-da.
It here before.
>> hey, that's mine!
>> rick: I don't like the look
of that rick, morty.
We got to escape.
Of that rick, morty.
>> morty: I'm not gonna help
We got to escape.
you, rick.
>> morty: I'm not gonna help
Y-you're a monster.
You, rick.
>> rick: Don't be rick-diculous,
Y-you're a monster.
morty.
>> rick: Don't be rick-diculous,
>> morty: Will you -- will you
Morty.
stop saying that?
>> morty: Will you -- will you
It's stupid.
Stop saying that?
>> take his morty away.
It's stupid.
>> come with me.
>> take his morty away.
>> morty: Yeah, gladly.
>> come with me.
Geez, man. Ricks, huh?
>> morty: Yeah, gladly.
Hey, man, you seem to know how
Geez, man. Ricks, huh?
this place works.
Hey, man, you seem to know how
Is there any way we could shut
This place works.
down that grid and rescue all
Is there any way we could shut
those mortys outside?
Down that grid and rescue all
>> it would be pointless.
Those mortys outside?
Mortys have no chance of
>> it would be pointless.
defeating a rick.
Mortys have no chance of
In here.
Defeating a rick.
[ mortys sobbing ]
>> [ farts ]
>> ah. Isn't it beautiful?
>> rick: Yeah, yeah.
Looks like payday at
neverland ranch in here.
Zing!
Neverland ranch in here.
>> [ chuckles ]
Zing!
>> rick: That guy got it.
>> [ chuckles ]
>> unh-unh-unh, rick. Quiet.
>> rick: That guy got it.
You're missing my symphony.
>> unh-unh-unh, rick. Quiet.
[  mortys groaning, screaming]
You're missing my symphony.
>> rick: Hey, I'll take it over
[  mortys groaning, screaming]
mumford & sons.
>> rick: Hey, I'll take it over
Zip!
Mumford & sons.
>> [ laughs ]
Zip!
>> rick: This guy is on it!
>> [ laughs ]
>> he's not laughing at your
>> rick: This guy is on it!
dumb jokes, rick.
>> he's not laughing at your
That's just a random noise it
Dumb jokes, rick.
makes every 10 seconds.
That's just a random noise it
>> [ laughs ]
Makes every 10 seconds.
>> rick: [ groans ]
>> [ laughs ]
>> you see, rick, you're not as
>> rick: [ groans ]
clever as you think you are.
>> you see, rick, you're not as
I  wantedyou to find me.
Clever as you think you are.
We're not so [burps] different,
I  wantedyou to find me.
you and I.
We're not so [burps] different,
>> rick: Yeah, duh!
You and I.
>> see this right here, rick?
>> rick: Yeah, duh!
I crunched the numbers.
>> see this right here, rick?
I created a spectrum of all the
I crunched the numbers.
ricks.
I created a spectrum of all the
I listed them out from most evil
Ricks.
to least evil.
I listed them out from most evil
Here's where I am.
To least evil.
And lookit -- right here's where
Here's where I am.
you are, rick.
And lookit -- right here's where
This guy right here --
You are, rick.
super-weird.
This guy right here --
>> rick: I get it.
Super-weird.
So you want me to team up with
>> rick: I get it.
you to take down the council of
So you want me to team up with
ricks, right?
You to take down the council of
Is that where you're going with
Ricks, right?
this?
Is that where you're going with
'cause that's where I'd be
This?
going.
'cause that's where I'd be
>> please.
Going.
I think I'm doing pretty good on
>> please.
my own.
I think I'm doing pretty good on
I'm simply gonna download the
My own.
contents of your brain and then
I'm simply gonna download the
kill you.
Contents of your brain and then
>> okay, if we add a little more
Kill you.
titanium nitrate and just a tad
>> okay, if we add a little more
of chlorified tartrate...
Titanium nitrate and just a tad
[ mixture gurgles ]
Of chlorified tartrate...
...Ovenless brownies!
[ mixture gurgles ]
>> jerry: Mmm. Mmm!
...Ovenless brownies!
It's incredible what a gifted
>> jerry: Mmm. Mmm!
mind can accomplish when
It's incredible what a gifted
priorities are in order.
Mind can accomplish when
>> well, come on.
Priorities are in order.
I can't take all the credit,
>> well, come on.
jerry.
I can't take all the credit,
It was your idea.
Jerry.
Come here, jerry!
It was your idea.
[ both laugh ]
Come here, jerry!
>> jerry: Hey, uh, come here.
[ both laugh ]
I-I want to show you something.
>> jerry: Hey, uh, come here.
Okay, look, everybody makes fun
I-I want to show you something.
of me for getting these, but
Okay, look, everybody makes fun
you're a genius scientist.
Of me for getting these, but
What do you think?
You're a genius scientist.
See?
What do you think?
There's little r2-d2s where the
See?
george washingtons should be.
There's little r2-d2s where the
>> you know, jerry, I'm not
George washingtons should be.
gonna tell you that these will
>> you know, jerry, I'm not
increase in value or even hold
Gonna tell you that these will
their current value.
Increase in value or even hold
The truth is, you bought them
Their current value.
because you like them.
The truth is, you bought them
They have value to you.
Because you like them.
That's what matters.
>> jerry: [ voice breaking ] how
long are you staying?
>> until we find your rick.
Long are you staying?
>> jerry: I found mine.
>> until we find your rick.
I found mine.
>> morty: Help!
>> there is no escape, my son.
We will find our peace in the
next world.
>> morty: So, what --
Next world.
y-y-y-y-you're just gonna give
>> morty: So, what --
up?
Y-y-y-y-you're just gonna give
>> we're giving in -- to the
Up?
power of the one true morty.
>> we're giving in -- to the
One day, he will return.
Power of the one true morty.
>> together: Praise the one true
One day, he will return.
morty.
>> together: Praise the one true
>> morty: Ugh.
Morty.
All right, mortys, listen up.
>> morty: Ugh.
My name is morty smith, from
All right, mortys, listen up.
earth dimension c-137.
My name is morty smith, from
I know you're scared, because
Earth dimension c-137.
I'm scared.
I know you're scared, because
But that's no reason to accept
I'm scared.
our fate!
But that's no reason to accept
We're mortys!
Our fate!
We're not defined by our
We're mortys!
relationships to rick!
We're not defined by our
Our destiny is our own!
Relationships to rick!
>> this sounds like something
Our destiny is our own!
the one true morty might say.
>> this sounds like something
I'm sick of being a human
The one true morty might say.
shield.
I'm sick of being a human
I-I-I w-- I want to be a
Shield.
gardener!
I-I-I w-- I want to be a
>> I want to write really crazy,
Gardener!
intense action novels!
>> I want to write really crazy,
>> I'm more than just a hammer!
Intense action novels!
>> he is the one true morty!
>> I'm more than just a hammer!
>> hooray!
>> he is the one true morty!
>> the one true morty!
>> hooray!
>> hey, keep it down!
>> the one true morty!
[ mortys shouting ]
>> you've lived quite a life,
rick.
It's a real shame you're not
Rick.
gonna be around to see it
It's a real shame you're not
through.
You're crying?
Over a morty?
>> rick: No, I'm just allergic
to dipshits.
>> ugh. Pathetic.
To dipshits.
We both know that if there's any
>> ugh. Pathetic.
truth in the universe, it's that
We both know that if there's any
ricks don't care about mortys.
Truth in the universe, it's that
[ mortys shouting ]
Ricks don't care about mortys.
do your worst, you little
[ mortys shouting ]
bastards!
Do your worst, you little
Kill me! Do it!
Bastards!
Do I-I-I-I-it!
Kill me! Do it!
>> rick: Morty! Thank god!
Do I-I-I-I-it!
Get me out of this.
>> rick: Morty! Thank god!
Come on!
Get me out of this.
>> morty: You're lucky I'm not a
Come on!
rick.
>> morty: You're lucky I'm not a
>> rick: Point taken, but this
Rick.
is [burps] no time for arcs.
>> rick: Point taken, but this
[ energy powering down ]
Is [burps] no time for arcs.
>> oh!
[ energy powering down ]
>> [ laughs ]
>> oh!
>> thank god!
>> [ laughs ]
[ dialing ]
>> thank god!
[ ringing ]
[ dialing ]
[ telephone rings ]
[ ringing ]
>> yeah, hello.
[ telephone rings ]
>> rick: Hey, what do me and
>> yeah, hello.
o.J. Not have in common?
>> rick: Hey, what do me and
>> huh? W-who is this?
O.J. Not have in common?
>> rick: I found the real
>> huh? W-who is this?
killer, bitch!
>> rick: I found the real
Get over here!
>> yo, ding-dong, we're done
here.
Time to go.
Here.
>> well, jerry [belches]
Time to go.
I guess this means goodbye.
>> well, jerry [belches]
>> jerry: W-w-well, does it have
I guess this means goodbye.
to?
>> jerry: W-w-well, does it have
I mean, you -- you look just
To?
like rick.
I mean, you -- you look just
We could maybe, you know, get
Like rick.
rid of him.
We could maybe, you know, get
I'm not saying kill him,
Rid of him.
necessarily.
I'm not saying kill him,
I -- I'm also not saying
Necessarily.
necessarily not kill him, but --
I -- I'm also not saying
>> jerry, w-we both know it
Necessarily not kill him, but --
wouldn't work.
>> jerry, w-we both know it
It's time to go back to our
Wouldn't work.
lives.
It's time to go back to our
I love you, jerry.
Lives.
I love you.
I love you, jerry.
>> jerry: [ sighs ]
[ whimpers ]
>> together: Hut! Hut! Hut! Hut!
Hut! Hut! Hut! Hut! Hut! Hut!
Hut! Hut! Hut!
>> morty: W-what -- w-what's
gonna happen to all these
mortys?
Gonna happen to all these
>> they'll go back to their
Mortys?
families, attend school
>> they'll go back to their
regularly, play video games,
Families, attend school
date girls.
Regularly, play video games,
Poor little rickless bastards.
Date girls.
>> earth rick c-137, the council
Poor little rickless bastards.
apologizes for its false
>> earth rick c-137, the council
accusation, and in the way of
Apologizes for its false
reparations [belches] for our
Accusation, and in the way of
terrible mistake, we would like
Reparations [belches] for our
to compensate you with this
Terrible mistake, we would like
voucher for a free replacement
To compensate you with this
morty in the event that
Voucher for a free replacement
y[belches]our current [belches]
Morty in the event that
morty should --
Y[belches]our current [belches]
>> rick: Uh, guys, not a good
Morty should --
time.
>> rick: Uh, guys, not a good
Come on, morty. Let's hit it.
>> morty: Is it time for arcs
yet, rick?
I did a pretty good job back
Yet, rick?
there for a human cloaking
I did a pretty good job back
device.
There for a human cloaking
Saved your ass.
Device.
>> rick: All right, morty.
Saved your ass.
Don't break an arm jerking
>> rick: All right, morty.
yourself off.
Don't break an arm jerking
>> morty: Man, I can't believe
Yourself off.
you, rick.
>> morty: Man, I can't believe
That right there, that w-- that
You, rick.
was a great opportunity to show
That right there, that w-- that
a little humanity, you know?
Was a great opportunity to show
To connect with me a little.
A little humanity, you know?
>> rick: Hey, morty, you want
To connect with me a little.
connection, go be part of some
>> rick: Hey, morty, you want
stupid club, like all those dumb
Connection, go be part of some
ricks.
Stupid club, like all those dumb
You know, maybe I don't connect
Ricks.
because I'm the rickest rick
You know, maybe I don't connect
there is.
Because I'm the rickest rick
And, you know, it would
There is.
g-- [belches] go without saying
And, you know, it would
that the rickest rick would have
G-- [belches] go without saying
the mortyest morty.
That the rickest rick would have
>> morty: It would go without
The mortyest morty.
saying, huh?
>> morty: It would go without
>> rick: Yeah, it would.
Saying, huh?
Did you hear me say it?
>> rick: Yeah, it would.
>> morty: Nah.
Did you hear me say it?
The mortyest morty.
>> morty: Nah.
>> rick: Just don't get too big
The mortyest morty.
for your loafers, buster brown.
>> rick: Just don't get too big
A cocky morty can lead to some
For your loafers, buster brown.
big problems.
A cocky morty can lead to some
It can be a real bad thing for
Big problems.
everybody.
It can be a real bad thing for
>> morty: Oh, yeah? How's that?
Everybody.
>> rick: U-uh, I'll explain when
>> morty: Oh, yeah? How's that?
you're older.
>> rick: U-uh, I'll explain when
[ camera shutter clicks ]
You're older.
>> what a mess.
[ camera shutter clicks ]
>> pride cometh before the fall.
>> what a mess.
I guess he got what he deserved.
>> pride cometh before the fall.
>> what is that?
I guess he got what he deserved.
[ electricity crackles ]
>> what is that?
>> hand me the laser
[ electricity crackles ]
difibulator.
>> hand me the laser
>> hey, guys, uh, c-can I help?
Difibulator.
>> no! Go clean the toilets.
>> hey, guys, uh, c-can I help?
Maybe you'll make friends with
>> no! Go clean the toilets.
some turds.
Maybe you'll make friends with
>> you make us ashamed to be
Some turds.
ourselves!
My god.
I've seen this technology
before.
[ device beeping ]
Before.
>> this rick was being
[ device beeping ]
controlled remotely --
>> this rick was being
puppeteered by somebody else.
Controlled remotely --
This is the receiver.
Puppeteered by somebody else.
>> yeah, but where's the
This is the receiver.
transmitter?
>> yeah, but where's the
[ beeping continues ]
>> rick: Wubba dubba dub dub!
Oh. Hey, jerry.
W-w-w-what are you doing in my
room, buddy?
>> jerry: Nothing.
Room, buddy?
[ shakily ] I was just, um,
>> jerry: Nothing.
[sniffles] checking the smoke
[ shakily ] I was just, um,
detectors.
[sniffles] checking the smoke
>> rick: All right.
Detectors.
Okay, get out.
What's that dipshit doing out
there?
Are you friends with him?
There?
You know he eats his own shit,
Are you friends with him?
right?
You know he eats his own shit,
[ laughing ] oh, my god, this is
Right?
rich!
[ laughing ] oh, my god, this is
I've got like [belches] 10 ricks
Rich!
to call right now.