( all shouting )
Wait.
BOTH: Grunkle Stan!
Kids!
I can't believe it!
I thought I lost you two.
Ahh!
Mr. Pines,
it's really you!
I've been hugging strangers
to practice for this moment.
We missed you,
you old codger.
( chuckles )
I've missed you
knuckleheads too.
It's good to have you back.
So...what's everyone
doing here?
( gasps )
Yeah, there's, like,
monsters and gnomes.
And is Pacifica
wearing a potato sack?
Hey! Even in a sack
I still look better than you.
It's...
It's a long story.
Hey, is anyone
gonna feed me?
Larry King's disembodied
wax head wants num-nums.
We're trying to
ration our food,
remember?
Mmm...mmm...
Uhh, it's happening again!
MAN: Hey, everyone!
Eye bat!
( all gasp )
Evasive maneuvers!
Shh! Keep it down!
GNOME:
Get the lights!
( raccoon chittering )
♪
Welcome to what's left
of normal around here--
home base.
( whimpering )
Ow!
We have...
♪ Several injuries ♪
Ooh!
Ow!
My liver, girl!
( gasps )
Rumble McSkirmish?
( electronic voice )
Do not be afraid.
Weirdmaggedon
has taught me
there are some battles
I cannot win.
I am now Humble McSkirmish.
Grunkle Stan,
how'd this all happen?
So I was hammering
signs out back
when the sky started
vomiting nightmares.
I listen to
a lot of AM radio,
so I knew what this meant--
the end of the world.
(cackling )
What I didn't expect
was what happened next.
( roars )
Turns out whatever
you and my brother
did to the Shack
with your unicorn voodoo
made the crazy place
invincible to weirdness.
Of course--
the unicorn spell!
That's why this
is the only place
Bill's magic can't touch.
That's when Possum Breath
over here shows up
leading a bunch of injured
stragglers through the forest.
They needed a place to stay,
and since
the Mayor got captured,
I elected myself
de facto chief.
The plan's to stay in here
and eat brown meat
until we run out.
Then I vote
we eat the gnomes.
Hey, I'm short,
not deaf!
Shh! Shh! Stress will
make you chewy.
Grunkle Stan,
we can't all just hide
inside the Shack.
There's a town
in need of saving!
Me and Ford tried to do it,
but he got captured by Bill.
Serves that jerk right!
My brother's had
some stupid plans,
but going up against
an all-powerful space demon
was his worst one yet.
Trust me,
we have everything
we need right here.
It's not the Ritz,
but at least the monsters
inside know how to massage.
You know Shiatsu?
Yes, I've taken
some classes.
So, you're really
just gonna let Bill win?
Look, kiddo.
We got a good deal here.
Besides, I'm sure wherever
the rest of the townsfolk are,
they're fine.
( broadcast news alert )
This is Shandra Jimenez
reporting live from
the inside of Bill's castle.
Here for the first time
are images of what's happened
to the captured townsfolk.
Viewers are advised
to look away
if they don't want to see
their friends
turned into a twisted throne
of human agony.
Mom and Dad?
My family!
Deputy Durland!
Is there no one who will
save the people of this town?
I'm Shandra Jimenez,
and I'm being turned into
stone by a flying eyeball.
( all gasp )
Oh, no.
My parents are bad,
but even  they  don't
deserve to be turned to stone.
Curse you, Bill!
Why must you take
everything we love?
( wails )
Guys, don't you see?
Our friends need us,
but we only save them
if we fight back!
Mabel is right.
Bill wants us to run and hide.
He wants us to think
he's invincible.
But Ford told me
before he was captured
that he knows
Bill's secret weakness.
( all murmuring )
Weakness?
Now, if we band together,
if we combine
all of our strength,
our smarts,
our...whatever Toby has...
Aureus  rashes!
...then we just might be
able to rescue Ford,
learn Bill's weakness,
and save Gravity Falls!
( all cheering )
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Have you all forgotten
who's in charge here?
Besides,
we're only safe inside!
It's not like we can take
the Mystery Shack to Bill.
McGUCKET: Wha-- Whoa!
Holy hootenanny!
Flapjack and fiddlebanjos!
Sorry. Sorry.
Got a little excited.
What I meant to say is,
I think I figured out a way
to fight Bill and rescue Ford.
But we're all gonna
have to work together!
Now...
if you just...
( low chatter )
SOOS:
Don't worry, Ford.
We're coming for you!
Let me go!
You insane three-sided--
Wha-- What is this place?
( chain clanking )
BILL:
♪ We'll meet again ♪
♪ Don't know where,
don't know when ♪
♪ Oh, I know we'll meet again
some sunny day ♪
Wh-- Where am I?
You're in
the penthouse suite, kid!
The tip of the pyramid!
Have a drink.
Make yourself comfortable.
You know that couch is made
from living human skin?
( groans )
Aah!
Quit the games, Cipher!
If I'm still alive,
you must want
something from me.
Ah, sharp as ever,
Fordsy.
As you may have noticed...
I've recently had a
multi-dimensional makeover!
I control space and matter,
and now that that dumb
baby's out of the way,
time itself!
But I wasn't
always this way.
Oof!
You think those
chains are tight?
Imagine living in
the second dimension--
flat minds in a flat world
with flat dreams.
I liberated my dimension,
Stanford, and I'm here
to liberate yours.
There's just one hitch.
As it turns out,
my weirdness can't escape
the magical confines
of this town!
There's something
keeping me in.
Incredible!
Gravity Falls' Natural Law
of Weirdness Magnetism.
I studied this years ago!
And did you find a way
to undo it?
Of course!
There's a simple equation that
could collapse the barrier.
But I'd never tell you!
Listen, Ford,
if you just tell me
that equation,
finally your dimension
will be free!
Anything will be possible!
( all screaming )
I'll remake a fun world-
a better world!
A party that never ends
with a host that never dies!
No more restrictions!
No more laws!
You'd be one of us.
All-powerful!
Greater than anything
you've imagined!
And all I need is your help.
You're insane
if you think I'll help you.
Ha ha ha! I'm insane
either way, brainiac!
But have it your way.
I'll just fish around
and get that equation
directly out of your mind!
Not so fast!
You know the rules, Bill.
You may be able
to haunt my dreams,
but you can't enter my mind
unless I shake your hand
and let you in.
( sighs )
You're making this
so much harder
than it needs to be.
Everyone has a weakness,
tough guy!
I'll make you talk!
It's only a matter of time.
Aaaah!
All right. I've made
some thingamadiculous
robomajigs in my day,
but this is the first one
that  won't  be used for evil!
Whoa! These blueprints
are incredible, McGucket.
MABEL: This is your most
amazing invention yet.
Question: Does it have
any gun-swords?
I watch a lot
of anime and, uh,
trust me, you're gonna
want some gun-swords.
What's an "anime"?
We have much to discuss.
STAN:
Discuss, nothing!
These scribbles are a bunch
of cockamamie balderdash!
Excuse my French.
( voice speaking French )
And where would you
even find a bunch of idiots
crazy enough to build it?
Grunkle Stan,
you're lookin'
at those idiots.
( all cheering )
Idiots!
( action movie-style
music plays )
Whoa--What--
What are you--
Hey-- Hey, now.
Hey! Don't touch that.
Hey--
Aah!
Uhh! Uhh!
Aaah!
( "action" music continues )
Thanks for these
apocalypse sweaters, Mabel.
The end of the world
has never been so comfortable.
ALL: Mm-hmm!
( wind whistling )
Uhh! Fine,
I'll  wear  it.
But I'm  not  gonna
like it.
Admit it. This is the best day
of the end of the world.
I think we actually have
a chance to beat Bill
and win back our future.
Yeah. Getting
to actually  live
to see our
13th birthday party
is the only birthday present
I want right now.
Hey, if we're
lucky enough to get there,
I guarantee this whole town
is gonna throw you
the best birthday party
you've ever seen.
Thanks, Soos.
Hey, has anyone
seen Grunkle Stan?
This whole plan is bonkers.
But of course, no one asked
the Chief what he thinks.
After all I've done
for everyone!
Schmebulock.
Yeah, exactly--
it's a total load
of schmebulock.
Is something wrong,
Grunkle Stan?
You're acting
grunklier than usual.
It's this darn plan
to save my brother.
If you didn't notice,
I already saved him once
from that portal,
and he never thanked me!
He causes
the end of the world,
and somehow it's still always
"Stan's the screw-up,
Ford's the hero."
Well, maybe people
think he's a hero
because he didn't want
to hide in the Mystery Shack!
Well, maybe if he hid in
the Mystery Shack he
wouldn't have been captured!
Guys! Guys! Trust me,
tomorrow's gonna be great!
I believe in us.
COW MONSTER: Help! Leader Mabel!
I keep accidentally flexing
through my sweater!
Aah! It happened  again!
Those weird cow-monsters
are delightful!
Coming!
( bleats )
McGUCKET:
All right, fellas!
Let's hope this turns out
better than my
other inventions!
Everybody ready?
Dipper, now!
( machinery rattling )
ALL:
Huh?! Whoa!
( steam whistle blowing )
Forgive me, boy.
Your hyper-flammable
merchandise
is the only
thing keeping me goin'.
What in blazes?!
FORD:
No! No! Nooo!
( all cackling )
( groaning )
Ready to talk now?
( gasping )
I won't.
I won't let you
into my mind!
What do you think, pals?
Another 500 volts?
( crackling )
Hey, do you hear that?
( crashing )
( roaring )
What?! I just fixed that door!
It's the Shacktron, dude!
LARRY KING: They made the house
into a robot.
Fascinating!
So the mortals are
trying to fight back, huh?
Adorable!
Henchmaniacs,
you know what to do!
Take them out!
This was a bad idea.
P.A.: Uh, hey, dudes.
Is this thing on?
- SOOS:  Tes--
- ( feedback screeches )
Heh. Uh, I just wanted
you monster dudes
to hand over Ford,
or we'll have to, like,
fight and junk?
Heh heh. Hey,
you're a little cutie.
I have butchered millions
on countless moons!
Whoa. I liked you better
before you talked.
Real-- real bring-down,
this guy.
Attack!
All right, dudes!
Everyone!
Like we planned!
Three, two, one. Go!
( all shouting )
( henchmaniacs shouting )
Ha ha ha!
Good pig.
Get 'em, Gobblewonker!
( McGucket laughs )
Hyah! Hyah!
WENDY:
Oh, no, you don't!
- ( Wendy grunts )
- ( eye bat squeals )
( screams )
( roaring )
Everyone! Incoming!
Does this thing
have an escape hatch?
( all screaming )
Everybody! Maximum power!
And... now!
( roaring )
( screaming )
BILL:  Guys, seriously?
You had, like,
one job to do here.
Bravo,
Dipper and Mabel!
Well, would ya
look at that?
Those kids really
care about you.
And you care about them.
( monster voice )
Don't you?
What are you...
Oh. Oh, no.
BILL:  Perhaps torturing
those kids will make you talk!
No. No! Not the kids!
You ca--
Lets get this over with.
What the-- No!
No! No! No! No!
( Stan screaming )
Attack!
( roaring )
Aah! My eye!
Do you have any idea
how long it takes
to regenerate that?
We've got him distracted!
Now's our chance!
Rescue team,
move out!
OK, everyone!
We get in,
rescue Ford,
get out,
save the world.
Piece of cake.
Just so we're clear,
if I die,
I'm suing all of you.
Hey, on second thought,
maybe we could
come up with a plan
that doesn't involve us
plummeting to our
certain death.
Now!
Ahh!
( screaming )
Oh, man, oh, man...
Whoo-hoo!
( cackling )
( grunts )
( Stan shouts )
- ( Wendy grunts )
- ( Stan shouting )
( all gasp )
DIPPER:
Oh, man. It looks
even worse up close.
MABEL:
I found Great-uncle Ford!
He's golden!
But not in the good way!
STAN: Great. Grab him
and let's get out of here.
But how are we going
to unfreeze them?
GIDEON:
I know!
( Gideon panting )
Gideon!
What happened to you?
Bill captured me.
He's been forcing me
to do cute dances in this cage
for all eternity.
( sobbing )
I'm so tired of being cute!
How do we undo this?
GIDEON: Mayor Tyler.
He's the load-bearing human.
Pull him out,
and the whole thing goes down.
( grunting )
Aaah!
Ah. My mouth tastes
like nightmares!
Aah! I think
I'm dark and tortured
for  reals  now.
This experience will
forever scar Tad Strange.
No more sailor suits!
( panting )
- MANLY DAN: Wendy!
- WENDY: Guys!
Mom! Dad!
Durland!
My Blubs!
Don't you  ever  scare me
like that again!
( all cheering )
Kids! Ah, you did it!
I knew I could
count on you two. Ha ha!
Fiddldeford! I--
I haven't seen you
since we parted ways.
You must hate me.
I've tried forgettin'.
Maybe I should
try  forgiving.
Come here, old friend.
Hey, good to see you too, bro.
Now let's get out of here, huh?
Listen, Uncle Ford,
we don't have a lot of time.
Remember how you told me
right before you were frozen
that you knew Bill's weakness?
Yeah, a secret way
to defeat him?
I-- I do!
Now, does anyone have a pen?
Pencil? Anything?
Ah.
Perfect!
Uh, we've got Bill outside,
but I don't know how long
we can keep him occupied.
Yes, yes. Good, good.
Drawing a circle
on the floor.
Well,
he's lost his mind.
My mind is fine.
d there  is  a way to beat him--
th this!
The world's most confusing
game of hopscotch?
No, a prophecy.
Although it would be
a pretty fun game of hopscotch.
FORD:  Many years ago,
I found ten symbols in a cave.
Some I recognized then.
Some I only recognize now.
The native people
of Gravity Falls
prophesized that
these symbols
could create a force
strong enough
to vanquish Bill.
With Bill defeated,
his weirdness would be reversed
and the town could be saved.
This whole time
I thought it was
just superstition.
But seeing you all here now
I finally understand
that it's destiny!
Dipper, the pine tree.
Mabel, the shooting star.
The question mark.
This one's unsolvable.
That one's easy.
You've been rockin'
that dumb hoodie
since the seventh grade.
Whoa. Destiny hoodie!
The tent of telepathy sign!
That must be Gideon.
Whoo! An excuse to stand
next to Mabel!
Don't turn this
into a big deal.
Oh, I won't.
(whispers)
I  will.
( Bill grunting )
BILL:  What the--
Hey, Achilles!
Nice work with the heel!
( all gasp )
Fore!
Hold hands, everyone!
This is a mystical
human energy circuit.
Ice? Who's Ice?
They symbol's needn't
all be literal, Dipper.
It just has to be someone cool
in the face of danger.
ALL CHANTING:
Wendy! Wendy!
(giggles)
Shut up, you guys.
Much like the spectacles
need to be someone scholarly.
Heh heh!
This is freaky.
FORD:
Now hold hands, everyone.
Ew! I'm not touching that.
Do it, sweetie.
do the one thing
no one in our family
has ever done--
touch the hillbilly.
( all gasp )
Great-uncle Ford,
I think it's working!
( McGucket cackling )
Yes, this is it!
The rest of you get out!
It's too dangerous!
We just need
one more person...
Stanley! Stanley,
get over here!
You're the only one left.
You realize this is
a bunch of hogwash, right?
You really think
some caveman graffiti
is gonna stop that monster?
Dang it, old man,
now's not the time!
Come on!
What are you  doing?
You're gonna ruin this!
I've never held hands this long,
and I  very  uncomfortable!
Whoa. Hey, I'm not
the enemy here, people.
Don't forget who literally
created the end of the world.
I'm sorry, Stanley. I know.
Just help me fix it! Please!
Fine. Just do one thing.
Say "thank you."
What?
I spent thirty years
trying to bring you back
into this dimension,
and you still
haven't thanked me!
You want me
to shake your hand?
Say "thank you"!
Fine. Thank you.
Now, see?
Between me and him, I'm not
always the bad twin.
Between "him and me."
Grammar, Stanley.
I'll "Grammar, Stanley"  you,
you stuck-up son-of-a--
Don't jeopardize this,
you idiot!
FORD: Everything's on the line!
Stop it!
( both shouting )
DIPPER: Join hands!
BILL:  Oh, no, it's Bill!
Right? Isn't that what
you're all thinking?
Hey, Gideon,
why aren't you dancing?
Chop chop, huh?
BILL:   Ha ha ha ho!
This is just too perfect!
Didn't you brainiacs know
the zodiac doesn't work
if you don't all hold hands?
And what's better,
you've brought every
threat to my power together
in one easy-to-destroy circle!
( gasps )
Oh, no!
Aaah! My hair!
Aaah! My hair also!
You guys want to see
what happens to your friends
when you can't get along?
Hey! You give them back!
You've gone too far,
cipher!
Yeah! We're not
scared of you!
Oh, but you should be.
Aaah!
Oh, no!
Ya know, this castle
could really use
some decoration!
( thunder crashing )
( both gasp )
Looks like it's too late
for your friends, Stanford!
( both yell )
Kids!
But you can still
save your family!
Last chance:
Tell me how to take
Weirdmageddon global
and I'll spare the kids!
No! Don't do it!
Yeah!
Bill makes bad deals!
Don't you toy with me,
shooting star!
I see everything!
Ow! Not again!
Why?! Every time!
Nice shot, pumpkin!
I just regenerated that eye!
I  know  that hurts,
because I've accidentally
done it to myself--
multiple times!
Aaah! Aaah!
Save yourselves!
Run! We'll take care of Bill!
What?!
That's a suicide
mission!
Trust us.
We've beat him before...
and we'll beat him
again!
Hey, Bill! Come and get us,
you pointy jerk!
( Bill howls )
What? No!
It's too dangerous!
Not so fast!
You two wait here!
I've got some children
I need to make into corpses!
(monster voice)
See ya real soon!
( cackling )
Bill, no!
What do we do?
what do we do?
Kids!
- ( kids panting )
- ( Bill roaring )
When I get my hands
on you kids,
I'm gonna disassemble
your molecules!
You've tricked me
for the last time!
( both screaming )
GRUNKLE STAN:
Ohh! I can't  believe  this!
The kids are gonna die,
and it's all my fault--
because I couldn't shake
your stupid hand!
Ahh, Dad was right about me.
I  am  a screw-up.
Ah, don't blame yourself.
I'm the one
who made a deal with Bill
in the first place.
I fell for all
his easy flattery.
You would have seen him
for the scam artist he is.
How did things
get so messed up
between us?
We used to be
like Dipper and Mabel.
The world's about to end
and they still work together.
How do they do it?
Easy. They're kids.
They don't know any better.
Whoa, where you goin'?
I'm gonna play
the only card we have left.
Let Bill into my mind.
He'll be able
to take over the galaxy,
and maybe even worse,
but at least he  might
let the kids free.
What?! Are you kiddin' me?!
Are you honestly telling me
there's nothing else we can do?!
Bill's only weak
in the mind space.
If I didn't have this darn plate
in my head,
we could just erase him
with the memory gun
when he steps
inside my mind.
What if he goes
into  my  mind?
My brain isn't good
for anything.
( chuckles )
There's nothing in your mind
he wants. It  has  to be me.
We need to take his deal.
It's the only way
he'll agree to save
you and the kids.
Do you really think
he's gonna make good
on that deal?
What other choice
do we have?
Aaah!
DIPPER: I'm starting to think
there's no way out of here.
Like Grunkle Stan always says,
when one door closes,
choose a nearby wall
and bash it in
with brute force!
( grunting )
Aaaaah!
Ha! Now let's round up
the townsfolk,
and together
we can defeat--
Oh, no!
( all laughing )
You'll never
take us alive, monsters!
That's fine with us!
( all cry out )
Oh, no!
BILL:  Peek-a-boo!
( both scream )
All right, Ford,
time's up!
I've got the kids!
I think I'm gonna
kill one of 'em now,
just for the heck of it!
Eeenie-meenie...
minee...
FORD: Wait!
I surrender!
Good choice.
STAN: Don't do it, Ford!
It'll destroy the universe!
FORD:
It's the only way!
( Bill cackling )
Even when you're about to die,
you Pines twins just
can't get along!
My only condition
is that you let my brother
and the kids go.
Fine.
No, Grunkle Ford!
Don't trust him!
It's a....deal!
( cackling )
Oh, I'm here.
I'm finally here!
Look at this place--
a perfect, calm,
orderly void.
Gotta hand it to you, Ford,
you really know
how to clear your--
( clicks tongue )
What?!
Ha ha! Do a pretty good
impression
of my brother, don't I?
Switch clothes and no one
can tell us apart.
Welcome to my mind.
Surprised you didn't
recognize it.
What?! The deal's off!
What the--
No, no, no, no!
STAN: Oh, yeah.
You're goin' down, Bill.
You're gettin' erased.
Memory gun.
Pretty clever, huh?
Y-You idiot!
Don't you realize
you're destroying
your own mind too?
Eh. It's not like
I was using this space
for much anyway.
Let me out of here!
Let me--
Oh-- Why isn't this working?!
Hey, look at me.
Turn around and look at me,
you one-eyed demon!
You're a real wiseguy,
but you made one fatal mistake.
You messed with my family.
You're  making a mistake!
I'll give you anything--
money, fame, riches,
infinite power,
your own galaxy!
Please! No!
What's happening to me?!
( Bill's voice
fragments and distorts )
Staaanleeey!
Aaaaah!!!
( panting )
Heh. Guess I was good
for something after all.
( clank )
( all grunt )
( wind howling )
( henchmaniacs cackling )
( roars,
screams )
( all screaming )
Hey! Hey!
BOTH: Oh...ohh!
( whooshing )
Whoa.
Huh.
( birds squawking )
( chirping )
( wind whistling )
Oh, my gosh!
Grunkle Stan,
you did it!
Oh, uh, hey there...
kiddo.
What's your name?
Grunkle Stan?
Heh. Who ya talkin' to?
C-Come on.
It's  me.
It's me, Grunkle Stan!
Grunkle Stan, it's me!
We had to erase his mind
to defeat Bill.
It's all gone.
Stan has no idea,
but he did it.
He saved the world.
He saved me.
You're our hero, Stanley.
( sniffles )
( crying )
( Dipper grunting )
Hey, this is a real nice place
ya got here.
It's  your  place,
Grunkle Stan.
Don't you remember?
Even a little?
Nope, but this chair
hugs my butt like it remembers.
Ah.
Hey, why the long faces?
You guys look like
it's someone's funeral.
Who's that big guy
crying in the corner?
( sobbing )
We saved the world,
but what's the point?
Grunkle Stan's
not himself anymore.
There's gotta be
something we can
do to jog his memory!
There isn't.
I'm sorry.
Stan's gone.
I  know  my Grunkle is
in there somewhere!
There's gotta be
something around here
that can help
bring him back!
This'll work!
This has to work!
Here's the first day we came
to Gravity Falls, Grunkle Stan.
And here's a macaroni
interpretation of my emotions.
That time
we went fishing.
That Summerween
we spent together.
Don't you remember
anything?
I'm sorry. I don't know
what this is
or who you are or--gah!
Quit it, Waddles!
I'm trying to remember
my life story!
What did you say?
I said get Waddles off of me!
It's working!
Keep reading!
Skip to my page!
He needs to remember
our boss-employee
relationship.
Hey! Just cause I have amnesia,
don't go tryin' to give
yourself a raise, Soos.
It's happening!
Keep going!
OK. OK!
"Day Two.
Grunkle Stan smells weird
but we're
starting to bond.
He told us a lot about being
a businessman in the '80s
and seemed happy when
we pretended to listen.
He also gave me
a grappling hook
which everyone
is impressed by.
And in more important news,
I've met some
neighborhood hotties!"
( all laugh )
SHANDRA:
Good Morning, Gravity Falls!
It's another beautiful day,
but every day is beautiful
now that the...
unpleasantness is over.
( bats screeching )
Git outta here,
ya ornery critters!
( roaring )
Ah, good as new.
Oh! Looks like
you've got a friend!
Robbie, would you be
a dear and get us
the sawed off shotgun?
Ugh. Fine,
whatever.
Brains and so forth!
Nope! None of that,
thank you.
( laughing )
None of us really understand
what just happened,
and none of us want to.
That's why I'm passing
the Never Mind All That Act.
If anyone goes asking
around about the "events"
of the last few days,
what do we say?
CROWD:
Never Mind All That!
And if you break the rules,
we're gonna zap ya!
Zap! Zap!
We're mad with power!
BOTH:
And love.
SHANDRA:
In other news,
the Northwest family
has gone broke.
After pledging
his allegiance to Bill
and then placing all
his savings in weirdness bonds,
Preston Northwest
had to sell his mansion
to preserve his family fortune.
You're only going to
have one pony now!
But fortunes have also
turned for local maniac
Fiddleford McGucket
who, after regaining his sanity,
has made millions overnight
submitting his patents
to the US government.
I'm gonna buy me a bigger shed!
Hey, that one's for sale!
In other good news,
town hero Stanley Pines
has fully recovered his memory
and will be throwing a party
to celebrate his niece and
nephew's thirteenth birthday
and final day in town.
But other than that,
I can safely say
our beloved Gravity Falls
is back to normal.
And now, Bodacious T,
with sports.
It's called Death Ball!
ALL:
♪...to you ♪
( squeals )
( all cheering )
I can't believe you all
got together
just to throw
a party for us!
After all the Pines family
has done for the town,
it's the least
we could do!
You've helped
everyone here.
Thanks to y'all savin' us,
I learned to open
my heart to kindness.
No more evil-doin'.
From now on, I'm gonna
try to be Li'l Gideon,
regular ol' kid.
Oh-- Ha ha! Whoo!
I am bustin' a move
on this skatin' board.
More like busting
your pants, loser!
Heh heh heh heh!
( blows landing )
( boy screams )
Hee hee hee!
Dude, make a wish, dawg!
Ya know, on my
first day here,
if you had asked me
what I wanted,
I would have said
adventure, mystery,
true friends.
But looking here at all of you,
I realize that
every wish came true--
I have everything
I wanted.
If I had only one wish,
it would be to shrink all
of you with a shrink ray
and bring you home
with us in my pocket.
But since that's impossible--
Is  that impossible?
Since that's
probably  impossible,
my only wish is
for everyone to
sign my scrapbook.
I'll never
forget you guys.
Wait.
Now  I'll never
forget you guys!
I now officially declare you:
technically teenagers.
Welcome to
Angst and Acne Forever.
ALL CHANT:
One of us! One of us!
Whoo-hee!
Whoopee!
So how do you feel?
Samey,
but differenty.
PACIFICA: Hey, you two.
When are you gonna
open your presents already?
I broke a nail wrapping them.
Ha ha!
Pacifica.
Stanley, I need
to talk to you.
I didn't want to say anything
with everyone listening,
but we've got
a problem.
Weirdmageddon
has been contained,
but I'm detecting
some strange new anomalies
near the Arctic Ocean.
I want to go investigate it,
but I think I might be
too old to go it alone.
Are you sayin' you
need someone to help you
sail around the world
on the adventure
of a lifetime?
I don't just want  someone
to come with me, Stanley.
I want it to be you.
Will you give me
a second chance?
You think we'll find treasure?
And babes?
Ha! I'd say there's
a high probability!
But what should we do
with the Mystery Shack?
I think the town's
had enough mystery
for one lifetime.
Are you thinkin'
what I'm thinkin'?
( Stan, Ford whispering )
( bell ringing )
GRUNKLE STAN: Everyone,
I have an announcement
to make.
Me and my--heh!--
nerdy bro over here
have some catchin' up to do,
we're gonna be away for a while.
That's why I'm shutting down
the Mystery Shack for good!
( all gasp )
You shut down
your  mouth  for good!
I'm sorry, Mr. Pineses,
it's just that this shack
is the most magical place
on earth.
Sure, the attractions
are all fake,
but  dreams  aren't fake.
Like this mermaid:
It's not just a dead fish butt
sewn to a monkey carcass,
it's a marvelous creature
that makes us believe
that anything is possible.
You shut down this shack,
and you shut down our dreams!
At least...  my  dreams.
ALL: Aw.
( sighs ) I'm sorry, Soos,
it's just there's no one
around to run it.
At least there  wouldn't  be
if I hadn't just found
the perfect replacement.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the Mystery Shack
is under new management!
( all cheer )
You...you mean it,
Mister Mystery?
You're Mister Mystery now,
Soos.
Try not to burn
the place down.
I'll move in immediately.
( truck beeping )
( all cheering )
( birds chirping )
Do you  really
have to go?
There is still so much
we haven't done together.
Summer's over,
Candy.
It's time for us
to grow up.
But not
too  much.
Aaah! I hate my dumb heart
for making me feel things!
Cut. It. Out. Heart!
Hey, can you punch
my heart too?
No, mine!
Punch  my  feelings away!
Candy and Grenda,
thank you for
being my people.
You'll always be
my best friends.
Grunkle Stan,
thanks for wearing
my Goodbye sweater.
Ah, it's cold out.
I had to.
What? But it's, like,
eighty-something degrees
out today.
BOTH: Can it, Soos!
( all laugh )
Hey. You mean a lot to me,
man.
You too.
Something to
remember me by.
Oh, and this.
Read it the next time
you miss Gravity Falls.
Last bus leaving Gravity Falls.
All aboard.
Guess we said goodbye
to everyone except...
Waddles.
I...don't know
how to explain this,
but...
Mom and Dad won't let me
bring a pig home
to California, so...
you have to stay here!
( squeals )
Come on, come on!
I have to  go.
I'm...I'm sorry, Waddles!
You know what? Forget it!
I lived with this pig
all summer,
now  your  parents
are gonna have to!
Hey, bus guy!
This pig is coming
with the kids!
Now, hold on a second.
Bringing animals aboard
a moving vehicle
is strictly prohibited
by--
Wah-- Welcome aboard.
You can sit in
the front row, pig.
Kids, you knuckleheads
were nothin' but a nuisance
and I'm glad to be rid of ya.
We'll miss you too,
Grunkle Stan.
Ready to head
into the unknown?
Nope.
Let's do it.
( all shouting farewells )
Bye! Bye, everybody!
I'll miss you guys too!
SOOS: Bye, dudes! Bye!
DIPPER:  If you've ever
taken a road trip through
the Pacific Northwest,
you've probably
seen a bumper sticker
for a place
called Gravity Falls.
Well, I've moved in.
It's not on any maps,
and most people
have never heard of it.
Some people think it's a myth.
But if you're curious,
don't wait.
( all scream )
Take a trip.
( roaring )
Find it.
It's out there somewhere
in the woods.. waiting.