MALORY: Now tell me exactly
what happened.
LANA: You, through some shady
deal with the Border Patrol,
sent us to south Texas to capture
an individual named Moreno...
ARCHER: Mexico's most notorious coyote...
ARCHER: Which is español for
people-smuggler.
LANA: Thanks, that's --
ARCHER: And also for coyote, turns out.
LANA: Archer --
ARCHER: It's a loanword.
Or is it a calque?
LANA: Why do you always do this?
ARCHER: Because I'm always bored.
CYRIL: Is he -- this is
totally nerve wracking!
How are you bored? !
LANA: Don't engage him.
ARCHER: Because I've been lying
in scorpion piss for two hours,
in the sunblasted shithole
which is Texas, waiting for a
stupid truck stuffed with smallish
brown people who just want a job!
CYRIL: And probably
Mexican cartel gunmen!
LANA: What'd I just say?
ARCHER: Big whoop, I'm
spooning a Barrett fifty-cal.
I could kill a building.
LANA: Just put one through the engine
block when the truck has to stop.
Please.
LANA: This is what he does.
He knows we're tense because
we're normal human beings.
My theory, and I'm serious, is
that he's got some rare kind of
pervasive developmental disorder, or
even undiagnosed atypical autism.
ARCHER: Your uh, mic's hot.
LANA: I know.
ARCHER: Wow.
Well, here comes the truck...
LANA: Okay, we're in position.
ARCHER: Great, so after we catch him, you
can intentionally hurt his feelings.
LANA: Okay, first of all --
CYRIL: Can I hold the fake baby!
LANA: Will you man up? !
Kimberly Kevlar? !
Here we go.
Archer, you ready?
ARCHER: Hang on Lana, I'm stacking
rocks in order of descending size.
LANA: See, right there, that's...
CHUY: Oye! Mueve el coche!
LANA: Hi, yeah, we broke down?
And --
CHUY: Bueno pues, los traspaso!
CYRIL: Don't run over us, we have a baby!
CYRIL: Oops.
WOMAN: Es un robo!
Vaya!
LANA: Archer!
ARCHER: Not talking to you.
CHUY: Ay!
ARCHER: I can do this all day!
Since I find repetitive
behavior so calming!
LANA: Jesus Christ, I'm sorry!
ARCHER: Ow!
Apologize to my tinnitus!
Now hands up, Moreno!
It's over!
MALORY: What're you -- that's not Moreno...
MERCEDES: I am Moreno!
ARCHER: [awed gasp]
MALORY: Moreno is a woman.
LANA: No shit.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
MALORY: I don't understand.
If Moreno had surrendered,
how did it go so wrong?
LANA: Uh, well, kinda slowly at first...
I said slowly!
ARCHER: Whoa, hey, ladies, c'mon!
I know the adrenaline's still
pumping, but let's, ya know,
de-escalate the situation.
LANA: Oh for -- de-escalate your dick.
ARCHER: De -- wait.
Escalate shutting up.
Hola, soy Sterling Archer, agente de --
MERCEDES: De ISIS, no?
LANA: Wait, how did you --
ARCHER: Lana, Mexico gets the news!
I think, do you guys,
uh, las notícias...?
LANA: Well, here's some news--
Now this is happening.
ARCHER: I actually have
some thoughts on that.
LANA: No, you actually --
ARCHER: Do, and those thoughts
are, how about we let Señor... ita?
MERCEDES: Sí.
ARCHER: Awesome, Señorita Moreno
go, with a stern warning, if she
promises never to do this
again, maybe over a drink?
MAN: Hola?
ARCHER: Oh shit, I forgot
there's people in there.
Cyril, open the door, idiot.
CYRIL: Don't push me!
LANA: And do not!
Open that door!
CYRIL: But -- c'mon,
they gotta be roasting.
LANA: Well I'm sorry, but if
we let 'em out, then boom!
They scatter!
ARCHER: (laughing) To where? !
LANA: Uh, our overburdened
health care system?
Ooh!
Or maybe our tax-funded
government schools, for which -
spoiler ahead - they don't pay taxes!
ARCHER: How is a Lorax-blowing
treehugger like you anti-immigration? !
LANA: Because illegal immigration--
ARCHER: Exactly! I mean, it's
not like your ancestors, ya know...
had papers!
LANA: Wow.
ARCHER: Cyril I said open the door!
CYRIL: And I said don't push me!
LANA: And then very, very suddenly.
ARCHER: Because I couldn't hear you!
Over the sound!
Of now I'm punching you!
LANA: Dammit Archer, let him --
ARCHER: Oops.
CYRIL: Lana!
Have you lost your mind? !
ARCHER: No, just my temper.
Now open the goddamn door.
ARCHER: And Señorita
Moreno, you're free to go.
Although the appropriate thing would
be to buy me a thank-you drink.
MERCEDES: Uh...?
ARCHER: What're you doing.
CYRIL: What are you doing? !
You almost killed Lana!
LANA: Nnghh...
ARCHER: No, see, she's fine!
CYRIL: She's not fine, she's
at least got a concussion!
ARCHER: So?
You get like, six freebies.
CYRIL: No you don't!
ARCHER: Yes you do,
Cyril, now put it down!
CYRIL: You put it down!
It's over!
We are turning Moreno over to the border
patrol and taking Lana to a hospital!
ARCHER: Can't let you do that.
The first part, hospital's
probably a good idea.
CYRIL: Well, then we'll just see what
your mother has to say about it!
ARCHER: Do not call her, I swear
to God I'll -- wait, hang on,
are you wearing kevlar?
CYRIL: Yes, because I'm
not an idi -- oh no.
ARCHER: Sorry, I know that hurt.
CYRIL: Nnghhhh...
ARCHER: There, just like
"The Defiant Ones."
Now then, I believe there was some
mention of a thank-you drink?
MALORY: So, just so I'm clear...
You expect me to believe
that Sterling beat both of
you up, then shot Cyril?
LANA: Uh...
CYRIL: Uh...
MALORY: For some
haggard Mexican?
- I wouldn't really describe her as haggard...
- I would.
CYRIL: Of course you would.
LANA: But, shut up, tempers were kinda
high, about the illegals in the truck.
MALORY: Oh who cares about them.
CYRIL: Not Lana.
MALORY: Still, though, it doesn't--
Do you mind? !
CHERYL/CAROL: Yes, it's the most
stupidest boring job in the whole stupid
boring world!
But you insist that we do it.
MALORY: Not right this second!
CHERYL/CAROL: Remind me, Pam,
when did Ms. Archer say she
wanted us to shred this crap?
PAM: You did say right this second.
MALORY: I said it on Tuesday!
CHERYL/CAROL: Well? !
MALORY: Well what? !
CHERYL/CAROL: I actually
don't have a follow-up.
PAM: But speaking of, I bet a Mexican
would do this for a buck an hour.
MALORY: Those documents are top-secret!
CYRIL: You let Pam do it.
PAM: Dicknuts.
I'm just sayin, they work hard
as hell, and they work cheap.
CHERYL/CAROL: Cheap, because
they don't pay taxes!
LANA: Thank you!
CHERYL/CAROL: And when did
you work with Mexicans?
PAM: Where do you think milk comes from?
PAM: How's it hangin, Jorge?
JORGE: Bien, Miss Pam.
How are joo?
PAM: Yeah, I think you're ready.
CHERYL/CAROL: Milk comes from Mexicans?
Oh my God, what's cereal made from? !
Thank you.
PAM: Labor of love.
MALORY: Well?
Then what?
I suppose next you'll tell me
Sterling drove off in the truck
with this Mexican woman?
CYRIL: Uh, no.
Because if you will recall...
Archer shot out the engine block...
And I don't think she was the
only one he drove off with...
MALORY: So where did they all go?
And how?
LANA: Who the hell knows where? !
CYRIL: Although we do have
a working theory on how...
ARCHER: Hey I'm serious, if I have to
pull this car over you will regret it!
ARCHER: So share the goddamn Doritos!
Yeah, lookin right at you, Lupe.
BILBO: You want me to look for what?
MALORY: A station wagon!
Clean the impending massive
heart attack out of your ears.
BILBO: A station wagon.
In all of Texas.
LANA: Yeah, or Arizona, Mexico, New Mexico...
CHERYL/CAROL: Oh my God.
PAM: You just got that.
BILBO: Mmmokay, but that's gonna be kind
of a needle in a -- hey, is that it? !
LANA: Oh. No, it was--
BILBO: Is that it?
Is that it?
Or is it that?
MALORY: Alright, point --
BILBO: Wait wait wait wait!
Is that it? !
MALORY: Point taken!
BILBO: Ow!
Hey, ya know what? !
MALORY: Swear to God, you people
make me want to pump nerve gas
through the vents.
KRIEGER: Just say the word.
LANA: Krieger!
No!
Or, nein, or -- And how the
hell is this our fault?
BILBO: Rrrnn...
KRIEGER: She slapped you so hard you died.
BILBO: No, I think I'm really dyin...
KRIEGER (chuckling) I know.
Hey, there's Archer.
ARCHER: Aaaaaaagh!
Ugh, whoever that was, I'm serious,
pretty sure you've got giardia.
MERCEDES: I'm serious, please, thank you,
but we need to get back into Mexico.
Solo para reagruparnos!
What the hell kind of plan is this? !
ARCHER: Mmm, I dunno if
I'd call it a plan...?
MERCEDES: No one would!
We can't drive around Texas!
What about the border patrol? !
ARCHER: The what?
RED: What in the... hell? !
Ten-eighty, we got a ten-eighty!
CAT: Neat!
MERCEDES: Puto cabezamierda
pendejo cabron!
ARCHER: Ow! Ow!
I'm really starting to
regret helping you!
MERCEDES: Wh-?
This is the opposite of help!
Which no one asked you for anyway!
ARCHER: That's what makes it so noble!
MERCEDES: Está loco!
CHUY: Loco, no sé.
Tal vez autismo.
ARCHER: Goddammit Chuy
I don't have autism!
I thought if I let you go
you'd at least blow me!
MERCEDES: Pinche
cabezamierda pendejo cabron!
You think I am some kind of whore? !
ARCHER: No, but -- Chuy, back me
up here, was there not, like, a
cock-hungry vibe?
RED: Driver.
Driver.
Driver!
ARCHER: Hey guys!
Can you escort us to a hospital?
I bet at least three of these
woman are about to give birth.
Whoa, okay, okay, I'm pulling ov --
RED: We're ten-fifty we're ten-fifty!
ARCHER: What the shit? !
Who did that? !
Malo, Lupe, muy malo!
Oh, plus you are just covered in...
polvo Dorito!
MERCEDES: Diós mio, don't kill them!
ARCHER: What? !
God, what kind of person
do you think I am?
MERCEDES: I really think
you might be insane.
ARCHER: That was more of a rhetorical--
MERCEDES: But I also think you
make a big risk, to help some poor
people who just want a better life
for their family.
And that, to me, is muy admirable.
ARCHER: See?
I knew you wanted to blow m --
Sorry, that was inappropriate.
Although so was the response.
RED: Drop the weapon!
Drop it!
ARCHER: Here.
MERCEDES: You are crazy!
They'll kill us!
ARCHER: Uh-uh, empty.
MERCEDES: Wh-?
RED: Last warning!
ARCHER: Those are
three-fifty-seven, ow, Ruger sixes.
They each fired six.
MERCEDES: How did you count them? !
ARCHER: I'm just super good at that.
Oh my God, maybe I am autistic.
RED: O.K. ya dirty-ass beaner! That's it!
[ CLICK CLICK CLICK CLICK! ]
MERCEDES: Qué? !
I'm sorry, I couldn't hear
you over the sound of...
espera, tenía algo para esto.
RED: But I'd like to take this opportunity
to apologize for that racial slur.
MERCEDES: Sí?
What about the racial profiling?
Whatever happened to probable cause?
RED: Our probable cause is the border!
Which we protect from terrorists?
Look, we're just doin our job here.
ARCHER: Shittily...
Two-for-twelve at that distance?
Although, two does seem like plenty.
LUPE: Mijo, no debes beber.
ARCHER: Really, you learn
that in med school? !
Lo siento, Lupe, tengo mucho dolor.
But quit hogging the beads, I'm
sure Marisol and Paz wanna pray.
And these people aren't -- I
mean not to sound racist, but
we all know who the terrorists are...
LUPE: Los musulmanes.
ARCHER: Lupe!
C'mon, you're in America
now, you just imply it.
RED: Hey, let us go.
You got our first aid kit, the
radio outta the truck so you
can monitor the police band...
ARCHER: And, not to sound racist again?
But how many Mexicans does it
take to hook up a car stereo? !
MERCEDES: Hey!
ARCHER: Well? !
MERCEDES: Well what? !
ARCHER: Don't actually have a follow-up.
But seriously, Chuy, que the hell pasa?
CHUY: I dunno, the police band is
working, but now the eight-track is not.
ARCHER: Why!
Would we need the eight-track? !
Oh, that can't be good...
MERCEDES: Basta!
Vamonos!
We go to hospital!
You two!
Get your ass off the car!
RED: You can't just leave us here!
We're twenty miles away
from our last call-in!
We'll die out here!
ARCHER: Goddamnit... I'm actually gonna
take that back... I'm glad you took the
time to fix it.
Eight-track was the way to go.
LANA: What do you mean "Way to go"?
Which you clearly said sarcastically.
MALORY: I mean,
thanks to you, now there might not be any...
reward money, which I had
earmarked for -- vital operations.
LANA: You were gonna re-do your office.
MALORY: Picture it all sort of
pan-Asian Mod, and the carpet
just a sea of white!
But now I'm stuck with cat-puke green.
Because you couldn't control Sterling.
LANA: Since when is babysitting Archer
my job, my God, that's exactly my job...
MALORY: Which, to belabor
the point, you failed.
Now he's run off with this old
Mexican woman to who knows where!
LANA: Ewww!
MALORY: Put a shirt on,
what is wrong with you? !
CYRIL: Archer!
Is what is wrong with me!
And not that I care, at all, but
have you tried calling him?
MALORY: Please, with
those idiot voicemails?
LANA: Ugh.
Although, it couldn't hurt...
ARCHER: Hang on, I should get that...
MERCEDES: Now?
ARCHER: Trust me, if you knew my mother...
MERCEDES: Please, if you knew mine.
But you should not be talking right now.
KINDLY OLD VET: And he
really shouldn't be drinkin.
ARCHER: Really?
You learn that in med school?
That you obviously didn't get into? !
I'm sorry, veterinarian,
I'm in a lot of pain.
KINDLY OLD VET: I don't
even know how you're alive.
ARCHER: I'm very strong.
And also very drunk.
Which, paging Doctor D.T.
McShakyhands?
Seriously, get your shit together.
Mother?
Listen, I'm sorry, I take...
ARCHER: Equal responsibility, with Lana...
LANA: Wh-? !
ARCHER: But -- ow!
C'mon, Katy Hepburn!
The stupid Border Patrol shot
me, twice, and I could really
use a medivac chopper.
I'm kinda near -- hey, where --
Goddammit man, pace yourself!
MALORY: See?
They just get more and more
elaborate, and then it's "ha ha
beep" and then somehow I'm the idiot.
ARCHER: What? !
No no no this isn't a voi--
[ dial tone ] Smail.
Well, I'm sure there's a lesson
in there somewhere, but -- ow!
KINDLY OLD VET: Hic!
That oughta do 'er.
MERCEDES: Gracias a Diós!
And to you, doctor!
You truly have the gift of healing!
KINDLY OLD VET: Boy, I wish you'd
tell that to the licensing board.
ARCHER: You don't even
have a vet license? !
KINDLY OLD VET: Thanks to
one petty local politician.
And one petty barn fulla dead horses.
ARCHER: Will you shut
up and stitch me up? !
MALORY: Although... if that
wasn't a prank, and the
Border Patrol did shoot him...
LANA & CYRIL: (snide laugh)
Inappropriate.
MALORY: Oh he just has to ruin everything...
KINDLY OLD VET: Yeah, so watch
out for dehydration...
MERCEDES: Thank you, doctor, we will.
KINDLY OLD VET: And also
for internal bleeding.
MERCEDES: We --
KINDLY OLD VET: And sepsis.
KINDLY OLD VET: And MRSA.
MERCEDES: We --
KINDLY OLD VET: And probably not
a bad idea to get him
tested for feline AIDS.
ARCHER: We get it!
Now can we go already? !
He said, in agony, because the
unlicensed vet drank all his tequila!
LUPE: Es mejor, no debes beber.
ARCHER: Lupe, ya tengo una madre!
Now go!
MERCEDES: Thank you, doctor.
KINDLY OLD VET: Oh, don't thank me.
Seriously, I probably did more
harm than good, so if there's
any way to get to one, a medivac
chopper wouldn't kill him.
Less he got flung up
into the blades somehow.
Yeah, that'd do it...
MALORY: That will do, thank you!
LANA: I -- wait, but two Border
Patrol agents are missing,
Archer's missing, and you
want us to do... nothing?
MALORY: Yes, just like
you've done up to now.
LANA: Malory, we --
MALORY: But thank you both for
all that you did do.
Which, again, was nothing.
CYRIL: Nothing -- I got shot!
MALORY: Any idiot can get shot, Cyril!
Ask Brett!
Now if you'll excuse me, I need
to make some calls to see if I
can get my son out of this mess.
PAM: How's it hangin, Grimace?
CYRIL: Owww!
Why?
ARCHER: Why's the AC on?
MERCEDES: That's not
the AC, it's the heat!
ARCHER: Then why's it so cold?
LUPE: Porque vas al cielo...
ARCHER: Really doubt I'm going to heaven...
LUPE: Well, dying.
MERCEDES: No he's not!
ARCHER: Well, you say that...
MERCEDES: We'll never make it in
time in this crappy car!
You need a helicopter!
ARCHER: Yeah, I dunno if you heard, but--
I don't have access to a helicopter.
MERCEDES: They do.
RED: C'mon, we're in
enough trouble already!
MERCEDES: With who.
- Dammit... - You call headquarters,
you say an innocent Amer --
Republican was shot in a
gunfight with some illegals...
ARCHER: Wh-?
No, that'll just make
you people look worse!
No, not worse as in -- okay, screw
you guys, you know what I meant.
But if they call this in, you'll --
MERCEDES: We will be far away by then.
And besides, what kind of car will
the Border Patrol be looking for?
RED: A... ridiculous lowrider truck with
fender-flares and louvers and shit?
MERCEDES: Exacto.
And so, Mr. Archer, I'm
afraid for us, this is adios.
ARCHER: Adios?
Not hasta pronto, or --
So, I'm guessing that's a
no possible on the blowjob?
MERCEDES: Adios, lindo.
RED: Well, if that ain't a big loada shit...
Turns out he's some kinda spook.
ARCHER: Dude, phrasing!
He's right here!
Don't listen to him, you're beautiful.
As is whatever you're doing,
with the, morphine-wise.
Keep that coming.
RED: That was my boss's boss's boss.
He says yer ass gets total immunity!
ARCHER: Ha ha!
For helping the most notorious coyote
in todo Mexico, Mercedes Moreno? !
RED: Mercedes?
ARCHER: Vrooom!
RED: Shit, she must be her daughter...
ARCHER: Wait, whose daughter?
RED: Maria Moreno, dumbass.
She's who we're after.
Bet she smuggles in a thouzna
them sumbitches a year.
But word on the street
is, now she's expanding!
Gonna start bringin em in convoys!
And blow me if we can catch her.
CAT: Mmm!
ARCHER: But if Mercedes isn't...
then why would... but... oh, hang on a sec.
Dear Sterling.
You probably should not be
reading this out loud, bec --
MERCEDES: Because hopefully you
are with the Border Patrol, on
the way to a real hospital.
I'm so sorry you got shot.
And I don't know how to tell you this,
but we did not meet by accident.
We knew you would be there, Sterling.
MERCEDES: Vale vale, ahí estan.
Prepárate.
We knew your strengths... And we also
knew your -- well, one of your many, many
weaknesses.
MERCEDES: Por suerte no
es Ray Gillette, eh?
And then... well, you know the rest.
ARCHER: What the... mierda!
MERCEDES: Cuidate, Sterling Archer,
te guardaré siempre en mi corazón.
ARCHER: But... who? !
Oh hang on, there's a --
MERCEDES: P.S., and as for who -- wait, hang on.
Oh, Lupe says she will
be praying for you.
And as for who, I hate to be the
one to tell you this, but maybe
you know someone who values money...
ARCHER: Oh my... Mother.
MERCEDES: More than their
so-called principles?
So what do you care if it's in pesos?
Well, actually, no, I was,
but then I thought...
white carpet?
Because he wouldn't believe what
those *** are.
What are you doing?
What? Nothing. I'm just a hologram.
Anyhoo...
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com