>> ARCHER: What do you mean,
your water broke?!
>> LANA: What do you mean, what
do I mean? I mean that!
I'm going into labor!
>> CHERLENE: Wait. What?!
>> LANA: I'm having a baby?
>> CHERLENE: Gross!
>> ARCHER: Bu-But it's early.
Is-is that early?!
>> LANA: Like, ten days, but...
>> ARCHER: But that's bad.
Is that bad?!
>> LANA: Archer, none of this
is ideal!
>> HOLLY: Hey!
>> HOLLY: What the hell are you
people doing in San Marcos in
the first place?!
>> LANA: Selling weapons to
Calderón!
>> ARCHER: That we got from him!
>> HOLLY: What?!
>> HOLLY: What what? You didn't
think that was something I'd
like to know about?!
>> SLATER: I'm positive we
talked about this.
>> HOLLY: No, we didn't!
>> HOLLY: When?! When did we
talk about this?!
>> SLATER: 80% positive.
If the CIA is backing the rebels
against Calder...
Ohhh!
>> ARCHER: Lana!
Was that a contraction?!
>> LANA: Yup. Ohh!
God, I hope so. Yup.
>> ARCHER: Time!
Start a clock, assholes!
>> SLATER: Uh, okay. Mark!
(beep)
>> CHERLENE: Twain!
No, that's barges.
>> LANA: Shut up!
(groans)
But, hey, speaking of time...
>> ARCHER: What's your Bishop
Score?!
>> LANA: How should I...? Wait.
How do you even know what a
Bishop Score is?
>> ARCHER: I got certified as a
doula, which, turns out, is not
that hard.
Does the CIA know Calderón has a
nerve gas missile at the palace?
>> ARCHER: What?!
>> CHERLENE: Cool.
>> HOLLY: We didn't give him
gas!
>> LANA: Well, he's got it,
and we can't override the launch
sequence, so we've...
>> HOLLY: Get that idiot
Calderón on the phone!
>> ARCHER: Oh, did I mention, a
tiger ate him?
>> HOLLY: What?!
>> CHERLENE: Well, not ate ate.
>> ARCHER: Well, no, but by
now...
Okay, Slater, I know it's a
little sooner than we wanted,
but...
>> SLATER: Operation Dropkick.
Roger that.
>> LANA: What's Operation
Dropkick?
>> HOLLY: Well, the endgame has
always been for us to invade
>> SLATER: Hey, Donna, we got a
carrier group in the Gulf,
right?
>> LANA: Wait. If you were going
to invade San Marcos, then why
have you been selling weapons to
Calderón?
>> HOLLY: So he could fight the
rebels.
>> HOLLY: Well, technically,
they're mercenaries from
Honduras and Guatemala, but yes.
>> LANA: Okay, so, am I just
stupid, or...?
>> CHERLENE: Duh. Pregnant.
>> SLATER: Yeah, airstrike,
naval bombardment, amphibious
>> HOLLY: Calderón needed
weapons to fight the rebels, but
he didn't have money to buy
weapons.
He only had cocaine, but Iran
was like, "No way. Cash only."
So...
>> ARCHER & LANA: Iran?!
>> HOLLY: Ooh, sorry. Iraq.
Wait. No, Iran.
No, doesn't matter who.
Anyway, to buy the weapons, we
needed to... monetize the
cocaine.
(Lana gasps)
>> LANA: Oh, my God.
We've been trying to monetize
cocaine for, like...
I mean, you even came to the
house, where we...
We've been selling cocaine for
the CIA so they could buy arms
from Iran?!
Did we at least free some
hostages?!
>> HOLLY: No, this was about our
annual budget.
>> ARCHER & LANA: What?!
>> HOLLY: If we don't spend it
this year, we can't get an
increase next year.
>> ARCHER: You son of a...
>> HOLLY: Oh, come on, Archer.
Drop the act!
He was in on it from day one.
>> ARCHER & LANA: What?!
(Lana growls)
(Archer chokes)
(Cherlene squeals and laughs)
>> LANA: You lying son of a
bitch!
(Archer gasps, mutters)
>> LANA: You knew about this the
entire time?!
>> ARCHER: No, no.
(Archer choking)
(Cherlene squeals)
>> SLATER: Hey, do you mind?
I'm trying to call in an
air strike here.
>> HOLLY: Ooh, hey, what's our
ride situation?
>> SLATER: Hang on.
Thanks, doll.
Air strike on the palace is a
go, and I suggest we take
>> HOLLY: Good. Yeah, we need
plenty of room... until we dump
them at a black site.
(Archer gasps, coughs)
>> HOLLY: Come on, even if you
people hadn't lost 50 million
bucks worth of our cocaine, you
know way too much.
>> CHERLENE: Uh, I don't know
anything!
>> HOLLY: I believe that to be
literally true.
Oye, muchachos!
Agarrenlos!
(Lana grunts)
(grunting)
(gun cocks, Lana yells)
>> HOLLY: Okay. Whoa! Whoa!
>> SLATER: Jesus! We give up.
>> HOLLY: Whoa! Whoa! Come on.
>> SLATER: Don't shoot!
(Lana sighs)
>> LANA: Now then.
Let's get this baby out of me.
>> CHERLENE: Gross!
>> LANA: Will you sh...
(Lana groans loudly)
>> ARCHER (weakly): Time?!
>> SLATER: Nine minutes!
What? This is exciting.
>> KRIEGER: Right?
>> FEMALE COMPUTER VOICE:
Minutes to launch-- 60.
>> RAY: Yeah, Krieger, I guess
trying to defuse a warhead
tipped with deadly nerve gas is
technically exciting.
>> KRIEGER: Yeah, right?
>> RAY: What is wrong with you?
>> KRIEGER: Nothin', Roy.
>> RAY: Or Ray.
>> KRIEGER: Eh. Doesn't matter
who.
>> CYRIL: Krieger!
(Krieger and Ray gasp)
>> CYRIL: Where are we on the
missile?!
>> KRIEGER: Uh, kind of just
like... on it.
Oh, do you mean where are we in
the process of disarming it?
Ooh! Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
(Cyril sighs)
Ow! Come on. Ow! Ow!
>> CYRIL: Okay.
>> MALORY: What happened?!
Did it explode?!
>> CYRIL: Uh, no.
>> MALORY: Well, it's just a
matter of time before it does,
with those idiots working on it!
We need to leave!
>> CYRIL: Well, A: I'm
president for life, so I'm not
going anywhere, and B...
>> COMANDANTE: Señor Presidente!
Our radar station has detected
incoming bombers!
From their heading, they
appear... American!
(Malory gasps)
(Cyril clears his throat)
>> CYRIL: And B...
>> COMANDANTE: And I hate to
tell you this, but the First
Lady and I are having an affair.
(Cyril sniffles)
>> CYRIL: Damn, dawg.
That was my B.
>> JULIANA: It's over, Cyril.
It's over!
>> CYRIL: Nothing is over!
Nothing!
You don't just turn it off!
It wasn't my war!
You asked me.
I didn't ask you!
And I did what I had to do to
win!
But somebody wouldn't let us
>> MALORY: Yes, and that
somebody is a U.S. Navy carrier
group, so let's go already!
(Cyril sniffles)
>> CYRIL: Okay, but I'm taking
these.
>> MALORY (laughing): Oh, we're
taking everything!
Furs, jewels, the silverware,
bullion, anything you can cram
in a suitcase!
>> PAM: Mm, mm. Wouldn't bullion
leak out of a...?
Ow! Ow!
Cut it... Ow, goddamn it!
I... Ow!
>> MALORY: Gold bullion, you
idiot!
>> PAM: I don't know what that
is!
>> JULIANA: And I don't know who
you think you are!
>> MALORY: Oh, yes, we are, and
if you've got any sense, you'll
fill your pockets, too!
Because your regime is
officially over.
And I've seen coups from Angola
to Zanzibar, and this is how it
ends: in the trunk of a taxi
to the airport, your belly
full of diamonds and vodka,
praying your driver doesn't
rat you out to the Reds
at the last checkpoint.
Because then, the last thing
you'll ever hear, besides a
pistol cocking behind your head,
is Ivan's laugh--
(Pam cackling)
>> MALORY: What... in the name
of God... is funny?!
>> PAM (laughing): You said
you've seen cooze.
(Pam clears her throat)
Appropes.
(Pam grunts)
>> REBEL SOLDIER 1: Vamonos!
Los Americanos vienen!
>> REBEL SOLDIERS: Corre!
Corre! Corre!
>> REBEL SOLDIER 2: Espere!
Espere! Esp-- wughh!
>> CHERLENE: Aww...
All the gardeners are running
away.
>> HOLLY: Because this entire
country's about to be up to its
>> SLATER: And unless you people
want to wind up classified as
enemy combatants, you...
(gunfire)
>> ARCHER: Six minutes!
Got to remember to breathe,
though. That's the...
>> LANA: Oh, get out, you lying
sack of bastard!
>> ARCHER: Okay, A: He and
Mother are the lying sacks of
bastard.
I didn't know it was the CIA's
cocaine.
And B: Seriously, buddy, let's
try and work on that breathing.
>> CHERLENE: What's wrong with
her?
>> ARCHER: Wha...?
She's having a baby!
>> CHERLENE: Gross.
(Cherlene slurping)
(Lana breathing rapidly)
>> ARCHER: Doing good, buddy.
>> LANA: Archer!
If you call me buddy again, I
will put the bullets in your
body by hand!
>> ARCHER: Shh, and we're
breathing...
(both breathe deeply)
>> LANA (exhaling): Ooh...
>> ARCHER: There we go.
Okay, Carol!
(Cherlene slurps)
>> CHERLENE: What?
Jesus! What is your problem!
>> LANA: Morphine, want, find,
give!
>> ARCHER: Shh. Come on, Lana,
you don't need that.
>> LANA (gasps): How dare you
tell me what I...
Okay, Carol, I need you to look
down there and give me a
sit-rep.
>> CHERLENE: Down where?
>> ARCHER: There, down there, at
her, um...
>> CHERLENE: Ew! No! You do it!
>> SLATER: I'll do it!
I can't look down there because
there's, like, a hundred percent
chance that at some point in the
future we're gonna have sex,
so...
>> ARCHER: Shh. So just look
down there and...
>> CHERLENE: I'm not looking at
her goddamn va... Joinks!
Well, you don't need to shave.
(laughs) That thing is smooth.
>> LANA: I...!
Thank you.
>> CHERLENE: And also kind of
mauve.
>> LANA (sighs): Okay.
>> SLATER: Eh, I'd say more of a
mauve-taupe?
Ow!
(Lana grunting loudly)
>> ARCHER: Breathe, bu...
breathe, friend.
Because, uh...
Wow. Okay.
>> FEMALE COMPUTER VOICE:
Minutes to launch...
six...
(Gillette yells)
(Krieger screaming)
>> GILLETTE: Where the...
(approaching footsteps,
screaming continues)
>> KRIEGER (panting): Okay...
I have some thoughts on this.
>> GILLETTE: Really?
>> KRIEGER: Yes.
>> GILLETTE: Which are...?!
>> KRIEGER: Oh. Okay.
So, I don't think we can disarm
this thing.
>> GILLETTE : Really?
>> KRIEGER: Yes.
Oh. Okay. So, it doesn't have an
explosive payload, so it's
basically just a flying
trash can.
The only dangerous part is the
nerve gas.
(jet engines whooshing)
>> GILLETTE: I'm listening.
>> COPILOT (over radio): Roger
that, flight deck. Um...
>> PILOT: Range-- 150.
ETA-- 12 minutes.
>> COPILOT: Hey, is your dad
still big into tapas?
>> PILOT: My what?
Oh, no, that wasn't my dad.
>> COPILOT: Well, who was it?
>> PILOT: Doesn't matter who.
>> PAM: Because these trunks
feel light.
Do you swear they're full of
cocaine?
>> MALORY: As God... is my
witness.
>> PAM: God hates you.
Open 'em up.
>> MALORY: Wha...?
(horn honking)
>> CYRIL: Will you two come on?!
>> PAM: On what?
>> MALORY: Ugh!
(jets whooshing)
>> MALORY (gasps): If we get out
of here alive, I'll buy you all
new cocaine.
>> PAM: You heard her, Cyril--
that is legally binding.
>> CYRIL: Yeah, we'll stop
at a notary.
>> MALORY: There's no time!
>> SLATER: Hey. Hi!
Do you people hear that?
>> HOLLY: After the air strike
on the palace, you won't be able
to swing a dead cat around here
without hitting a Marine.
>> CHERLENE: Plus, if you did, I
bet they'd smash your teeth down
your stupid throat.
>> ARCHER: Okay, uh...
Lana, I need to borrow your
weapon.
>> LANA: No! I will see you in
Hell first.
>> ARCHER: I... Okay, Carol,
grab that one.
(cocks weapon)
>> CHERLENE: Private Me,
reporting for sploosh.
>> ARCHER (groans): Take
Tweedledick and Tweedleballs, go
get the jet ready for takeoff...
>> CHERLENE: Outlaw country!
>> ARCHER: Let me finish!
>> ARCHER: And make sure they
don't escape.
>> CHERLENE: Oh, my God, good
thing you added that last part.
You heard the doula-- move it!
>> LANA: And get me some
frickin' morphine!
>> ARCHER: Lana, come on, what
kind of doula would I be if I
let you have more...
(rifle clicks)
>> ARCHER: Wha...?
(Lana grunting loudly)
>> ARCHER: Wow.
>> ARCHER (chuckling): You were
really gonna shoot me in the
face?
>> LANA (sniffles): Is that so
much to ask?
>> COPILOT: Uncle.
Uh, friend of the family.
>> PILOT: Dude. Drop it.
(classical piano music playing)
>> COMANDANTE: We should get to
the shelter soon.
>> JULIANA: You coward.
>> COMANDANTE: Wha...?
>> JULIANA: I've never loved
you.
(Comandante sighs)
>> COMANDANTE: Okay.
>> CYRIL: But what if the rebels
recognize me?
>> PAM: Yeah, and then drag him
out of the car and kneel him
down and shoot him in the back
of the head and string him up on
a lamppost like Mussolini!
>> CYRIL: Yeah. What then?
>> MALORY: That's a chance I'm
willing to take.
>> PAM: Me too.
(Pam munching, chewing)
>> MALORY: Cyril, look...
(Cyril screaming)
(Krieger and Gillette screaming)
(all screaming)
(screaming stops)
(song playing quietly on radio)
>> KRIEGER: Hi, guys.
>> MALORY: What the hell are you
idiots...
(rumbling)
(song continues on radio):
¶ It's them broken hearts...
>> KRIEGER: Oh, come on, we
couldn't leave it in the rocket.
(car thuds, all gasp)
And we couldn't just leave it
lying in the road.
Come on, you don't want a thing
like that falling into the wrong
The only thing necessary for
evil to triumph is that good men
do nothing.
>> MALORY: Said the clone of
Adolf Hitler.
>> KRIEGER: Well... Edmund
Burke, but...
Doesn't matter who.
(over radio): ¶ ...auto parts
This year. ¶
(rattling)
>> PILOT: Dude, drop it.
>> COPILOT: I'm not gonna judge
you.
>> PILOT: The ordnance, Mike.
Drop the ordnance.
>> COPILOT (chuckles): Oh.
Duh.
>> PILOT (sighs): Idiot.
(explosions thundering)
>> MALORY: Cyril, for God's
sake, be careful!
>> CYRIL: Would you shut up?
(all gasping, grunting)
>> MALORY: Idiot.
(Lana screaming)
>> OTHERS: Huh? What the...?
>> MALORY: Lana?
(Lana screaming)
>> LANA: Archer!
What... are you doing?
>> ARCHER: I'm trying to get
this stupid angle right, Lana,
so you can look in the mirror
and see if you're crowning.
>> LANA: What?!
>> MALORY: For the love of
Christ!
>> ARCHER: Mother, hey, go over
there and tell me if you can...
>> MALORY: Get out!
And, Pam, get in here.
>> LANA (panting): No, no...
>> MALORY: Shh...
Everything's all right.
Here.
All right, now, Pam, I want
you to...
>> PAM: You know how many times
I've helped a cow give birth
in the barn?
Plus, one time, my sister Edie?
Well, she couldn't have it in
the house.
Long story.
A long, racist story.
>> RAY: I had black guy.
>> CYRIL: (groans) I wasn't in
the sperm donor pool.
>> RAY: Phra... Wait, are we
still doing phrasing?
>> KRIEGER: Huh.
Should I be in there?
I feel like I should.
I mean, I am a doctor.
>> RAY & CYRIL: No, you're not.
>> KRIEGER: Well, no, but...
a student of life.
(Archer grunting, loud crashing)
>> RAY: Loud.
(more crashing)
I have cigarettes, if you want
them!
>> ARCHER: (grunts) No, Ray, I
just feel like smashing stuff.
Jesus, I feel so helpless out
here!
What if something goes wrong?
What-what if there's a-a birth
defect or...
>> LANA: (grunts) No. No, no,
stop.
No, what if there's aren't
enough hands and feet?
>> MALORY: Shh, it's going to...
>> LANA: Oh, my God, what if
there are too many hands and
feet?
>> PAM: Hey! I have the correct
number of hands, but they're
currently kind of full and you
need a slappin', so...
>> LANA: Wait... (gasps)
>> MALORY: Oh, please.
Like you're the only one who
ever had a baby in a war zone.
>> LANA: You know...
>> PAM: Okay, okay, okay.
Get some hay ready to dry this
little bastard off because now
you are gonna push!
>> LANA: (grunts) No, no, no,
no, what if we... Ow!
>> PAM: You old bitch!
Now move that big fat smelly
ass, you hear?
A Day No Pigs Would Die?
Anybody?
Not a big Robert Newton Peck
crowd, huh?
>> MALORY: Who is...
>> PAM: Oh, shut up. Now push!
(Lana screaming)
>> ARCHER: (gasps) Lana!
>> CYRIL: Hey, hey, come on,
they've got this.
(baby crying)
(all gasp)
(Archer laughs)
(Cyril grunts)
>> PAM: Well, it's a girl!
>> OTHERS: Aw!
>> PAM: And whoever had black
guy, pay up.
>> ARCHER: Aw, shit.
>> RAY: Goddamn it!
>> PAM: Yep.
Got ourselves a little quadroon.
>> MALORY: (sighs) You did good,
kiddo.
>> LANA (dreamily): Mmm, yeah.
Oh, and, uh, I quit.
>> MALORY: Wha... Why?
>> LANA: Because you lying to me
I can handle-- I'm used to
that-- but...
(sighs) not Archer.
>> MALORY: Oh, for... He didn't
know that I made a deal to sell
cocaine for the CIA.
>> MALORY: Lana Kane, you have
known me for a long, long time.
When have I ever been honest
with Sterling?
>> LANA: Huh.
>> MALORY: Exactly.
Now, if you two will excuse me,
I need to go threaten and/or
bribe some federal agents.
Well, at least put a seatbelt on
it!
>> ARCHER: See?
>> KRIEGER: I thought it was
just for takeoff and landing!
>> MALORY: Jesus Christ.
>> ARCHER: So, um, how's she
doing?
I told her you didn't know
anything about the CIA deal.
>> ARCHER: Well, thanks for
telling the truth, Mother-- sure
>> MALORY: You keep it up,
mister, and I'll walk right back
in there and tell her the whole
thing was your idea.
>> ARCHER: Did you guys hear
that?
>> OTHERS: No.
>> MALORY: All right, Holly,
this is my offer and it is
nonnegotiable...
>> PAM: (gasps) You think she's
buying more coke?
>> CHERLENE: (groans) You and
your stupid, stupid cocaine!
Can't you give her a brain chip?
>> KRIEGER: A what?
Like you gave Cherlene so she
could become a country singer.
>> KRIEGER: Oh, no, that wasn't
a brain chip.
It was just the sticker off the
backpack of a little Lego
spaceman.
>> PAM: What?
>> CYRIL: A Lego sticker?
So my whole life, all I ever had
to do was believe in myself?
And inject a sticker into my
brain?
>> HOLLY: Are you out of your
mind?
Showing up at the mansion,
pretending to search for the
>> HOLLY: While planting the
seed in your idiot son's brain
>> MALORY: Which I could have
handled if the CIA had kept its
fat nose out!
>> HOLLY: And yet here we are,
with a $50 million hole in our
account.
>> MALORY: There's 40 of it.
An original Ivan Blitko we stole
from Calderón.
>> HOLLY: What am I supposed to
do with that?
What am I supposed to do with a
canister of nerve gas?
>> HOLLY: No, uh-uh.
That is now CIA property.
>> MALORY: Ooh, and won't that
be a feather in your cap.
They might even make you
director.
>> HOLLY: Hmm... or at least
Deputy Ops.
>> MALORY: Which-- and I'm just
spitballing here-- would mean
you could outsource a good deal
of business to a private firm.
(Malory slurps)
Like ISIS.
>> HOLLY: So you lose us $50
million and you want to get on
the CIA payroll?
>> MALORY: Right after you
renovate my offices.
>> HOLLY: Ha! You really are out
of your mind.
>> MALORY: Or right after I take
this deal to your partner in the
cockpit...
>> RAY: So, what's your deal?
>> SLATER: What's my deal?
>> RAY: Never mind.
>> MALORY: Because you suddenly
decided to take up skydiving.
(cocks gun)
>> HOLLY: I think we may have a
deal here.
(knocking)
>> ARCHER: Knock, knock.
>> LANA: Who's there?
>> ARCHER: Shit, I-I had
something for this.
>> LANA: (sighs) Come see the
baby, stupid.
>> ARCHER: Wow.
>> LANA: Yeah.
>> LANA: (sighs) Yeah.
>> ARCHER: I-I had black guy.
>> LANA: Yeah. So, about that...
>> ARCHER: I don't think it's
racist, it's just that I
thought...
>> LANA: Archer, shut up.
>> ARCHER: (chuckles)
You shut up.
(clears throat) Okay, so,
remember when you had cancer?
>> ARCHER: (chuckles) Um, uh,
vaguely.
>> LANA: (sighs) Okay.
Well, we all thought you were
gonna die.
And one night you got really
drunk and we almost had sex and,
right before you passed out, you
told me Malory had convinced you
to freeze a bunch of your sperm
at Dr. Feldman's office.
(high-pitched ringing)
And then you didn't die, and
then a few years went by and I
started thinking about having a
baby, but I was single.
And all the other stuff aside,
physically, you're an amazing
human being.
And all the other other stuff
aside, I do actually love you.
(muffled): And so here's this
viable sample just sitting there
at Dr. Feldman's, whose security
system is a joke, by the way.
And so I guess it maybe wasn't
the most ethical thing I've ever
done in my entire life, but...
(echoing): Archer?
Archer.
Archer...
>> ARCHER: Wuzzat?!
Wait, wait, huh, huh? What?
>> LANA: You okay?
>> ARCHER: (exhales) Yeah.
Sorry. For a second, I-I thought
I was just now coming out of a
coma from when I drowned, saving
your life eight months ago.
(Archer sighs)
Lana, am I just now coming out
of a coma from when I drowned
saving your life eight months
ago?
>> LANA: No.
>> ARCHER: Hmm.
Lana, am I just now coming out
of a coma from when I drowned,
saving your life eight months
ago?
>> LANA: No.
>> ARCHER: Then what are you...
Baby, what is she saying?
Baby?
Baby.
Baby!
(baby cooing)
>> ARCHER: M-meep.
>> LANA: Sterling Archer, I'd
like you to meet your daughter,
Abbiejean.
(Abbiejean cooing)
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> MAN: Made... in Georgia.