MALORY (O.S.): Hurry,
hurry, sit down, come in!
I have the most fantastic news!
ARCHER: What, did
Bub finally die?
LANA: Who's Bub?
MALORY: My mother, and before
you make some snotty comment,
yes I have a mother, do you
want to hear my news or not?!
LANA: Yeah, if you're done
yelling at me for no reason.
MALORY: Last night, an Air Force B-52
bomber crashed off the coast of Bermuda!
RAY: What? That's bad news!
ARCHER: Well it's about frickin time!
What, we're we not bombing them in
advance of an amphibious invasion?
LANA: Why would we invade.
Bermuda.
ARCHER: Ah, Bermuda. I
was thinking Bahamas.
LANA: Same question.
ARCHER: Same answer, Why not? It's
how we got the Virgin Islands.
CYRIL: Actually, the United States
bought the Virgin Islands from Denmark.
ARCHER: Okay, Mr. Peabody...
MALORY: Are you finished?
ARCHER: Yes.
MALORY: Good. Because the B-52 was -
ARCHER: In the middle of
the Bermuda Triangle, is this
about the Bermuda Triangle, because
that's my fourth biggest fear!
MALORY: It's about
the B-52's payload!
MALORY: Namely, a Mark-28
hydrogen bomb.
EVERYBODY: Ohhhh!
MALORY: Which ISIS...
is going to recover.
EVERYBODY: What!?
MALORY: And then give to the U.S.
government in exchange for a huge reward!
CYRIL: So, ransom it back.
MALORY: No, not ransom it, Cyril, we're-
look, semantics, whatever, this is -
CYRIL: Treason?
MALORY: A huge
opportunity for ISIS!
Or the Russians... MALORY: The B-52 is
on the ocean floor here, at a depth
of eight thousand feet...
ARCHER: or thirteen hundred
thirty-three fathoms.
LANA: How do you know that?
ARCHER: How do you not?
MALORY: So recovering the bomb
requires a deep submergence
vehicle. The only American DSV is here,
in the Pacific. The Russians have
one in the North Atlantic, so if
they hear about the wreck and start
- steaming toward it-
- They don't actually steam anymore, Mother.
MALORY: It's a figure of speech,
like "shut your hatch,"
because my point was, the Russians will
beat them to it. So we are going to
beat the Russians.
ARCHER: Give it up, folks!
Mike Eruzione!
LANA; Well - shut up - since
Krieger doesn't have a
submersible hidden in his lab...
KRIEGER: Or do I?
I don't, actually.
ARCHER: Then how are we supposed to
beat anybody to a hydrogen bomb, under
two-point-two-seven
leagues of water?!
CHERYL/CAROL: Oh my Jesus
God damn alright already!
MALORY: Can I
possibly help you?
CHERYL/CAROL: Please, I know
you were talking loud so
I'd hear you, so whatever, but
we're not speaking so if you
want a deep submergence whatever you can
talk to my stupid gross brother Cecil!
Who, by the way, is
here to see you.
Ms. Archer will see you now.
CECIL: Thank you, Cheryl, I-
CHERYL/CAROL: Rrraaaghh!
I hate you!
CECIL: Hello, I'm Cecil Tunt.
I believe you're in need
of some assistance?
ARCHER: (chuckling)
Yeah, RienPoortvliet just called,
he wants you to pose for him.
C'mon, beloved
illustrator of "Gnomes"?
Jesus, read a
coffee table book!
[theme music]
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
ARCHER (O.S.): Wow, you own an
island, an undersea laboratory,
and this... choppersaurus?
Guess it doesn't suck to
be a billionaire, huh?
CECIL: Probably not, but
Cheryl and I split our
parents' estate, so technically I'm
only worth five hundred million.
Which also doesn't
suck, obviously.
CHERYL/CAROL (O.S.): Unlike you
who totally sucks obviously!
PAM: Will you shut up?!
I swear to God, if you get us kicked
off before I get my jumbo scrimps on -
You'll wish you were
Michael Findlay.
CHERYL/CAROL: A, Cecil won't
kick you off, he wants
everybody here, for no good reason--
MALORY: He doesn't need one,
he's an American hero. Who's
going to make me rich.
CHERYL/CAROL: And B, that's
not even real shrimp.
This is all vegan-soy-bullshit.
PAM: Pffrrfft! Prrfft! Puh!
CHERYL/CAROL: Because he's
totally vegan, because his
stupid gross girlfriend Tiffy's a
vegan, and a... brother-stealer!
TIFFY (O.S.): Who can also
totally heeearyoooou...
CHERYL/CAROL: Which is amazing
because why aren't you dead
from protein deficiency?!
TIFFY: Uh, because I get all
eight essential amino acids
from amaranth and quinoa without
murdering helpless animals?
CHERYL/CAROL (O.S.): Oooooh!
TIFFY: kkkuughh!
CECIL (O.S.): Hey, Tiff?
Could you, instead of antagonizing
her, maybe go ahead and take off?
Love yoooou.
We'll rendezvous with my research vessel
in a few hours, so in the meantime,
I guess, continue to make such
wildly liberal use of the bar.
ARCHER: Done! You're okay, Cecil. I
don't get why Cheryl hates you so much.
CECIL: Right?
ARCHER: I mean, you've got
this whole Jacques Cousteau-
- thing going on, that's-
- Just one of many philanthropies. I have so
much on my plate, as it were.
Children Without Plates, speaking of
plates, uh, Doctors Within Borders...
ARCHER: Within borders.
CECIL: Well, of countries
ravaged by war.
ARCHER: Right, otherwise-
CECIL: Otherwise there's not really much point.
Then there's Nourish A Child, Shoe
A Child, Bespectacle A Child,
umm, One Laptop Per Child Soldier...
ARCHER: Wait, what?
CECIL: Which, unfortunately, soon became
One Thousand Laptops Per Warlord.
ARCHER: Man, all those charities
have gotta cost, like -
CECIL: Hey! I should
go help Tiffy.
Since we're flying into the Bermuda Triangle...
where mysteries abound!
ARCHER: What kind of mysteries?
CECIL: I'm kidding!
ARCHER: Well Cheryl,
you come by it honest.
LANA (O.S.): Speaking of...
ARCHER: Aagh! Lana c'mon,
we're about to fly into the
Bermuda Triangle, my nerves
are frayed enough as it is.
LANA: Really.
ARCHER: No, Long Island Iced
Tea number three really took
the edge off. Want one?
LANA: No, I'm not drinking, but-
ARCHER: Oh my God! I totally saw this coming!
LANA: You saw what coming?
ARCHER: Did you not join
the Nation of Islam?
LANA: No, Archer, I -
ARCHER: You know they won't
let you keep dating Cyril,
right? Plus no bacon?
LANA: You done?
ARCHER: Well for now, but after I take a nap-
LANA: You'll wake up just in
time to get shot for treason, because
your mother wants to ransom a hydrogen
bomb back to the United
States government.
ARCHER: It's a reward! And maritime
salvage law is very clear on the subject.
According to Cecil.
LANA: And what's he
getting out of this?
ARCHER: I... guess whatever useless
thing philanthropists normally get from
squandering their
money on the poor.
LANA: So what, he's conducting a huge
naval operation just for a warm fuzzy?
ARCHER: I -- hey, wait a second!
LANA: What?
ARCHER: I think I have
room for a fuzzy navel.
CHERYL/CAROL (O.S.): Wow Tiffy,
who taught you how to fly?
Was it that goose you freed,
ruining last year's Christmas
dinner, or --
TIFFY: Rrrgh, Cecil, I swear to Goddess...?
CECIL: I know, Tiffy, but please, try
to focus on the greater good. In the
words of the immortal Jeremy Bentham-
TIFFY: Good thing I'm
immortal, cause if she says one
more word to me I will slam
this helicopter into
the frickin ocean.
CECIL: Well, you seem busy.
MALORY: So say it's worth two billion,
a fair reward on that would be...
CECIL: um, hello!
MALORY: Oh, Mr. Tunt! Please,
join me, you're just the person
I want to talk to...
CECIL: And I you. About my
sister. I was curious if
you'd noticed anything...
well, curious, about
her behavior.
MALORY: Ha! Ha! Ha!
Oh, you're serious.
CECIL: I'm afraid so, yes.
MALORY: Well how much
time do you have?
CECIL: As much as you need...
CECIL (O.S.): Oh my God, I
don't know what to say... I have
figuratively lost my tongue.
MALORY: With Brent it
was almost literally.
That's why we can't
have scissors.
CECIL: I had no idea her mental state
had declined to such an extent. I mean,
the arson's not surprising...
CHILD CECIL: What have you done?
CHILD CHERYL/CAROL: Ha haha!
Take that, gazebo!
CECIL: But you're
telling me she had...
MALORY: Mm! Choke-sex,
that's her kink!
With a KGB cyborg. After she led him
straight to the ISIS safehouse,
at 921 East
Seventy-Third Street.
CECIL: Oh my -- wait,
is that classified?
MALORY: I won't tell if you won't tell...
CECIL: Mmmkay! Well, I
appreciate your candor in this matter, Ms. Archer-
MALORY: Oh no, it's Ms.
Oh.
CECIL: Ms., yes, thank
you for, um... yes.
ARCHER (O.S.): Come on, you
call this fully stocked?
And no Georgia peaches?
What the--?
ARCHER: What're you doing?
CHERYL/CAROL: I --
what're you doing?!
ARCHER: Hairy navel. Started
as a fuzzy, but I'm calling
this vacation, so... Okay.
Love our little talks!
PAM: Rrowrf. Nom nom nomnomnom.
CECIL: Hi, it's Pam, right?
Enjoying the cruelty-free
vegan seafood buffet?
PAM: Mrmff, it's pretty good, once you
get over how allergic I am to soy.
CECIL: What?! Oh my
God, don't eat that!
PAM: Wh-? Hey! I am
a consenting adult.
Plus I assume you've got an epi-pen
on this big Riptide-lookin' bastard?
CECIL: I -- yes, in the first
aid kit in the cockpit, but -
PAM: Well then shut up.
CECIL: Shutting up, yes. But before I do, could I...
ask you a few questions?
LANA: How is everybody
okay with this?
GILLETTE: How are you not?
CYRIL: Lana, you heard Ms.
Archer, it's either us
or the Russians, and -
LANA: I did not hear that, actually, but-
GILLETTE: But if you found
somebody's wallet, you'd
expect to get a reward, so -
LANA: What if they
won't pay a reward?
Then what, she just
keeps the bomb?
CYRIL: C'mon, it's not
gonna come to that.
GILLETTE: Ooh, but if it does
we could move to Cecil's island
and be a rogue state!
CYRIL: Coool...
LANA: Ugh, forget it.
Oh, and also dummies? We're five
hundred miles from the nearest tree.
CYRIL: Hey thanks, Magellan!
Hey wait, why the heck are you
painting my face like this?!
GILLETTE: Cause you look fierce.
Rrowr.
PAM: Rrowrf.
CECIL: Well thank you, Pam,
I appreciate your candor,
and -- you really, really should
really stop eating those.
PAM: Last one.
Mmrowmf.
LANA: Malory, please, is there any way
I can get you to reconsider this?
MALORY: Well, if you feel that strongly...
LANA: I so do.
MALORY: Cecil says marine salvage goes
for ten to twenty percent of the item's
value, but since all I'm asking is a
measly three percent, if you've got
sixty million dollars
lying around...?
LANA: Bwexqueeze me?!
MALORY: I know, right?
It's a steal at twice the price.
GILLETTE: Yeah and about that, Cyril
figured out how big our bonuses should be.
MALORY: Your what?!
CYRIL: I -- Ray made me!
GILLETTE: Cyril! C'mon
you're fierce, rrowr!
ARCHER (O.S.): Rrraarrgh!
No! Don't!
[grrrrzzz]
CECIL: Uh, could I speak
to you for a moment?
ARCHER: "Wildly liberal use,"
Cecil, those were
your exact words!
CECIL: No, of course, that's totally fine,
but I wanted to talk to you about -
ARCHER: Don't say high-
functioning alcoholism.
CECIL: I wasn't. Going to.
ARCHER: Well then
what's on your mind?
CECIL: Well, it's about my sister...
ARCHER: Hey whoa! I dunno what
she told you but Carol's a consenting adult, so-
CECIL: Well that's actually
kind of my point, I wanted
to ask if you'd ever
seen my sister acting strangely, or-
ARCHER: Ha! Oh, you're serious.
[creepy music]
CHERYL/CAROL: Just ignore
it, it's non-diegetic.
PAM: Last one,
stinky-pinky-swear.
Mrowf.
CHERYL/CAROL (O.S.): Psst! Pam!
PAM: Aw crap, already?
CHERYL/CAROL (O.S.): Pam!
PAM: Look, auditory hallucinations aren't
gonna make you any less delicious.
PAM: Hey! I was talking to that!
CHERYL/CAROL: Shhh! Shut up!
I need your help!
PAM: And that's how you ask?
CHERYL/CAROL: Cecil's like,
interviewing everybody!
PAM: Yeah, he -- is he?
Doing that?
CHERYL/CAROL: Yes! And I
think he's taping it!
Look, there's
cameras everywhere!
PAM: Huh.
CHERYL/CAROL: I think he's
taping them saying I'm crazy
so he can show it to a judge and
get a conservatorship over me!
PAM: Huh.
CHERYL/CAROL: "Huh" what?!
PAM: I mean... ya think that's
the worst idea anybody ever had?
CHERYL/CAROL: Oh. My God.
PAM: I know, it's hard to hear, but-
[thwap]
PAM: Owww!
CHERYL/CAROL: I thought
you were my friend!
PAM: Yeah and for like six months you
also thought you were a werewolf!
Aw crap, I can't feel my face.
PAM: Last one, swear to God.
ARCHER: Swear to God, every full moon
she'd make us lock her in the ISIS vault.
CECIL: Oh my God, how
are you laughing?
That's not funny, it's tragic!
ARCHER: I -- no yeah, but you
know, plus time, it equals -
CECIL: Thank you, I've
heard quite enough.
Now if you'll please excuse me, I-
TIFFY (O.S.): Cecil? My darling whom I love?
TIFFY: And also strangers
whom I don't even like?
Our ETA is fifteen minutes.
And the seas are really choppy, so
we may be in for a rough landing.
CECIL: Thank you love yoooooou.
So you may want to
switch to coffee.
ARCHER: Ha! Ha! Ha! Ahhh.
Oh, you're still serious.
CHERYL/CAROL: Or am I?
I am, actually.
MALORY: Have you people
lost your minds?!
LANA: 'cause apparently it's going around...
MALORY: Because - shut up - if
we recover the bomb, I will decide if
any of you receives a tiny bonus, so -
CYRIL GILLETTE: If?! If?!
ARCHER: Guys, shut up,
I got this, shut up.
What do you mean, if?!
Also, what are we talking about?
MALORY: Nothing. There's nothing to talk
about, because I am -- Jesus Christ!
ARCHER: Okay, it's either
the altitude or a stroke.
Mother, it's Sterling!
Do you smell toast?
MALORY: Pam?!
PAM: Grrrgh, grrrgh!
LANA: What the-
TIFFY: -- hell are you doing?!
The cockpit is off
limits, missy!
CHERYL/CAROL: Oh yeah?!
Well so's my inheritance!
[creepy music]
Goddammit, shut
up John Williams!
TIFFY: Oh my God you
really are crazy!
Would a crazy person do this?!
Ungh!
TIFFY: Yes!
ARCHER: What the
hell's going on?!
CECIL: It's Cheryl!
She's in the cockpit!
I think she's trying
to kill us all!
ARCHER Oh good.
For a second there I
thought I drank too much.
[slurrp]
TIFFY CHERYL/CAROL:
[struggling sounds]
CECIL (O.S.): Cheryl!
Cheryl, open the door!
LANA: Rrrr! Rrrk! Why the
hell's there a lock on it?!
CECIL: Well obviously to
prevent this exact scenario
from ever happening, but-
LANA: Now?! Really?! You think this is a
good time to be facetious?!
CECIL: I'm -- fairly certain you're
not using "facetious" correctlrrmp.
LANA: Cheryl? Can you come out here so
we can talk about this like adults?
Who aren't gonna die
in a helicopter crash?
CHERYL/CAROL: We'll crash with the tapes!
Of all of you stupid
jerks saying I'm crazy!
LANA: The what?
CECIL: [shrug]
CHERYL/CAROL (O.S.): The tapes!
It's part of his sneaky
plan to get a conservatorship over
me so he can steal my inheritance!
ARCHER: That's why she
hijacked his helicopter?
Man, talk about rich
people problems.
PAM (O.S.): Grrrgh...
CYRIL: What're you -- Archer, Pam is dying!
ARCHER: Cyril shut up!
I'm in charge here!
And...okay, here's
what we're doing!
[slurrp]
ARCHER:(burps)
Emergency tracheotomy!
PAM: Grrrk?!
CYRIL: With a crazy straw?!
ARCHER: It's fine, it's pretty
sterile, that Hairy Navel
was mostly Kentucky Moon.
PAM: Grrrgh!
GILLETTE: That's not how
you make a Hairy Navel!
ARCHER: I know, it's a new drink, help
me think of a name, so far all I've
got is Horatio Cornblower.
Which... Okay, Pam!
Here's what's happening!
I'm gonna make a
small incision in
your trachea with this...
PAM: Grrrrk?!
CYRIL: Archer!
ARCHER: Yeah right, that's not sterile...
MALORY: Ugh! And since when do
you carry a switchblade?!
ARCHER: It's a long
story, Mother!
Neat.
Well, not so much long as
just not very interesting.
Okay, Pam, you with me? Then, I'm
gonna stick this in the incision,
and you should be good to go.
Ready?
PAM: Nnghnnnngh!
ARCHER: I -- no, don't--
Pam, stop it!
[krunch]
PAM: Nnghnnnngh!
ARCHER: Okay, sorry in
advance for this... [krunch]
PAM: Ungh!
ARCHER: Unnngh!
PAM: Frstrrrdkerrrrrt!
Erperperrrrrn!
CYRIL: Oh my God, the first aid kit!
I think it might have an epi-pen!
PAM: Rrrrhrrrr!
ARCHER: Ow, jeez, and
hopefully a cold pack...
GILLETTE: Go get the
damn first aid kit!
ARCHER: I am! But not
because you said so!
CYRIL: Just breathe
Pam, it's on the way!
So, you think Cecil's really trying
to steal Cheryl's inheritance?
MALORY: Who cares?!
GILLETTE: Well you should.
MALORY: Because...?
GILLETTE: Because you've been
trying to get your bony manhooks
on her money for years, and
how the hell're you gonna
do that if Cecil gets it?!
MALORY: Tapes! We have to find
and destroy the tapes there
must be some sort of recording
device somewhere and
why are you still
standing there go!
CYRIL: What about Pam?!
MALORY: I'll buy you a new one!
CYRIL: Oww!
PAM: Grrgh, grrgh!
MALORY: Oh, quit milking it.
ARCHER: Hey hey hey,
whoa, Lana stop!
LANA: What?!
ARCHER: If you damage that, it might
not work in the event of an emergency.
LANA: And what would
you call this?!
ARCHER: Oh right.
Speaking of, Pam's dying
of anaphylactic shock.
You got a first aid kit?
CECIL: I -- it's in the cockpit!
LANA: Which is locked,
and -- no nonono!
BLAM
BLAMBLAMBLAMBLAMBLAMBLAMBLAM!
CECIL: Gagh!
LANA: And also
apparently bulletproof.
ARCHER: Well yeah, you'd want
it to be, to prevent-
CECIL: You shot me!
You idiot!
ARCHER: Hey! First of all,
if I shot you you'd know it!
And secondly, now
who's the idiot?
CECIL: Wh-? You! All of you!
You're here because I wanted
you here, so I could -
ARCHER: Help us get the
hydrogen bomb, yeah.
CECIL: Oh my God!
There is no bomb!
LANA: What?!
MALORY: Well, guess I
had that coming...
PAM: Grrgh!
MALORY: Well you don't
have to rub it in!
CECIL: I just wanted to get you people
on tape saying Cheryl was crazy, so I
could get control of her inheritance
to fund my numerous philanthropies!
[shunk]
CHERYL/CAROL: A-ha! Hang on.
Now shut up! And land...
This... shitheap!
Ahem. Now, I believe there was some
mention of anaphylactic shock?
LANA: Thank you!
ARCHER: She's my patient, Lana!
LANA: Wait, so if all you wanted was to
get us on tape saying she's crazy...
CHERYL/CAROL: Which I'm
totally not, by the wrrmp.
LANA: You could've done
that in a lawyer's office.
Why drag us all the way out to the
middle of the frickin ocean?!
CECIL: Well... promise
you won't get mad?
LANA: Uh, no?
PAM (O.S.): You ssshole!
PAM: Stupid! Drunk ass!
Switchblade
tracheotomygivin dicknuts!
ARCHER: Ow!
PAM: Rrrgh!
Sorry, thanks, I
feel a lot better.
ARCHER: Yeah that's why I jammed it
in your neck, I figured if -- oww!
ARCHER: What the
hell was that for?!
PAM: Horatio Cornblower?!
ARCHER: I know, right?
You got anything?
PAM: Dicknuts.
CYRIL: Okay, we got the tapes!
MALORY: Big whoop.
CYRIL: I -- wait, I thought you
wanted -what just happened?
MALORY: It was a hoax!
There is no bomb!
GILLETTE: Boom! Guess
you had that comin'
MALORY: Oh, put another
man's penis in it.
TIFFY (O.S.): Attention unwelcome passengers...
We are now landing, so please
find your seats and
fasten your seat belts.
Or not, because frankly, I could give
a shit if all you people live or die.
LANA: The odds on which I'd put at about...
whatcha think,
Cecil? Fifty-to-one?
MALORY: Lana? What's going on?
ARCHER: Somebody shot him.
MALORY: Will you...?
Lana, what's going on?
LANA: Why don't you ask Cecil?
CECIL: Ow! God, your
hands are like --ow!
Well as you may know, one of my many
philanthropic endeavors is an undersea
research laboratory, which, as
luck would have it, is actually
beneath us right now.
LANA: Cut. To the chase.
CECIL: Ow! Anyhoo, the lead scientist is
threatening -- well, he can tell you.
CECIL: Ahem. Captain Murphy?
[creepy music]
CHERYL/CAROL: Please tell
me you guys heard that.
MURPHY: Ahhhh. Mister Tunt.
CECIL: Don't worry,
he can't see us.
MURPHY: No, but I can hear you...
CECIL: Although he can hear us.
MURPHY: Yes I can, and please hear me.
For years, decades,
I have begged the so-called leaders of
the world to stop poisoning our oceans.
But they have ignored my pleas.
As I will ignore theirs, Mr. Tunt.
Unless my
list of demands is met in the next...
Tsk tsk, twelve hours. At which
point, I will launch our
missiles on Washington,
Miami, and New York.
Hope everybody has a gas mask.
[zzzrpt]
LANA: Why do they
have missiles?!
MALORY: And what did he
mean by "gas mask"?!
CECIL: I, you know, that was,
I think, maybe, probably,
because the missiles are definitely
tipped with VX nerve gas?
EVERYBODY: [gasp]
ARCHER: Oh my God!
LANA: What?
ARCHER: The -- it's-- the -- dammit!
Still can't beat
Horatio Cornblower.
PAM: Dicknuts!
Hrmmmff.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com