(Archer moaning deliriously)
>> LANA: Archer.
>> ARCHER: Lana?
(Lana yelps)
Lana!
>> LANA: Whoa, Jesus Christ!
Chill out, Miggs!
>> ARCHER: I'm sorry, it's just
been so long.
>> LANA: Okay, it's been...
>> ARCHER: Oh, my God.
You're pregnant again?!
>> LANA: What?
>> ARCHER: How long have I been
down here, left to rot in this
godforsaken hole?!
>> LANA: Like... three weeks.
>> ARCHER: Hmm, seems so much
longer than that.
>> LANA: It...
>> ARCHER: So, please tell me
that's an entire canard à la
presse with a file in it.
>> LANA: Half a chicken, no
file, just that weird
quasi-cornbread they have here.
>> ARCHER: Ugh, why do you even
bother?
>> LANA: That's weird, I was
asking myself the same thing on
the way down here.
>> ARCHER: And then brought
crappy food anyway?
>> LANA: And then left?
>> ARCHER: No, no, no, wait,
come on, Lana, I-I'm sorry, but
I-I'm starting to lose it down
here.
You-you got to make him let
me go!
>> LANA: Make him how?
>> ARCHER: Well, I hate to
even ask, but...
>> LANA: Blow him?
>> ARCHER: Your words.
>> LANA: And then what, Archer,
you want me to blow the whole
army?
>> ARCHER: How is there still
an army?
How have the rebels not wiped
them out already?
>> LANA: Because turns out,
he's actually very good at
commanding an army.
>> CYRIL: And as Third and
Fourth Battalion withdraw, here
comes First Armored, and now the
rebels are outflanked.
>> COMANDANTE (laughs): Sir,
it's brilliant!
>> CYRIL: A classic pincher
movement.
Just like Hannibal at the battle
of Cannae.
And also Keith, in my
Warhammer guild.
>> LANA: So, get used to that
weird cornbread, 'cause you
might be down here a...
>> ARCHER: Lana, I need a
woman's touch!
(Lana grunts)
Oh! Ow!
I'm sorry, Lana.
I said a woman, not a
stevedore who lost his hand
in a stevedoring accident
and then got a hand transplant
from an actual bear.
>> LANA: So, did you want to
just do it right through the
bars or...?
>> ARCHER: I mean, we do.
And sometimes they do.
>> CALDÉRON: Hello.
>> LANA: I... wait.
So, in three weeks, you go from
you're gonna execute Archer
to now you guys are, like,
swinger pals?
>> CALDÉRON: Well, I wouldn't
say "pals."
>> ARCHER: Wow, not what you
said yesterday.
>> CALDÉRON: Oh, come on, that
was the pruno talking.
>> LANA: Well, I hate to break
up this delightful ménage, but
Presidente Cyril wants her back
upstairs.
>> ARCHER: Wait, what?
>> CALDÉRON: What?
>> JULIANA: Why.
>> LANA: Guess.
>> JULIANA: Ah.
>> LANA: Mm.
>> CALDÉRON: Ow!
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait!
>> BOTH: What?
>> CALDÉRON: Archer, do you want
me to move over one?
>> ARCHER: Eh.
>> CYRIL: Ah, Madame First Lady.
So good of you to join me.
>> JULIANA: It's not as if I
had a choice.
>> CYRIL: Well...
>> JULIANA: Nor am I still the
the first lady.
>> CYRIL: Well, maybe not
technically, since your husband
divorced you and then was
immediately deposed by me, but
the situation is, as they say,
fluid.
>> LANA: Ugh.
I brought her, can I go now?
>> CYRIL: Yes, for the love of
God, get out.
>> LANA: I meant home.
>> PAM (laughing): What are you,
nuts?
Cap'n Crunch here just
took all the coca fields back
from the rebels.
We're sitting on an endless
supply.
>> LANA: Of what, coca leaf
smoothies?
(rhythmic gulping)
Oh, my God.
That's a coca leaf smoothie.
>> CHERLENE: And they're gross.
It basically tastes like a fart
of itself, but it's better than
the cocaine donuts and whipped
cocaine she was eating.
(Pam burps)
>> PAM: 'Cause that's just empty
calories.
>> LANA: Well, and cocaine.
>> PAM: Which, if I'm being
totally honest, I maybe might
have a problem with.
>> LANA: No.
>> CYRIL: And, Lana, the rebels
still control the airport.
It's their HQ.
So, unless you want to walk, you
can't go home.
>> MALORY: And why on Earth
would you want to?
(Lana sighs)
>> CYRIL: Uh...
>> MALORY: Why bother going
back?
The U.S. government stole your
livelihood, forced you to become
a criminal.
And I hate to say it, but it's
not like you have a man waiting
for you.
>> LANA: I... You know...
>> MALORY: Whereas here we have
everything we need.
It's like San Marcos has been
waiting thousands of years for
us to arrive.
Lana, this could be our...
>> LANA: Don't.
>> MALORY: Zion, yes, there, I
said it.
(Pam burps)
>> PAM: Wait, they got weed
here, too?
>> LANA: That's not what the
song's about!
>> CHERLENE: Told you.
>> LANA: But I just this second
realized why you want to stay
down here.
Cyril's just the Vader to your
Palpatine.
>> MALORY: Is that a reference
I should get, or...?
>> LANA: Seriously?
>> MALORY: Well, I'm sorry,
Lana, I didn't go to rabbinical
school.
>> LANA: It's from... No, you
know what? Never mind.
But, spoiler alert, Vader ends
up killing Palpatine.
>> CYRIL: Hey.
>> CHERLENE: But only for three
days, right?
And then he moves the rock and
comes out of his cave stronger
than ever.
>> PAM: Then he shuts off the
tractor beam, releasing the Jews
from captivity.
>> LANA: What?
>> CYRIL: Hey.
>> MALORY: Wait, yes, now that
sounds familiar.
>> LANA: It cannot possibly.
>> MALORY: Gospel of Luke?
>> CYRIL: Hey.
>> LANA: Oh for... Ray, you used
to be a preacher, you want to
back me up here?
>> RAY: I actually don't know.
My church didn't really do the
New Testament.
>> LANA: The one with Jesus
Christ in it.
>> RAY: I mean, I take your
word for it, but...
>> CYRIL: Hey!
Will you idiots get out?!
I'm trying to talk to the first
lady!
>> CHERLENE: Of what, this
country or country music?
'Cause I'm first lady of both!
CYRIL No, you're not...
>> CHERLENE: Outlaw country!
(jail door bangs shut)
(Cherlene sighs)
>> CALDÉRON: Oh, my God, my
beautiful and also
multi-talented wife!
You are here!
>> CHERLENE: I know, right?
It's like, finally.
>> ARCHER: As in...
this is a good thing?
(plays random notes)
>> CHERLENE: Duh!
I'm finally gonna get the outlaw
country cred I deserve.
>> CALDÉRON: Oh, my God, you've
always deserved it.
>> ARCHER: Wait, how does being
in jail...?
>> CHERLENE: Paging Dr. Black,
Dr. Man In Black!
Johnny Cash was in Folsom Prison
and San Quentin, so...
>> ARCHER: Yeah, to visit.
>> CHERLENE: Hmm?
>> ARCHER: He just played for
the prisoners, dummy.
He wasn't actually in prison.
(plays "womp womp")
But don't worry.
We're gonna get out of here and
go join the rebels.
>> CALDÉRON: Yes, then you and
I, my beautiful wife, will live
a simple life in the hills,
scratching shit food, like yams,
out of the ground with a, uh,
yam-scratcher.
>> CHERLENE: Okay, A-- start
counting backwards from a
million years, and when you get
to zero that still won't
happen.
>> CALDÉRON: Aw.
>> CHERLENE: And B-- how...
how do we get out of here?
>> ARCHER: Well, we're, uh,
still fine-tuning it, but...
>> CALDÉRON: We have no plan,
whatsoever.
>> CHERLENE: Okay, good, because
I didn't want to step on
anybody's toes, but byoink.
>> CALDÉRON: Whaaaaat?
>> ARCHER: Where did you get
that?
>> CHERLENE: Let's just say,
"I honestly don't know."
>> ARCHER: Fair enough.
>> CHERLENE: Cyril says the
rebel headquarters are...
Wait, is it "are" or is it "is"?
>> ARCHER: It's "where," idiot!
>> CHERLENE: The airport!
Jesus!
>> CALDÉRON: And you, sir, will
keep a civil tongue in your head
when you are addressing
the First Lady of the
government-in-exile of La
República de San Marcos!
>> CHERLENE: And also country
music.
>> ARCHER: I facetiously beg
milady's pardon.
>> CHERLENE: Oh, milady
facetiously grants it.
>> ARCHER: Oh, goody.
Now let's steal a car, go join
the rebels, then come back here
and crush Cyril's stupid army.
>> CALDÉRON: You make it sound
so easy.
>> ARCHER (chuckling): Well,
it's Cyril.
I mean, unless he's got a
nuclear warhead in his pants...
>> CHERLENE: Which he totally
does.
>> KRIEGER: Which, guys, can we
talk about this?
>> KRIEGER CLONE 1: The time for
talk is kaput, Klon-Bruder.
Now is the time for action!
>> KRIEGER CLONE 2: Clone bone!
>> CHERLENE: And by that I mean
his... you know...
>> ARCHER: Yeah, we...
>> CHERLENE: Let me finish!
...penis.
No, you ruined it.
And by "it," I meant the moment.
Not his penis.
>> ARCHER: I...
>> CHERLENE: Penis.
>> ARCHER: Will you shut up?!
I know what I'm doing!
>> CALDÉRON: Yes, but don't do
what you are doing!
(Caldéron and Cherlene yelp)
(Archer chuckles)
>> CALDÉRON: Are you crazy?!
This car is worth one quarter of
$1 million!
>> CHERLENE: Well, was.
>> ARCHER: And did you ever
think maybe your fleet of
priceless cars is the reason
you're fighting off a
rebellion?
>> CALDÉRON: I'm fighting the
rebels because that is what we
do!
My father fought the rebels, his
father fought the rebels...
>> CHERLENE: So, like a family
business.
>> ARCHER: That manufactures
oppression.
>> CALDÉRON: Well, and cocaine.
In fact...
>> CHERLENE: Stop!
(Archer and Caldéron scream)
(tires screeching)
>> ARCHER: What?!
>> CHERLENE: That.
(Archer gasps)
I mean, if you think we have
time.
(tiger roars)
>> ARCHER: I... Is there a
tiger?
>> CALDÉRON: Of course there is
a tiger.
Where did you think you are,
Tegucigalpa?
(Archer giggles gleefully)
(tires squealing)
>> CYRIL: And so, by the power
self-vested in me, I now
pronounce us man and wife, and I
may also kiss the bride.
(Cyril kissing, Juliana grunts)
>> PAM: Yay!
>> MALORY: Ugh, second worst
wedding ever.
>> RAY: Yeah, but at least
nobody died.
>> PAM (laughing): Yet!
(clears throat)
Inappropes.
>> MALORY: What is wrong with
you?
>> PAM: I'm trying to make that
a thing people say, like,
"Damn, dawg, that's inappropes!"
Plus, I think I'm addicted to
cocaine.
>> MALORY: Well, but look on the
bright side.
With any luck at all, it will
save me the trouble of killing
you myself.
>> PAM (sniffling): Damn,
dawg...
>> RAY: Inappropes.
>> PAM: Yay!
>> ARCHER (quietly): Yay!
Yay!
(tiger roars)
They should've sent a poet.
Oh, and some meat.
Do we have any meat?
(elephant trumpets)
>> CALDÉRON: Literally tons.
>> ARCHER: No, I didn't mean
another animal.
I meant like a steak, or some...
>> CALDÉRON: Typical American.
You think meat comes from the
supermercado, all wrapped in a
nice plastic wrap.
>> ARCHER: Yeah, you're
describing meat.
>> CALDÉRON: No, no, no.
Meat is blood and bones and
sinew!
>> ARCHER: Well, now you're
describing not-meat.
>> CALDÉRON: Meat is whatever
the tiger says is meat, because
God made him the boss and all
the other animals his food!
(tiger roars)
>> ARCHER: Hang on, buddy.
And thank you, George Bore-well,
for that clunky analogy in
defense of totalitarianism, but
I'm not feeding Shane an
elephant.
>> CHERLENE: Who the hell is...
(gasps)
Oh, my God, he's totally a
Shane.
So let me bounce this off you
guys...
>> KRIEGER: What say we don't
launch this giant nerve gas
missile at, uh...
where did you say you were
launching it?
>> KRIEGER CLONE 1: Wouldn't you
like to know?
(hearty laughter)
>> KRIEGER: I would, actually.
Come on, you guys are acting
a little... insane.
>> KRIEGER CLONE 1: Do you know
what's insane?!
>> KRIEGER: Yeah, this.
All of it, everything.
The rocket, uh... I'm not really
comfortable with the
clone-bone.
>> KRIEGER CLONE 1: You're not
doing it right.
Now move, so I can begin the
launch sequence.
>> KRIEGER: Over my dead...
...body, man that was a jinx,
huh?
(cocks gun)
No, no, no, wait, wait, wait!
>> ARCHER: Hang on!
As amazing as it would be,
we can't take Shane with us.
>> CHERLENE: Yeah, we can,
watch.
>> BOTH: No, no, no, no!
No, don't!
(low rumbling growl)
>> CALDÉRON: Okay, okay, okay,
okay.
>> ARCHER: Carol, listen to me
very closely.
>> CHERLENE: Why, you gonna walk
me through your organic method
of vaginal hygiene?
>> ARCHER: My what?
>> CHERLENE: You're a bigger
pussy than Shane!
Come here, boy! (smacking lips)
(tiger roars, Caldéron screams)
>> ARCHER AND CHERLENE: Shane!
(Caldéron screams)
>> CHERLENE: Do something!
(Caldéron screaming)
>> ARCHER: Like what?
>> KRIEGER CLONE 1: Get him!
(grunting)
>> KRIEGER CLONE 2: We're
coming, brother!
>> KRIEGER CLONE 3: Hiy...!
(gunshot)
(Krieger Clone 3 screams)
>> KRIEGER CLONE 2: No...!
>> KRIEGER CLONE 1: Brother...!
(thuds)
You bastard!
Brother, the launch sequence!
>> KRIEGER: No!
(keyboard clicking)
(strained grunting)
(gunshot)
>> KRIEGER CLONE 1: Don't stop!
(four gunshots)
(grunting)
>> KRIEGER CLONE 2: Almost...
there.
>> KRIEGER: Oh, come on!
>> KRIEGER CLONE 2: Shut... up.
>>> SEXY ROBOT VOICE: Launch
sequence initiated.
>> KRIEGER: No!
>> KRIEGER CLONE 1 (sobs): No!
(thuds)
(strained grunting)
(choking)
>> KRIEGER: Ha-ha!
It doesn't work with a bow...
tiiiiiiiiieeeeee!
(loud thuds)
>> ARCHER: Shane!
Shane...!
>> CHERLENE: Shane...!
(Caldéron screaming)
(tiger roars)
(scream stops abruptly)
>> ARCHER: Shane?
(tiger snuffles)
(low, contented growl)
>> CHERLENE: Well, we should've
guessed that was gonna happen.
(chuckling)
>> ARCHER: W... we should've?
>> CHERLENE: Well, or at least
could've.
I mean...
>> ARCHER: Yeah, I-I-I guess,
uh... I guess a leopard can't
change his spots.
>> CHERLENE: Uh... I don't know
that much about leopards.
>> ARCHER: That was actually
a proverb.
>> CHERLENE: That was actually a
tiger.
>> SEXY ROBOT VOICE: Minutes to
launch: 180.
>> KRIEGER: Huh.
That is a lot longer than I
thought it would be.
>> ARCHER: Okay, when we get to
rebel HQ, they might be
aggressive at first, but...
>> CHERLENE: They wouldn't if we
had a damn tiger.
(Archer sighs)
>> ARCHER: No.
We're-we're not going back.
Unless...
No.
>> CHERLENE: What if...
>> ARCHER: He had his chance!
>> JULIANA: A what?
>> CYRIL: A charivari.
Also called a shivaree?
You know, it's that thing where
everybody bangs pots and pans
outside our room as we...
consummate.
(chuckles)
>> JULIANA: Oh... n-no.
We're not doing that.
>> LANA: Ha-ha!
Ow!
Ray, my feet are already killing
me.
>> RAY: Sorry.
>> MALORY: He's probably not
used to leading.
>> RAY: You know...
>> MALORY: You, on the other
hand... lead away.
>> PAM: Mind if I cut in?
>> COMANDANTE: No.
>> MALORY: Yes!
>> PAM: Screw you guys.
Hey, Krieger!
>> KRIEGER: What the hell is
going on?
>> PAM: Cyril's the new
dictator...
>> CYRIL: President.
>> PAM: Shut up, and he just
married crazy tits, and I need
a dance partner.
So nobody noticed that I've
been missing for three weeks?
>> RAY: Um...
>> MALORY: Well, I certainly
didn't.
>> PAM: We figured the vampires
>> MALORY: The what?
>> LANA: Wait, what?
>> KRIEGER (sighs): They're not
vampires, they're my clones.
Or I'm their clone, or...
>> MALORY: Oh, please, you and
your clone nonsense, it's all
a bunch of...
>> LANA: Holy shit.
>> CYRIL: Why was I not informed
of this, Krieger?
>> PAM: If he even is Krieger!
>> CYRIL: Huh?
>> PAM: The real Krieger could
be down there!
>> KRIEGER: Oh, for... that is
just...
I won't even dignify that with
a response.
Uh, uh... (snapping fingers)
>> LANA: Pam?
>> KRIEGER: Pam!
>> PAM: Uh-huh.
>> KRIEGER: I've got a
concussion.
And this regular tie means
nothing, I don't like bow ties
so I switched.
>> LANA: Well, you certainly
sound concussed.
>> PAM: He sounds like a
vampire!
I say we tie him up and let the
sun sort it out!
>> LANA: You need to hush.
>> SEXY ROBOT VOICE: Minutes to
launch: 150.
>> MALORY: What is that?
>> PAM: What is going on?
>> CYRIL: Tell me that robot's
not talking about launching this
rocket, Krieger.
>> PAM: Or should we say
Count Krieg...
Ow! Ow!
Ow, cut it out! Ow!
Goddamn it! Ow!
>> LANA: Thank you.
>> PAM: Vampire lovers.
>> KRIEGER: Yeah, so, here's
the thing...
>> ARCHER: This is it, rebel
headquarters.
Now, remember, let me do the
talking.
>> CHERLENE: Got it.
>> ARCHER: I'm serious.
>> CHERLENE: I got it.
>> ARCHER: Look at me.
>> CHERLENE: I got it!
Jesus!
>> ARCHER: Okay.
Then here we go.
(rebels shouting in Spanish)
>> REBEL SOLDIER: Pinche cabrón!
>> CHERLENE: Ow!
>> ARCHER: Goddamn it!
You said you'd let me do the...
(grunts)
(Cherlene laughing)
>> REBEL SOLDIER 2: ¡Espere,
espere!
¡Mira, mira!
Es la cantante!
>> CHERLENE: ¶ It's all about me
this time... ¶
Aw...
>> MALORY: So.
You're saying this gigantic
rocket is not only full of
deadly nerve gas, but also aimed
God knows where?
>> KRIEGER: Well, that statement
presupposes the existence of
God, but...
>> MALORY: Krieger, I am about
two seconds away from telling
Pam to get a wooden stake.
>> PAM: Yay!
>> KRIEGER: I'm not a vampire!
>> MALORY: Doesn't matter to
the stake.
>> KRIEGER: Then yes!
It's full of nerve gas, and I
don't know where it's aimed!
>> LANA: What?
What's the range on this thing?
>> KRIEGER: I don't know, 2,000
miles?
(Malory gasps)
>> MALORY: How far away is the
Upper East Side?
>> KRIEGER: I don't know,
1,980-something miles?
(Malory screams)
>> CYRIL: Okay, this is a
presidential order from the
president.
Shut it down!
>> KRIEGER: I can't!
>> PAM: Can't, or won't?
>> KRIEGER: Can't!
>> PAM: Oh.
I didn't hear you.
>> LANA: Ray, can you override
the launch sequence?
>> RAY: Um...
>> SEXY ROBOT VOICE: Launch
sequence accelerated.
>> RAY: No.
(all exclaiming)
>> MALORY: Oh, for God's sake.
>> SEXY ROBOT VOICE: Minutes to
launch: 90.
>> LANA: Cyril...
>> CYRIL: Uh, it's actually
Señor Presidente, but...
>> LANA: Shh, hush.
Now I know you've had a fun time
as dictator, and we all enjoyed
this little break from him,
but Cyril-- and if you tell him
I said this, I'll break your
frickin' arms-- it's... ugh...
Archer time.
>> CYRIL: Wha...?
Oh, all right.
>> LANA: Krieger, I assume the
whatever...
>> PAM: Doppelkriegers.
>> LANA: I assume they had a
lab, so take Ray and see if you
can find some info on how to
shut this damn thing down.
We'll go get Archer.
>> PAM: Ooh, and Cherlene!
>> LANA: Ooh, and no.
Because she isn't here.
>> CYRIL: Oh!
Damn it, Archer!
Damn you!
You can't even let me pretend to
be magnanimous while inwardly
gloating!
>> MALORY: Oh, shut up.
What does the note say?
>> LANA (reading):
So, airport?
>> PAM: But the note says not...
(mumbling)
>> CYRIL: Well, I guess that
settles that!
I mean, it's not like we can
just waltz into enemy territory
and...
Well, I certainly can't.
>> LANA: Can't, or...
>> CYRIL: Both, either, all.
They'd shoot me on sight, Lana.
And if you want Archer so damn
bad, you can go get him your...
(tires squealing)
Huh.
I didn't think she'd actually
do it.
>> MALORY: Then you're an idiot.
>> CYRIL: Oh, I'm the idiot?
>> MALORY: Yes.
(Archer grunts)
>> ARCHER: What the...?
Holly?
>> HOLLY: Archer?
>> SLATER: Rando?
>> ARCHER: Slater?
>> HOLLY: Who the hell is Rando?
>> SLATER: Him!
>> HOLLY: That's Sterling
Archer!
>> CHERLENE (loudly): A-hem!
And I am Cherlene?
The Queen of Outlaw Country?
>> SLATER: What the hell are you
doing here?
>> ARCHER: What the hell are you
>> HOLLY: I could ask you the
same question.
I  amasking you the same
question!
>> ARCHER: We came to join the
rebels.
>> SLATER: What?
>> ARCHER: What's the FBI doing
in San Marcos?
With a cocaine smuggler?
(Holly sighs)
>> HOLLY: I'm not FBI, and he's
not a...
>> SLATER: Well, technically,
I am, but...
>> HOLLY: We're both CIA.
>> ARCHER: What?!
>> CHERLENE (whispering): C...
I... A.
>> SLATER: And we're also
the rebels.
>> HOLLY: And you are in a mundo
of   caca.
>> LANA: Okay!
Listen, stop, listen to me!
>> ARCHER: Lana?!
>> LANA: Holly?
What's the FBI doing...
>> ARCHER: These dickheads
aren't FBI, Lana, they're CIA!
And also the rebels!
Huh.
Thought that would get more of
a reaction.
>> LANA: Yeah, no, that is,
um... news, uh...
but my water just broke, so...
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> MAN: Made... in Georgia.