>> KRIEGER: Okay, specs
are all in the green.
So, let me just reboot the
CPU, and...
Beep boop, you are no longer
a cripple.
>> RAY: One, two, three,
Go Herd.
>> KRIEGER: Well?
>> RAY: Well?
Well, you could've done this
weeks ago!
So it's about goddamn time!
>> KRIEGER: Ooh, hang on a sec?
(Ray yells)
Yeah, touchy thing, bionics.
You were saying?
>> RAY: Thank you.
>> KRIEGER: No, what were you
saying like you meant it?
>> RAY: Thank you, Krieger,
for once again giving me the
precious gift of legs.
>> KRIEGER: You're welcome.
>> RAY: Now, if you will excuse
me, I need to remove my
underwear with a blowtorch.
>> MALORY: Ha!
Perfect, this is absolutely
perfect.
Cherlene!
>> CYRIL: Ow! God!
Come on!
>> LANA: Seriously, thanks for
the deaf baby.
>> MALORY: Oh, shut up. Cher...
>> CHERLENE: What?!
Goddamn, woman, inside voice!
>> MALORY: How...
would you, my little country
songbird, like to be on
Travis County Limits?
>> CYRIL: Ooh, is that like
Austin City Limits?
>> MALORY: It's comparable,
hush. Cherlene?
>> CHERLENE: I don't know.
I guess.
>> MALORY: You...
would be wonderful, and it would
be wonderful publicity, and...
wonderful.
(groans)
>> CHERLENE: All right.
When is it?
>> MALORY: Tapes tomorrow night,
but we should leave today.
I don't want you flying the same
day you're performing.
>> CHERLENE: Oh, don't worry
about that.
>> MALORY: Well, but...
>> CHERLENE: Because Cherlene
don't fly.
>> MALORY: Airplane air is so
dry, plus you're breathing in
God knows what those
tuberculars in coach are...
Excuse me?!
>> CHERLENE: I don't fly.
>> MALORY: I... but-but I've
seen you fly.
>> CHERLENE: Well, maybe you saw
Cheryl fly.
>> LANA: In a helicopter, the
space shuttle...
>> PAM: Cyril choke-banged you
on a blimp?
Oh, come on, we were all
thinking it.
>> ARCHER: What, how are you all
so goddamn loud?
>> LANA: Could you not find
a punch bowl?
>> ARCHER: It was too heavy.
(loud crashing nearby)
(Woodhouse grunting)
(grunting and crashing
continues)
(groans)
>> ARCHER: And also too spilly.
Now, what's with all
the yelling?
>> MALORY: I booked Cherlene on
Travis County Limits, and...
>> ARCHER: Is that like...?
>> MALORY: It's comparable!
But it's tomorrow night and she
refuses to fly.
>> ARCHER: Wait, really?
So you've only got 24 hours
to drive to Texas?
>> MALORY: Well, 36 but...
>> ARCHER: But after we get a
bus and a blocker car it'll be
24, right?
>> MALORY: What?
>> LANA: Oh. Oh, God, no.
>> ARCHER: Yes!
>> LANA: Archer?
>> ARCHER: Lana!
>> MALORY: Sterling!
What are you talking about?
>> LANA: Smokey and the goddamn
Bandit.
>> MALORY: What?
>> ARCHER: We're going
¶ Eastbound and down!
>> MALORY: I will never
understand his idiotic
fascination with all this Burt
Reynolds Smokey trucker
nonsense.
>> LANA: I think part of it is
because you didn't get him
that CB McHaul toy truck he
wanted for his birthday.
>> MALORY: Wha...?
He was 30!
>> LANA: And words fail me.
I have no words.
>> ARCHER: How about
ten-goddamn-four?!
>> MALORY: How about how much
did this cost?
>> CHERLENE: How about a
Jacuzzi, bitches? Woooooo!
>> ARCHER: You know what they
say-- can't put a price on
free advertising.
>> MALORY: No, they don't, and
free this isn't.
>> ARCHER: Exactly.
How much are they
paying Cherlene?
>> MALORY: It's public
television, they don't pay
anything.
All they do is suck money in.
They take our taxes...
>> LANA: Or donations, whatever.
>> MALORY: Of pre-tax dollars
from pot-taking Bolshevik
lesbian couples!
Then PBS mixes it all in with
their huge N.E.A. grants,
launders it in inner-city
methadone clinics, and pumps it
right back out to pro-abortion,
super-PACs!
>> LANA: Still no words.
(Pam grunting)
And, wow, maybe I
have aphasia.
>> MALORY: Where do you think
you're going?
>> ARCHER: She's driving the
bus.
Mother, get on the bus.
Lana, you're riding with me.
>> LANA: In what?
(tires screeching)
>> ARCHER: In the blocker car,
duh, if Cyril didn't just break
the stupid axle.
>> MALORY: The what?
>> LANA: Okay, first of all...
>> MALORY: How much did that
cost?
>> ARCHER: Well, again, it's
advertising, so...
>> MALORY: For what?
>> ARCHER: Hmm, I guess Pontiac?
>> MALORY: God.
>> ARCHER: And where are you
going?
>> LANA: Well, speaking
for the tiny, delicate life
blossoming inside me, nowhere in
a car with T-tops and a
four-barrel.
>> ARCHER: Wha... Who's gonna do
snappy dialogue with me,
underscored by sexual
attraction?
I'm so angry right now I can't
even...
(sniffs)
Oh, goddamn it!
Did you fart in that?
(Pam laughing)
>> LANA: Damn it, Cyril,
slow down!
>> MALORY: Cyril, do nothing
of the sort!
Because if we miss that taping,
I won't be responsible
for my actions.
>> LANA: Are you ever?
>> MALORY: She said, single and
pregnant.
Oh, wait.
>> CYRIL: Can you two please
go... anywhere else?
It's bad enough I have to drive
24 hours straight.
>> LANA: Well, Krieger said he
needed Ray's help on some sort
of project.
>> RAY: This quit being funny
two hours ago!
>> KRIEGER: It's not supposed to
be funny.
>> MALORY: So shut up and drive
the damn bus!
Sorry, I'm a bit stressed out
about Cherlene getting
a record deal.
>> LANA: Right, and your ten
percent of it.
>> MALORY: Or 50 or whatever.
>> LANA: What?
>> CYRIL: 50, really?
>> LANA: Who are you, Colonel
Mom Parker?
Nothing?
>> CYRIL: Meh.
>> MALORY: And not that I care
what any of you think, about
anything, but I lost everything
when the Feds took ISIS, and Ron
took what little I had left, so
now I need to make it back
somehow.
And I'm not doing that selling
cocaine, thanks to Sterling,
who, unbelievably, is even
worse at this than at spying.
>> ARCHER: Hey, so...
Yeah, hi, uh, I think maybe
somebody's holding down
the talk-button thingy?
>> CYRIL: Uh... oh!
Uh, sorry, Archer.
>> LANA: Exactly the opposite of
how it works.
>> CYRIL: What?
Oh.
Uh, sorry, Archer.
(Archer sighs)
>> ARCHER: Ten-ten-four, good
buddy.
>> MALORY: Sterling?
>> CYRIL: Well, he can't hear
you now, I... ow!
Ow!
Whose ring is that, the pope's?!
>> PAM (laughing): Ouch!
>> ARCHER: Shut up.
>> PAM: Seriously though, I'm
sorry you heard her say that.
That's got to be a real knee to
the old emotional nut sack.
>> ARCHER: Well, I guess it
would be, if A-- I weren't the
world's greatest spy.
>> PAM: Eh.
>> ARCHER: Shut up, and B-- if
they weren't sitting on a
hundred pounds of coke.
>> PAM: What?!
>> ARCHER: Affirmatory,
good buddy!
>> PAM: Holy dickburn!
So you got a buyer lined up
in Texas and everything?!
>> ARCHER: Well, not exactly,
or at all, but, Pam, come on.
We're talking about Texas.
Somebody, somewhere, wants
enough cocaine to forget they
live there.
>> PAM: Yeah, but not
>> ARCHER: Maybe we'll get
lucky, find an entire town
that wants to commit suicide.
>> PAM: Wonder if there's a
statewide database of towns
with sucky high school
football teams cross-indexed
with towns a black person just
moved to.
>> ARCHER: Jesus, Pam,
I was kidding.
>> PAM: (laughs) Duh, me too,
lickbag.
>> ARCHER: Well, but see if
there is one, just
for shits and giggles.
>> PAM: Um, so, hey,
speaking of...
>> ARCHER: The hat fart was
technically a shart?
(laughs)
How are you still single?
>> PAM: Right?
(chomps)
(belches)
>> LANA: Cyril!
(Cyril screams)
>> LANA: Goddamn it!
>> CYRIL: I'm-I'm sorry!
>> MALORY: What the hell is
going on up here?!
>> CYRIL: I must've dozed off!
>> LANA: Really?
You don't just hate signs?
>> CYRIL: No, Lana, I don't
ha... Ow!
>> LANA: In addition to sushi,
booze, and soft cheeses,
I'm also supposed to abstain
from bus crashes!
So stay awake!
>> CYRIL: I'm trying,
but 18 hours?
I don't know how Pam's doing it.
>> LANA: Seriously?
>> PAM: Woooooo!!
(laughs)
(Archer yells)
>> ARCHER: What the...?!
>> PAM: Hey, sleepyhead!
Welcome to Texas!
>> ARCHER: Already?
What the shit, Pam?!
>> PAM: That's how we do
backseat drivers.
>> ARCHER: I was driving!
>> PAM: Yeah, and sucking at it.
>> ARCHER: Goddamn it!
How long was I out?
>> PAM: Like, 12 hours?
Five states, dozen cupcakes,
a bunch of truck stops.
>> TRUCKER (over CB): Uh,
breaker breaker, you got your
ears on, Snowball? Come back.
>> PAM: Hang on.
>> ARCHER: Your handle is
Like Jerry Reed's character
in the Smokey-verse?!
>> PAM: Who?
>> ARCHER: Oh. Is it from
from the cupcake?
>> PAM: Cupcakes? Oh! (laughs)
Oh, no.
>> ARCHER: Then what's it...?
>> PAM: Truck stops...
are crazy awesome!
This is Snowball, good buddy.
>> TRUCKER: You might wanna
check your six, Snowball.
>> ARCHER: Ew, is that about
the shart?!
>> PAM: Wha...? No, lickbag!
>> ARCHER: It was a reasonable
assumption.
>> PAM: What the...?
>> TRUCKER: Looks like you got
a chain gang knocking
on your back door.
>> ARCHER: Bikers?
What the hell do they want?
>> CYRIL: I think they want us
to pull over.
>> MALORY: Obviously, you idiot!
Why?!
>> CHERLENE: Kidnapping!
It's a kidnapping, it's
a kidnapping to kidnap me,
Cherlene!
>> LANA: Why would bikers want
to kidnap you?
>> MALORY: Why would anyone?
>> CYRIL: Yeah, you're not
>> CHERLENE: Yet! Duh!
Neither was Frank Sinatra Jr.
Now pull over!
>> LANA: We are not...
>> CHERLENE: Hey, treebeard!
Take me with you!
You can do unspeakable things
to and/or on me!
I... (shrieks)
>> LANA: You are not getting
kidnapped just to boost
your singing career!
>> MALORY: Well, now wait a
a minute.
>> ARCHER: Wait a minute!
Did you tell anybody
we were hauling a shitload
of coke?!
>> PAM: Uh...
(phone rings)
mm... maybe.
>> ARCHER: Maybe?!
>> PAM: Or definitely.
>> ARCHER: Goddamn it, Pam!
>> PAM: I wanted people
to like me.
>> ARCHER: People who like you
because you have cocaine aren't
people you want as friends, Pam.
And not to sound elitist,
but neither are people who need
a roll of quarters
to take a shower!
>> PAM: It's not just a shower,
it's more communal, like
a Japanese onsen, or...
>> ARCHER: Wow! I didn't think
it was possible, but I somehow
just got even angrier!
>> PAM: What the heck are you
looking for?
Gun-gun-gun-gun! Cyril look out!
>> CYRIL: No!
(all yelling)
>> CYRIL: Oh, God!
(bikers scream)
>> PAM: They're shooting at
them!
>> ARCHER: And I'd love nothing
more than to shoot back, Pam,
but somehow, I can't find
my gun!
>> MALORY: For the love of God,
just pull over!
>> LANA: Cyril, do not stop
this bus!
>> MALORY: Let's just give them
Cherlene.
That is the very definition
of a win-win!
>> CHERLENE: Yes!
>> LANA: No!
>> CHERLENE: Why do you always
ruin everything for me?!
>> LANA: Why do you always never
shut up?!
>> ARCHER: Because where the
hell is my gun?!
>> PAM: Are you, like, sure you
brought it?
(gunfire, both scream)
>> LANA: Ugh! Move!
(Cyril gasps)
>> MALORY: Oh, shut up.
>> LANA: Seriously.
(tires squeal, horns blare)
(bikers scream)
>> ARCHER: Where's my gun, Pam?!
What, did you spit it in some
trucker's mouth, too?!
>> PAM: Okay, so, apparently a
big thing at truck stops is a
game called craps.
And apparently I'm not good
at it.
(Pam screams)
>> CYRIL: Lana, Lana, Lana!
>> LANA: Thank you, Cyril,
I have eyeballs!
(biker screams)
(Lana chuckles)
>> LANA: Yeah, bitch, that's how
I roll! Shit!
(all scream, tires screech)
>> ARCHER: Because even a
goddamn baby knows, in craps,
you never bet on the hard ways!
Ow!
Oh shi...
>> ALL: ...it!
(both screaming)
>> PAM: You mad?
>> ARCHER: Give ya three
guesses, Pam.
>> PAM: No?
No?
>> ARCHER: Wrong, Pam.
Although I bet I'm not
as mad as Mother's gonna be
when I tell her this was all
your fault!
>> PAM: Aw, come on, Archer,
don't do that!
That's not what good buddies do!
>> ARCHER: Okay, first of all,
you have wildly misjudged
our relationship!
>> LANA: Archer!
>> ARCHER: Lana!
>> PAM: Yeah, you're one
to talk.
>> ARCHER: And you're lucky
I don't have my gun!
>> MALORY: And just why the hell
don't you?!
>> ARCHER: Yeah, tell them why
that is, Pam!
>> PAM: Oh, come on, please?
>> ARCHER: I...! (groans)
I-I didn't think I would
need it.
(Cherlene gasps)
>> CHERLENE: You didn't think?!
Well, it's a good damn thing
I ain't paying you to think!
>> ARCHER: Yeah, you're not
actually pay... Ow!
>> CHERLENE: The quite-soon-
-to-be-number-one country
singer in America?!
And you don't think I'm
a kidnapping risk?!
>> ARCHER: Wait-- you do?
Ow!
>> LANA: Yeah, you know, I'm
with Archer.
I think those bikers just
wanted to rob us, or...
>> PAM: What?! I mean, that's
just absolutely crazy.
We have nothing.
>> MALORY: Well, I would like to
revisit this whole kidnapping
idea when we have more time,
but she still has a show in two
hours and we've still got...
>> CYRIL: I think about a
>> LANA: And one extremely flat
tire, so...
(screams)
>> CHERLENE: Fix it!
I will be on my tour bus
putting whiskey and glue
>> MALORY: You heard her.
>> PAM: Yeah, you guys chill on
the bus.
I'll help lickbag here change
the tire.
>> MALORY: Oh, my God.
>> PAM: Sorry, I had to sell it.
Chop-chop! Get the lead out,
lickbag!
>> ARCHER: (sighs) And what's
with the "lickbag" stuff?
>> PAM (laughing):
It's your CB handle!
I told it to everybody
from here to Kentucky!
(clicks tongue)
Good buddy.
(chomps)
>> ARCHER: (grunting)
Whew!
Okay, that's got it.
>> MALORY: Well, it took you
long enough.
>> ARCHER: Yeah, Mother, nine
whole minutes start to finish,
what an incompetent boob.
>> MALORY: Your words.
>> ARCHER: You know...
>> CHERLENE: Rrrgh!
Can we freaking go already?!
>> PAM: Yeah, whatcha waiting
for, lickbag?
(belches)
(engine accelerating, tires
squealing)
(freestyle scatting)
(clears throat)
>> PAM: Ten-four.
>> LANA: So, I think we may have
a problem.
>> ARCHER: Yeah, no shit.
I keep waiting for her to
have a heart attack, but...
>> LANA: Not Pam.
>> PAM: Yay!
>> LANA: The cops.
>> PAM: Boo.
>> ARCHER: Oh, shit!
>> LANA: Yeah, I'm gonna pull
over.
>> MALORY: No! No!
Curtain is in ten minutes!
>> LANA: What do you want me to
do, run from the cops?
>> MALORY: I want you to take
that exit for the venue.
Let Sterling deal with this in
that ridiculous blocker car.
>> ARCHER: Yeah, good, you guys
get out of here; we'll lure
them away and outrun them.
>> PAM: In this shit-heap?
Are you nuts?!
>> ARCHER: Are you?
You want them to get pulled over
with 50 pounds of cocaine?
>> ALL: What?!
>> ARCHER: Or kilos, or
whatever.
>> MALORY: You put 50 kilos of
cocaine on this bus
without my permission?!
Sterling?!
>> LANA: You have to press
the button.
>> MALORY: The what?
>> LANA: Oh, for... You dated
Burt Reynolds!
>> PAM: They don't have the
coke, lickbag!
We do!
Right here in the Trans Am!
>> MALORY: Oh.
Well, then problem solved.
(sirens wailing)
>> ARCHER: So, I have a
question.
>> PAM: I switched the coke in
Little Rock, 'cause
I was worried that...
>> ARCHER: That because of your
fat, blabbering mouth Lana would
get caught with it and have
to have her baby in prison?
Or because you were low on
cupcakes?!
(tires squealing)
>> PAM: Does the why really
matter?
>> CHERLENE: ¶ Eastbound and
down
Loaded up and truckin'
¶ We gonna do what they
say can't be done
We got a long way to go
¶ And a short time to get...
>> PAM: Yeah!
Check it out, lickbag!
Cherlene wrote a song about us.
>> ARCHER: What? She didn't
write a...
That's from Smokey and the...
Goddamn it!
>> PAM: Oww!
What the shit, Snidely
Whiplash?!
>> ARCHER: Now both of our cars
are messed up!
I just leveled the playing
field!
>> PAM: Oh, my God, I can't feel
my face!
>> ARCHER: Gee, Pam, I wonder if
that's got anything to do with
your cocaine-only diet!
>> PAM: Well, it's a small
price to pay for beauty!
(gun clicking)
(gunshot)
>> ARCHER: Damn it!
>> PAM: Man, and here you are
without your gun.
That's pretty ironic, huh?
>> ARCHER: No, Pam, once again
you're confusing the word ironic
with "you are an idiot".
What's ironic is that every
other store we drive by
is a gun shop!
>> PAM: Oh.
Okay, so then what's satire?
>> ARCHER: Nobody really knows!
Hang on!
(tires squealing)
And then back up a sec.
You're endangering your
life for beauty?
>> PAM: Yes, duh.
Look, how hot am I now?
Let me answer that for you.
As balls.
That's why everybody likes
me now.
>> ARCHER: Who, your trucker
buddies?!
They only like you because
you have coke, Pam.
>> PAM:, Well, and the
snowballs, but...
>> ARCHER: And for what it's
worth, we all kind of liked
you the way you were.
(gunshot)
>> PAM: Really?
>> ARCHER: Well, we hated you
less. You kind of turned
into a ginormous asshole.
>> PAM: Yeah, with ginormous big
tittays.
>> ARCHER: Oh, for...
Pam, who cares?
That's just subcutaneous
adipose tissue.
Albeit a shitload of it.
But I can't bang you if you
die from an overdose.
>> PAM: Aw, you want to bang me?
(gunshot)
>> ARCHER: Obviously!
I mean look at those big
bastards!
Sucks we're gonna go to prison,
though.
>> PAM: Prison?
But it's my first offense.
>> ARCHER: Well, except for
treason, but explain all that
to the Brazos County judge,
and maybe he'll...
>> PAM: Wait a minute, we're in
Travis county.
Why does their car
say Brazos county?
>> ARCHER: Give you
three guesses!
>> PAM: Crooked cops?
>> ARCHER: Yes!
>> PAM: Hang on,
I still got two...
>> ARCHER: Pam, get the coke!
>> PAM: Yeah!
Holy coke snacks.
Enable the shit out of me!
>> ARCHER: What?
Not to snort, you idiot!
>> PAM: Well, I don't want to
shoot it.
That seems like a
pretty slippery slope!
>> ARCHER: Pam, any cocaine is a
slippery slope!
It's the world's most addictive
drug.
>> PAM: Hang on, I heard it was
nicotine.
>> ARCHER: It may very well be,
Pam, but in our current
situation I would argue that
cocaine is more dangerous,
because we're about to get
murdered for it!
(gunshots)
(tires squealing)
>> PAM: Yeah, but not overall,
is what I'm...
>> ARCHER: Pam, they don't want
us, they just want the coke,
so throw it out!
>> PAM: Of the car?
>> ARCHER: Pam!
>> PAM: Jeez, okay!
But you're gonna owe me!
>> ARCHER: What could I
possibly owe you?!
>> PAM: I believe there was some
mention of bone-throwing?
>> ARCHER: Okay, yeah, that
seems like a win-win.
>> CHARLENE: ¶ I'm eastbound
Just watch ol' Bandit run! ¶
(screaming)
(sirens stop)
>> CHERLENE: Woo-hooo!
Thank you!
Good night, Travis County!
There will be no encore!
Woooooo!
(crowd booing)
>> MALORY: Wait, what?
>> CHERLENE: Outlaw country!
>> MALORY: No, no, no, you don't
walk off after one song; you get
back out there this instant.
What are you doing?
>> CHERLENE: Uh, it's called
cultivating mystique?
>> MALORY: But...
>> CHERLENE: It's also called
sniffing a shit-ton of glue in
my tour bus hot tub because I
personify outlaw country?
>> MALORY: The...
>> CHERLENE: Outlaw country!
Woooooo!
>> TONY: Howdy, Tony Foti,
Stringer Records, and I want to
make that little gal famous.
Are you her manager, Mrs...?
>> MALORY: Oh, no, it's actually
Ms....
>> LANA: It's actually Mrs.
>> MALORY: Will you put...
>> TONY: It genuinely does not
matter.
Give me a call when y'all are
ready to make some gold records.
Yee-haw! (slaps)
>> MALORY: Ooh!
Well, that went better than
expected.
>> LANA: Yeah, maybe you can use
the gold records to pay Archer
and Pam's bail.
>> CYRIL: I actually don't think
you can.
>> ARCHER: Plus there's no
need.
>> LANA: Wait, what?
>> MALORY: Sterling!
>> ARCHER: Yeah, no, everything
is, uh, totally fine now, and we
totally got away.
So, all set.
>> MALORY: Yes, but how?
The police were right
>> ARCHER: Which is right where
I wanted them, so I could go
old school Bandit.
With an inverted
triple Needham.
>> MALORY: Well, it was your own
fault for bringing cocaine
without asking, but I suppose
all's well that ends well.
>> PAM: Well, except for...
>> ARCHER: Pam?
All's well that ends well?
>> PAM: Oh, right.
But what about the hundred
pounds of coke you dumped
on the highway?
>> MALORY: What?
>> ARCHER: Pam!
>> BALLADEER: Looks like old
Snowball done it again!
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> MAN: Made... in Georgia.