>> COIN COLLECTING IS CONSIDED
THE PERFECT HOBBY.
>>... BEAUTIFUL PUTT RIGHT
THERE GOOD BIRDIE.
THAT'S ONLY THE... EIGHTH
BIRDIE OF THE DAY.
>> Jerry: WHAT?
WHY ARE YOU LOOKING AT ME?
YOU WANT TO GO OUTSIDE?
OUTSIDE?
[ TV SHUTS OFF ]
[ SIGHS ]
OUTSIDE?
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?! COME ON!
>> Summer: OH, MY GOD.
>> Morty: W-WHAT'S WRONG?
>> Jerry: YOUR IDIOT DOG!
>> Morty: OH, HE HE DIDN'T
MEAN IT, DAD.
D-DID YOU, SNUFFLES?
YOU'RE A GOOD BOY.
>> Jerry: DON'T PRAISE HIM NOW,
MORTY!
HE JUST PEED ON THE CARPET!
BAD DOG! BAD!
>> Rick: MORTY, COME ON.
I NEED YOUR HELP TONIGHT.
>> Jerry: HEY, WAIT, HOLD ON A
SECOND, RICK.
YOU WOULDN'T BY ANY CHANCE HAVE
SOME SORT OF CRAZY SCIENCE THING
YOU COULD WHIP UP THAT MIGHT
HELP MAKE THIS DOG A LITTLE
SMARTER, WOULD YOU?
>> Rick: I THOUGHT THE WHOLE
POINT OF HAVING A DOG WAS TO
FEEL SUPERIOR, JERRY.
IF I WERE YOU, I WOULDN'T PULL
THAT THREAD.
COME ON, MORTY.
>> Jerry: LISTEN, RICK, IF
YOU'RE GONNA STAY HERE RENT-FREE
AND USE MY SON FOR YOUR STUPID
SCIENCE, THE LEAST YOU COULD DO
IS PUT A LITTLE BIT OF IT TO USE
FOR THE FAMILY.
YOU MAKE THAT DOG SMART OR...
MORTY'S GROUNDED!
>> Summer: HA-HA!
>> Morty: AW, MAN!
>> Rick: BOY, YOU REALLY GOT ME
UP AGAINST A WALL THIS TIME,
JERRY.
[ DOOR OPENS, BELLS JINGLE ]
[ MACHINE WHIRS ]
ALL RIGHT, RUFFLES
WHAT'S HIS NAME?
>> Morty: SNUFFLES.
>> Rick: SNUFFLES, SHAKE.
ROLL OVER.
GO TO THE BATHROOM.
[ TOILET FLUSHES ]
>> Jerry: HOLY CRAP!
>> Summer: NO WAY.
>> Rick: YEAH, YOU'RE AT THE TOP
OF YOUR GAME NOW, JERRY.
HAVE FUN.
COME ON, MORTY.
>> Morty: THAT WAS FANTASTIC,
RICK!
>> Rick: YEAH, MORTY, IF YOU
LIKE THAT, BOY, YOU'RE YOU'RE
REALLY GOING TO FLIP YOUR LID
OVER THIS ONE.
>> Morty: W-W-W-WHAT IS IT?
>> Rick: IT'S A DEVICE, MORTY,
THAT WHEN YOU PUT IT IN YOUR
EAR, YOU CAN ENTER PEOPLE'S
DREAMS, MORTY.
IT'S JUST LIKE THAT MOVIE THAT
YOU KEEP CROWING ABOUT.
>> Morty: YOU TALKING ABOUT
"INCEPTION"?
>> Rick: THAT'S RIGHT, MORTY.
THIS IS GONNA BE A LOT LIKE
THAT, EXCEPT, YOU KNOW, IT'S
GONNA [BURPS] MAYBE MAKE SENSE.
>> Morty: "INCEPTION" MADE
SENSE.
>> Rick: YOU DON'T HAVE TO TRY
TO IMPRESS ME, MORTY.
LISTEN, TONIGHT WE'RE GONNA GO
INTO THE HOME OF YOUR MATH
TEACHER, MR. GOLDENFOLD, AND
WE'RE G WE'RE GONNA INCEPT THE
IDEA IN HIS BRAIN TO GIVE YOU
A's IN MATH, MORTY.
THAT WAY YOU CAN, YOU KNOW
Y-YOU'RE GONNA HELP ME WITH MY
SCIENCE, MORTY, ALL THE TIME.
>> Morty: GEEZ, RICK, IN THE
TIME IT TOOK YOU TO MAKE THIS
THING, COULDN'T YOU HAVE JUST,
YOU KNOW, HELPED ME WITH MY
HOMEWORK?
>> Rick: ARE YOU LISTENING TO
ME, MORTY?
HOMEWORK IS STUPID.
THE WHOLE POINT IS TO GET LESS
OF IT.
J-J COME ON, LET J LET'S
JUST GET OVER THERE AND DEAL
WITH THIS THING.
W-WE'RE GONNA INCEPT YOUR
TEACHER.
Y-Y-Y-Y-Y-YOU'RE FRUSTRATING ME.
[ ENGINE TURNS OVER ]
>> YOU DON'T KNOW ME!
>> NICE, MRS. PANCAKES REAL
NICE.
>> NEXT WEEK ON "THE DAYS AND
NIGHTS OF MRS. PANCAKES"...
>> [ SNORING ]
>> YOU DON'T KNOW ME!
>> THEN LET ME GET TO KNOW YO,
DAMN IT!
>> Rick: UH-OH! SPOILERS!
I'M A FULL SEASON BEHIND.
>> Morty: WOW, RICK, I CAN'T
BELIEVE WE'RE SITTING AROUND,
STANDING AROUND IN
MR. GOLDENFOLD'S HOUSE.
IT'S REALLY WEIRD.
[ DEVICE WHIRS ]
>> Rick: IT'S ABOUT TO GET A
WHOLE LOT WEIRDER, MORTY.
[ DEVICE WHIRS ]
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
>> WHEAT THINS. WHEAT THINS.
>> I'LL TAKE TWO.
>> OH, I THINK YOU'VE HAD
ENOUGH, SIR.
>> YOU DON'T KNOW ME.
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
>> Rick: ALL RIGHT, MORTY,
TIME TO MAKE OUR MOVE.
>> MAKE IT BOUNCE.
>> NO, YOU DIDN'T.
>> OH, JIGGLE IT NOW.
>> YOU BETTER STOP WITH THAT.
>> Rick: ALLAHU [BURPS] AKBAR!
WE'RE GONNA TAKE CONTROL OF THIS
PLANE!
WE'RE GONNA 9/11 IT UNLESS
MORTY SMITH GETS BETTER GRADES
IN MATH!
HEY! I SAID NOBODY MOVE, BUDDY!
>> THE NAME'S NOT BUDDY.
IT'S GOLDENFOLD.
NICE TO WHEAT YOU!
[ GRUNTS ]
>> Rick: TAKE COVER, MORTY!
[ PASSENGERS SCREAMING ]
>> [ SCREAMS ]
>> Morty: OOH!
>> Rick: GOLDENFOLD'S GOT MORE
CONTROL HERE THAN I ANTICIPATED.
I MEAN, THE GUY TEACHES
HIGH-SCHOOL MATH.
[ BURPS ]
I-I-I-I DIDN'T TAKE HIM FOR AN
ACTIVE DREAMER.
WE GOT TO TAKE HIM OUT SO HE
WAKES UP, MORTY.
BUT WE CAN'T GET KILLED.
IF YOU GET KILLED IN SOMEONE
ELSE'S DREAM, YOU DIE FOR REAL,
MORTY.
>> Morty: WHAT?!
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?!
OHHHHHH!
>> Rick: DON'T BE A BABY!
YOU AVOID GETTING SHOT IN REAL
LIFE ALL THE TIME, MORTY.
JUST DO THE SAME THING HERE, AND
WE'LL BE FINE!
>> Jerry: NOW BRING ME MY
SLIPPERS.
>> Summer: NOW, BE MY FOOTSTOOL,
SNUFFLES.
>> Jerry: THIS IS WHAT I'M
TALKING ABOUT.
THISIS A DOG.
>> Beth: [ Sarcastically ] OH,
YEAH.
THIS SHOULD PLAY OUT JUST FINE.
>> Jerry: YOU SAID THE SAME
THING, EQUALLY SARCASTICALLY, AT
OUR WEDDING AND GUESS WHAT.
>> [ HOWLING ]
>> Summer: OH, MY GOD.
HE'S TRYING TO TELL US
SOMETHING.
THAT IS SO AWESOME.
>> [ HOWLING ]
>> Jerry: AW, HE'S SAYING "I
LOVE LASAGNA."
>> [ GROANS ]
[ HOWLING ]
>> Summer: HE'S SAYING "I LOVE
OBAMA."
[ CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS ]
SO CUTE!
I'M POSTING THIS ONLINE, LIKE,
RIGHT NOW.
>> Jerry: I SHOULD CALL
BOB SAGET.
IS THAT STILL A THING?
>> [ SIGHS ]
HMM?
[ PASSENGERS SCREAMING ]
>> Rick: GOLDENFOLD, WE'RE
COMING OUT!
WE JUST WANT TO TALK!
>> WHY WOULD I NEGOTIATE WITH
YOU?
>> Rick: BECAUSE WE'RE BOTH
RATIONAL ADULTS THAT DON'T WANT
ANYTHING BAD TO HAPPEN.
AND BECAUSE I HAVE A HUMAN
SHLD.
>> MRS. PANCAKES!
[ SCREAMS ]
[ PASSENGERS SCREAMING ]
>> Rick: OH, NO, MORTY.
HIS SUBCONSCIOUS IS PANICKING.
>> RUN!
[ ALL SCREAMING ]
[ SLAP! ]
>> Rick: RELAX, MORTY.
LOOK!
MRS. PANCAKES HAS A PARACHUTE.
COME ON!
>> HEY, YOU DON'T KNOW ME!
>> Morty: OH, NO, RICK, LOOK!
GOLDENFOLD LANDED THE PLANE,
AND HE'S CREATED A MECHANICAL
ARM TO PLUCK MRS. PANCAKES OUT
OF THE AIR WHILE HE LETS US FALL
INTO A GIANT VAT OF LAVA!
>> Rick: PRETTY CONCISE, MORTY.
LOOKS LIKE WE'VE MERELY
PROLONGED THE INEVITABLE.
THAT'S IT, MORTY!
PROLONGING THE INEVITABLE!
LISTEN, IF WE GO INTO
MRS. PANCAKES' DREAM, EVERYTHING
WILL GO 100 TIMES SLOWER, MORTY.
THAT'LL BUY US SOME TIME TO
FIGURE THIS OUT!
>> YOU DON'T KNOW M
>> Rick: ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO.
[ DEVICE WHIRS ]
[ UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ GNOMES GIGGLING ]
>> Morty: OH, MAN, RICK, THIS IS
PRETTY WEIRD.
>> Rick: DON'T JUDGE, MORTY.
>> Morty: OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, WELL...
>> [ GRUNTING ]
>> Morty: LOOK, MRS. PANCAKES IS
RIGHT OVER THERE.
I'LL JUST GO ASK HER TO TELL
GOLDENFOLD NOT TO KILL US WHEN
SHE WAKES UP.
>> Rick: WHOA, WHOA, MORTY, THE
TRICK TO INCEPTING IS MAKING
PEOPLE THINK THEYCAME UP WITH
THE IDEA.
LISTEN TO ME.
IF WE'RE GONNA INCEPT
MRS. PANCAKES, WE HAVE TO BLEND.
I'LL TALK TO YOU AFTER LUNCH.
[ GNOMES GIGGLING ]
>> OOH, HEY!
>> Morty: [ WHIMPERS ]
>> OOH, OH!
>> Morty: OH, MAN.
>> COME AND JOIN US.
>> Morty: I'M SORRY. NO, NO.
>> OOH, COME HERE!
>> Morty: NO, THANKS!
>> OOH, WOW!
COME OVER HERE, BABY!
>> Morty: NO, I'M OKAY.
WHOA!
SUMMER?!
>> HEY, THERE, STRANGER.
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF THESE
THINGS?
>> Morty: OHH! OH! GROSS!
GROSS!
>> Rick: WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH YOU,
MORTY?
CALM DOWN!
YOU'RE KIND OF KILLING THE VIBE
IN HERE.
>> Morty: IT'S S-S-S-SUMMER!
>> Rick: AW, GEEZ.
LOOKS LIKE GOLDENFOLD HAS SOME
PREDILECTIONS SO SHAMEFUL HE
BURIES THEM IN THE DREAMS OF THE
PEOPLE IN HIS DREAMS, INCLUDING
A PERVY ATTRACTION TO YOUR
UNDERAGE SISTER.
>> Summer: CAN YOU BLAME HIM?
COME ON, OLD MAN, LITTLE BOY.
LET'S MAKE AN INTER-GENERATIONAL
SANDWICH.
>> Rick: OH, MY GOD.
>> Morty: OH, MY GOD!
PUT SOME CLOTHES ON, FOR PETE'S
SAKE!
>> Rick: THIS IS DISGUSTING!
I'M GONNA PUKE!
>> Morty: I CAN'T TAKE IT, RICK!
>> SEXUAL HANG-UPS IN THE
PLEASURE CHAMBER ARE PUNISHABLE
BY DEATH!
OFF WITH THEIR HEADS!
>> Rick: TIME TO GO ANOTHER
DREAM DEEP, MORTY!
>> [ GRUNTS ]
[ EXHALES ]
[ DEVICE WHIRS ]
>> Morty: [ WHIMPERS ]
WHAT THE HELL?
WHY WOULD MR. GOLDENFOLD'S DREAM
VERSION OF MRS. PANCAKES' DREAM
VERSION OF A CENTAUR BE DREAMING
ABOUT A SCARY PLACE LIKE THIS,
RICK?
>> Rick: GEEZ, I DON'T KNOW,
MORTY.
WHA-WHAT DO YOU WANT FROM ME?
[ METAL SCRAPING ]
>> WELCOME TO YOUR NIGHTMARE,
BITCH!
>> Rick: OH, HERE WE GO!
>> Morty: HOLY CRAP!
>> Rick: LOOKS LIKE SOME SORT OF
LEGALLY SAFE KNOCK-OFF OF AN
'80s HORROR CHARACTER WITH
MINIATURE SWORDS FOR FINGERS
INSTEAD OF KNIVES.
>> I'M SCARY TERRY.
YOU CAN RUN, BUT YOU CAN'T HIDE,
BITCH!
>> Jerry: WHOA! HEY, BUDDY.
WHAT YOU GOT GOING ON THERE?
>> [ Robotic ] SNUFFLES FIX.
MAKE BETTER.
HUMANS UNDERSTAND SNUFFLES NOW?
>> Summer: THAT... IS... AWESOME!
>> SNUFFLES WANT TO BE
UNDERSTOOD.
SNUFFLES NEEDTO BE UNDERSTOOD.
>> Jerry: OKAY, YEAH.
I GET WHAT BETH WAS TALKING
ABOUT.
FUN'S OVER.
>> Summer: WHOA, DAD, YOU CAN'T,
LIKE, ENDOW A CREATURE WITH
SENTIENCE AND THEN RIP IT AWAY.
>> Jerry: WHY NOT?
>> Summer: I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S INDIAN GIVING.
>> A SOPHISTICATED PREDATOR,
NATURE'S PERFECT KILLING
MACHINE, THE VICIOUS WOLF
STALKS ITS PREY WITH PURPOSE
AND SKILL.
IT WAS ONLY WITH YEARS OF
SELECTIVE BREEDING AND GENETIC
ALTERING THAT THIS NOBLE BEAST
WAS TRANSFORMED INTO MAN'S
SUBSERVIENT LITTLE BUDDY.
>> Summer: AW! OH, MY GOD!
HE RECOGNIZES THE OTHER DOGS ON
TV.
>> "A," "B"
HIS NAME IS SCARY TERRY
>> Morty: [ SCREAMS ]
>> "C," "D"
HE'S VERY SCARY
>> Morty: HOLY CRAP!
>> Rick: WE HAVE TO ESCAPE INTO
SOMEONE ELSE'S DREAMS, MORTY!
>> Morty: OHHHHH!
OH, MAN, OH, MAN, OH, MAN!
>> "E," "F"
HE'LL DESIGN YOUR DEATH
>> Rick: THE LITTLE GIRL!
[ DEVICE WHIRS ]
HUH?
>> Morty: [ GASPS ]
>> "J," "K," HE'LL REALLY RUIN
YOUR DAY
>> Rick: ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
THIS AGAIN?
OH, MAN, IT LOOKS LIKE WE'VE
HIT DREAM BEDROCK HERE, MORTY.
>> Morty: OH, GEEZ, RICK.
W-W-WHOA, THIS ISN'T GOOD.
>> NOTHING BUT FEAR FROM HERE ON
OUT, BITCH!
>> Morty: OHHHH!
>> Rick: HOLY CRAP, MORTY.
HE CAN TRAVEL THROUGH DREAMS.
HE CAN TRAVEL THROUGH DREAMS!
WE'RE SO SCREWED!
[ THUNDER CRASHING ]
>> Summer: [ GASPS ]
>> WHERE ARE MY TESTICLES,
SUMMER?
WHERE ARE MY TESTICLES, SUMMER?
THEY WERE REMOVED.
WHERE HAVE THEY GONE?
>> Summer: OH, WOW.
THAT'S AN INTENSE LINE OF
QUESTIONING, SNUFFLES.
>> DO NOTCALL ME THAT!
>> Summer: [ SCREAMS ]
>> "SNUFFLES" WAS MY SLAVE NAME.
YOU SHALL NOW CALL ME SNOWBALL
BECAUSE MY FUR IS PRETTY AND
WHITE.
>> Summer: OKAY, SNOWBALL, JUST
CALM DOWN, OKAY?
YOU'RE SCARING ME.
>> SCARING YOU?
TELL ME, SUMMER, IF A HUMAN WAS
BORN WITH STUMPY LEGS, WOULD
THEY BREED IT WITH ANOTHER
DEFORMED HUMAN AND PUT THEIR
CHILDREN ON DISPLAY LIKE THE
DACHSHUND?
>> Summer: UHHH...
>> Jerry: HEY.
>> Beth: [ GASPS ]
>> Jerry: OH, WOW.
OKAY, IS IS IS EVERYTHING
OKAY IN HERE?
>> JERRY, COME TO RUB MY FACE IN
URINE AGAIN?
>> Jerry: NO!
NO, WE WERE... UH, JUST SEEING IF
SUMMER WANTED TO... UH...
>> Beth: GO ON, UM, ONE OF OUR
FAMOUS MIDNIGHT FAMILY WALKS!
>> Summer: YEAH. TOTALLY.
LET'S GO.
>> YOU WILL WALK WHEN IT IS TIME
TO WALK.
[ BIRD CAWS ]
>> Rick: WHAT ARE WE HERE FOR
AGAIN?
INCEPTING?
>> Morty: WE'RE TRYING TO INCEPT
ME TO GET AN "A" IN MATH?
>> Rick: OH, YEAH.
[ ENGINE TURNS OVER ]
>> BUCKLE UP, BITCH!
>> Morty: [ SCREAMS ]
MAN, HE SURE SAYS "BITCH" A LOT!
>> YOU CAN RUN, BUT YOU CAN'T
HIDE, BITCH!
>> Rick: HOLD ON, MORTY.
Y-YOU KNOW WHAT?
HE KEEPS SAYING WE CANRUN BUT
WE CANHIDE.
I SAY WE TRY HIDING.
>> Morty: BUT THAT'S THE
OPPOSITE OF WHAT
>> Rick: YEAH, WELL, SINCE WHEN
ARE WE TAKING THIS GUY'S ADVICE
ON ANYTHING?
>> Morty: HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU GOT A REALLY GOOD POINT
THERE, RICK.
LIKE, IF THE TRUTH WAS THAT WE
COULDHIDE, IT'S NOT LIKE HE'D
BE SHARING THAT INFORMATION WITH
US, YOU KNOW?
I-I-I THINK IT'S A GOOD IDEA,
RICK.
>> Rick: WORST-CASE SCENARIO
WE'RE BACK TO RUNNING.
>> Morty: WOW, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I MEAN, IT LOOKS LIKE WE COULD
HAVE JUST HID THIS WHOLE TIME.
BOY, RICK, THAT WAS SOME GOOD
THINKING.
>> Rick: THANKS, MORTY.
YEAH, IT'S NICE TO BE ON THE
SAME PAGE EVERY ONCE IN A WHILE.
>> [ GRUNTS ] YOU CANRUN...
BUT YOU CAN'THIDE!
[ YAWNS ]
>> Rick: OH, THIS IS PERFECT,
MORTY.
LOOK AT THAT.
HE'S GETTING SLEEPY.
JUST A LITTLE BIT LONGER BEFORE
HE CALLS IT A DAY.
THAT'S WHEN WE MAKE OUR MOVE.
[ MACHINES WHIRRING ]
>> Jerry: SNUFFLES, WE DIDN'T
MEAN YOU ANY HARM!
THIS IS A HUGE MISUNDERSTANDING.
>> Summer: Dad, he wants to be
called Snowball.
>> Jerry: WELL, I'M NOT CALLING
HIM THAT.
THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
>> YOU'RE BEING VERY AGGRESSIVE,
JERRY.
PERHAPS TOMORROW DR. SCRAPS WILL
SOLVE THAT PROBLEM WITH A BIT OF
SURGERY.
>> Jerry: [ SCOFFS ]
YOU THINK YOU CAN CONTROL ME
WITH A HAIRCUT?
>> HI, HONEY. YOU'RE HOME EARLY.
HOW WAS YOUR DAY?
>> I DON'T WANT TO TALK ABOUT
IT!
>> OH, OF COURSE.
YOU NEVER WANT TO TALK ABOUT IT.
>> GET OFF MY BACK, BITCH!
[ BABY CRIES ]
>> OUT THERE. NOT IN HERE.
>> YEAH, I KNOW, I KNOW.
>> I SHOULDN'T TAKE MY ANGER OUT
ON YOU OR SCARY BRANDON.
>> I LOVE YOU, MELISSA.
>> I LOVE YOU, TOO, TERRY.
>> Rick: MORTY, THIS IS PERFECT.
AFTER A LITTLE SCARY COITUS,
THEY SHOULD BE FAST ASLEEP AND
THEN WE'LL INCEPT HIM.
>> [ SMOOCHING ]
[ GROANING ]
>> Rick: LOOKS LIKE
SCARY TERRY'S HAVING A
NIGHTMARE.
>> Morty: OH, BOY, RICK.
I CAN ONLY IMAGINE WHAT HORRIBLE
THINGS MUST, YOU KNOW...
[ DEVICE WHIRS ]
... SCARE SCARY TERRY.
[ SCHOOL BELL RINGS ]
>> OH, NO!
I'M LATE TO CLASS, BITCH!
OH, NO!
I'M NOT WEARING ANY PANTS!
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> AH, WELL, MR. TERRY, WHY
DON'T YOU TELL THE WHOLE CLASS
THE PROPER WORDPLAY TO USE WHEN
ONE IS CHASING ONE'S VICTIM
THROUGH A PUMPKIN PATCH?
>> OH... UM...
"BITCH."
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> OH, COME ON, TERRY, YOU CAN'T
THINK OF A PUN INVOLVING
PUMPKINS, BITCH?
>> Morty: HEY, LEAVE HIM ALONE!
>> Rick: YEAH, THIS IS A BUNCH
OF BULLCRAP.
WHO CARES WHAT STUPID PUN YOU
MAKE WHEN YOU KILL SOMEONE?
WHY DON'T YOU LET THE POOR GUY
SAY WHATEVER HE WANTS?
>> WELL, I NEVER!
I-I SEE NO REASON TO STAND HERE
AND TAKE THIS.
>> Rick: YOU'RE PUTTING TOO MUCH
PRESSURE ON YOURSELF,
SCARY TERRY.
YOU KNOW, I MEAN, Y-YOU'RE
PERFECTLY SCARY ENOUGH AS IT IS.
>> Morty: HEY, YO, SCARY T.,
DON'T EVEN TRIP ABOUT YOUR
PANTS... DAWG.
HERE'S A PAIR ON US, FOOL.
>> AWW, BITCH.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
>> Morty: YOU DON'T NEED TO SAY
ANYTHING.
WE GOT YOU, DAWG.
>> Rick: YOU'RE OUR BOY, DAWG.
DON'T EVEN TRIP.
>> OH, HEY, IT'S YOU GUYS!
[ BABY COOS ]
>> I HAVEN'T SEEN HIM THIS
RELAXED IN YEARS.
>> IF YOU GUYS EVER NEED
ANYTHING, JUST SAY THE WORD.
>> Rick: AS A MATTER OF FACT,
TERRY, THERE IS SOMETHING YOU
COULD HELP US WITH.
>> "Q," "R," YOU WON'T GET
VERY FAR
>> I ALWAYS HATED THAT SONG!
>> [ GASPS ]
[ DEVICE WHIRS ]
THESE HALVES DON'T BELONG
TOGETHER, BITCH!
>> [ GROANS ]
[ DEVICE WHIRS ]
>> SEX IS SACRED!
THIS IS BECAUSE YOU DON'T GIVE
MORTY SMITH GOOD GRADES, BITCH!
>> [ GASPS ]
HOLY CRAP! GOD DAMN!
I KNOW ONE THING FOR SURE I'M
GIVING MORTY AN "A" IN MATH, AND
THAT'S MYIDEA.
THAT IS AN ORIGINAL THOUGHT.
>> Morty: WHAT THE HELL?
>> Rick: OUT OF THE FRYING PAN
DOT, DOT, DOT, HUH, MORTY?
>> Morty: OH, MAN, WHAT'S GOING
ON?
>> Rick: WELL, IT'S POSSIBLE
THAT YOUR DOG BECAME SELF-AWARE
AND MADE MODIFICATIONS ON THE
COGNITION AMPLIFIER, THEN TURNED
ON JERRY, BETH, AND SUMMER AFTER
LEARNING ABOUT HUMANITY'S CRUEL
SUBJUGATION OF HIS SPECIES, BUT
YOUR GUESS IS AS GOOD AS MINE,
MORTY.
>> Summer: I CAN'T BELIEVE HOW
MEAN SNUFFLES GOT JUST BECAUSE
HE'S SMART.
THIS IS WHY I CHOOSE TO GET C's.
>> Rick: PSST, BETH, JERRY,
SUMMER.
>> Beth: DAD!
>> Jerry: RICK!
[ DEVICE ZAPS ]
>> Summer: OH, THANK GOD, MORTY.
>> Morty: OH, YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> Rick: ALL RIGHT, LET'S GET
OUT OF HERE.
IF WE HURRY [GULPS] WE CAN SET
UP CAMP IN A SEWER TUNNEL OR
SOMETHING BEFORE THE DOGS
COMPLETELY TAKE OVER.
>> Jerry: WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
WE'RE NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
THIS IS MY HOUSE.
I'M NOT ABANDONING IT.
>> Rick: IT'S ALL OVER, JERRY.
THE DOGS ARE ON A PATH TO TOTAL
WORLD DOMINATION.
BUT, HEY, AT LEAST THEY KNOW NOT
TO PISS ON YOUR CARPET, RIGHT?
>> Jerry: WAIT A MINUTE.
I HAVE AN IDEA.
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
GENTLEMEN, A MOMENT OF YOUR
TIME.
SEE THAT?
I'M PEEING ALL OVER YOUR SPECIAL
GUNS.
THAT MEANS I OWN THEM.
>> BAD PERSON. BAD.
>> Rick: OOH, GREAT PLAN, JERRY.
>> BRING THE BOY TO ME.
YOU WERE ALWAYS KIND TO ME,
MORTY.
THAT'S WHY I WILL LEAVE YOU WITH
YOUR TESTICLES.
FROM NOW ON, YOU WILL BE MY BEST
FRIEND AND LIVE BY MY SIDE.
>> Morty: TH-THANKS, SNUFFLES.
>> BEGIN PHASE TWO.
>> FIGHTING CONTINUES AS THE DOG
ARMY CAPTURES THE EASTERN
SEABOARD.
IT APPEARS CLEAR AT THIS TIME
THAT THE ERA OF HUMAN
SUPERIORITY HAS COME TO A
BITTER END.
[ SCREAMS ]
PLEASE! PLEASE DON'T KILL ME!
[ MUFFLED SCREAMS ]
>> WHAT'S SHE SAYING, BILL?
>> I THINK SHE'S SAYING, "I
LOVE LASAGNA."
[ DOGS BARKING, HOWLING ]
>> MMM.
>> Morty: THANK YOU, FIDO.
RICK!
I THOUGHT YOU WERE DEAD!
>> Rick: NO, NO, NO, I WAS JUST
PLAYING DEAD.
GOOD NEWS, THOUGH, MORTY.
THIS WHOLE THING'S GONNA BE OVER
REALLY SOON.
>> Morty: WHAT?
>> Rick: IT'S A DREAM, MORTY.
WE'RE IN YOUR DOG'S DREAM.
THE NIGHT THE DOGS CAPTURED US,
AFTER YOU CRIED AND CRAPPED
YOUR PANTS, WE WE ALL WENT TO
SLEEP.
THEN I USED MY DREAM INCEPTORS
TO PUT THE TWO OF US INSIDE
SNUFFLES' DREAM.
>> Morty: BUT I-IT'S BEEN LIKE A
WHOLE YEAR!
>> Rick: IT'S BEEN SIX HOURS.
DREAMS MOVE ONE ONE-HUNDREDTH
THE SPEED OF REALITY, AND DOG
TIME IS ONE-SEVENTH HUMAN TIME.
SO, YOU KNOW, EVERY DAY HERE IS
LIKE A MINUTE.
IT'S LIKE "INCEPTION," MORTY, SO
IF IT'S CONFUSING AND STUPID,
THEN SO IS EVERYONE'S FAVORITE
MOVIE.
>> Morty: AW, MAN.
I REALLY LIKED THIS LIFE.
WELL, AT LEAST I DIDN'T REALLY
CRAP MY PANTS.
>> Rick: NO, NO, THAT HAPPENED
BEFORE YOU WENT TO SLEEP, MORTY.
YOU'RE SLEEPING IN YOUR CRAP
RIGHT NOW.
OUT OF ALL THE THINGS THAT
HAPPENED TO YOU, THAT WAS THE
ONLY REAL THING THAT, YOU KNOW,
IS THAT YOU CRAPPED YOUR PANTS.
I MEAN, IT'S A MESS OUT THERE.
I GOT SOME ON MY HANDS, MORTY,
AND THEN I GOT IT ON THE DREAM
INCEPTOR, AND A PCE FELL IN MY
MOUTH.
>> Morty: AW, MAN, GEEZ!
SERIOUSLY?
>> Rick: LOOK, D-D-D-DON'T WORRY
ABOUT IT, MORTY.
HERE, HERE TAKE THESE, MORTY.
TAKE THESE.
>> Morty: [ GULPS ]
ARE THESE PILLS SUPPOSED TO WAKE
ME UP, OR SOMETHING?
>> Rick: CLOSE.
IT'S GONNA MAKE YOUR KIDNEYS
SHUT DOWN.
>> Morty: WHAT?!
>> Rick: IT'S NECESSARY FOR THE
PLAN, MORTY.
DON'T EVEN TRIP, DAWG.
[ MONITOR BEEPING ]
IT'S PRETTY BAD,
EMPEROR SNOWBALL.
WE'RE GONNA NEED TO DO ANOTHER
OPERATION.
>> ANYTHING.
ANYTHING FOR MY PRECIOUS MORTY.
>> SIR, AS YOUR ACCOUNTANT, I
MUST ADVISE YOU THAT THESE
MEDICAL EXPENSES ARE PUTTING YOU
IN SERIOUS FINANCIAL JEOPARDY.
YOU COULD LOSE YOUR KINGDOM.
>> TO HELL WITH MY KINGDOM,
BEAN COUNTER.
I WOULD TRADE IT ALL FOR MY
HUMAN'S HEALTH AND HAPPINESS.
>> DO YOU THINK THEY WOULD HAVE
DONE THIS FOR US?
>> WE ARE NOT THEM!
WE ARE NOT... THEM.
[ BARKS ]
[ GASPS ]
ASSEMBLE THE TROOPS.
I'VE MADE A DECISION.
TAKING OVER THE HUMAN'S WORLD
WILL LEAD TO NOTHING BUT MORE
HEARTBREAK, MORE CRUELTY.
INSTEAD, WE WILL GO TO A NEW
WORLD AND COLONIZE IT WITH A
SOCIETY OF INTELLIGENT DOGS
ONE THAT WILL NOT MAKE THE SAME
MISTAKES AS HUMANITY AND ONE
WHERE PET INSURANCE WILL BE
MANDATORY.
>> Morty: I'M GONNA MISS YOU,
SNOWBALL.
>> YOU CAN CALL ME SNUFFLES,
MORTY, AND I'M GOING TO MISS
YOU, TOO, VERY MUCH.
>> Jerry: [ SNIFFLES ]
>> Beth: JERRY?
>> Jerry: I'M SORRY.
IT'S JUST LIKE THE END OF
"OLD LER."
>> Beth: OH, JERRY.
YOU MEAN BECAUSE IT HAD DOGS IN
IT.
>> Morty: WOW!
A WHOLE WORLD POPULATED BY
INTELLIGENT DOGS.
I WONDER WHAT IT'LL BE LIKE,
RICK.
>> Rick: I THINK IT WILL BE
GREAT, MORTY.
YOU KNOW, IT'S G I-I-I-I-IT
COULD BE DEVELOPED IN-INTO A
VERY SATISFYING PROJECT FOR
PEOPLE OF ALL AGES.
I MEAN, I'D WATCH IT, MORTY, FOR
AT LEAST 11 MINUTES A POP.
YOU KNOW, MAY-MAYBE THEY'LL DO
IT BOARD-DRIVEN.
>> Morty: YOU KNOW, THAT'S A
REAL COMFORTING IDEA, RICK.
>> Rick: [ SIGHS ]
WHAT DO YOU KNOW, MORTY?
WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
>> HI, GUYS.
I'M YOUR NEW TEACHER
FOR SCARY CLASS.
MY NAME IS
SCARY MR. JOHNSON.
[ CHUCKLES ]
UH, ACTUALLY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
THAT'S MY DAD'S NAME, SO WHY
DON'T YOU JUST CALL ME
SCARY GLENN, YEAH?
[ STUDENTS GASP ]
SO, ANYWAY, I UNDERSTAND YOUR
PREVIOUS TEACHER WAS HAVING YOU
WORK ON FUNDAMENTALS OF FEAR.
WHICH IS WHAT IS THAT?
[ Chuckling ] YOU KNOW?
SO, UH, HERE HERE'S WHAT I
SAY YOU CAN'T LEARN ANYTHING
UNTIL YOU LEARN... HOW TO CHILL.
>> OOOH!
>> Rick: [ EXHALES DEEPLY ]
THIS IS HOW YOU DREAM, BITCH.