Schenectady?!
You're in Schenectady?!
After all your naggy lectures about how
I need to stop micro-managing ISIS?!
RON: You do!
And this is... macro-managing!
C'mon, some things I gotta do myself!
CHERYL/CAROL: Mr. Archer's on line two.
MALORY: I'm on the phone!
CHERYL/CAROL: Yeah, duh, line two.
MALORY: Wh-?
ARCHER: Mother?!
MALORY: Sterling --
ARCHER: Don't talk, just listen!
My cover's blown and I
need an extraction!
MALORY: Oh my -- wait,
extraction from where?
ARCHER: Montreal, long story, but my money
and passport were confiscated, so --
MALORY: So where in Montreal exactly?
ARCHER: Uh... Like, the GPS coordinates, or --
LOUDSPEAKER: Bienvenue au Casino de Montreal.
MALORY: Confiscated by whom?
A croupier?
ARCHER: No!
MALORY: Or a herd of Quebecker whores?!
ARCHER: I wouldn't say herd...
MALORY: Well, after you get some
free penicillin, compliments of the
Socialist Republic of Canada --
ARCHER: Wait, really?
MALORY: -- you can extract
yourself, mister!
ARCHER: Mother I don't have a passpor --
RON: -- I mean don't
get me wrong, I respect that,
but comparing ISIS to six
Cadillac dealerships is like comparing
apples to... six Cadillac --
MALORY: Ron!
RON: What?!
MALORY: Sterling is stranded at
the Montreal Casino with his
pockets turned out and -- and
this is just speculation --
some new drug-resistant form of V.D.
RON: Reeally...
MALORY: And you're in Schenectady. Again!
RON: I'll be home tonight!
MALORY: Oh, I know!
Because what's tonight?!
RON: Uh, Tuesday? Night?
MALORY: Box seats!
For the opening of "Carmen" at the Met!
RON: Babe, c'mon, I
promise, I'll be there!
MALORY: Well if you're not, you can
just not bother coming home at all!
RON: I --
CHERYL/CAROL: Trouble on the old hooomfront?
MALORY: Oh for the -- eavesdrop much?!
PAM: Scream into a speakerphone much?
MALORY: Pam...?
PAM: What?!
You want us to wear earplugs every
time you're on the damn pho --
CHERYL/CAROL: Ooh, or helmets!
MALORY: It is just idiots,
all the way down.
And his money, I get it, that's all
craps and whores, but his passport?
How the hell did he lose his passport?
ARCHER: Bekuz, shuddup, bekuz I dunneebit...
Bekuz I dunnever go homerika,
bekuz, shuddup, bekuz je -- hic!
Je tam!
CALL GIRL: Tabernac...
MALORY: It's my third biggest fear.
He brings home a whore and
says "We're married!"
Oh, and the whore has bangs.
Ugh, thank God I don't have to worry
about anything like that with Ron.
"Hi, I'm Ron Cadillac, aka Mr. Boring."
Jesus God, what am I doing with...
RON: Ron Cadillac!
They don't make the rules!
You do!
Well obviously they do make the
rules, that's why it's come to this.
Which is why Ron Cadillac is opting out!
And also why Ron Cadillac is gonna
swing by Montreal on his way home.
Because Ron Cadillac is frickin epic.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
[ Phone Ringing ]
CHERYL/CAROL: What.
Yes, I'll accept the charges. What.
ARCHER: Carol, hey, shut up, I need you
to go down to Western Union and wire me
a thousand dollars.
CHERYL/CAROL: Wow.
ARCHER: Yeah.
CHERYL/CAROL: No.
ARCHER: Yes!
CHERYL/CAROL: No!
ARCHER: Oh for -- then
just lemme talk to Pam!
CHERYL/CAROL: Absolutely not.
Huh?
Because pick any one of an
infinite number of reasons!
Yeah, okay, hang on...
KRIEGER: Mmmmyeah, no, I would,
but I can't really leave the lab at the moment...
But I can transfer you...
GILLETTE: No, I seriously
thought you were joking.
Yeah, hang on...
CYRIL: [Convulsive Laughter]
ARCHER: Okay.
Okay!
Lemme talk to Lana!
BROKE GUY: Tabernac!
You know there is a line?!
ARCHER: There's gonna
be a line at your wake!
So shut your poutine hole,
and lemme --
Lana?! Lana listen, I --
LANA: Noop.
ARCHER: -- need you to --
ARCHER: Stop saying noop!
LANA: Noop, Archer.
Noop.
And it's gonna sound like I'm
hanging up but -- [ Dial Tone ]
BROKE GUY: Why do you
casser le telephone?!
ARCHER: Because I'm out
of people to call!
Even Woodhouse wouldn't help me...
What do you mean, no?!
I basically own you!
And I basically own him.
Jesus, this is actually
almost depressing.
[ HONK HONK ]
RON: Need a ride, champ?
ARCHER: Although not as depressing as
Ron what the hell are you doing here?!
RON: Giving you a ride home.
C'mon, hop in!
ARCHER: Did Mother send you?
RON: Uh, not exactly, I uh, just thought
it'd give us a chance to uh, bond.
ARCHER: Yeah, don't take this the wrong way,
Ron, but I'd rather bond with a C.H.U.D.
BROKE GUY: Il est la!
Il est la!
ARCHER: But C.H.U.D.'s live
in New York so let's go!
RON: What the hell is a chud?!
ARCHER: They were people, but then
they got splashed with toxic waste.
RON: Aw, that's a load of crap...
ARCHER: It's a movie!
RON: But those baby alligators people
flush down there, now that's --
ARCHER: Ron! C'mon, seriously,
at some point I'm gonna have to
take a shit, so --
RON: So why didn't you go before we left?
ARCHER: Not now!
In the future!
And I won't be able to if I'm
thinking about giant alligators
rampaging up into my toilet!
RON: Talk about tearing you a new one...
ARCHER: For the love of Christ,
man! Stop!
I meant, stop talking, about
assripping sewer-gators.
RON: Yeah, I know.
ARCHER: So?!
He asked, incredulously!
RON: You said you didn't have a passport.
ARCHER: So?!
He asked, equally incredulously!
RON: So that.
ARCHER: Oh. So...?
And that's not sarcastic incredulity,
I honestly wanna hear your
thoughts on getting me across.
RON: Why not?!
ARCHER: Because what if
they check the trunk?!
RON: Why would they?
ARCHER: Because that's exactly their job!
RON: Yeah, on the Mexican border!
Who the hell's gonna
sneak in from Canada?!
ARCHER: Arctic wolves?
RON: And even if you had a passport,
what if they checked you for a gun?
ARCHER: I --
RON: You do have a gun, don't you?
ARCHER: Yeah, I --
RON: Yeah, I, so uh, maybe keep it handy.
ARCHER: What?
Wait, why would I -- Ron?
Ron. Ron.
Roooooooooooooooooooon!
RON: What?!
ARCHER: Oh.
Never mind, I got it.
ARCHER: Ron! Let me outta
the goddamn trunk!
We passed the border an hour ago!
RON: Actually more like three hours.
ARCHER: I -- well
apparently I took a nap!
Probably all this carbon dioxide.
RON: It's actually monoxide--
ARCHER: Whichever!
Of carbon's many oxides!
Just lemme out! I gotta bitch of a
headache and a bladder full of bourbon!
RON: Just hang on!
They always hit me between
Schenectady and Albany.
ARCHER: Who hits you?!
RON: Uh... Those guys.
ARCHER: What the shit!
Ron!
RON: Yeah, so listen!
Remember when I said maybe
keep your gun handy?!
ARCHER: Yeah, vaguely!
RON: Well the thing is --
ARCHER: What's the thing, Ron?!
Oh.
Never mind!
ARCHER: Goddammit Ron, keep it straight!
ARCHER: Ha ha! Wooooooo!
Did you whoa whoa whoa Ron, compensate!
RON: I am compensating!
ARCHER: No no no no no,
look out, you're --
Overcompensating.
Is what I was gonna say.
Right before I was thrown clear of the
vehicle, almost exactly one hundred
linear feet.
RON: Gimme a break, huh,
that wasn't my fault!
ARCHER: Yeah no, I mean obviously this
was all due to the butterfly effect.
- The what -- - Butterfly effect,
ya know, a butterfly in Africa
lands on a giraffe's nose, the
giraffe sneezes, that spooks
a gazelle, the gazelle bonks
into a rhinoceros, and the
rhinoceros blindly stampedes
into a phone booth,
calls New York somehow and says "Hey go
kill this idiot Ron for a suitcase!"
Because the rhinoceros speaks English!
What's in the suitcase, Ron?
Why is that in the suitcase, Ron?!
RON: What, I should use a plastic bag?
ARCHER: Or this new thing
called the bank?!
RON: Well, it's not exactly...
Clean, money.
ARCHER: No, shit.
LANA: No, I'm serious... Name one, just
one single favor, that Archer ever did
for any of you.
EVERYBODY: [ Ummm ]
CHERYL/CAROL: Oh!
Oh my God, chlamydia.
Which put me over my deductible,
so the rest of that year all my
doctor visits were totally free, score!
EVERYBODY: Wow.
CHERYL/CAROL: Right?
PAM: How much did you
go to the damn doctor?
CHERYL/CAROL: I dunno, like, a lot...
I kept getting chlamydia.
Oww!
GILLETTE: Get! Off! Chlamydiot!
CHERYL/CAROL: Oh, I get it...
because of the chlamydia.
Oh, and I'm an idiot.
ARCHER: Because of course
you keep getting robbed!
Why're you driving around with a
suitcase full of dirty money?
RON: It's kind of a long story...
ARCHER: Well we've got all day!
Nobody's gonna pick us up, we look like...
The Ballad of the Flim-Flam Man.
RON: The what?
ARCHER: Guy Owen?
Jesus, Ron, read a book.
Maybe between biannual
suitcase robberies.
RON: I don't know who
keeps tipping 'em off.
And anyway, you mean semiannual.
ARCHER: They're the same thing!
RON: No, biannual means every two years --
ARCHER: That's biennial!
Bi-, or semi-annual,
means every six months!
RON: Oh.
Then yeah, biannually.
Or semi.
ARCHER: Speaking of...
RON: Manhattan, yes, thank you,
and you're sure you can
get us there by seven?
TRUCKER: Oh yeah. Just
hop in the back there.
ARCHER: What like, the back back?
TRUCKER: Yeah, sorry, you'all
can't ride in the cab.
Insurance bullshit, compliments of
them democratic queers in congress.
ARCHER: Or whomever.
Okay, things are looking up!
RON: No no, hey, c'mon, don't do that!
You're gonna get him in trouble!
ARCHER: Ron, nobody's
gonna miss one beer.
Or the eleven more I'm gonna drink.
RON: C'mon, he's an independent trucker...
A small business owner,
out here busting his hump to
provide for his family...
I'm tellin ya, guys like him
are the lifeblood of America.
Not to mention he's driving us
non-stop straight to Manhattan.
ARCHER: Exactly, which should
take about three hours.
Which equals twelve beers.
CHERYL/CAROL: Ugh, okay, here's
your fur coat, from the world's
farthest-away cold storage.
MALORY: Wh-? Did they tell you
to put it in a headlock?!
CHERYL/CAROL: No.
MALORY: Well?!
CHERYL/CAROL: I don't know!
They were like, Persian!
ARCHER: You lost me.
RON: Cadillac's not my real last name.
ARCHER: I -- well yeah, I figured
the odds on that were pretty huge.
RON: I changed it.
From Kazinsky.
And before I sold cars... I stole 'em.
ARCHER: You what?!
RON: I mean, this was years and years ago...
Me, Tony, Donny, Joey
and Fat Mike.
That was my crew. And kiddo,
we'd boost anything on wheels.
Or one time, ya know, not even on wheels.
That was forty-five, though,
that didn't hurt the war effort.
Anyhoo... One day it dawns on
me, we're doin' all this work,
but the guys makin' the real money own
the chop shops... So we revised our
business model.
For a few years, lemme tell ya
kid, we were going gangbusters.
Until one day, I'm out gettin meatball
subs for the crew, and... boom.
The cops got all of 'em.
ARCHER: Aw, Fat Mike too?
RON: All of 'em.
And they all got twenty years,
because not one of 'em,
not one of 'em gave me up.
Anyway, I used our stash to buy
a legit used car lot, and then
my first dealership, and eventually--
ARCHER: Six, yeah, got it.
So the money is...
RON: The least I can do.
It's like back pay, for
all the years they lost.
Plus most of it's from charging poor
saps for that frickin' undercoating.
Never.
Get the undercoating.
But I still don't know who keeps
hiring goons to stick me up.
ARCHER: Yes, you do.
RON: What're you talking about?
ARCHER: Ron, who hasn't been complaining
about not getting his money?
RON: Son of a... Fat Mike!
Wait'll the crew hears this!
He'll be eatin his meatball
subs through a straw.
ARCHER: Wow, and here Mother
thinks you are hands down the
most boringest man on this
entire planet of Earth.
RON: Wh-? She said that?!
- I mean... - He is hands down
the most boringest man on this
entire planet of Earth.
ARCHER: Not in those exact words, but--
RON: She thinks I'm boring?!
ARCHER: Well not after you tell her
you stole a Sherman tank, Master P!
RON: No no no, you can
never tell her about that!
I'm serious, about any of it!
ARCHER: I --
RON: None of it! Do you hear me?!
ARCHER: Okay!
RON: That's all behind me!
I'm -- almost completely legit now!
You gotta promise me you're
not going to tell her!
ARCHER: Okay! I promise!
Not that I'll ever get the chance...
Hey guys, if that's, ya know...
how you selfidentify.
ARCHER: Wow.
Okay, so...
Apparently we have stumbled
into what I'm just gonna assume is --
-- some kind of unspeakably
rapey snuff film --
yep, look at that, there's even a craft services table...
But my uh...
RON: Stepdad.
ARCHER: Mother's husband, has to
be back in time for the opera,
I know, rich people problems,
so even though all you guys
have bats and pipes and --
wow, Shorty over there's got a
club with lumps on it, kickin it Bedrock
style -- does anybody have a gun.
Anybody? Gun?
Probably looks a little
something like this? No?
Okay, so I guess just me then.
Now, for various reasons which
frankly don't concern you,
we can't call the police,
so we're just gonna go, but --
RON: What?!
No no no no no, screw that!
Shoot these degenerate pricks!
ARCHER: Ron?
RON: Starting with C.W. McCall-girl
over there!
ARCHER: Ron.
RON: Well at leastkneecap the sonsabitches!
ARCHER: Ron!
RON: What?!
What, you outta bullets?!
Well, how the hell was
I supposed to know?!
ARCHER: You saw me shoot the mob guys!
- So?!
- So it holds a finite number of bullets!
It's not a frickin phaser!
RON: A what?
ARCHER: Oh my God! It's just like
Carol said the old gypsy woman said!
CHERYL/CAROL: Yeah, she said
it would be like some freaky
parallel universe, where John
Waters directed "The Road Warrior"!
ARCHER: Uh-huh.
Then what, they kill me?
CHERYL/CAROL: No, shut up,
that's the awesome part!
ARCHER: There it is! Look, Ron!
The train!
I gotta start going to that gypsy.
RON: We'll never... we can't make it...
ARCHER: Yes we can!
If... dammit, if only there
was a way to slow them down!
Make it rain?
What am I, an Indian?
PAM: Pacman Jones!
ARCHER: Oh.
RON: Huh-uh! No!
ARCHER: Yes, Ron! You
don't defy the gypsy!
RON: What about my crew?!
I've been ripped off
the last three times!
What're they supposed to live on?!
ARCHER: What're they gonna live on
if you're eaten by tranny bikers?!
Ron, look!
We'd already be dead if they weren't in...
disturbingly sexy high heels!
[ Train Wistle ]
RON: Oh, half.
ARCHER: Okay, that's still a baller move.
Master P would totally be proud.
Or he'd release a diss track.
RON: What is it -- half the time
I don't even know what the hell
you're talking about!
ARCHER: Well guess what! Me neither!
That son of a -- Come on,
we've got a train to catch!
RON: Diss tracks.
Jesus Christ, why'd we even fight a war?
ARCHER: Ron!
RON: What, I'm serious!
ARCHER: So's this train, asshole!
RON: Oh, I'm the asshole?!
ARCHER: It's -- just get a running start!
RON: I'm not jumping on that damn thing!
ARCHER: Really?!
How bout now?!
RON: Son of a...!
ARCHER: Come on! Run like you're younger!
Okay, now gimme your hand!
RON: I can't!
ARCHER: Yes you can!
RON: Rrrrrrngh!
C'mon grab it, grab it!
ARCHER: Well now hang on a second...
RON: What're you doing?!
ARCHER: Thinking about how much I
hate it that Mother married you!
RON: You don't hate it she married me --
ARCHER: No, yeah, I --
RON: -- you hate it she married anybody!
Cause you want her all to yourself!
ARCHER: What?!
RON: Paging Doctor Bates!
Doctor Norman Bates --
ARCHER: Hey shut up!
And also eww!
And --
RON: Sterling, please!
Oh my God.
Thank you, Sterling.
ARCHER: You're welcome, shut up.
Norman Bates. Ya know...
RON: I apologize, that was out of line.
But come on, you gotta admit the
relationship you two have is... unhealthy.
ARCHER: No, Ron, I don't have
to admit that, because --
Okay, try not to ruin it this time.
HOBOS: Waaaaaaaooof!
RON: Jesus...
ARCHER: Yeah, you see how their legs broke?
That's because they didn't
use the parachute fall.
Which I don't have time to
teach you properly, but --
RON: Why would you want to?
ARCHER: I -- because I
take pride in my work?
RON: Why would you teach
it to me it at all?!
ARCHER: Oh. We gotta jump off the train.
RON Wh-?! We just jumped on the train!
ARCHER: Yeah, and it's going
about twenty miles an hour, and
there goes a sign for Catskill, so --
RON: So it'll take six hours to get home.
ARCHER: If we don't get
rousted by the bulls.
I also don't have time to
teach you how to speak hobo.
RON: But wait a minute, hang on, why
would you want me to make the opera?
ARCHER: I dunno, maybe you
were right about a few things,
and maybe you're good for Mother, and...
maybe shut up
before I lose my temper again.
RON: I got a dealership in Catskill...
ARCHER: So we grab a Caddy
and drive in style.
RON: Yeah, yeah, yeah, we could just make it...
But it's going too fast to jump off!
Look at those poles zipping by!
ARCHER: No, no, no, don't
look at the poles!
They give you a false perspective!
Try and focus on a distant
landmark, like -- The ground.
Woooooooo!
Hey! See how I did that?
Ron?
RON: Seven-thirty! We just might make it!
You sure he'll be out there?
ARCHER: He better be.
Yeah, there he is...
WOODHOUSE: Here you go, sir.
I took the liberty of taking in
the jacket a bit, and --
ARCHER: Woodhouse.
WOODHOUSE: Yessir?
ARCHER: Doesn't even come close
to making up for leaving me
stranded in Montreal.
WOODHOUSE: No sir.
ARCHER: So go get ready.
Your punishment will begin when I get
back from dropping him off at the opera.
RON: Wait, you think that's a good idea?
ARCHER: Ron?
Look, I know we accidentally
bonded a little, but do not
tell me how to discipline my servant!
RON: I meant dropping me off.
If your mother thinks we're all buddy-buddy...
ARCHER: Yeah, that would drive her insane...
WOODHOUSE: Sometimes I think
I should just run away.
But who would take me in?
No one, Woodhouse... no one.
MALORY: And just what
in the hell is this?
ARCHER: Just dropping off my buddy Ron!
MALORY: Buddy?!
Why, how, and since when?!
RON: Long story babe, and look,
we really gotta hustle if we
wanna make that curtain!
ARCHER: Yeah, and I gotta go make an
old man eat a big bowl of spiderwebs.
See ya buddy!
RON: Duh duh duh, duh duh duh duh...
ARCHER: Duh duh duh, duh duh duh duh...
Woodhouse, I'm gonna check that bowl!
WOODHOUSE: [brief, low sob]
Good day.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com