LANA: What do you
think you're doing?
ARCHER: My job, Lana.
LANA: And what part of your job,
exactly, is groping my ass?
ARCHER: The part that
calls for spycraft.
C'mon, we're posing as newlyweds--
LANA: Yeah, posing.
ARCHER: -- and I am
drunk on nuptial bliss.
LANA: You're drunk
on champagne.
ARCHER: Little column
A, little column B.
LANA: Mrvit!
ARCHER: Fine, but when you take my hand off
your lately almost overly ample butt --
LANA: Odd choice
of dying words...
ARCHER: I don't just question
your commitment to the mission, Lana, I
question your commitment to America.
LANA: Instead of feeling me up in the lobby --
ARCHER: Wait til we're in the
room, got it.
LANA: -- what say we
focus on the mission:
catching the North Koreans who are
in New York to buy enriched uranium.
ARCHER: Can't we do both?
LANA: Can't you shut up?
ARCHER: Can't you put a
price tag on freedom?
I mean you can't put a
price tag on freedom.
Always never forget that.
DESK CLERK: Here's your key for the
honeymoon suite, congratties, and if I
could just get a credit card for the
room and any incidentals, we'll be --
LANA: Broke, Jesus, the
room's that much?!
DESK CLERK: Is there a problem?
LANA: Not if we're
buying it as a condo.
DESK CLERK: I may have something a bit
more in your price range... basement okay?
ARCHER: No it's not, because as
love-besotted newlyweds we want the
honeymoon suite.
And price range is...rangeless.
LANA: Archer...?!
ARCHER: Shhh, a few minutes more, darling,
and you can have your way with me.
LANA: Ugh, I wish...
ARCHER: I know. Soon.
DESK CLERK: Alrighty, and
we are just all set.
Enjoy your stay.
ARCHER: Enjoy your stay...?
DESK CLERK: Oh, right, sorry!
Enjoy your stay --
LANA: No no no -
DESK CLERK: Mr. and Mrs. Archer!
LANA: Ughhh, it's like my heart's
being gripped by the icy fingers of
some terrifying Ghost
of Honeymoon Future.
ARCHER: (chuckles)
Lana.
Lana!
Lana!!
C'mon, if you don't answer I'm gonna
scream as loud as I possibly --
LANA: What?!
ARCHER: I'm sorry, I meant "Mrs.
Archer."
LANA: mmmm MALORY: I heard you.
WAITER: I apologize, madame, but --
MALORY: For what, Dunkirk? Or
that effeminate yet somehow
condescending tone?
Damn, I'm sure my card was in here...
TRUDY BEEKMAN (O.S.): Malory,
please, allow me...
MALORY: No no no, I'm --
TRUDY BEEKMAN: Embarrassing
yourself, dear.
MALORY: Thank you, Trudy.
PAM: Oh man, this
must be killing you!
CYRIL: What, the salmonella
dripping all over my desk?
PAM: It's lamb,
ding-dong, not salmon.
CYRIL: I --
PAM: I'm talking about Mr. Archer and Lana!
In a deluxe honeymoon suite!
CYRIL: Oh for -- Pam,
they're on a mission!
PAM: Ary position! By now, since I bet
they already did all the good ones...
CYRIL: Rrgh! Pam, they're --
PAM: Ungh ungh ungh ungh ungh ungh ungh
ungh ungh ungh ungh ungh
ungh. Want some?
CYRIL: I --
PAM: Psych!
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com | Sync to web-dl by aneurysm
CYRIL: Okay, first of
all, just shut up.
And second, I trust
Lana completely.
Especially with
regard to Archer.
She'd rather have sex with...
you.
PAM: Why, what'd she say?!
CYRIL: And third, Lana's pretty satisfied
in the old romance department.
PAM: And the old accounting department...
CYRIL: What's that?
LANA (O.S.): [sex noises]
CYRIL (O.S.): [sex noises]
PAM: What's that?
CYRIL: Well good thing you
work at a spy agency!
Miss... Spy On People!
PAM: What, I only
watched for a second!
CYRIL: You need medication, Pam!
Pills!
Big pills, like they
use at the zoo!
CHERYL/CAROL: But we have to go now, the
vet comes back from lunch in twenty
minutes!
CHERYL/CAROL: Let's go, bitches!
Tiger tranqs!
CYRIL: We are not.
Breaking into the zoo.
To steal tiger tranquilizers.
CHERYL/CAROL: Cyril,
they have all kinds.
CYRIL: And I have to direct-deposit
the annual bonuses, so if you two
could go be crazy and
horrible elsewhere...?
PAM: Like the Tuntmore Towers Hotel,
where Lana's shacked up with Mr.
Archer...
CHERYL/CAROL: Wait, what?!
PAM: Yeah, we can see if he's into all
that freaky gender-reversal stuff.
CYRIL: That -- wait, what?!
PAM: Cyril. I watched for
more than a second.
CYRIL: I -- you --
CHERYL/CAROL: Yeah, let's go down there!
I own that dump,
we can get a suite and totally
spy on Mr. Archer and --
CYRIL: Lana! Okay,
I'm going with you.
CHERYL/CAROL: Yeah whatever,
but on the way we're --
PAM: Not swingin by the zoo.
ARCHER (O.S.): Laaaaame.
LANA: What's lame, Archer?
LANA: The fact that we're up against at
least four highly-trained North Korean
agents? Or the fact they've all got--
ARCHER (O.S.): Peppercorns, Lana.
LANA: Well, I was gonna say Tokarevs and
Shpagin-41 submachine guns, but yeah,
let's go with peppercorns.
ARCHER (O.S.): Thank you!
ARCHER: Because without peppercorns,
it's not steak au poivre.
LANA: [annoyed sigh]
ARCHER: It can't be.
By like, definition.
LANA: Archer, we're supposed to
be stopping the North Koreans
from buying part of a nuclear bomb, not
ordering every single item on the
room service menu --
ARCHER: Just the dinner menu.
LANA: -- pounding two three-
hundred dollar bottles of
Glengoolie Frickin Blue --
ARCHER: Two? I ordered three...
LANA: -- then passing out
on the bed totally naked,
for a -- what'd you call it?
ARCHER: Power blackout.
And you're welcome.
LANA: Yeah thanks, the memory
of your bare ass will bring
me comfort and warmth during
the coming nuclear winter.
ARCHER: Relax, it's North Korea. The
nationstate equivalent of the short-bus.
LANA: Nice.
ARCHER: What's nice is this hot tub. Which
get in, before you blow our cover,
any more than you already have, by
not performing your wifely duties.
LANA: Excuse me?
MALORY: You said my card was used at the
Tuntmore Towers Hotel? This morning?
MALORY: Hm? Oh yes, I remember now. Yes,
yes, it's all fine, mmmmmkaybyebye.
I am literally
going to kill him.
GILLETTE: Well, figurative --
MALORY: Literally! I'll lure him to my condo
in Miami, drug his steak au poivre,
drive him out to the Everglades,
slather him with rancid chicken fat,
and then toss him to the gators!
RAY: Pretty specific for a hypothetical...
MALORY: Oh, he is going to pay
for this.
Literally.
Cyril? Cyril.
Ugh, fine! Then I'll do it!
PAM (O.S.): Are they doin it?!
Are they bangin?!
CYRIL: No, Pam, they
are not "bangin."
PAM: Well these ribs
sure as hell are.
CHERYL/CAROL: Oh my God, right?
We should take some
to the tigers!
PAM: And miss
these two doin it?
CHERYL/CAROL: Oh my God, right...
CYRIL: Will you hags stop it?! Look,
there's nothing going
on over there!
CHERYL/CAROL (O.S.): Unless she's
screaming at him to get it up.
CYRIL: She's not --
PAM: That's what she was screamin at you.
Okay, so I watched
the whole thing.
CYRIL: Ugh, were you
raised in a barn?!
PAM: No. I just slept
out there a lot.
LANA: Sooo, you got an ETA on when
you might possibly be ready to help?
ARCHER (O.S.): Hard to say, really...
ARCHER: Chi's taking her sweet time here.
Not criticizing,
thorough is good.
Look, just gimme ten -- Twenty minutes, and --
LANA: Archer? I don't know how
long the North Koreans will be out of
their room, so while you ladies discuss
the pros and cons of a clear coat --
ARCHER: You say that like there are cons.
LANA: I'll go be thorough at my job and
plant the Geiger counter, so we know
if and when the
uranium shows up.
ARCHER: Do you even know
if that thing works?
[beeping noises]
KRIEGER: Well, Pigley Three, that would
certainly explain the glowing...
And probably a few other things.
PIGLEY: Grunt.
LANA: Why do you let
him push your buttons?
Why not push his buttons? Because
he has no buttons. He's buttonless.
The only way to make him as crazy as he
makes you, is to... ha, ha, ha, haaaa.
PAM (O.S.): Seriously...
Who are you, Van Cliburn?
Knock off the tickling
and work that shit.
CHERYL/CAROL: Yeah, right?
A baby could -- unghh!
MASSEUR: I'm sorry, Miss Tunt!
Did that hurt?
CHERYL/CAROL: Yesss...
PAM: Cyril, they bangin yet?
CYRIL: Wh-? No! Actually, Archer's alone...
Lana's either in the bathroom or...
Oh my God! What --
ARCHER: The hell is this bullshit?!
CHI: What?! You say
you want clear coat!
LANA(O.S.): Yeah, why not?
I mean it's not like
it hasn't crossed your mind, and
you're not getting any younger, so --
ARCHER (O.S.): Lanaaa!
LANA: Jesus, what?!
Is it the Koreans?!
ARCHER: Only if they're who
screwed me out of my bonus!
[crunch]
Which would be weird!
LANA (O.S.): Your bonus?!
ARCHER: If you could
even call it that!
What's yours, is it shitty?! Go
online and check your bank account!
LANA: Now. When I'm suction
cupped on a window,
thirty stories above the ground.
ARCHER (O.S.): Yeah, you
should have five bars.
LANA: Okay so, it's gonna sound
like I'm hanging up? But -- [BEEP]
ARCHER: Lana. Lana!
Holy shit, I think
she's gone rogue!
But whoa, don't pack up. My toes
aren't gonna do themselves.
LANA: And even if you're not
necessarily doing it for the right
reasons, he's --
ARCHER (O.S.) Hey! Hey!
LANA: [weary sigh]
ARCHER: Phone, gimme!
LANA: Did you seriously climb all the way
up here just to see what my bonus is?
ARCHER: No, I sarcastically climbed all
the way up here to see what your bonus
is! He said, sarcastically!
Phone!
LANA: Okay, Jesus! Keep
your voice... Whoa.
ARCHER: Sucks, right? I mean that's not
even -- remotely fair! What the
shit?!
LANA: Apparently we're in a crazy
parallel universe, where bonuses are
based on merit instead of whether or
not you crawled out of your -- mother!
CYRIL: Lanaaa!
LANA: Archerrrrr!
ARCHER: I'm comiiiiing!
Phrasingboom!
Lanaaaa!
LANA: Aaaaaaaaagh! Wh-?!
ARCHER: Woooohoohoohooooo!
Ungh!
LANA: Oh my God... Archer... that was...
ARCHER: A ninety-dollar
manicure, I know.
And I couldn't care less, but Chi...
Lana, she worked really hard on it.
PAM: Oh man, they gotta
bump uglies now!
CYRIL: They -- wait, what?!
PAM: Cyril, a near-death experience
is like, the ultimate aphrodisiac!
CAROL/CHERYL: Penultimate. The
ultimate's doing it on top
of a tranqed up tiger.
LANA: So listen...
ARCHER: No you listen, and then shut up --
LANA: You shut up, I was on the verge of --
ARCHER: Dying.
LANA: Making a --
ARCHER: Stain on the sidewalk.
LANA: Decision! So --
ARCHER: So since we're keeping
score for bonus purposes, Lana!
In addition to saving your
life a gazillion times --
LANA: Your fault to begin with ARCHER:
Since I started working at ISIS, I've
been shot, stabbed, set on fire,
poisoned, shot, sexually assaulted,
partially chewed, shot, and declared legally dead!
Twice on the same day!
LANA: You said "shot"
like three times.
ARCHER: That's just by you!
Total it's more like... holy shit, nineteen!
And now you get your bonus and mine?!
LANA: Archer, I didn't --
ARCHER: Do anything to deserve it! Exactly!
LANA: And again, excuse me?
ARCHER: There is
no excuse for you.
LANA: Alrighty. Think
I made my decision.
MALORY: And it is final.
ARCHER (O.S.): Because I
borrowed your credit card?!
MALORY: You didn't
borrow it, you stole it!
ARCHER (O.S.): Little column A, little column --
MALORY: Be advised! That until
I say otherwise, Mister Stickyfingers...
ARCHER: Seriously, does this
never dry?
MALORY (O.S.): Lana is
now agent-in-command!
LANA: Wait, what?
ARCHER: Yeah hang on,
you're breaking up?
LANA: So, my first command, as
agent-IN-command, she said commandingly, is --
PAM (O.S.): Get in
my big ol vagina!
I'm Lana!
CYRIL: Okay, you know what?
ARCHER: I am outta here!
LANA: Oh my God, okay, you're abandoning
the mission to go home and pout?!
ARCHER: I'm not going home, I'm going
down there to kick some Kim Jong Ass!
LANA: Wh-? No! We're
doing surveillance!
ARCHER: Yeah, which is apparently French
for just sitting around on your ass!
LANA: Yeah, which is why it's
surprising that you're so shitty at it!
Wh-? No no no Archer don't --
[door slam]
LANA: Suck so hard! Rrrgh!
CYRIL: Okay, c'mon,
we're outta here.
PAM: What're you, nuts?
CHERYL/CAROL: Oh my God
there's nuts in this?!
PAM: Ugh, you're
allergic to penicillin.
CHERYL/CAROL: Oh right.
Aaand...
PAM: There's no
penicillin in this --
CHERYL/CAROL: Good,
cause I'm allergic.
PAM: -- because why the hell would there
be penicillin in chocolate mousse?
CHERYL/CAROL: God, gross!
There's moose in this?!
PAM: Not that kind of moose.
CHERYL/CAROL: Elk then, whatever, ugh...
CYRIL: Look, you two stay if
you want, I'm leaving. There's
no point spying on Lana,
because I trust her completely.
CHERYL/CAROL: And also because
they're not even in there anymore?
CYRIL: Little column
A, little column B.
LANA: You are not
jeopardizing this mission!
ARCHER: No yeah, that's
exactly what I'm doing.
LANA: Because your ego
needs its own zip code!
I meant I won't allow you!
ARCHER: Allow me?!
I mean please, allow me...
NORTH KOREAN AGENT: ISIS!
LANA: Unghh!
ARCHER: [chuckles]
LANA (O.S.): [moaning)
ARCHER: Wow, that's
gotta hurt, huh?
LANA: Archer...
ARCHER: No, obviously it hurts
getting Tom Dempsey'd in
the tits like that...
LANA: Archer.
ARCHER: But I meant watching
me save your ass for the
gazillion and one-th time.
LANA: Archer!
ARCHER: She's in command.
ARCHER (O.S.): Oh okay, so I guess
you think this is my fault.
LANA: You guess?
ARCHER: Well I'm not
a mindreader, Lana!
NORTH KOREAN BOSS: Silence!
We deal with you soon enough!
LANA: And by deal with, obviously, he means --
ARCHER: Shoot.
LANA: [SIGH]
ARCHER: I mean, I assume. And negativity
is infectious, by the way. You're the
agent-in-command, Lana, you should
be focused on keeping my morale --
LANA: Hi, excuse me? Could you go ahead
and shoot one or both of us now?
ARCHER: Also a good leader
is never sarcastic.
NORTH KOREAN BOSS: Oh, we don't shoot you!
After mission
finish, we take you back to glorious
Democratic People's Republic of Korea!
ARCHER: Oh, then do go
ahead and shoot us.
LANA: Archer!
ARCHER: What Lana, it's
none of those things!
Not democratic, not a republic, and
definitely not glorious! Jesus,
watch Frontline once in your life...
NORTH KOREAN BOSS: This ISIS camera, yes?
LANA: Uh...
ARCHER: Yes! And as all North Koreans know,
cameras steal your soul, so --
NORTH KOREAN BOSS: It is your
Indians who think that!
ARCHER: Wow, okay, so since
we're being racist...!
PAM (O.S.): Cyril!
Don't leave, it's on!
CYRIL: What do you...?
On as in how on?!
PAM: On as in on on.
CHERYL/CAROL (O.S.): On as in
"hot Asian group sex" on...
PAM: Thricely redundant...
CYRIL: Give me those!
[gasps]
Oh my God! We've
gotta do something!
[FRRRPT]
PAM: It's rosemary-mint.
LANA: Why? Why
did you say that?
ARCHER: To lure them closer.
LANA: Well it worked.
ARCHER: Yeah, they really hate the Japanese...
LANA: You better have a plan.
ARCHER: Me? Lana, you're
agent-in-command.
LANA: Archer?
ARCHER: No, I just don't wanna
step on your -- Toes!
NORTH KOREAN AGENT: Gaagh!
ARCHER: Nailed it boom!
LANA: How did you...?
ARCHER; Do you have any idea how many
times I've had to get out of handcuffs?!
ARCHER: Lana!
LANA: Whew! Well, thank God you've
been arrested so many times.
ARCHER: Arrested?
LANA: I -- look, whatever, thanks,
that was actually pretty impressive.
ARCHER: Well not really, I thought
this was the door to the hallway.
LANA: Sooo...
ARCHER: Do you think there's thirty
stories' worth of towels in here?
NORTH KOREANS (O.S.):
[angry shouting]
CYRIL: C'mon Figgis, Lana's in trouble,
so you just gotta man up and... ooh!
PAM (O.S.): Aw, man... am I missing
all the hot Asian group action?
CHERYL/CAROL: No, nobody's doing anything...
Well, Lana's destroying the
toilet.
PAM: Join the club...
CHERYL/CAROL: That's what you get for eating elk.
LANA: [grunts]
ARCHER (O.S.): Uh, couple things...
One, we've got about thirty seconds
before the door is matchsticks. Two,
you're never gonna break that win --
[SMASH!]
LANA: What was that? I couldn't hear
you over the sound of your wrongness.
ARCHER: It's okay, I'll skip ahead
to three, which is now what, idiot?!
Because I left my jetpack
in my other pants!
LANA: I -- we can signal to somebody or--
ARCHER: Like who, a blimp captain?!
LANA: No, like -- holy
shit, is that Cheryl?
ARCHER: What the hell's she doin--
CYRIL (O.S.): Suppressing fire
Extinguisher!!
ARCHER: Is that --
LANA: Cyril?!
CYRIL (O.S.): Lanaaaaaaaaa!
LANA: I'm coming, Cyril!
ARCHER: Lana wait!
Bet that's the first time
you ever said that. Right?
Okay, now we can go.
LANA: Ya know...?
ARCHER: Go!
LANA: Rrrgh!
ARCHER: What the --
LANA: Cyril!
ARCHER: Smoke fiiiiight!
Woohoohoohooooo!
CHERYL/CAROL: Ugh, no
way, that is so unfair!
PAM (O.S.): What,
are they bangin?!
CHERYL/CAROL: They will be...
Raves make everybody horny.
LANA: [fighting sounds]
ARCHER: And that! Is for ruining!
My fake honeymoon!
CYRIL: Ungh! Oof!
Archer wait, it's me!
ARCHER: I know!
ARCHER: Oof! And this
is for the Pueblo!
LANA: Cyril, hit the deck!
ARCHER (O.S.): Wait, why just Cyri--
LANA: Get some you sons of
bitches. Get some!
PAM: Aw man, I totally missed it...
CHERYL/CAROL: Oh my God, the toilet?!
PAM: No! Jesus.
Although it is clogged.
CYRIL: Wow, Lana, that was...
ARCHER: Right? Totally passive-aggressive.
LANA: No, that was
active-aggressive!
Because you ruined the mission!
CYRIL: Yeah, you jerk.
LANA: And why the
hell are you here?!
CYRIL: Uh, police scanner?!
LANA: Cyril.
CYRIL: Well, ya know, I mean you two,
all alone in the honeymoon suite...
LANA: Oh my God.
ARCHER: [chuckling]
LANA: Well you can forget about the huge
decision I made, that you know nothing
about, because I
just unmade it.
CYRIL: I -- What was
that all about?
ARCHER: Ohh, wouldn't you like to know...
CYRIL: Do you?
ARCHER: No.
LANA (O.S.): Malory,
you cannot be serious!
MALORY: I know, I'm sorry, it's because
I use humor as a coping mechanism.
LANA: I meant --
MALORY: And so, while I think it's hilarious
that your bonuses will now be used to
pay this ridiculous hotel bill...
Which somebody could make go away
with a snap of her bony fingers!
CHERYL/CAROL (O.S.): Ugh!
I told you, I have to answer
to my board of directors!
I don't, at all.
PAM: Do you even
know what that is?
CHERYL/CAROL: I don't, at all.
MALORY: I just can't seem to
find the humor in what should
have been a simple mission
turning into a total farce!
LANA: It wasn't --
ARCHER: Lana. It was by definition a farce.
MALORY: Capped off by the fact
that no one thought to stick
around and catch the madman
selling the uranium!
ARCHER: Lana was in command.
MALORY: Yes, was.
LANA: (sigh)
ARCHER: [chuckling]
MALORY: Lucky for the madman.
Whoever he was...
KRIEGER: Aww, maaaan...
Well there goes my master plan!
Yeah, get in there, eat 'em up.
God knows you earned it.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com | Sync to web-dl by aneurysm