And that's your message?
My god, who...
Who's there?!
What do you want?!
Because all you're
gonna get is holes!
I-I mean holes in you, not my...
sterling?
Hello, mother.
Where the hell have you been?!
I don't know.
Wh-- and why do you
have a cleaver?!
"All interoffice
fraternization of an intimate
Nature is hereby prohibited,
to include, but not limited to,
Trysts, assignations -
-" What's this even mean?
It means no more
banging co-workers.
Oh, so it doesn't affect you...
Oh, wait. Guess what.
Hey, this isn't my fault!
It's exactly your fault, idiot.
When mother found out
you cheated on lana --
Hey, you cheated on lana plenty!
Yeah, but with starlets, models.
Oh, and one time,
two actual princesses.
Two at the same time?
Yeah, they were sisters. Sploosh.
Cyril, you threw lana
Away on chicks like -- like carol.
it's cheryl. archer: Exactly.
Back me up here.
You slept with her, too!
When I was bored.
Like, stuck at home, waiting for
The cable guy, or -- oh, hey,
What you doing Thursday
between 00 and noon?
1:00 and 4:00?
I'll be doing one
of your co-workers.
Well, do it before
quitting time Friday!
Why would ms.
Archer give us until Friday?
I did that, because
somebody in this building is
Gonna have sex with me.
Yeah?
You think between now and friday,
you can score some roofies?
Uh, pam, I will end you.
Where the hell is my staple gun?!
I think I saw cyril with it.
He went through my desk?!
I guess. I mean, he said he did.
Oh, I don't know why i'm surprised.
I mean, can you believe him,
cheating on lana?
Baffling. Said the kettle!
Which is why I started
that new policy.
Yeah? You idiots run around
Here like it's spring
break on south padre.
Just sex, sex, sex...
Sexy, sexy, eh?
Nikolai?! Is from
frederick's of latvia.
Mother! Oh, hello, son.
What?! Nikolai...
Why did he just call me son?!
Nikolai. What is this?!
You mean besides
incredibly awkward?
No, I think "Incredibly
awkward" Just about sums it up.
W-- mother!
Nikolai, could I call you back?
Da. I will be here maybe one hour.
Mother! jakov:
Then I try to hit gym.
The gym. That'll be the day.
Are you out of your mind?!
I must be, because it looks
like you just destroyed my
Steuben bar set!
Well, you just
destroyed my innocence!
Oh, please.
That brazilian au pair did
that when you were 13!
12! And why does nikolai jakov, the
Head of the kgb, have a
direct line to your office?!
Well, you know, from time to time -
no, just leave that.
You'll cut yours-- sterling!
And a follow-up question!
Why did he just call me son?!
That's...Often a figure of speech.
Yeah?! How often?!
Very often.
Just not in this case.
I know what --
What?
Terrific.
Two steuben glasses left,
and you break one.
I'm sorry, krieger, but it's over,
so here's all your
Creedence clearwater albums back.
And now a sad moon is on the rise.
I know. Devastating.
But it's not you,
it's your weak, womany hands.
They're not -
it's like being choked by a
Child, which I thought
would be hot, but --
Wait. No. I'll take steroids.
I can't wait. I need a man
now with monster hands.
Oh, like lan-- ah! Hey, you!
You know, the whole
monster-hands thing -- starting
To border on mean.
oh, you gonna run
cry to ms. Archer,
like when cyril Cheated on you?
Hello.
Well, at least my
ex-boyfriend isn't a noose I
Made out of extension cord.
guess what. She wasn't the
only one cyril cheated with.
And what is that supposed to mean?
figure it out, truckasaurus.
Oh, that gives me an idea.
But I already have a father!
His name was john
fitzgerald archer, and he
Was a fighter ace and he won the
Navy cross and his
men called him --
"Black jack" Archer.
I know, dear, I know.
Because I made it all up.
But the military funeral!
ready!
Oh, my god.
If we miss that train,
I will go blind.
fire!
But the 21-gun salute!
I donated 600 bucks
To a junior rotc
team up in yonkers.
What? Which they used to go
to a competition in albany,
Where they won third place!
What? malory: So a lot
of good came out of that.
Oh, so, all's well that ends well?!
What was I to do?
Tell a 3-year-old his
father might be in the kgb?!
What?! What do you mean, might be?!
So, there may or may not be a
few other possibles in the mix.
What?
Seriously?
You cheated on me with carol?!
cheryl! Exactly.
And I can explain that.
Well, if you'd let me!
Yeah, tell me how my father
might be nikolai jakov,
Head of the kgb,
or len trexler, head of odin!
I assume those are my only choices!
Oh, my -- who else?!
Gene krupa.
What?! The drummer?! No,
wait, not krupa.
The other one, with the teeth.
Buddy rich.
Oh, my -- i could never
say no to a drummer.
Could you say no to anybody?!
I said no to plenty.
No. No. Yes. Have sex with me.
No. Please? No.
Oh, come on!
Nobody would ever know!
Yeah. I'd know.
No! Da!
No! jakov: Let me talk to him!
No! jakov: Kroshka.
Nikolai, he's not even here.
He stormed out, thanks to you!
But I could talk sense into him!
After all, I am his father.
Oh. So...
Len trexler or buddy rich?!
Get me that crazy german! Now!
Hostile work environment.
jakov: Shut up!
We're going to kidnap
agent sterling archer.
oh, yeah, then what?
You hurt his feelings?
Nyet! Then we put new mind-control
Microchip into his brain.
We use its remote-control
capability to bring him here,
Make the papa test.
And if I am archer's father, I
Turn him against his own
mother as soviet agent.
Make him a, how you say, vole.
I think you mean "Mole."
mole.
Vole is also rodent but more
closer related to lemming.
Ah, da, da, da.
Come on, buddy.
Can't you read, ass douche?!
You're not supposed to
be here without a kid!
as it happens,
I am here with a child.
mani, can we have more
money for the sweets?
What?! That's not even a real baby!
Und that is?
I thought you were
Off to the fair mit
your prize turnip!
Listen, you kraut puke!
Hallo? Oh, ja.
You should go.
Oh, you're lucky his
father's not here.
He knows krav maga!
He'll kick your balls right
through your head, nazi shit-ass!
Mani, these peoples!
Well, you wanted him
to grow up in the city.
Oh, scheisse! Nein, major, not you!
Ja, listening.
And after you take archer to the...
...Kgb safe house on gansevoort,
You will implant the
microchip into his brain.
Got it.
Ja, seriously.
Okay, uta, we have a job, so --
W-where is the diaper bag?
I forgot where I put it.
huge surprise.
Idiot!
What is wrong with you?!
And just who the happy
hell do you think you
Are, hanging up on me?!
Oh! You gonna tell your boyfriend,
len trexler, or
Maybe gene krupa?!
It was the other one!
Maybe. Or you, maybe, or -- whoever
It was, he wasn't there to raise
Sterling, so I don't
need him butting in now!
We'll see. What?
Nothing. Nikolai,
what are you scheming at?!
Nothing. Again he hangs up on me!
And there goes the last steuben.
sploosh!
Yes. that's what I'm talkin' about!
Yep, yep, yep.
wait...You think it's safe?
No.
Okay, we got the french
Chick and carol and
anybody else, rambone?
No. Hi, cyril.
Scatterbrain jane?! Really?!
Well, see, she had just been
diagnosed with breast cancer.
oh, right!
I forgot, your dick's
full of radiation and...
Mastectomy coupons.
Boy, you are just so determined
not to be cool about this.
Yep. Anybody else?
Ms. Archer, you're
trying to seduce me.
Aren't you?
Nope! lan okay.
No. No one. lana: Okay, get out.
Of...My own office?
Yep. cyril: Why?
Oh, you don't want to be here...
When I bang every last
Dude in the building.
Whaty. lana:
Right here on your blotter.
No! lana: Yep.
You can't do that! lana: Really?
Is it opposite day already?
Uh, attention?
Hi, this is agent kane, and if
You want to have ball-slappy sex
With me on cyril's desk, please
Line up and take a number.
You heard the lady!
Take a number!
86'ed?!
Unh-unh! You don't 86 me!
'cause my dad won the navy cross!
Use the door!
Help! Please help me!
My baby! He's swallowed something!
He's choking!
Uh, who gives a shit about a baby?
Who would want to
raise a child here?
Well, that was a
huge waste of time.
I said, don't take
your clothes off.
Well... Begged, even.
Well! This is good to go.
So was this.
So, let's get number 2 in here.
You really think
this is gonna work?
Pam, look at me.
Yeah...Sploosh.
Now serving number 2!
I'm 2!
That's me! Move, dude!
Animals!
You're all just animals!
Lying in wait at
The watering hole,
taut buttocks all aquiver...
What the... gillette:...
Aching to pounce
On the supple,
brown flesh of your woman.
Shut up! gillette:
They're gonna mess her up.
Why are you even here?
gillette: Hello...
But you're gay! gillette:
Girl, please.
Nobody's that gay.
Wait. What? What, what?
What part of "You pay
me $600" do you not get?
The...Part where we don't have sex?
You get to say we did,
Which is like half the
reason men have sex!
But that's a lot of money.
Not compared to
rotator-cuff surgery.
What? Which you're gonna need
After the jillion high-fives you
Give your little bros.
Okay, I'm in! But the first guy you
Tell is cyril,
and you make up the sickest --
Yeah, shut up. Do you take plastic?
5% discount for cash.
I thought it was 10%.
I can't wet my beak?!
Hey, seriously,
Kidnappers, super not in the
mood for this right now.
Or that. What is that?
Is that a drill?
Okay. I don't want that.
Okay, so, I make a
Klein hole in the skull mit this.
You can shut that off.
Then, into the hole, i smoosh this.
What is that? manfred:
Und then they can
Control his brain.
But is soviet technology,
so it's a "Kreppenschutze."
This is amazing, no?
What is amazing is
We just ran into him on the street.
Hey. manfred: It's a huge city.
Hey, proposition!
First person to untie me, guy or
Gal, I will let him or
her give me a handy.
Come on, let's share the
lkma of hu n kindness!
What an arsch hole! Come on.
Don't worry, your time is coming.
Wait? My time? Do you mean me?
And by "Don't worry,"
Do you mean the chick's
gonna be doing the handy?
And either way, can we
do it without that thing?
Hey, seriously.
Give me a hanjo.
It doesn't work.
I drill hole in head of
man who maybe is my son,
put chip in his brain,
and now you tell me it doesn't work.
you should have asked
me before, you...
See, in testing we have had
Teensy problem with signal from
Satellite.
When it is in small window, just
Over the target, it can signal
The chip.
but when it exits this
Window...
This problem does not
Sound teensy!
it is, compared to the
Problem we had with interference
From cellphones.
...Which, in lab, sent our
Subjects into ferocious,
Homicidal rages.
So, obviously, we need to tweak it.
Damn that crazy, jealous russian.
Bet he's hatching some
Half-assed,
vodka-soaked scheme to --
Hello? Sterling?
Sterling, listen very -
ha! Voicemail.
You know what to do. What?
we're sorry... Damn it!
Carol? Carol!
And just where the hell is she?!
krieger! Aah!
Oh! Oh, god, sorry!
Sorry. what are you doing?!
I thought you said,
"Start slacking off."
not "Slacking off"!
Dude, swear to god,
She gave me a jane hathaway,
right on my chest!
My man knows what
I'm talkin' about!
Doesn't anyone work around here?!
And, cyril, I am so disgusted
With you right now,
I just want to vomit.
That's exactly what I said to lana.
37?
Ooh! C'est moi.
move.
Just get it done by Friday.
Oh, come on, sterling,
pick up, pick --
Sterling? archer: Hello?
Sterling, what's wrong?
Are you -- alternate voicemail.
You know what to do, stupid.
we're sorry, the number...
malory: I'm done.
He's dead to me.
"Mother."
Ubil...Mat.
Kill...Mother.
Oh, my god, I'm exhausted.
Whereas I am merely confused.
If you told every
guy the same thing,
then they all know that none
of them had sex with you,
so they're all gonna
realize they're all lying.
Hey, yeah.
Wait a minute.
But, remember, they're s.S.
what? brett: Um,
I had sex with lana.
me too.
Lana kane, you magnificent bastard.
I just hope cyril doesn't,
like, snap.
cyril? Snap?
Snap. P girl,lease...
7...6...2...
Millimeter...Full metal jacket.
Someone's in here!
Holy shit snacks!
You made over 20 grand!
Minus my 60 bucks.
Plus cyril's broken heart.
Not too shabs, pam.
Are you kidding?!
36 guys?!
It's like "Schindler's
list" Up in here!
pam! And I'm like that little
Gandhi dude, helping out
with the books, and the --
Inappropriate analogies!
What the hell is wrong with you?!
nothing!
I'm a desirable, full-bodied
Woman, but nobody
will have sex with me!
And I have so much love to give!
Get on the desk. Really?!
Yeah, come on, before I
Change my mind,
but you cannot say a word.
I won't tell anybody!
No, honey, I mean during,
cause I'm gonna pretend
You're alex karras.
And that's your message?
My god, who...
Who's there?!
What do you want?!
Because all you're
gonna get is holes!
I-I mean holes in you, not my...
Sterling?
Hello, mother.
Where the hell have you been?!
I don't know.
Wh-- and why do you
have a cleaver?!
I don't know.
Well, you're safe now...
So get out.
I'm hungry. So lick that coat!
You smell like a -- grilled cheese.
What? Grill me a cheese.
I'm not grilling you a cheese!
Oh, for god's sake.
Waltz in here, dressed like
some sort of cattle rapist,
waving a cleaver and reeking
of what I hope to god is meat,
and that's all you have to say?
I don't know. I was worried sick.
Called you twice, came this
close to leaving -- and why
Doesn't your voicemail just say
"Leave a message, I'm a jackass"?
I don't know.
I don't know, I don't know.
What is wrong with you?
My head hurts!
And I have no father!
Sterling, of course you
have a father, just maybe
Not the one you wanted.
And you! Irnd me neither!
Because even though
that whole weekend
is just a big jazzy blur,
I'm pretty sure it wasn't buddy.
all these years, you lied to me!
I -- sterling,
I was protecting you!
From what, this sandwich?!
This is swiss, mother!
Because that's all i had, you ass!
Just like I'm all that you have!
Well, I hate it! And I hate you!
Sterling malory archer,
you will eat every last
Crumb of that sandwich.
No! malory: Then get out.
I'll call you a cab.
What? Sterling,
stop that this instant!
Ubil mat!
Kill mother.
Kill mother!
Police, police.
Have to call the -- aah!
I'm having a nightmare,
and you lock me out of your bedroom?!
Sterling, no! Stay back!
Only this time,
you'll be crying for help, and
I'll be the one drinking
and laughing in there with
Uncle buddy!
Sterling, I'm warning you!
Sterling!
Sterling?
sterling?
Sterling!
What?! God!
Well, whose fault is that?
Waving a cleaver,
screaming in russian?
I'm sorry. malory: Ass.
Seriously, I don't know
what's going on with my head.
Filthy coat.
Can't tell what's cow's
blood and what's yours.
The wet blood, mother, is mine!
And it's ruining my
brand-new linens!
Sorry! malory: This is why
I can't have nice things.
Why, because you shoot them?
Serves you right.
You nearly scared me to death!
Well, you obviously
weren't that scared,
judging by your grouping.
Hah! Guess the old
gal's still got it.
All 6, right in the
10 ring. Hooray.
Just like I taught you,
without any help from...
Whoever your father is.
Yeah, you were always there for me,
which I never really thank you for.
Sterling, I don't need thanks.
That's what makes me
such a wonderful mother.
Are you kidding? Don't be shitty!
Can't we just enjoy the moment?
Yeah, how could we not?
Ass.
Sync by YYeTs.net
Transcript by Addic7ed.com