FARGO.
All new Wednesdays at 10:00.
Starts April 19 on FX.
Woman: Son of a bitch!
Woman (Announcing):
FXX presents Archer.
So, what are we doing?
Are we just jumping
right into this, or...
- Not literally, you ass!
- Ow! Ow! Will you...
- You scared me half to death!
- Ow! Damn it!
- You idiot!
- Ow! Stop it!
What is your... ow!
(Huffs)
I would like a drink, please.
Ow. Join this
great new club.
Brandy, if you have it.
Fresh out, turns out.
Good lord. You should have
your underbutler fire
the housekeeper.
Yeah, maybe after he's done
getting the caviar stains
out of my spats.
I was being facetious,
Mr. Archer.
- I...
- I know you're poor.
- Well, middle class.
- This cannot be the middle.
- Look, Miss...
- Vandertunt.
Heiress to the vast vandertunt
publishing fortune.
Right.
So, I've had a long day.
(Gulping)
(Gulping continues)
My partner was murdered.
My office was burgled.
I pissed off two crime bosses
and a dirty cop,
and crushed the ankles
of a psychopath who,
just for kicks, melts people.
So, as much as I would
genuinely like to,
I'm afraid I don't
have time to kill you.
You misunderstand me,
Mr. Archer.
I want you to help me
fake my death.
For which I am prepared
to offer you $10,000.
Oh.
And my body.
The ten grand is plenty.
I'm afraid
this is nonnegotiable.
(Breathily)
Do your worst.
(Chuckles)
I will.
♪ (Jazzy theme) ♪
*ARCHER*
Season 08 Episode 02
"Archer Dreamland: Bernice"
(scoffs) So, when I said,
"Do your worst"...
(Chuckling)
I-I know. Sorry. Long day.
Uh, plus my ear hurts?
(Gasps)
(Singsongy)
I have codeine!
Because heirs to fortunes
like your family's
don't fake their own deaths.
They murder their parents
and blame it on some poor
hispanic or negro.
Yes, I thought about that,
but I don't know
any hispanics or negroes.
No, they make up
the hispanic or negro.
I honestly wouldn't know
where to begin.
Okay, but...
Boy, these are good.
- Mmm! Aren't they?
- Zesty.
But putting aside, for now,
why you'd want to fake
your own death...
Because I have to
get away from my family.
They're a seething cauldron
of neurotic, alcoholic,
narcissistic, quasi-incestuous
megalomaniacs!
How quasi?
(Sighs)
I don't know. A four?
Out of what? Are you
going to help me or not?
I... look, I really don't think
you've thought this thing
through.
Mm. For starters,
even if you pull this off,
what are you gonna do for money?
Well, I...
I shall work, of course.
(Chuckles)
As what?
Uh, one of those.
A... food-perambulator.
Well, my apologies.
I thought you were
heading into this
half-cocked.
- Said the pot to the kettle.(Giggles)
- My ear hurt!
You're not some runaway kid
whose family couldn't
care less she's gone.
They're gonna
be looking for yourself.
So, to make this work,
you'd need a body.
And not just any body.
A body your same size,
same height and weight, your
same general bone structure.
A body... I mean,
if you're gonna do
what has to be done here,
a body with your exact same
dental records. (Squealing)
- (Laughing giddily)
- Who is that?
I don't know! (Laughs)
- I mean, obviously she's a maid.
- Really.
- I just don't know her name, because...
- She's a maid?
Obviously.
Did you kill her?
Wha... no! Jesus!
(Scoffs)
My brother did.
(Exhales)
Well, technically, I suppose
the drunken abortionist did.
But my brother got her pregnant
in the first place.
And my father
would've killed her
if she had refused
to get an abortion, so...
- But, I mean, not really?
- Really.
Why do you think
my father started
the Spanish-American war?
- Wasn't it sugar?
- He got my aunt pregnant.
- And sugar?
- I guess. I don't know. Shut up!
(Sighs) The point is,
this poor girl was dead
- the minute her panties hit the straw.
- The...
- In the stables.
- Ah.
- But want to know the best part?
- That wasn't it?
- Look!
- What are you... Uh, no, don't...
Not one cavity, not one filling!
- Since when and how do you know that?
- Don't you see?
Her teeth are perfect.
My teeth are perfect.
Ergo, this plan is perfect!
I mean, dentally, maybe,
but if she just disappears?
Think of her family.
Do you think I haven't?
- Yes.
- What?
I think you haven't.
(Sighs)
If you help me do this,
I'll make an anonymous payment
to her family
for an additional $10,000.
Um, how does that
bring them closure?
(Scoffs) It comes with a note
saying she's dead.
Look, nothing we can do
will bring
this poor girl back to life.
- I know, but...
- Not even a voodoo priestess,
flown here from Haiti
at great expense,
and then every year,
on grandma's birthday,
- they throw it your face!
- Uh...
So the best thing we can do now
is to fill this car
to the rafters with dynamite
and shove it over a cliff.
(Chuckles)
Ah! That is literally
the worst thing we can do.
Oh, right. (Sighs)
Dynamite would blow her teeth
all over the stupid beach.
- Well, and...
- And then what's the point?
(Crunching)
Exactly.
Archer: So we'll fake
the crash tonight,
but first we're gonna plant
a few seeds.
(Scoffs) First of all,
if I wanted your seed...
Seeds of deception.
Oh, sorry.
I thought you meant...
I know what you meant.
What in god's name
are you doing?
- Scrooching down.
- Well, stop it!
- Stop that this instant!
- You stop...
Shut up. I don't want anybody
in dreamland to see me.
Well, I don't want
anyone to see me
being chauffeured by a dwarf!
Yeah. Then we'd have to
find a dead dwarf
and a tiny chauffeur uniform.
- Why?
- To... oh, never mind.
But she can't be
dressed like a maid,
so we need to put her
in your clothes.
(Gasps) Right! Then we should
go to my hotel.
Which is...
- Nice?
- Where...
Oh!
Is your hotel?
The chesley, on sunset. That
wasn't so hard, was it?
(Snorting chuckle)
That's what I said.
(Guffawing)
(Groans)
(Dutch crying)
Trexler:
Hey, hey, hey, hey. Come on.
Where's my tough guy?
Huh?
Where's my tough old Dutch?
(Sniffles)
There he is.
Huh? Now listen.
(Sniffles)
Shut up and listen to me, okay?
Because I know...
(Stifled sob)
I know this isn't,
you know, ideal,
but you got to
pull yourself together!
(Sobbing)
No, no. I'm sorry.
That was a poor choice of words,
but for Christ's sake, man.
There's two dead men
walking around there
who stole from me...
(Crying softly)
I.E., my whores, and from you,
I.E., your feet!
And you are gonna find them,
and you are gonna
bring them to me,
and then I'm gonna
make them wish
they were in hell
with a case of the clap!
How can I?
(Sniffles)
They took my feet, Lenny.
They took my (Sobbing)
Fee-ee-ee-ee-eet!
(Sniffles)
Ow.
- Ow!
- Shut up.
(Dial tone)
Sorry.
I don't pay you to be sorry.
I pay you to make
other people sorry.
Now here.
(Line ringing)
Do what he tells you.
What who tells me?
The guy that's gonna fix you.
Man: Hello?
(Speaking German)
- Archer: What?
- Cheryl: Absolutely not!
- Archer: Why not?
- I'm not gonna stuff
that poor girl into my clothes,
in the trunk of a car,
like so much...
Forcemeat!
- So much what?
- Forcemeat. Such as one might find
in a quenelle, roulade,
or galantine.
(Scoffs) Well, now you're
just being obtuse.
- I'm being obtuse?
- Yes.
As opposed to you,
who wants to parade
a corpse through a hotel lobby
just so you can dress her
in your room?
Well, I'd hardly
call this a parade.
Man: Oh, good morning,
Miss Vandertunt. (Gasps)
Can I... help you?
No. We're fine.
No, thank you.
My maid, whose name is, um...
Bernice?
Somewhat obviously.
Bernice! Yes, Bernice.
And she was dead drunk
in a nearby saloon.
Poor thing.
(Chuckles)
The curse of the Irish,
and so forth.
Ah, jeez.
Well, let's get her inside.
No! Oh, no.
Thank you. Thank you.
- No. We'll use this one.
- No, no, no.
- That... that one's good.
- Let's... No, this one!
No! We are not
going through
a revolving door with Bernice.
But it wastes so much
less air conditioning
than a regular door.
The regular door
is wide-ass open!
Oh, right.
Well, then, what's the point?
Exactly.
(Bell dings)
Honestly,
I don't know why
you're so angry.
Which I think is why I'm so angry.
(Bell dings)
- And I can see why you would be.
- Trexler: Oh, yeah?
I mean, you don't think
I'm being unreasonable?
No! I mean, no.. I mean...
Because not only
did I pay a lot of money
for those magical
disappearing whores,
I also paid you a lot of money.
Well, yes, but that was...
I mean, that was more
to look the other way, so...
Figuratively!
Not literally,
while those assholes
were taking my load!
(Clears throat)
Do you have a cat?
I smell dander.
Now, you listen to me,
figgis, you schnorrer.
You're gonna find my whores,
and you are gonna find
the bastards who took my whores,
and crippled
my right-hand man, or...
Or... I'm just
spit-balling here...
what if I just gave you
back the money?
Because I do not want the money!
That is why I exchanged the
money for goods and/or services,
which is the core concept
of economics.
Isn't it sugar?
Or, like, scarcity...
of sugar?
You got one week, figgis.
Or else.
Wow. Goosebumps.
Cyril: A week?
How in the risen Christ am I supposed
to find them in a week? I...
I don't even know where to think
about thinking to start looking!
(Chattering in Chinese)
Okay, okay! Okay!
Okay! Goddamn it!
(Chattering stops)
Okay. I got to go to work,
but I'll be back tonight.
And when I get back, I
wouldn't mind if the place
smelled like lemon pledge
and orange chicken.
Mm, maybe Chinatown?
Oh, yeah. Hey, and while we're
at it, why not regular China?
Or maybe sarcastic island,
off the coast of
that was uncalled for.
- Will you shut up?
- Gladly.
And then ask yourself...
Cui bono?
Archer: What?
I said, "why was your
office ransacked?"
Because somebody
killed my partner
and he left an envelope
full of clues in the safe.
Why on earth would he do that?
What? No, not the killer, my...
And what on earth are you doing?
Trying to offset
some of the blue.
She looks like
a-a rodeo clown.
You've clearly
never been to a rodeo.
Must you rob this poor girl
of her very last
shred of dignity?
You did that! You did that when
you stuffed her in the trunk
of your Rolls-Royce,
you spoiled little...
(Muffled grunting)
- Wait. Really?
- Mm!
Oh...
Okay.
(Muffled grunting)
(Zipper unzips)
Oh! Cover her face.
(Chuckles)
Wait, what?
I don't want her watching us.
(Chuckles)
Oh. Okay.
So...
Why did someone
murder your partner?
That's what I'm trying
to find out.
Really? I would
think who
- is much more important than why.
- I...
Because if you found
out who killed him,
you could make them
tell you why.
Wow, you're
a regular monsieur...
And last night,
whoever, or whoevers,
broke into your office
presumably knew
you'd be elsewhere.
- I... huh?
- So,
who knew you wouldn't be there?
Well, I mean, it was late
at night. There was no reason
for anybody to think
I would be at the office, so...
Pam: You lost me.
Cyril:
"Cui bono," you dummy. It's Latin.
It means "To whose profit."
So?
So, who knew you
wouldn't be there?
So, you big ox,
when Trexler loses...
Who gains?
Cheryl: Oh, come now.
Don't be such a pout.
I think getting Bernice
through the lobby
went about as well
as could reasonably be expected.
(Clattering)
(Barking)
(Groaning)
(Clears throat)
Sorry.
- Besides,
- if... If you don't shut your fat mouth,
it's gonna be you going
over that goddamn cliff
instead of Bernice!
Please!
Then you'd never get paid.
(Tires screech)
It would be worth it.
What's this?
Why have we stopped?
To get some answers.
I won't be long. Stay here.
I shall do nothing of the sort.
(Sighs)
Of course you shalln't.
Why, the very idea...
sitting in a car in the street
like some sort of...
- Dirty cop.
- Well, or any tradesman, really.
- Oh!
- I need you to stop talking.
And when we get in there,
I need you to continue
to stop talking to anybody.
You're hurting me!
(Whimpers)
And it's the highlight
of my day.
(Exclaims in German)
(Speaking German)
- Archer: Do what?
- What?
- What do you want?
- Couple minutes with Mother.
- (Scoffs) Knock yourself out.
Well, I'm sorry
I can't be of more help
to you, lieutenant, but...
"Can't" and "won't"
are two very different things,
Mother.
And yet the end result
is still the same.
Why, Mr. Archer.
- Mother.
- Archer.
- Figgis.
Poovey.
You look like shit.
(Sighs)
Couldn't sleep.
- Noisy house guests.
- What do you mean, "House guests"?
(Chuckles) Wouldn't they be cave guests?
♪ ♪ (Rimshot)
(Man) Stop it! What are
you doing here, anyway?
I heard they did
a nice wedge salad.
Ooh.
We don't.
Aw. And now that
we've settled that,
if you two
will please excuse us?
Okay, Mother,
but remember what I told you.
Remember what I told you.
(Snickers, sniffs)
It is just dandertown frolics.
Move, dick!
Slang for "detective,"
so not an insult!
What is insulting is that you've
kept me waiting for ten hours.
I... sorry.
I've had a busy day.
Malory: I'll bet. I've had
quite a busy day myself
trying to shut down rumors
I had anything to do with
that bloodbath
down in long beach.
I wouldn't say
"Bloodbath."
No, although, now that
I come to think of it,
the easiest thing
would be to just
tell Len Trexler it was you.
That would be pretty easy.
But I have another job for you.
Great. Come back at midnight.
I'll give you the details.
- And don't be late again.
- Um, okay.
- Anything else?
- Well, uh,
it's just that
while I was down in Long Beach,
somebody broke into my office
and tossed the place.
And? And, well, I
mean, it's just,
not many people knew
I wouldn't be there.
In your office, late at night.
- Yes.
- And?
And I will see you at midnight.
No, it's just, what's
a society dame like you
doing in a place like this?
Leaving it. Let's go.
- Wha... rude!
- Bernice is waiting.
Oh, right.
(Gasps)
Miss Kane!
Archer.
Wow. Fancy meeting
you here, huh?
At my job? Yeah. I mean,
what are the odds?
- One to one?
- Yeah. I don't know. Maybe.
So, um...
Yeah. So, uh, okay.
See... see you
around, or...
(Gasps) Oh, my God!
You have a crush on her!
What? No I don't. I...
Yes, you do!
That was the cutest thing!
And I think she has
a crush on you.
- No, she.. Wait. Really?
- Absolutely!
Why-Why... Why do you
think that? Did she...
Just admit that you like her.
- Well, yeah. I mean, of course I..
- Hey! Yeah.
Me and him?
We just (Bleep)!
What is wrong with you?
Well, for one thing,
I may be literally
starving to death.
- (Gasps) Clams!
- What?
Oh, we should stop
for fried clams
at one of those
darling little shacks.
Archer: We're not
stopping for fried clams.
There is a dead woman
in the trunk!
Well, obviously, I meant after.
Also, I think
we're being followed.
What? We're not
being followed.
There aren't any headlights
back there.
I think their headlights are off.
No, they're not,
because it's pitch dark and
we're not being followed!
- I think we're being followed.
- We're not being followed!
And also, how have you
not been murdered?
I think we're being f...
(Tires screech)
We are not being followed!
I am a trained
private investigator!
If we were being followed,
I would know it!
- Fine. Then drive.
- Actually, we're here.
(Trunk opens)
Sorry, Bernice.
Won't be long.
Okay. So, I'm gonna soak
the upholstery with gas,
set a 20-second
cordite fuse,
then we'll put Bernice
in the driver's seat,
jam a rock on the accelerator,
light the fuse,
and then slam it into... oh!
(Cheryl screams)
Archer!
(Groaning)
(Shushing)
(Groaning continues)
Shh!
(Speaking French)
Wha...
(Mutters)
(Woman screaming)
(Man yelling)
Sorry!
Our headlights don't work!
(Cackles)
So, you're just
straight-up crazy.
(Blows raspberry)
Ow. (Groans)
Well?
Are we doing this or what?
Because if I don't
get some clams soon,
I won't be responsible
for my actions.
What? I told you
we were being followed.
(Grunts) That was just a car
with broken headlights.
It was a coincidence.
(Grunts)
Because we weren't
being followed!
(Sighs)
Goddamn it.
Hello!
♪ (Jazz) ♪
Sync corrections - by srjanapala
Man:
Made in Georgia.
Man: Dateline,
Los Angeles, California, 1947.
Menu rumors cause confusion
at local nightclub.
What are you doing here anyway?
I heard they did a nice wedge salad.
- Ooh!
- We don't.
Aw.
Archer: Dreamland.
All new Wednesdays at 10:00.
On FXX.
Announcer: The Americans.
All new Tuesdays at 10:00.
On FX.
(Squeaking)
Lose the shoulder pads
and cut back on the lipstick.
You're playing a recluse who hasn't seen
the sun for 20 years, for Christ's sake.
Poor Bette.
So dreadfully overweight.
♪ (Orchestral)
Man: I'm getting paid to learn
how to run a business,
do things when I want
and how I want,
get paid more
than some office job.
I got freedom.
(Siren wailing)
Freedom from all of it.
(Dog barking)
(Siren wailing continues)
(Man exhales)