Agent Sterling Archer,
codename Duchess.
Licensed to kill.
Primary skills: covert operations.
Unarmed combat.
Firearms.
Explosives.
Asset acquisition.
Enemy agent disposal.
Current status: missing.
MALORY: For three months!
Sterling's been missing for three
months and you idiots have nothing!
GILLETTE: Well name-calling's
not gonna get us -- [ BLEEP ]
Anywhere.
LANA: Which is where
Archer could be.
Malory, we've checked every safe
house, run down every lead...
CYRIL: And he hasn't touched any of his
bank accounts, so unless he... oh.
LANA: Were you gonna say
"unless he's been skimming
tons of cash from his operations
accounts all these years"?
CYRIL: Yeah, duh, right?
MALORY: Wh-?
He wouldn't dare steal from me!
GILLETTE: Oh please, we all --
think he would dare to do that.
LANA: So we've got a g highly-ih
skilled covert agent,
who probably has millions
of dollars in cash...
GILLETTE: Who doesn't
want to be found.
MALORY: Being looked for by people
who don't want to find him!
EVERYBODY: What does that mean?
MALORY: Oh, don't give me that!
You're all secretly
delighted that he's gone!
LANA: I wouldn't say delighted, but...
GILLETTE: I cannot say I miss
the bullying.
CYRIL: Me neither.
Plus ISIS actually turned
a profit this quarter.
MALORY: Be that as it -- no, never mind!
Because since you've all been
half-assedly phoning it in --
LANA: Malory, he can't!
Be found!
I mean, if he's even still...um...
MALORY: Still what.
CHERYL/CAROL: Aliiive.
Jeezow, talk about duh.
I bet he totally already
killed himself.
PAM: No he didn't!
What's wrong with you?!
CHERYL/CAROL: Nothing!
Because my skeevy Russian fiance
wasn't murdered in front
of my very eyeballs
at my stupid wedding!
ARCHER: Noooooooooooooooooooo!
Kaaatyaaa!
Noooo ho ho wah ha haaa!
BARRY: Woooooh!
How's it feel, Archer?!
Now both our weddings
are canceled!
ARCHER: Baarryyyyyyy!
BARRY: Is that how
you crash a wedding?
Yes it is, Bionic Barry, yes it is...
MALORY: No!
No matter how distraught Sterling is
over Katya, he won't kill himself.
He'd never do that to me.
He's alive, somewhere, and
since you fools can't find
him I called in someone who can.
Say hello to Rip Riley, manhunter.
RILEY: Manhunter?
- Now if that is the pot calling
the kettle black... MALORY: Oh Rip,
you old so-and-so!
RILEY: How are you, Malory?
Besides gorgeous?
MALORY: Oh I'm not, I'm a mess!
I'm worried half to death about Sterling, and --
RILEY: Well, don't be.
I tracked him down.
MALORY: Already?!
LANA: Wh-? How?!
RILEY: Uh, this new thing
called intelligence gathering?
Anyhoo, he's on a little island
called Wapuni in French Polynesia --
GILLETTE: With his millions in caaaash...
RILEY: Tending bar.
GILLETTE: Or nooooot.
RILEY: So I'll pick him up tonight,
then say, three days back to New York,
so if you're not busy Friday night...
MALORY: I'll book us our old
booth at 21.
RILEY: Outstanding.
Riley out.
PAM: What a hunk!
CHERYL/CAROL: Total sploosh.
LANA: Actually yeah, gotta
give him the sploosh.
GILLETTE: And, whatever my
equivalent of sploosh is,
which, I guess is just sploosh.
Only with semen.
Sync & corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
WOMAN: Oh my God, I can't
believe I just did that...
You know, I'm not like that --
ARCHER: No, hey c'mon, don't do that...
Don't ruin your post-coital bliss
with a bunch of misplaced guilt.
WOMAN: How is it misplaced,
I'm on my honeymoo-hooon!
ARCHER: Well at least
you got a honeymoon!
My fiance was murdered!
WOMAN: Wait, what?
ARCHER: Yeah!
Oh! And you married an idiot!
Who plays thirty-six holes of golf
on the first day of his honeymoon?
Because not to, whatever, but that
cannot bode well for your marriage.
WOMAN: Get the hell out,
you piece of shit!
ARCHER: Seriously, I hope she didn't
sign a pre-nup, because -- Oh my God!
Hey so, what happened was,
somebody ordered room service,
but the regular room service
guy, uh, he died, so I came in
here and fell on the bed --
Wait, you're not her husband.
And you're not one of my dick
bosses, so can I help you, or...?
RILEY: Yes, you can quickly and
quietly walk down to the dock
and board my seaplane.
ARCHER: Okay A, rhetorical,
and B, your what?
RILEY: Seaplane?
Looks like an airplane
had a baby with a boat?
ARCHER: I know what a
seaplane is, idiot!
RILEY: And yet you're
surprisingly unclear on the
phrase "quickly and quietly."
ARCHER: And even more
unclear on who you are?
RILEY: Name's Rip Riley.
Your mother hired me to
bring you back, Sterling.
ARCHER: She what?!
I mean who?!
I'm Randy! See?
So you can just go back to...
that other guy's mother and tell
her that even if you did
find that other guy,
he's never coming back to ISIS!
Wait, did you say ISIS, or...?
How did ISIS suddenly get in
the mix, is what I'm asking.
RILEY: And I'm asking you, for
the second and last time,
to get on that plane.
ARCHER: Ya wanna try and make me?
RILEY: No, I don't.
And I promise -- you
don't want that either.
ARCHER: Hey, so listen...
I think we got off on the wrong foot?
But I'm willing to, ya know, let
bygones be gone by the wayside...
RILEY: Good to know...
But I'm there yet.
ARCHER: Well, give it some time.
Speaking of, how long
is this stupid flight?
RILEY: Eh, about forty hours in the air...
ARCHER: Hooray...
RILEY: But I have to
island-hop to re-fuel.
Old Lucy Goosey here only has a range
of about a thousand nautical miles.
ARCHER: Making it wildly
impractical, got it.
RILEY: This plane is
totally practical!
ARCHER: Maybe for this
ridiculous image you're trying
to cultivate for yourself...
RILEY: What image?
ARCHER: Sky Captain
of Yesteryeeear!
RILEY: At least I'm not sky
captain of I ran away from home,
ARCHER: I didn't run
away from home!
I'm a grown man!
Whose fiance was murdered
in front of his very eyes!
So excuse me for needing
some time to grieve!
RILEY: By tending bar
and banging newlyweds?
ARCHER: Apparently that's
my grieving process!
And also I need to
use the bathroom!
RILEY: A, it's called the head.
And B, no.
Pee in your pants.
ARCHER: Yeah, wrong number.
And I've literally had nothing but
liquor and mangoes for three months,
so unless you wanna fly a thousand
nautical miles sitting next to that...
RILEY: Okay, I'm setting
the auto-pilot.
But this better not be a ruse.
ARCHER: A ruse?
Brrring! Brrring!
Hello?
Hi, it's the 1930's, can we have our
words and clothes and shitty airplane
back?
RILEY: Let's go, kid.
ARCH: Call ya back, 1930's!
And hey, watch out for
that Adolf Hitler!
He's a bad egg!
RILEY: No, one pedal fills it with water --
ARCHER: I did that!
RILEY: And the other
pedal flushes it!
ARCHER: No, it doesn't!
Ugh, you come try, I gotta
choke down this gag reflex.
Yeah, ha ha!
Quit being a dick for five
seconds and unlock the door!
RILEY: It doesn't have a lock!
ARCHER: Dammit, I'm gonna
puke and there's no room
in the toilet or the sink!
RILEY: What the hell'd
you put in the sink?!
ARCHER: A ruse!
You big dumb idiot.
And also a bunch of shaving
cream and toilet paper.
Just because.
LANA: And where does Malory get
off implying we didn't try our
best to find Archer?
GILLETTE: No, she
straight up said it.
What she implied was that
we're jealous of Archer,
and that you hate yourself cause
you're still attracted to him.
LANA: I -- that's -- what?!
PAM: Oh please, you're
so hot for him I could
re-heat this chili in yer cooch.
LANA: Don't you have some...
humans to resource?!
PAM: Actually, no.
Most of my job's dealing
with sexual harrassment
complaints against Mr. Archer, so...
are we gonna some cooch chili
or what?
RILEY: Wuzza... wuzz...
What in the holy hell are you doing?
ARCHER: Well it was gonna
be an Old Fashioned,
but I couldn't find any bitters, so --
RILEY: How long was I out?!
ARCHER: Hard to say.
After I shaved and stuff I
took a pretty long nap, so --
RILEY: Uncuff me, you idiot!
Holy God, if we overshot
our chance to refuel...!
ARCHER: I thought you
put it on auto-pilot!
RILEY: It just maintains
course and altitude!
It doesn't know how to find the
only airstrip within a thousand
miles so it can land
itself when it needs gas!
ARCHER: Well, then I
misunderstood the concept.
RILEY: Uncuff me!
ARCHER: Okay, God!
Wait, first promise you
won't take me back to ISIS!
RILEY: ISIS?!
You'll be lucky if I can
get us back to land!
Now uncuff me!
ARCHER: Okay, God!
Wait a minute.
Is this a ruse?
ARCHER: Because if it is?
Pretty elaborate.
RILEY: Dammit!
There goes number two!
ARCHER: But it can land
on water, right?!
I mean, isn't that
the whole point?!
RILEY: It's a kinda
different story when we're
dropping like a ton of bricks!
Damn, I can barely hold her level!
ARCHER: Want me to
help steer, or...?
RILEY: Haven't you
done enough already?!
ARCHER: Wh-?!
How is this suddenly my fault?!
RILEY: Okay, this is it!
C'mon Lucy Goosey, you can do it!
Looking good, girl...
I think we're gonna be okay!
ARCHER: Wait, you didn't
put the wheels down!
RILEY: The wh -- Noooo!
ARCHER: Woooooo!
Two personal records!
For breath holding and number of
sharks shot in the frickin face!
Did you see that?
Dude are you even alive?
MALORY: No, that side's too low!
CHERYL/CAROL: Well I
can't tell from here!
MALORY: Well I can,
and it's too low.
CYRIL: I think you mean premature...
MALORY: What'd you say?!
CYRIL: Nothing!
LANA: It's just that Archer obviously
doesn't want to come back,
so I don't know how Riley's
gonna get him on a plane...
CHERYL/CAROL: Which, I bet will crash...
CYRIL: Yeahhh!
MALORY: Now you listen!
Sterling is coming home safe and
sound, and when he does it'll be no
thanks to you people, so you can
forget about getting Carvel!
GILLETTE: Aww... Cookie Puss.
RILEY: Wuzza... wuzz...
what the... what in the holy
hell are you doing now?!
ARCHER: Ugh, wondering why
this is called a D-Ration.
Oughta call it a Y-ration.
As in "Hey, this
tastes like catshit."
RILEY: They're not candy bars,
jackass, they're survival rations!
And they might have
to last us a while!
ARCHER: Umm...
RILEY: You son of a -- okay, that is it!
As of right now, I'm -- what the...?!
ARCHER: Looking for this?
RILEY: Give me that weapon.
ARCHER: No. You're agitated.
RILEY: I'm "agitated" because
you crashed my plane in the God
knows if it's even the
middle of the Pacific Ocean!
ARCHER: Yeah, which you're floating
on, and not getting shit out of
a shark in!
RILEY: Wait, what?
ARCHER: I saved you from a shark!
Let's see, after I pulled you out
of that shitheap of a plane,
but before I gave you CPR
and bandaged your head!
RILEY: Oh.
Well... thanks.
ARCHER: You're welcome.
Sorry I ate so much food.
RILEY: Yeah, that was
a pretty dick move...
ARCHER: If it makes you feel any
better I puked most of it up --
RILEY: It doesn't --
ARCHER: raft's pretty bobby.
RILEY: Well we've got a few
gallons of fresh water,
a desalinator for when that runs out...
let's see,
flare gun and some flares,
fishing gear... oh!
And this guy.
ARCHER: What is that?
RILEY: Emergency beacon.
Beams a signal directly to the ISIS satellite...
BILBO: Oh well that's
just great!
Now I get to deal with this, as
my hot meatball sub congeals
into a big fat disappointing
blob of shit.
SIGINT NERD: Nobody's
gonna touch that?
RILEY: Yeah.
So I figure three days for ISIS
to get a rescue team out here.
ARCHER: Nice!
So we just kick back, catch a
few rays, catch some sushi...
RILEY: Well it's not gonna
be a picnic, but --
ARCHER: Hey, can I
check that thing out?
RILEY: Okay, but don't
mess with the knobs, I've
got the frequency all set, so --
ARCHER: Hey thanks, Guglielmo Marconi.
Who I think invented the radio.
Over.
MALORY: But if the emergency
beacon is going off --
oh my God, their plane crashed!
CHERYL/CAROL: (gasps) I said
that would happen and it did!
What if I have
psycho-kinetic powers?!
PAM: I dunno, just try
to only use em for good.
CHERYL/CAROL: No.
MALORY: Well?!
Don't just sit there sweating
like a gigantic cheese!
Do something!
BILBO: Ow, and I am.
Our satellite's locked on
the beacon, which is, jeez,
the middle of nowhere.
MALORY: Lana, Ray!
Get there this instant!
LANA: Uh, sorta following
up on his thing about the
middle of nowhere... how?
The black titanium
corporate card?!
PAM: I thought it was just a myth!
Like a big, beautiful,
no-limit unicorn!
MALORY: Charter a private jet to
Honolulu, then I don't care if you have
to buy a plane, get out
there and find him!
CYRIL: Wait, no, that's
not in the budget!
MALORY: Say budget
to me again, Cyril.
CYRIL: Save your receipts, please.
MALORY: And call me the very
instant you have an update!
And you!
You lose my son, you'll have to drink
your meatballs subs through a straw.
BILBO: Again, ow.
And again, the satellite is locked
on the beacon, so unless he,
I dunno, throws it away... MALORY: Wh-?
Why the hell would he do that?!
ARCHER: I told you!
I'm not going back there!
RILEY: Well, you say that...
ARCHER: Riley no shit, I will shoot you.
RILEY: And then I'll shoot you.
With a flare.
And then I'll use a D-ration bar
and two survival crackers to
make s'mores over the crackling fire
that used to be your chest cavity.
ARCHER: God damn, dude.
RILEY: Sorry, but you're
acting really crazy.
ARCHER: Well?!
Being a spy makes you crazy!
I mean what kind of job is that,
where your fiance gets murdered?!
Hello, stress!
Don't even get me started on my mother,
I mean she -- RILEY: She can be
a steel-clad bitch, I know,
why do you think I left ISIS?
ARCHER: Wh-?
You were an ISIS agent?!
RILEY: Briefly, way back.
Didn't work out, because,
ya know, your mother...
ARCHER: Was impossible
to please, right?
RILEY: God, if you only knew...
ARCHER: What?
RILEY: ...
how much your mom loves you!
You would at least have the
heart to go tell her you're
quitting in person.
ARCHER: Eesh.
Rather get shot with a flare...
RILEY: Oh, man up!
Talk to your mother.
Then you can go be a bartender, and
destroy a new marriage every week.
ARCHER: C'mon, that
marriage was doomed.
RILEY: And so are we, if we don't
work together out here, so... truce?
ARCHER: Uh, ya, and hey,
we're not doomed!
Look!
Over here! Hey!
RILEY: No no no wait, get down!
ARCHER: Wh-?
Don't you wanna get rescued?
RILEY: Yeah, but those
could be pirates!
ARCHER: Okay, well, they'll
just have to do 'til we
find some cowboys and Indians.
RILEY: What?!
ARCHER: What what.
What're you talking about?
ARCHER: I'm sorry... I didn't know pirates
were...still a real thing.
ARCHER: Man, this is not
at all what I pictured...
I mean, you hear "pirate ship"
you think sails, cannonballs...
oh, and not one of these guys has a beard.
RILEY: You done?
ARCHER: Hang on.
Planks.
Now I'm done.
RILEY: Because the fact that
we're still alive tells me they
wanna try to r --
ARCHER: Don't say rape.
RILEY: Ransom us.
ARCHER: Awesome.
Compared to rape.
Which seems like a thing
pirates would do.
RILEY: But those numbskulls who
picked us up were so drunk --
ARCHER: Now that did seem piratey.
RILEY: -- they forgot to search me.
ARCHER: Well, unless you've
got a bunch of Navy SEALs
stuffed in your pants...
RILEY: No!
I've got the signal beacon!
ARCHER: So?
RILEY: So we just stall the
pirates until the ISIS rescue
team shows up, boards the
ship, and takes 'em all out!
Bing, Bang, Boom.
[ laughter ]
RILEY: Which is funny why?
ARCHER: Well, gee,
where do I start?
GILLETTE: I will start with the
caviar and the '38 Montrachet,
then do the Kobe tartare
with this '42 Lapin,
and then this chocolate
terrine looks insaaane.
And then I guess just send me
to fat camp and pray to God
I don't eat all those fat,
delicious little chiddrens.
Because I will gobble them up.
RILEY: Wow, ISIS has
really gone downhill.
But there must be
some good agents.
ARCHER: It kills me to say
it, but it maybe Lana...
LANA: Ray, I doubt that's what
Malory had in mind when she gave
us the card.
Ya know, we are on
a rescue mission.
GILLETTE: Ugh.
Rescue me from myself...
such a fatty.
ARCHER: But even so, I wouldn't put
all my rescue eggs in that basket.
RILEY: Well?!
You got a better plan?!
ARCHER: I don't, I'm
not really a planner.
My process is a little more...
organic?
PIRATE: Datang!
Untuk kapten!
ARCHER: So let's just play it by ear,
see where the afternoon takes us.
See?
This is why I like
to keep it loose.
I mean the wine's crap,
but -- Oh, sorry.
No offense, captain.
CAPTAIN: No, I am who am sorry.
This from million dollar yacht.
Now I don't feel bad
for killing them.
ARCHER: Serves em right, those jerks...
CAPTAIN: But you know wine!
You rich man!
ARCHER: Who me? No, I'm --
CAPTAIN: Rich man!
My men take this off you!
The Omicron Spacemaster!
ARCHER: Oh, it's actually
the Sp -- acemaster, yeah.
Good ol' Spacemaster...
CAPTAIN: To Sterleen... Love, Muddah.
You muddah rich lady!
ARCHER: Uh... oh!
Yeah, crazy-rich, she invented
the splashless urinal cake.
CAPTAIN: The what?
ARCHER: They're -- doesn't matter,
she's rich and she loves me
and I'm really rich and this is
my manservant, uh... Jerkins.
RILEY: Funny stuff.
ARCHER: Not now, Jerkins.
So I bet she'd pay whatever
ransom you ask for.
Splashless urinal cakes have
been pretty good to us.
As you can imagine.
CAPTAIN: This good to hear...
ARCHER: But we can't do any
of that "mail somebody a finger"
- shit, or --
- No, no, no we take you back to my island!
Call you muddah, get
a big big money!
ARCHER: Awesome.
Compared to finger-mailing.
So tell me about this
island of yours?
BILBO: It's a tiny little
rock called Pangu...
Nothin else within a thousand
miles, and the beacon's been
headin straight for it
at about twenty knots.
MALORY: So a ship must
have picked them up!
But I've never even
heard of Pangu.
Is there a naval base there, or...?
BILBO: Mmmnot exactly.
It's more of a, uh...
LANA: Pirate fortress.
No, yeah, I just wanted
to make sure you said
the phrase "pirate fortress."
Which apparently, yes, you
did, say the word pirate,
followed by the word --
CAPTAIN: Fortress!
That is the word, My english so crap...
ARCHER: Eh, I bet you just need
more practice.
Try this: Jerkins,
you're a douchebag!
RILEY: Funny stuff.
CAPTAIN: Jehkin, you dooshaback!
ARCHER: Keep at it.
Oh and hey, did we cross the
international date line?
Because I can change the date for
you on that Omicron Spacemaster.
CAPTAIN: Eh?
Yeah, okay dumb guy... ARCHER: Wouldn't
want to be walking around like a
dickhead!
With the wrong date on your...
Omicron Spymaster!
CAPTAIN: Wh-?!
Wuzza hell dumb guy?
ARCHER: It's the
Omicron Spymaster!
Which is why it's got knockout
gas and a garrote and I think
even a laser and Riley do I have
to kill everybody myself?!
RILEY: Huh? Oh!
ARCHER: Seriously, what
the hell, Riley?!
RILEY: I didn't know you
were making a move!
ARCHER: Uh, dickhead?!
RILEY: Takes one to know one.
ARCHER: No!
Dickhead was the go-word!
RILEY: How was I
supposed to know?!
ARCHER: Oh. Yeah sorry, I forgot
to tell you the go-word was --
CAPTAIN: Dooshaback!
ARCHER: But even still,
Riley you gotta be quicker.
I mean, I know you're pretty old but --
RILEY: Well now that I know the
go-word, I --
ARCHER: No, idiot, it changes every time.
RILEY: Well what is it now?
ARCHER: Pirates!
RILEY: Kinda confusing, since we're on a --
Owww! Come on, that was right
next to my frickin ear!
ARCHER: Sorry, I know that hurts.
Happens to me kind of a lot.
I actually have like
mild tinnitis now.
I mean, it's gotten to where I had
to start sleeping with a fan on.
RILEY: Oh my God... ARCHER: Yeah,
otherwise it's like eeeeeeeeeee.
RILEY: No, you just
killed like, ten pirates.
ARCHER: Wow, and if the
five-year old me knew that
he would get a huge boner.
No idea why I said that.
RILEY: Well once these idiots
figure out they can turn those
twenty-millimeter cannons on the
wheelhouse, we'll be -- kinda confused.
ARCHER: What are they doing?
RILEY: It looks like
they're surrendering!
ARCHER: Why?
All they have to do is --
RILEY: Shut up, who cares why?
ARCHER: I do!
What if it's a ruse?
RILEY: It's not a ruse!
Say something, before
they change their minds!
ARCHER: Do they speak English?
Uh... hello, pirates!
Who speaks English,
let's see some hands!
ARCHER: Wow, way
more than I thought.
NOAH: Uh, excuse me?
Sorry, hi, I'm Noah?
ARCHER: What're you,
the first mate, or...?
NOAH: Oh!
Oh God no, no, I'm a bajak budak?
It's sort of a -- well, I guess the
nearest translation is slave-pirate?
ARCHER: Do you speak English?
NOAH: I do.
They don't, though, they're just
surrendering the ship to you.
Dan benteng?
PIRATE: Ya.
NOAH: And the fort.
You're the new captain.
ARCHER: The what?!
NOAH: Well if you kill the old
captain, you become the new captain.
I know you don't think of
pirates as having a lot of
rules, but they actually
do and that's a big one.
ARCHER: Well, tell them...
hands down!
NOAH: Tangan ke bawah!
ARCHER: Holy shit!
Did you see that?!
RILEY: No, I'm too busy looking at that...
ARCHER: What is...
what am I seeing?
NOAH: Oh, the women always us throw a
huge feast when we return to port.
Should I tell them
to cancel it, or...?
ARCHER: Huh?
No, we're totally feasting!
Say that!
NOAH: Mulai pesta!
RILEY: Nice plan.
Once they're good and drunk we'll
turn this tub around and head home.
ARCHER: Home?
Riley... I am home.
RILEY: Wh-? ! Over my dead body are you
running away to be a pirate!
ARCHER: Of course I'm not
gonna be a pirate...
I'm gonna be a pirate king.
Sync & corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com