(thunder rumbling)
(screaming)
>> ARCHER: Goddamn it, Ray.
Are you drunk?
>> RAY: No, dumbass, are you?
>> ARCHER: No.
>> LANA: Although not for lack
of trying.
>> ARCHER: Exactly, that's my
whole point.
(retching)
>> CYRIL: Oh, how can you drink
rum with all this turbulence?
>> ARCHER: Oh, my God!
That's my whole point!
>> MALORY: Enough already!
My God, are you people paid by
the word?
It's bad enough I'm packed into
this flying boxcar with you...
(gasping)
...without all this incessant
bickering.
It's like I'm stuck on a school
bus with the worst driver on the
planet!
(Ray muttering)
What was that?
>> ARCHER: It is kind of like a
school bus.
>> LANA: When have you ever been
on a bus?
>> ARCHER: No, from the movies.
We've got the whole Breakfast
Club in here.
I'm Emilio Estevez.
Cyril's obviously Anthony
Michael Nerd.
Mother, you're Paul Gleason.
Krieger's the loose cannon,
Judd Nelson, and Lana, you're...
um...
>> LANA: Wait, seriously?
Molly Ringwald.
>> ALL: Eh...
>> LANA: Oh, my God.
>> MALORY: What the hell are you
talking about?
Lana, come on, if any of you
ISIS women is Molly Ringwald...
>> CYRIL: It's obviously
Cherlene.
>> KRIEGER: Totally.
>> LANA: What?
>> ARCHER: Yes, she's the rich
one, she's a redhead...
>> LANA: So, what, you think I'm
Ally Sheedy?
>> MALORY: Are you all just
saying random words?
>> CYRIL: Ally Sheedy would've
been way more likely to get
pregnant in high school.
>> KRIEGER: Had there been a
sequel.
>> ARCHER: God forbid.
>> KRIEGER: Right?
>> CYRIL: And as for who's the
hot one...
>> LANA: Wait, what, of us?
I'm the hot one!
>> ALL: Eh...
>> LANA: Oh, my God.
>> CHERLENE: Oh, get over
yourself!
(muttering)
>> PAM: Shh! Will you shut up?
>> CHERLENE: Oh, please.
She knows we're in here.
>> PAM: She will if you
don't shut up.
>> MALORY (sighs): Pam, I know
you're in there.
>> PAM: No, we're not.
But if we are, which I don't
admit to, which Breakfast
Clubber am I?
>> ARCHER: Hmm, I guess the
janitor everybody thinks is
gross but turns out to be cool.
>> PAM: Aw.
>> CHERLENE (laughs): I love
that you take that as a
compliment.
(farts)
>> PAM: So, can we get out of
the crate now?
>> MALORY: No, but as it seems
we've arrived at a pause in the
idiocy, let's recap the plan for
when we land in San Marcos.
>> LANA: Yeah, because I'm
curious how we tell Calderón we
turned six million dollars'
worth of cocaine into one
million dollars' worth of
weapons.
>> MALORY: That's the CIA's
problem.
Calderón doesn't care.
It's all gravy to him.
>> ARCHER: Yeah, Lana.
I was actually wondering that
myself.
>> MALORY: All that matters is
that Calderón pays us for this
shipment.
Then we use the profits to buy
more weapons, which we sell to
him to make more profits to buy
more weapons.
Blah, blah, blah.
>> CYRIL (scoffs): Lana, for
God's sakes, it's Econ 101.
>> MALORY: Cyril, don't be
shitty.
>> ARCHER: Yeah, Cyril!
>> AIR TRAFFIC CONTROLLER: Tower
to unidentified aircraft, you
are now entering restricted San
Marcos airspace.
Identify yourself.
>> RAY: Uh, guys?
>> ARCHER: Just tell them Slater
sent us.
>> LANA: You think that's a good
idea, flying into a war zone,
telling them we're with the CIA?
>> ARCHER: If Slater even was
CIA.
>> MALORY: Now, he's the one who
teabagged you?
(Pam growls suggestively)
>> ARCHER (scoffs): Beanbagged.
>> MALORY: Oh, whichever.
>> ARCHER: It's a fairly
important distinction.
>> LANA: Sorry, can I be a nag
for a second?
>> ARCHER: Oh, my God, Lana,
I've had only, like, eight
drinks.
>> LANA: Okay, not that,
but wait, really?
>> ARCHER: Yeah, I've totally
cut back, and not that it's any
of your beeswax, but I've also
cut back on... you know.
>> MALORY: On what?
Sterling, with you, that could
almost literally be anything.
>> ARCHER: Anonymous sex, if you
must know.
>> MALORY: Ew!
>> AIR TRAFFIC CONTROLLER:
Beechcraft, please identify.
>> RAY: Guys?
>> LANA: Really?
>> ARCHER: I've totally,
relatively cleaned up my act.
So maybe keep that in mind when
you're choosing godparents.
(Lana laughs)
>> LANA: I will, Archer.
I really will.
>> AIR TRAFFIC CONTROLLER:
Beechcraft, identify.
>> RAY: Guys!
>> ARCHER: Goddamn it, tell him
Slater sent us.
>> LANA: Wait, wait, wait, wait.
>> RAY: Tower, this is
Beechcraft.
>> LANA: Ray!
>> RAY: Uh, Slater sent us?
(groans)
>> AIR TRAFFIC CONTROLLER:
Beechcraft, you are clear for
landing.
>> LANA: Thank you for hearing
my concerns.
>> ARCHER: Jesus, will you
relax?
(gulping)
(belches)
(groans)
(sighs) What's the worst that
could happen?
(tires squealing)
>> TROOPS: Get on the ground!
(indistinct shouting)
>> ARCHER: Don't shoot!
Don't shoot!
(shouting continues)
>> LANA: Way to go, Gilligan.
(gunshot)
>> CALDERÓN: Silencio!
Who is in charge here?
>> COMANDANTE: Señor Presidente,
I...
>> CALDERÓN: Not you, you
baboon-faced baboon.
I am obviously talking to these
gringos, and also, if I am here,
then you are obviously not in
charge.
>> COMANDANTE: I...
(gunshots)
(gun clicking)
(gunshot)
>> CALDERÓN: And to repeat,
who is in charge here?
>> ARCHER: That would be...
>> CALDERÓN: Because they are to
blame for this shipment of
weapons being late.
>> ARCHER: Her, that older woman
down there with the more or less
permanent scowl.
>> MALORY: Señor Presidente, it
is such an honor to meet you.
I'm Malory Archer.
>> CALDERÓN: Wow.
>> MALORY (chuckles): Well,
thank you.
Anyhoo, hello?
>> CALDERÓN: So, the stories are
true.
>> KRIEGER: What stories?
I... no, not what, huh?
Damn it, man, I was
sleepwalking.
>> CALDERÓN: Eh?
(muttering in agreement)
>> KRIEGER: Hey, what's
going on?
>> CYRIL (sighs): Maybe you're
their god.
(gasps)
>> CALDERÓN: Okay, all but him,
arrest.
(indistinct talking)
>> MALORY: Without even checking
the merchandise?
(snapping)
(groaning)
Although not that particular
merchandise.
(Pam and Cherlene shouting)
(guns clicking)
(speaking Spanish)
(shouting)
(gunshots)
>> CHERLENE: Goddamn it!
Who the hell drilled my box?!
>> ARCHER: So, we're just done
with phrasing, right?
That's not a thing anymore?
(gasps)
I know, right?
>> CALDERÓN: Cherlene.
>> CHERLENE: What?!
>> ALL: Wait, what?!
>> ARCHER: Yeah,
seriously, what?
>> CALDERÓN: "Outlaw Country,"
"Hoochie Coochie Coochie Man,"
"Travis County Limitado."
I am... I am your biggest fan.
Please, we go to the
presidential palace?
>> PAM: I'm fine, too,
by the way.
>> ARCHER: Oh, great.
>> LANA: That's good.
>> CALDERÓN: Please, come, come.
Come, come, come, come, come.
>> ARCHER: So, phrasing's just
dead then?
>> LANA: What is your...?
Wait, are you drunk?
>> ARCHER (scoffs): Please.
Off 12 drinks?
>> CALDERÓN: Viva Cherlene!
Viva Cherlene!
>> TROOPS (chanting): Cherlene!
Cherlene!
>> LANA: Wait a minute, you said
eight drinks!
(chuckles)
>> ARCHER: I lied.
I mean, yes, eight.
>> TROOPS: Cherlene! Cherlene!
>> PAM (laughing): Holy
dickballs!
I mean, I mean, I mean, just
holy....
>> LANA: Dickballs.
Yes, Pam, I got it.
>> CALDERÓN: Are you sure?
The room is okay?
>> CHERLENE: Yeah, it's fine,
whatever.
>> CALDERÓN: I-I cannot believe
it is actually you.
Here in my palace, I mean...
>> CHERLENE: Yeah, it's blowing
your mind, huh?
>> CALDERÓN: Boom!
(laughing): Yeah.
Can I please bring you anything?
A freshly squeezed juice, a
cocktail, a sandwich of your own
choosing?
>> CHERLENE: Don't you, like,
have a war to go to?
(scoffs)
>> CALDERÓN: It's in the
mountains far, far away where we
will crush the communist rebel
dogs!
Especially now that we are once
again receiving weapons.
>> MALORY: Yoo-hoo!
And about that, I was hoping
that you and I could discuss
our terms?
>> CALDERÓN: I... but Cherlene?
>> MALORY: Is exhausted.
As is my drink.
(sighs)
>> CYRIL: Why do we always have
to share a room?
>> RAY: The sinister gay cabal,
Cyril, you have fallen victim to
the sinister gay cabal.
>> CYRIL: Okay, you know...
>> RAY: I don't know why we
always get stuck together.
But I kind of don't mind it.
>> CYRIL: Hmm, actually I don't
either, now that I think...
>> RAY: Queer!
(laughs)
(rhythmic zipping)
(rhythmic shaking)
>> ARCHER: ¶ Apache
Helicopters
We should sell those
'Cause I'm a ropper. ¶
(laughs)
Ropper...
Wow, that's awful.
But so far, being an
international arms dealer is
not.
I could get extremely used to
this.
Matt, Joel, hi, shut up.
Let's set up lunch with Adnan
Khashoggi, I...
(knocking)
(door opens)
Whoa, whoa, uh, uh, oh, I ju...
oh, ah, I just... (chuckles)
I... oh, got a, I got a...
whoa, ho, ho, ho, oh, ho, ho,
oh, no!
(metal clanging)
(clears throat)
Uh, may I help you?
>> MAID: I'm sorry to bother
you, sir.
>> ARCHER: No, no, you didn't,
aren't, or rather you couldn't,
or still haven't, I...
>> MAID: I thought you might
need more towels.
>> ARCHER: Oh, uh, no.
I-I think I'm okay for right
now.
(buttons popping)
Although that being said,
it's better to be safe than
sorry, at least with regards
to towels.
(buttons popping)
But only towels.
>> KRIEGER: Hey, are there more
towels?
Hey, are there more towels?
Hey, are there more...?
>> CYRIL: You realize this
isn't a hotel, right?
>> LANA: And even if it were,
that is not how you'd go about
getting towels!
>> PAM: Who are you, Princess...
hang on... Lana?
>> LANA: Well played.
>> PAM: I've got crate lag.
>> LANA: And where are you
going with that?
>> PAM: Ice machine.
>> CYRIL: Ooh, hey, I could use
some ice.
>> KRIEGER: Oh, and if you see a
housekeeping cart, can you grab
me some towels?
>> PAM: Yep!
>> KRIEGER: You're not going to,
are you?
>> PAM: Nope!
>> KRIEGER: Goddamn it.
Ha, hee, cold, cold, cold...
>> LANA: And there, but for the
grace of...
Hey, get me a fizzy water!
(Pam farts, laughs)
Thanks!
>> MALORY: I'm sorry?
>> CALDERÓN: Tanks?
>> MALORY: For?
>> CALDERÓN: Hmm.
Hmm...
Maybe to start?
>> MALORY: I... defer to you?
>> CALDERÓN: Then yes, I think
to start.
(cork pops)
Yes?
>> MALORY: Oh.
Yes, please.
>> CALDERÓN: But soon I think
more, no?
>> MALORY: Well, I should
hope so.
Or is that not...?
>> CALDERÓN: No, please, of
course, I am willing to do
whatever it takes.
Anything.
>> MALORY: Well, then that makes
two of us.
>> CALDERÓN: Wait, really?
Anything?
>> MALORY: Yes?
>> CALDERÓN: Gas?
>> MALORY: I'm sorry?
>> CALDERÓN: You have gas?
>> MALORY: Wha...? No!
>> CALDERÓN: Oh, my God, oh, my
God, oh, my God, sorry, I'm
sorry, I'm sorry, I thought
you...
>> MALORY: No! For the... No!
>> CALDERÓN: I misunderstood.
I apologize.
>> MALORY: And well you should!
>> CALDERÓN: And well I do!
Please forgive me.
>> MALORY: I mean...
>> PAM: What a frickin' clip
joint.
>> KRIEGER: No towels.
>> PAM: No ice machine.
(Cherlene screams)
>> CHERLENE: No towel machine?!
>> PAM: Yeah, right?
>> CHERLENE: What is this--
Escape From...?
Wait, are we still in
New York, or...?
>> CYRIL: What?
No, we're in Central America.
(gasps)
>> CHERLENE: Oh, my God!
We did it!
We're free!
>> PAM: Do...?
>> CHERLENE: Outlaw different
country woooooo!
>> PAM: Sometimes I
worry about her.
>> CYRIL: Eh.
>> KRIEGER: Ooh, hang on, maybe
this is it.
>> PAM: I don't know.
It looks kind of...
>> KRIEGER: Ugh, Pam, they can't
leave valuable towels and ice
just lying around.
Hotel profit margins are
very thin.
(gasps)
Oh, oh, oh...
(muffled yelling)
(screams)
(all crying)
Me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me.
>> CYRIL: Krieger?
What'd you, see a ghost?
>> PAM: Oh, my God, please say
yes.
>> ARCHER: All right, is
that happy hour I smell?
>> CALDERÓN: Yes, Mr. Archer.
Please join us.
Your mother and I are drinking
wine that belonged to Benjamin
Franklin.
>> MALORY: We are?
>> CALDERÓN: And discussing a
shipment of four American tanks.
>> MALORY: Oh, tanks!
>> ARCHER: Thanks. Tanks?
>> MALORY: We do tanks!
We can do anything, as long as
you're willing to pay.
>> CALDERÓN: Me... me pay?
>> MALORY: Good, then it's
settled.
>> ARCHER: If you say so,
Mother.
>> CALDERÓN: No, no, no, I'm
sorry, I-I thought this was why
the CIA was buying my cocaine.
To sell to the American black
people, to make the money to buy
the weapons to give me to fight
the    comunistas.
>> MALORY: Exactly.
>> ARCHER: Wait, what?
Why wouldn't they just...?
>> MALORY: Sterling, shut up
and let me handle this.
Because the problem, Gustavo...
>> CALDERÓN: Ooh.
>> MALORY: I'm sorry, may I call
you Gustavo?
>> CALDERÓN: No.
>> MALORY: The problem, Señor
Presidente, the problem, you
see, the problem is...
is the White House has lost
faith in your ability to win
this war!
>> CALDERÓN: Ooh.
>> MALORY: And so, if you want
any more weapons, you'll have to
pay for them in cash.
>> CALDERÓN: Ooh!
>> MALORY: Starting now.
>> CALDERÓN: No, no, but I
cannot afford to do this!
>> MALORY: Oh, please.
Look at you, drinking Ben
Franklin's wine like it's
Kool-Aid, surrounded by
priceless art...
Not this one obviously, but...
>> CALDERÓN: Oh, no, this one
cost 40 millions.
>> MALORY AND ARCHER: What?!
>> CALDERÓN: Yes, it is an Ivan
Blitko.
So we have, in this area, these
very geometric shapes, in these
very bold colors here, and then
the thick black lines are coming
here, always drawing the eye to
here, and then, over
everything... just white.
Just layer after layer after
layer of pure white.
Until you can see nothing of the
painting below.
Not even with an infrared
camera.
>> MALORY: So... what's the
point?
>> CALDERÓN: The point?
What is the point of a beautiful
woman?
And speaking of!
>> JULIANA (chuckles): Hello,
darling.
>> CALDERÓN: My wife.
(Archer grunting)
(gulps)
(burps)
>> MALORY: Sterling!
Where are your manners?
>> ARCHER: Probably in my room,
so I should go there right now
and find them.
>> CALDERÓN: No, no, no, no,
no, please stay.
Mi amor, may I present to you
Sterling Archer, and also his
charming mother Malory.
>> JULIANA: Juliana Calderón.
>> MALORY: A pleasure to meet
you, Juliana.
>> JULIANA: Oh.
>> MALORY: I'm sorry, may I call
you...
>> JULIANA: No.
>> CALDERÓN: Uh, darling, how
was your afternoon?
>> JULIANA: Exhausting.
>> ARCHER: Mmm.
>> JULIANA: So hot and sweaty.
>> JULIANA: To be honest, I'm
really quite sore.
>> ARCHER: Mm-mmm!
This is why I disapprove.
Juliana sometimes goes among the
servants, pretending to be a
maid, or working in the laundry,
even one time helping to carry
some rocks?
>> MALORY: Oh, how...
>> JULIANA: Inspiring, really.
>> MALORY: Mmm.
>> CALDERÓN: I was just showing
them the Blitko.
>> JULIANA: Do you like what you
see, Mr. Archer?
>> ARCHER: You know, so much
that... I-I'm gonna go write
about it in my art journal!
>> CALDERÓN: She is going to
bring us some tanks, so that we
may crush the rebel dogs.
Did they tell you what is for
dinner?
>> CYRIL: Clones?
>> KRIEGER: Yes, clones!
My God, it was like looking
in... several mirrors!
>> PAM: Oh, man, oh, man, oh,
man, oh, man...
>> KRIEGER: Archer!
>> ARCHER: What?!
>> KRIEGER: Ow, ah, hang on...
gotta stitch... oh...
>> ARCHER: Damn it, I don't have
time for... wait, Pam, did you
find an ice machine?
>> PAM: Huh-uh.
Ow, hang on... (groans)
>> ARCHER: Goddamn it...
>> PAM: Clones!
>> ARCHER: What?
>> CYRIL: Krieger says-- ow,
hold on...
>> ARCHER: Goddamn it!
>> CYRIL: Krieger says he saw a
bunch of clones!
>> ARCHER: Of what?
We're running to find them.
>> PAM: Wait, what?
I thought we were running away
from them!
>> ARCHER: Hang on, shut up,
hold that thought.
>> KRIEGER: Guys, come on, let's
go!
>> PAM: Not without a bunch of
garlic and some wooden stakes.
They're clones, not vampires!
>> PAM: It doesn't matter to
the stake!
>> KRIEGER: What're you... we
can't kill them!
>> PAM: Well, not now.
We wait till morning and then
murder them in their coffins.
Cyril?
Thoughts?
>> CYRIL: I just really wish I
hadn't come on this stupid trip.
But since I did...
>> KRIEGER: Taaaaanks!
You jerks.
(muffled scream)
(Lana sighs)
>> LANA: Don't even want to
know.
>> ARCHER: Lana!
Lana!
Oh, my God, you gotta help me!
>> LANA: Oh, for the... there is
no ice machine!
>> ARCHER: Okay, not that, but
A) a palace this big
definitely has an ice machine,
maybe not in the hall, but it's
not like they make ice with
trays.
B)...
>> LANA: "B" is hey, shut up,
about that thing where you said
you're cleaning up your act.
>> ARCHER: Which I'm actually
pretty serious about, by the
way, but right now I want to
talk about this other thing
where I just banged Calderón's
wife.
Lana?
>> LANA: Uh, hang on.
Okay.
(clears throat)
Why would you do that?!
>> ARCHER: I... I'm sorry, do
you mean where?
>> LANA: No, Archer, I mean why!
What happened to no more
anonymous sex?
>> ARCHER: It wasn't anonymous,
Lana.
I thought she was the maid.
>> LANA: Why would you think
that?!
>> ARCHER: I'm sorry, do you
mean why?
>> LANA: Wh... Yes!
Why?!
>> ARCHER: Uniform, towels, the
usual maid stuff!
>> LANA: The... whoa-whoa-whoa-
whoa, back up.
What is your definition of
anonymous sex?
>> ARCHER: I don't know,
bird masks?
>> LANA: What?
>> ARCHER: Or a woman you
literally bump into on the
train.
Or the ferry.
Or in a port-a-john at the
Preakness that time, but not
somebody who works directly for
a president, I can tell you
that.
I mean, we're talking major
security clearance, so you got
to assume there's a pretty
thorough vetting process for...
that... you know...
>> LANA: You done?
>> ARCHER: Hang on.
Yes?
>> LANA: Okay. So.
Here's my advice.
(grunts, moans)
Do with it as you will.
(Archer moans, coughs)
(groaning)
>> CHERLENE: Hey, are you going
to this dinner?
(retches)
Or did you already eat...
crayons?
>> JULIANA: Should we not just
start?
(clears throat)
>> CALDERÓN: Not until the guest
of honor arrives.
>> CHERLENE: Woooooo-hoo!
(Calderón gasps)
>> CALDERÓN: Yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, come, come, come,
come, come, come, because I am
pulling out!
>> CHERLENE: Phrasing, boom!
>> ARCHER: Thank you.
(moans)
>> LANA: How's the balls?
>> ARCHER: Ruined?
I'm pretty sure?
>> CALDERÓN: Okay, you sit
there.
Uh... you.
Up.
>> MALORY: I beg your pardon?
>> CALDERÓN: Get up.
Come on, move it, up, up, up!
>> MALORY: Well, of all the...
>> CALDERÓN: Please, Cherlene.
Everyone, raise a glass, and
join me to toast Cherlene!
Because-- and I happen to know
this for a fact-- her debut
album has now officially sold
one million copies!
(Malory shrieks)
(others cheering)
>> CYRIL: Yay!
>> CHERLENE: How?
It came out, like, yesterday.
>> CALDERÓN: Yes!
Amazing!
A toast.
>> CHERLENE: No, like literally
yesterday.
>> CALDERÓN: And now it is
platinum.
A toast!
>> CHERLENE: I just don't see
how it's possible.
(forklift beeping)
(many forklifts beeping)
>> CALDERÓN: It doesn't matter
how!
A toast!
>> PAM: Hear, hear!
(murmurs of agreement)
>> CALDERÓN: And also let us not
forget my brave soldiers, yes,
out there, fighting those rebel
dogs, far away!
>> PAM: And plus that one right
there.
>> COMANDANTE: Señor Presidente!
The rebels have broken through
our lines!
They...
They are now within mortar
range!
(screaming)
>> CHERLENE: Oh, my God!
It's starting!
>> MALORY: What is?
>> CHERLENE: Cherlenemania!
>> LANA: It's a mortar attack!
>> CHERLENE: I know!
How frickin' outlaw country
is that?!
¶ I'll burn it down
I'll burn it down to the ground
To the sea...
¶ I'll burn it down
Down to the ground
¶ You don't mess with
This country queen
¶ Don't you mess...
With this country queen. ¶
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> MAN: Made... in Georgia.