(soft orchestral music playing)
¶
(booming explosion)
(distant screaming)
(panicked shouting)
(sirens wailing, horns honking)
¶
(sirens wailing, car horn honks)
(high-pitched ringing)
(muffled)
>> ARCHER: Mawp. Mawp.
Mawp!
(groans)
Was that a flashbang?
>> MALORY: Sterling?
>> ARCHER: Mawp?
Ow!
>> MALORY: Do something.
>> ARCHER: What?
I brought roses.
Jesus, Mother, it's just your
birthday, not the...
>> MALORY: About that!
>> ARCHER: Oh. Duh.
>> LANA: Archer!
>> ARCHER: (gasps) Lana!
>> LANA (mocking): "Lana!" Ugh.
(slurping)
Not her birthday.
>> ARCHER: Ah! (grunts)
>> CHERYL/CAROL: No, move!
Get away from us!
>> PAM: Yeah, they're shooting
at you!
>> ARCHER: Who?
>> CHERYL/CAROL: The
storm-ninjas!
>> ARCHER: What?
That's not a thing, idiot!
Oh. I stand corrected.
>> LANA: Son of a...!
Bitches, I am pregnant!
>> CYRIL: Yes! (laughs)
Who could forget?
With the bastard spawn
of a total stranger.
>> LANA: Okay, first of all...
Cover your eyes and ears!
>> CYRIL: You're not the boss
of me!
(explosion)
(high-pitched ringing)
>> CYRIL: Meep? Meep?
(laughs)
>> LANA: What's that, Beaker?
>> ARCHER: Oh, my God, is Beaker
not the best?
Meep, meep, meep!
And wait, what's his, uh...
the name of... Brett!
>> BRETT: No, no, no, leave
me alone!
>> ARCHER: Shut up.
Who's Beaker's boss?
>> BRETT: What?
>> ARCHER: Beaker's boss.
>> BRETT: Goddamn it, I can't
hear...
>> ARCHER: Brett?
Well, he died doing what
he loved.
Getting shot.
>> CYRIL: Meep. Meep.
>> LANA: Archer! Who the hell...
>> ARCHER: Shut up, it's on the
tip of my tongue!
>> LANA: What is?!
>> ARCHER: Beaker's boss!
>> LANA: What?
>> GILLETTE: She meant who the
hell are these guys,
you big dumb idiot asshole!
>> ARCHER: Said the guy in
>> GILLETTE: What the...?
>> ARCHER: I just frickin' got
here, Ray!
How the hell should I...
No...
>> LANA: No, no, no, no,
no, no...
>> CYRIL: What, what're you...?
Oh.
>> GILLETTE: Oh, boy.
>> AGENT: FBI!
Nobody move! FBI!
(Malory sighs wearily)
>> MALORY: Second worst birthday
ever.
>> ARCHER: What?
How is this better than
your second fake 50th?
>> HOLLY: Oh, come on, guys,
we talked about this!
You're supposed to yell
"FBI" at the beginning.
After the flashbangs,
but before Other Fat Mike
gets shot.
>> AGENT: Ow.
>> HOLLY: And what happened
with getting "FBI"
on the fronts of
the uniforms, huh?
>> AGENT: Ow!
>> ARCHER: Uh, what happened
with since when the hell
does the frickin' FBI get off...
>> HOLLY: Sterling Archer?
>> ARCHER: Yes! What?!
>> HOLLY: I'm Special Agent in
Charge Holly, and you are
extremely under arrest.
>> ARCHER: (laughs) For what?
>> HOLLY: Uh, in addition to
the attempted murder
of a federal agent?
>> ARCHER: Yes.
>> HOLLY: Well, there's gonna be
just a whole bunch of charges,
but mostly treason.
>> ARCHER: Treason?
>> LANA: What?
Archer, what'd you do?
>> HOLLY: No, no, not just him.
You, too, Miss Kane.
>> HOLLY: Yeah. Everybody.
Especially you, Ms. Archer.
>> LANA: Is this about the fake
hydrogen bomb?
>> HOLLY: No, but let's put
a pin in that.
This is about conducting
espionage operations, for years,
with no authority or
permission whatsoever,
from the United States
government.
(Lana gasps)
>> ARCHER: Wait, what?
Mother!
>> LANA: Like, 50 times I asked
>> MALORY: And like 50 times
I lied.
Sue me.
I want my phone call.
>> AGENT (over radio): Uh, sir?
It's like you said, he's
dug in there like a tick, and...
>> KRIEGER (over radio): Never!
You'll never take me alive!
(Holly sighs wearily)
>> HOLLY: Okay, breach it.
>> AGENT: Roger that.
(explosion)
>> KRIEGER: On second thought,
I very much prefer
to be taken alive.
Just let me clear the ol'
browser history and...
No, no, no, no, no... oof!
Oh, come on!
>> HOLOGRAM: Ooh, G-man-san.
>> ARCHER: I'm serious, you are
not putting those on me.
>> HOLLY: Mr. Archer, please
turn around and place your hands
behind your back.
>> ARCHER: (laughs) Or what?
What are you gonna do, taser...
(Archer gibbering)
(Archer sputters)
(Cheryl/Carol gasps)
>> CHERYL/CAROL: Do me! Do me!
Do me, do me, do me!
>> HOLLY: I'm not tasering you,
so just...
>> CHERYL/CAROL: Do me!
(Holly grunts)
(taser clicking,
Cheryl/Carol groaning)
(Cheryl/Carol sighs)
Thank you.
>> MALORY: Ugh.
Our tax dollars hard at work.
(laughing): Well, not mine,
obviously, but...
>> HOLLY: What's that?
>> MALORY: Damn it.
>> ARCHER: Whatever, Cyril.
I don't care who you are,
when you get zapped with 50,000
volts, it's like, like...
>> CHERYL/CAROL: Sploosh.
And then it's like wave after
wave crashing over you, into
you, and...
>> ARCHER: Will you shut up?
>> PAM: You shut up.
Let her talk.
>> ARCHER: You shut up!
>> PAM: Make me!
(shouting, grunting)
(Malory whistles loudly)
>> ALL: Ow! Ow!
>> CHERYL/CAROL: Jesus!
>> MALORY: All of you.
Shut your various holes
and listen to me very carefully.
>> CYRIL: Why, so you can tell
us more lies?
>> KRIEGER: Yeah.
(all muttering)
>> MALORY: So I can save you
from life in prison!
Sorry, Ramona, I know to you
it's just one big sexy briar
patch, but...
>> GILLETTE: You know...
>> MALORY: Zip it!
That goes for all of you!
And when we get in there,
you keep it zipped.
Because there's a chance I can
make this all go away,
but only if you people don't try
to save your own necks
by ratting out everyone else!
(all muttering)
>> MALORY: Damn it, trust me!
And say nothing!
You heard me, J. Edna.
>> LANA: Not one word.
>> ARCHER: Well, except for
those three.
And then those five. And...
>> LANA: Archer!
>> ARCHER: Then that one.
>> CYRIL: I really shouldn't
I mean, unless you can
guarantee me...
>> GILLETTE: Total immunity.
>> CHERYL/CAROL: And I mean from
everything.
>> GILLETTE: Including anything
you find on my computer.
Or in my crawlspace.
>> PAM: Oh, and throw a bone
into me.
>> AGENT 2: Excuse me?
>> GILLETTE: I said Ms. Archer
had an affair with the head of
the KGB for, like, 30 years.
>> CHERYL/CAROL (laughs): Yeah,
until he got blown up.
Which was actually my fault.
>> CYRIL: Because she was busy
having choke-sex with a
murderous cyborg, who then
became the new head of the KGB.
>> KRIEGER: Until I built a
sexier one out of illegal
Soviet parts.
And a corpse.
>> PAM: There was no shortage of
dead bodies around ISIS.
>> GILLETTE: One of which
belonged to the prime minister
>> CYRIL: Oh, Jesus, I forgot
about the...
>> CHERYL/CAROL: Giant pot farm
in West Virginia.
>> PAM: And this whole other
thing with the Yakuza.
>> GILLETTE: Irish Mob.
>> CHERYL/CAROL: Piracy.
>> CYRIL: White slavery.
>> PAM: No, actual piracy.
With, like, boats.
>> CHERYL/CAROL: I want to
say... Burt Reynolds?
>> CYRIL: Poaching alligators...
>> GILLETTE: Smuggling
>> KRIEGER: Defiling a corpse...
>> CYRIL: Defiling a different
>> PAM: Kidnapping the Pope...
>> CHERY/CAROL: (laughing)
Faking my own kidnapping!
Arson.
>> PAM: Bumfights!
You know, like when you pay
bums to...
>> CYRIL: Destroy an oil
pipeline in...
>> CHERYL/CAROL: I want to say
Burt Reynolds.
>> CYRIL: ...Turkmenistan?
>> KRIEGER: Odessa.
You know, the ratlines?
>> CHERYL/CAROL: Where you make
it look like a murder-suicide,
>> KRIEGER: Is it murder if they
were my own clones?
I'm seriously asking.
>> GILLETTE: Oh, because,
speaking of sexual assault...
>> PAM (munching): Which time?
'Cause for one of 'em
I got a pretty good excuse.
>> AGENT 2: Can I stop you?
Please?
>> PAM: That's what he said.
(Pam clears throat)
Inappropriate.
>> CYRIL: Geez, when you just
list everything ISIS has done,
it sounds kind of bad.
>> AGENT 3: And so if I were
you...
>> ARCHER: You'd get laid
>> AGENT 3: I'd start talking.
Everybody else is!
They're in there right now,
saying he's the brains
behind ISIS.
>> ARCHER: Exactly, I...
Hey, screw you!
>> LANA: Screw you!
Mr. My Mother's A Lying Bitch
And I'm Too Stupid To Realize
My Life's A Pathetic Joke!
>> ARCHER: Oh, nice to meet you,
Mrs. Hello My Kid's From A Sperm
Bank Since I Can't Keep A Man
Because In Addition To My
Jillion Neuroses
I Have A Weird-looking Vagina!
(Lana gasps)
(Archer and Lana grunting)
>> AGENT 3: Okay, knock it off.
Hey!
(FBI Agents grunting)
>> ARCHER: I can't believe they
fell for that.
>> LANA: Ahem. Miss what?
>> ARCHER: Sorry, it-it's not
that weird look...
Lana!
(gunshot)
>> ARCHER: Thought you were
gonna shoot me.
>> LANA: Day's not over.
>> ARCHER: And seriously, Lana,
sorry for what I said.
Then that's where you say...
(Archer yells)
>> LANA: Good-bye, Archer.
>> ARCHER: Where do you think
you're going?
>> LANA: Not to jail with you
and your mother.
>> ARCHER: Well, you know,
we can ask the judge...
>> LANA: You know prisons
aren't co-ed, right?
>> ARCHER: Oh. Okay, we got
to get out of here.
>> LANA: "We"? There is no
"we" anymore, Archer!
Well, there's this we...
>> ARCHER: Uh...
>> LANA: Oh, shit.
>> ARCHER: Yeah.
You're gonna be a great mother.
>> LANA: I could start smoking
crack today, and he'd still
turn out better than you.
>> ARCHER: And why is that?
Because I never had
a father, Lana?
So why don't you shut up,
and then also marry me.
>> LANA: What?!
>> ARCHER: I'm serious--
we can go underground,
get new identities,
and spend the rest
of our lives together, Lana.
We'll be a family.
You, me, the baby and your
not-that-weird-looking vagina.
>> LANA: Okay, don't take
this the wrong way...
but I would rather
lose the baby.
>> ARCHER: Wha... I...
>> LANA: Okay, that-that
wasn't...
I didn't...
>> ARCHER: Excuse me.
(Lana sighs)
(Archer laughing)
>> ARCHER: Jesus Christ,
come on, you idiot.
(Lana grunts)
>> CYRIL: "I have read this
statement, each page of which
bears my initials, and I do
hereby certify..."
>> PAM: "That the facts herein
are true and correct,
signed Pamela Poovey."
>> CYRIL: "Cyril Figgis."
>> RAY: "Raymond Q. Gillette."
>> KRIEGER: "Algernop Krieger."
>> CHERYL/CAROL: "Cheryl and/or
Carol Tunt."
Now, I would like
a ride home, please.
Preferably in an Apache
helicopter.
>> PAM: And I believe there
was some mention
of throwing a bone into me?
>> FBI AGENT 2: What are you
talking about?
>> PAM: A penis in my vagina.
Or wherever, but
come on, chop-chop,
I got to go start
enjoying my immunity.
(FBI Agent 2 laughs)
>> FBI AGENT 2: Yeah, you said
immunity. I didn't.
>> RAY: Dukes!
>> CYRIL: God!
>> KRIEGER: Damn it!
>> CHERYL/CAROL: So is that a
"no" on the Apache, or...?
(knocking)
>> FBI AGENT 4: Oh, my God,
okay, so this ditz...
Oh.
>> CHERYL/CAROL: Now who's the
ditz, huh?
>> LANA: Would you just come on?
>> CHERYL/CAROL: I'm seriously
asking.
>> PAM: Aw, but look at him.
All tied up like
a sexy little Christmas ham.
>> CYRIL: And can I just go
on record as saying
I think this is an extremely
bad idea?
>> LANA: You know what's a bad
idea? Prison.
>> ARCHER: Because, spoiler
alert, they're unisex.
>> PAM: Hello, best part.
>> HOLLY: Yeah?
>> ARCHER: Uh, uh...
>> CHERYL/CAROL (old lady
voice): Oh, Clyde?
Clyde, is that you?
It's me, dear,
Mrs. J. Edgar Hoover's mother.
>> HOLLY: Um... it's open.
Ma'am.
>> ARCHER: Nobody move!
Or...
>> MALORY: What the hell are
you doing?
>> ARCHER: Getting us out
of here.
>> MALORY: I've already done
that. Let him go.
And you'll just have
to put that on my...
whatever... crime tab.
>> HOLLY: No, no, no, no, no.
Taking a federal agent hostage
is a separate charge.
>> MALORY: Oh, well, then
perhaps we should get
him back on the phone.
>> HOLLY: I... that... I-I
don't... There's no need
to bother the... Eh, look.
If you'll just sign this form...
>> MALORY: Doo, doo, doo.
"In lieu of criminal
prosecutions for..."
Doo, doo, doo...
"Treason, I hereby forfeit
ISIS headquarters.
(all groaning)
And also agree to permanently
cease and desist
any and all ISIS operations."
(all gasping)
>> ARCHER: Oh, my God.
>> HOLLY: Or face a mandatory
sentence of life in federal
prison without parole.
>> ARCHER: You got to be
kidding me.
>> MALORY: "Signed, Malory
Archer."
>> LANA: Oh, my God.
>> ARCHER: No, uh-uh, nope.
Because correct me if I'm wrong,
but that entire document
is completely unenforceable.
I correct you. You are wrong.
>> MALORY: For God's sake,
Sterling, it's the government.
Even if it weren't legal,
they'd enforce it.
>> HOLLY: Hey, save it for four
ninths of the Supreme Court.
>> MALORY: Oh, shut up.
And unless there's
anything else?
>> HOLLY: Uh, just this,
releasing the bureau from any
claims relating to the death
of your employee...
Brett, uh, Bunson?
>> ARCHER: Oh, my God!
>> LANA: What?
>> ARCHER: Beaker's boss!
Bunsen frickin' Honeydew!
Woooooo!!
(groans)
That was figuratively
killing me.
>> ARCHER: I can't believe
they're taking our building.
>> LANA: Screw the building!
What about our jobs?
Oh, and our health insurance.
Which I'm pretty sure
I'm gonna need.
>> KRIEGER: I'll be your doctor.
>> LANA: Well, if I want
Hitler's DNA spliced into him,
I'll give you a call.
>> KRIEGER: Yeah, I'm around.
>> MALORY: Well, as for me, I
think I'll start shopping my
memoirs.
How does the title
Secrets and Silk grab you?
>> ARCHER: Tightly by my
childhood's throat.
>> MALORY: Oh, you're just
jealous.
>> CHERYL/CAROL: Yeah, jealous
of my fallback career.
>> PAM (laughing): As what?
An actual acorn?
>> CHERYL/CAROL: As America's
number one country singer.
>> LANA: And kudos.
But for the rest of us trapped
in the realm of possibility...
>> CHERYL/CAROL: I'm gonna be
bigger than Mac Davis.
And Mac Davis can
totally suck it.
>> ARCHER: And you can all suck
it because I am gonna play
professional lacrosse.
>> LANA: Okay, even if that were
a real thing...
>> ARCHER: Is it not?
>> LANA: ...you are way too old.
>> ARCHER: I am not...
Oh, my God. I am way too old.
(cracks knuckles)
>> PAM: Welp, hope I'm not too
old to get back into
underground fighting.
>> CYRIL: Darn.
All those jobs are awesome.
>> LANA: And by awesome you
mean delusional.
>> CYRIL: Because it's gonna
be hard to go back to an
accounting firm after this job.
>> ARCHER: Especially after
Mother gives you a shitty
reference.
Mother, do that.
>> CYRIL: I meant it'll be
boring.
Although, I guess
I could always go back
to being a defense attorney.
(all groaning)
>> LANA: When were you ever a
lawyer?
>> CYRIL: Lana, we had long
talks about this.
How I went to night school
to pass the CPA exam
because I was so burned out
defending scumbags
as a public defender?
Numerous... long talks.
>> LANA: With me?
>> CYRIL: Oh, for...
(Archer laughs)
Well, don't come crying to me
when that fatherless kid of
yours buys a gun and steals a
car, and he tries to run
but he don't get far!
>> CHERYL/CAROL: ¶ In the ghetto
where Mac Davis sucks it. ¶
>> ARCHER: Are you done?
>> CHERYL/CAROL: Are you done?!
Again, seriously asking.
>> ARCHER: Yes. So I guess we
should talk about the elephant
in the room. Namely...
What are we gonna do
with literally,
not figuratively,
a ton of cocaine?
>> MALORY: Well...
>> LANA: Wha...? Oh, come on!
>> ARCHER: What, Lana,
we must be talking...
>> CYRIL: Wholesale? Uh, 50, 60
million?
>> LANA (laughs): Wholesale.
So, what, we form a cartel?
>> MALORY: Well, how hard could
it be? I mean...
>> LANA: Don't.
>> MALORY: ...if Mexicans can
do it.
(ice clinks in glass)
>> ARCHER: $50 million, Lana.
We sell this and we're out.
I promise.
>> MALORY: Dr. Krieger has
devised a way to transport
the cocaine undetected.
>> ARCHER: You're probably gonna
want to try to minimize
the sweating.
We're gonna go ahead and take
the cocaine and the money.
>> MALORY: What do you mean
counterfeit?
>> ARCHER: The Yakuza?
>> MALORY: Amphetamines?!
>> ARCHER: Well, Pam screwed
the Yakuza out of a million
bucks of amphetamines, so now
they're gonna cut her head off.
>> CHERYL/CAROL: ¶ Baby, please
don't go ¶
>> ARCHER: Get down!
>> CHERYL/CAROL: ¶ Baby, please
don't go ¶
>> MALORY: Ron!
>> ARCHER: Yeah, this is
actually a little harder
than I thought.
>> CHERYL/CAROL: Because I don't
fly.
>> ARCHER: So, you've only got
24 hours to drive to Texas?
(laughing)
Did you tell anybody we were
hauling a shitload of coke?
>> CHERYL/CAROL: ¶ Yeah, your
girl done gone down to the
county farm ¶
Take me with you!
Outlaw country! Woooooo!!
>> MAN: Honey, you're number 14
nationwide.
>> ROY ACUFF: How bout a big ol'
country welcome for Cherlene!
>> CHERYL/CAROL: ¶ Before I be
your dog get you way down here
Make you walk alone
Baby, please don't go ¶
Woooooo!!
>> SANTOS: Incredible.
I must meet this woman.
>> CYRIL: Well, what do you
think is gonna happen
when three gringos waltz in
and start asking around
for the woman who runs
the entire Cali cartel?
>> ARCHER: Wooohooohooohoooo!!
(man grunts)
>> LANA: Are you sure you cannot
make love to me just once more?
>> ARCHER: Not without a blood
transfusion.
>> LANA: Very well.
>> ARCHER: Ow! Ow! Ow!
(yells)
>> CHERYL/CAROL: ¶ Baby, please
don't go down to New Orleans
You know I love you so
Baby, please don't go ¶
>> LANA: You're doing the exact
thing you promised me you
wouldn't!
>> ARCHER: I was kidding.
(tiger growls)
>> CHERYL/CAROL: ¶ Before I be
your dog
Before I be your dog ¶
>> SANTOS: Welcome to San
>> CHERYL/CAROL: ¶ Before I be
your dog get you way down here
And let you walk alone ¶
>> CYRIL: So, couple things.
>> ARCHER: Oh, goddamn it.
Did you fart in that?
>> CHERYL/ CAROL: ¶ You know how
I feel right now? ¶
(grunting)
¶ My baby's leaving
(laughing)
¶ On that midnight train
(siren blaring)
¶ And I'm crying
>> CYRIL: Suppressing fire!
>> CHERYL/CAROL: ¶ Baby, please
don't go ¶
>> ARCHER: Goddamn it, Cyril!
>> CHERYL/CAROL: ¶ Baby, please
don't go
Baby, please don't go ¶
>> HOLLY: You're running out
of options, Archer.
>> CHERYL/CAROL: ¶ Baby, please
don't go ¶
>> SANTOS: I want Archer dead!
>> CHERYL/CAROL: ¶ Baby, please
don't go down to New Orleans
You know I love you so
Baby, please don't go ¶
>> MALORY: I think you just
stumbled backwards
into a CIA arms deal.
(Cheryl/Carol screams)
(explosion)
>> RAY: They kidnapped Cherlene!
>> LANA: Archer!
>> PAM: We just started a
frickin' coup!
>> CHERYL/CAROL: ¶ Before I be
your dog get you way down here
Make you walk alone
Baby, please don't go, yeah ¶
>> LANA: Archer, my water just
broke.
>> CHERYL/CAROL: ¶ All right
now. ¶
>> ARCHER: And for what it's
worth, I'm pretty sure
I just invaded Laos.
(woman speaking Vietnamese)
And, Chi, I swear to God,
mention the compass again
and just see what happens.
(tiger roars)
>> ARCHER: Archer Vice.
>> LANA: What?
>> ARCHER: Nothing.
Shut up.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
>> MAN: Made... in Georgia.