♪ TA DUM,
LOCKING UP ♪
( chittering )
SHOO, POSSUM, SHOO.
GIT, McGUCKET, GIT!
♪ TA DUM, TA DUM
GOOD NIGHT, DINER.
GOOD NIGHT, TREES.
GOOD NIGHT, TINY MEN
STEALING MY PIE.
WAIT. WHAT?!
LIFT WITH YOUR KNEES.
NO, YOUR KNEES.
IF I GO ONE MORE
HOUR WITHOUT EATING,
I'M GONNA RESORT
TO CANNIBALISM.
MA'AM.
( shrieks )
LITTLE MAGIC MEN.
WHAT DOES IT MEAN?
WHAT DO I DO?
YES, HI.
I'D LIKE TO REPORT SOMETHING.
I'M AT GREASEY'S DINER.
YOU WON'T BELIEVE
WHAT I'VE WITNESSED.
IT'S UNBELIEVABLE.
IT'S INDESCRIBABLE.
IT'S...
( screaming )
IT IS UNSEEN.
WELL, BACK TO PIE.
I WAS THIS CLOSE
TO EATING YOU, STEVE.
♪
ALL RIGHT, AUTHOR,
WHO ARE YOU?
WHO ARE...
BLECCCH!
( coughs )
NOT AGAIN.
HEY, BRO-BRO,
LOOK WHAT I GOT.
YAY, A FILTHY
GREEN BOTTLE.
IT'S A BOTTLE MESSAGE
FROM MERMANDO, REMEMBER?
HE WAS PART FISH,
PART SHIRTLESS GUY.
( gasps ) WHAT IF HE WANTS
TO GET BACK TOGETHER?
I WOULDN'T GET
YOUR HOPES UP, MABEL.
TOO LATE.
HOPES ARE WAY, WAY UP!
( squeals excitedly )
"DEAR MABEL..."
SO FAR SO GOOD.
"IT IS WITH
A HEAVY HEART..."
SO FAR, SO GOOD.
"THAT I MUST INFORM YOU,
I'M GETTING MARRIED"?!
AND THERE IT IS.
"IN ORDER TO PREVENT
AN UNDERSEA CIVIL WAR,
ARRANGED WEDDING,
QUEEN OF THE MANATEES..."
AND SHE'S SO BEAUTIFUL.
THIS CAN'T BE HAPPENING.
OH, MABEL, YOU'LL
GET OVER HIM EVENTUALLY.
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND,
DIPPER.
ON MY FIRST DAY HERE,
I MADE THIS PAGE FOR
SUMMER ROMANCES.
LOOK AT MY LUCK.
TURNED OUT TO BE GNOMES,
CHILD PSYCHO,
MADE OUT WITH
HIS OWN HANDS.
AND NOW...
I WISH I COULD JUST
FORGET ABOUT THEM FOREVER.
HEY, IF IT'S
ANY CONSOLATION,
MY SUMMER MISSION
ISN'T A HUGE
SUCCESS EITHER.
I'M STILL TRYING TO FIND
THE AUTHOR OF THIS JOURNAL.
WITH HIS LAPTOP SMASHED,
I'VE LOST ANY LEAD
IN FINDING HIM.
WAIT A MINUTE.
DIPPER, LOOK!
- THROUGH YOUR BOTTLE?
- JUST DO IT.
"McGUCKET LABS."
WAIT. OLD MAN McGUCKET?
DIPPER, YOU DON'T THINK...
COULDN'T BE.
DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE,
UNLESS...
THIS MATCHES
WITH THIS.
THIS GOES OVER HERE.
AND THEN THE NAME...
SO THAT WOULD MEAN
OLD MAN McGUCKET
WROTE THE JOURNAL?!
♪ AM I BLANCHIN', GIRL,
WE BLANCHIN' ♪
♪  I LIVE UP IN
A MANSION ♪
♪ AM I BLANCHIN', GIRL,
WE BLANCHIN' ♪
♪ I LIVE UP IN
A MANSION ♪
UGH! I CAN'T GET
THAT TERRIBLE SONG
OUT OF MY HEAD.
YOU MEAN "STRAIGHT BLANCHIN'"
BY LI'L BIG DAWG?
IT'S THE CATCHIEST
SONG OF THE SUMMER.
WHAT IS BLANCHIN'?
RAPPERS CAN'T JUST
MAKE UP WORDS.
RAPPERS ARE VISIONARIES,
WENDY.
IF THEY TOLD ME
TO EAT MY OWN PANTS,
I WOULD DO IT.
♪ EAT YOUR OWN PANTS,
EAT YOUR OWN PANTS ♪
I GUESS I HAVE NO CHOICE.
WENDY, SOOS, WE NEED TO
GO SEE OLD MAN McGUCKET.
- WE'LL EXPLAIN
ON THE WAY.
- GAH!
HEY, WHAT ABOUT WORK?
KIDS!
WHY IS SOOS
EATING HIS OWN PANTS?
OLD MAN McGUCKET,
ARE YOU HERE?
HERE, HILLBILLY,
BILLY, BILLY, BILLY.
( laughing )
TOOK AN HOUR
TO THINK OF THIS,
BUT IT WAS WORTH IT.
Both: HA!
GET OUTTA HERE,
YOU SALT LICKIN',
HORNSWAGGLIN'...
McSUCKIT.
THEY GOT ME GOOD.
VISITORS!
COME, COME.
PULL UP SOME RUSTY METAL.
YOU'RE JUST IN TIME
FOR MY HOURLY TURF WAR
WITH THE HILLBILLY
WHAT LIVES IN
MY MIRROR.
QUIT STARIN' AT ME
WHEN I BATHE!
YOU CAN DROP
THE ACT, McGUCKET.
I KNOW YOU'RE
THE AUTHOR.
YOU STUDIED THE
MYSTERIES OF THIS
TOWN AND WROTE THIS BOOK.
DUDE, YOU'RE THE GENIUS
DIPPER'S BEEN SEARCHING
FOR ALL SUMMER.
UH, GENIUS?
I'M NO GENIUS.
I NEVER DONE NOTHIN'
WORTHWHILE IN MY LIFE.
EVERYONE KNOWS
I'M NO GOOD TO NOBODY.
I CAN'T REMEMBER
WHAT I USED TO BE,
BUT I MUST'VE BEEN A BIG
FAILURE TO END UP LIKE THIS.
BUT THE LAPTOP HAS
YOUR NAME ON IT.
WHAT ABOUT THIS BOOK?
ARE YOU SURE YOU
DIDN'T WRITE IT?
HERE, LOOK CLOSELY.
I TOLD YOU,
I DON'T RECALL.
EVERYTHING BEFORE
1982 IS JUST A BLUR.
JUST A HAZY...
( shrieks )
THE BLIND EYE!
ROBES. THE MEN.
MY MIND.
- THEY DID SOMETHING.
- WHO DID?
I... OH,
I DON'T RECALL.
OH, YOU POOR OLD MAN.
NO WONDER YOUR MIND'S ALL
( blows raspberry).
YOU'VE BEEN THROUGH
SOMETHING INTENSE.
WHAT IF McGUCKET
LEARNED SOMETHING
HE WASN'T
SUPPOSED TO KNOW,
AND SOMEONE, OR SOMETHING,
MESSED WITH HIS MIND?
WE'VE GOT TO GET
TO THE BOTTOM OF THIS.
THINK, DUDE.
WHAT IS THE EARLIEST
THING YOU CAN REMEMBER?
UH, THIS IS,
I THINK.
Wendy:
THE HISTORY MUSEUM.
THAT'S WHERE WE'RE GOING.
♪ AM I BLANCHIN', GIRL,
WE BLANCHIN' ♪
UGH, SOOS!
UGH!!
I'LL BUY YOU
A NEW ONE.
HELLO? ANYONE HERE?
ALL RIGHT,
KEEP YOUR EYES PEELED
FOR ANYTHING
SUSPICIOUS.
( sighs )
MABEL, ARE YOU OKAY?
YOU JUST WALKED BY
A CAT WITHOUT PETTING IT.
OH, WENDY, EVERYTHING
I LOOK AT
REMINDS ME OF
MY FAILED ROMANCES.
THAT FORMALDEHYDE HEART.
THAT ROMANTIC DIORAMA.
EVEN THIS POSTER OF
MY MOST RECENT EX-CRUSH.
AW, COME ON!
SO YOUR LAST
MEMORY WAS HERE.
- ANYTHING COMING BACK?
- GUYS, LOOK!
Dipper:
HEY, WHO'S THERE?
WELL, KETTLE MY CORN.
HE VANISH-IFIED.
IT DOESN'T MAKE SENSE.
WHERE DID HE GO?
I FEEL LIKE
ALL THESE EYEBALLS
ARE A-WATCHIN' ME.
WAIT.
THEY ARE.
MOVE ASIDE.
JACKPOT!
A SECRET PASSAGEWAY.
WE'LL HAVE TO BE
STEALTHY.
I'LL HAMBONE A MESSAGE
IF THERE'S TROUBLE.
I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT THAT MEANS.
( voices chanting )
( chanting continues )
WHO IS THE SUBJECT
OF OUR MEETING?
( gasping )
THIS WOMAN.
LAZY SUSAN?
WHAT IS IT
THAT YOU HAVE SEEN?
All: SPEAK!
UH, WELL, UH,
I WAS LEAVING THE DINER,
AND I SAW THESE LITTLE
BEARDED DOODADS,
AND I WAS, LIKE,
"WHAAAA?"
THERE, THERE.
YOU WON'T BE
"LIKE WHAAAA"
FOR MUCH LONGER.
WHAT IS THAT GIZMO?
IT LOOKS LIKE
A HAIR DRYER.
ARE YOU GUYS BARBERS?
( screaming )
LAZY SUSAN, WHAT DO YOU
KNOW OF LITTLE BEARDED MEN?
MY MIND IS CLEAR,
THANKS TO THE SOCIETY
OF THE BLIND EYE.
All: IT IS UNSEEN.
OH, MY GOSH.
THEY ERASED
LAZY SUSAN'S MEMORY.
GUYS, ARE YOU
SEEING THIS?
THEY JUST WIPED
LAZY SUSAN'S MEMORY.
THEY SHOULD'VE WIPED OFF
THAT AWFUL MASCARA.
I THINK SHE
LOOKS BEAUTIFUL.
SHE'S DOING THE BEST
SHE CAN, SOOS.
WHOA, TOUCHED
A NERVE THERE.
LAZY SUSAN,
HOW DO YOU FEEL?
I FEEL GREAT!
I CAN'T EVEN
REMEMBER WHAT WAS WRONG,
OR WHAT I'M DOING HERE,
OR IF I'M
A MAN OR A WOMAN.
YOUR MEMORIES
WILL BE SAFE WITH US,
BURIED IN THE HALL
OF THE FORGOTTEN.
Robed Men: INTO THE HALL
INTO THE HALL
OF THE FORGOTTEN.
GOOD CHANTING, BOYS.
HAVE YOU BEEN PRACTICING?
( all gasping )
MEETING ADJOURNED.
- UNSEE YOU LATER.
UNSEE YOU LATER.
AMAZING.
A SECRET SOCIETY
OF EVIL MIND ERASERS.
I'LL BET THEY ERASED
YOUR MEMORY A LONG TIME AGO.
IF WE COULD FIND
WHERE YOUR MEMORIES
HAVE BEEN HIDDEN,
IT COULD BE THE KEY
TO UNLOCKING
ALL THE MYSTERIES
OF GRAVITY FALLS.
ALL RIGHT,
MABEL, WENDY,
YOU TWO STAY HERE
AND MAKE SURE THOSE
ROBE GUYS DON'T COME BACK.
WHOOO! GIRLS CLUB.
SOOS, YOU, ME,
AND McGUCKET
ARE GONNA GO FIND
THE HALL OF THE FORGOTTEN.
- ( sucking sound )
- WHOA!
FOLLOW THAT HAT!
Robed Man: HALT!
IS SOMEONE THERE?
AAH! WHAT DO WE DO?
WHERE DO WE GO?
MAN, THESE ARE
REALLY POORLY MADE.
I COULD'VE SWORN
I HEARD SOMEONE.
PROBABLY JUST
THE JANITOR
KISSING THAT WAX
SETTLER WOMAN AGAIN.
WOOF! REMIND ME TO
ERASE THAT FROM MY MEMORY.
WHEW! THERE IT IS.
HURRY!
HONEY FOGELIN',
SALT LICKIN' SKULLDUGGERY.
MAN, YOU HAVE GOT TO
TEACH ME SOME OF THOSE
OLD-MAN SWEAR WORDS.
( sighs )
I JUST DON'T
GET IT, WENDY.
I HUG A LOT, I CAN
BURP THE ALPHABET,
I HAVE SCRATCH
AND SNIFF CLOTHING.
WHY DOES EVERY BOY
LEAVE ME?
PFFT, WHO CARES?
BOYS ARE THE WORST.
YOU SHOULDN'T GET
HUNG UP, MAN.
MAYBE I COME ON
TOO STRONG, YOU KNOW?
WELL, WHAT'S
YOUR OPENER?
PRETEND I'M A BOY.
MMM, TESTOSTERONE.
( spits )
( loudly ) HI. I'M MABEL!
I'M 12 AND OWN A PIG!
WANNA GET MARRIED?!
( laughs )
HONESTLY? THAT WAS PERFECT.
YOU SHOULD JUST
FORGET ABOUT GUYS, MAN.
WENDY, THAT'S IT.
FORGET ABOUT GUYS.
I JUST NEED TO TYPE
"SUMMER ROMANCES"
INTO THIS THING,
AND I WON'T FEEL
BAD ABOUT THEM ANYMORE.
WHOA, HOLD UP, MABEL.
WE DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT THAT THING DOES.
YOU COULD ACCIDENTALLY
ERASE, LIKE,
LEARNING TO READ
OR BREATHE OR...
OR ONE OF THOSE
TERRIBLE SUMMER SONGS
YOU CAN'T GET
OUT OF YOUR HEAD?
LOOK AT ALL THESE TUBES.
PEOPLE MUST'VE BEEN
GETTING THEIR MEMORIES
ERASED ALL OVER TOWN.
WHOA, LOOK AT THIS.
YES, ROBBIE, WHAT IS IT
THAT YOU HAVE SEEN?
SO I WAS ATTACKED BY
THIS MAGIC KUNG FU GUY
THAT WAS THROWING, LIKE,
BALLS OF FIRE AT ME.
I KICKED HIS BUTT,
THOUGH.
ROBBIE,
SPEAK HONESTLY.
I WAS SAVED BY
A 12-YEAR-OLD.
WHY ARE THEY ERASING
PEOPLE'S MEMORIES?
I STILL DON'T GET IT.
LOOKY, FELLERS.
IT'S THOSE WORDS
WHAT PEOPLE CALL ME.
OH, DUDE, YOUR MEMORIES.
WE DID IT.
GRABBY GRABBY.
( beeping )
I GOT IT!
I DON'T KNOW, MABEL.
ARE YOU REALLY SURE
THIS IS A GOOD IDEA?
ALL IDEAS ARE GOOD IDEAS.
- ( loud beeping )
- DO YOU HEAR THAT?
THE ALARM IN MY BRAIN
IS A-RINGIN' AGAIN. AH!
HALT! WHO'S THERE?
- OH, NO!
- RUN.
GET BACK HERE!
OH, YOU'VE REALLY
TARRED IT UP NOW, FIDDLEFORD.
THIS IS ALL YOUR FAULT.
WHY DOES MY BEARD
HAVE A BANDAGE?
DOES THAT EVEN MAKE SENSE?
WHY HAS NO ONE
POINTED THAT OUT?
OKAY, I THINK
WE'RE SAFE.
WE PLAYING
"GUESS WHO"?
DUDE, I KNOW
IT'S YOU, DIPPER.
SUCH BIG, STRONG HANDS.
( chanting )
YOU SHOULDN'T
HAVE COME HERE.
WE DO NOT GIVE UP
OUR SECRETS LIGHTLY.
WHO ARE YOU
BATHROBE-WEARING FREAKS?
WHY ARE YOU
DOING THIS?
WHAT'S WITH YOUR CREEPY
BRITISH ACCENT?
WELL, I SUPPOSE WE ARE GOING
TO ERASE YOUR MINDS ANYWAY.
Mabel:
TOBY DETERMINED?
Dipper:
BUD GLEEFUL?
Wendy:
THAT FARMER GUY?
CREEPY DUDE WHO
MARRIED A WOODPECKER?
YOU, TOO?
HOW'S THAT MARRIAGE
GOIN', BY THE WAY?
OH, GREAT, GREAT.
( whispering )
NOT GREAT.
AND YOU'VE NEVER
MET ME BEFORE.
AND IF YOU HAD,
YOU WOULDN'T REMEMBER.
I AM BLIND IVAN,
AND WE ARE THE SOCIETY
OF THE BLIND EYE.
FORMED MANY YEARS AGO
BY OUR FOUNDER...
OUR FOUNDER... DOES
ANYONE REMEMBER WHO HE WAS?
WE'VE BEEN USIN'
THAT RAY ON OUR OWN
BRAINS AN AWFUL LOT.
WHY WOULD YOU DO ALL THIS?
WHAT DO YOU HAVE TO GAIN?
AS YOU HAVE
NO DOUBT DISCOVERED,
GRAVITY FALLS
IS A TOWN PLAGUED
WITH SUPERNATURAL
STRANGENESS.
NO ONE KNEW HOW TO STOP
THE THINGS THAT WENT
BUMP IN THE NIGHT,
SO OUR FOUNDER INVENTED
THE NEXT BEST THING--
A WAY FOR US
TO FORGET.
WE TOOK IT
UPON OURSELVES
TO HELP THE TROUBLED
TOWNSFOLK
BY ERASING THE MEMORIES OF THE
STRANGE THINGS THEY'VE SEEN.
NOW THE PEOPLE OF
GRAVITY FALLS
GO ABOUT THEIR LIVES
IGNORANT AND HAPPY,
THANKS TO US.
AND AS A PERK,
WE HELP OURSELVES
FORGET THINGS THAT
TROUBLE US.
EVERYONE HAS SOMETHING
THEY'D RATHER FORGET.
IN FACT, YOUR OWN SISTER
WAS ABOUT TO USE
THAT RAY ON HERSELF.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT?
MABEL? SERIOUSLY?
HA-HA. MAYBE.
DON'T YOU SEE?
THIS IS RUINING LIVES.
WHAT ABOUT
OLD MAN McGUCKET?
HE LIVES IN A HUT
AND TALKS TO ANIMALS,
THANKS TO YOU.
DON'T YOU FEEL
BAD ABOUT THAT?
MMM, MAYBE A LITTLE.
BUT NOT ANYMORE.
YOU WON'T BE TELLING ANYONE
ELSE WHAT YOU'VE LEARNED HERE.
SAY GOOD-BYE
TO YOUR SUMMER.
GUYS, IF WE'RE GONNA
FORGET EVERYTHING,
I GOT SOME STUFF I WANNA
GET OFF MY CHEST.
MABEL, FOR HALF THE SUMMER,
I THOUGHT YOUR NAME WAS MAPLE,
LIKE THE SYRUP.
NO ONE CORRECTED ME.
I ONLY LOVE
SOME OF MY STUFFED ANIMALS,
AND THE GUILT
IS KILLING ME!
SOMETIMES I USE BIG WORDS
AND I DON'T ACTUALLY KNOW
WHAT THEY MEAN.
I MEAN, I'M SUPPOSED
TO BE THE SMART GUY.
IF I'M NOT THE SMART GUY,
WHO AM I?
OKAY, I'M NOT
ACTUALLY LAID BACK.
I'M STRESSED,
LIKE, 24/7.
HAVE YOU MET MY FAMILY?
( all talking at once )
OH, STOP BEING
A BUNCH OF BABIES.
- OWIE!
- ( all gasping )
All: McGUCKET?!
I RAIDED THE MINING
DISPLAY FOR WEAPONS.
NOW FIGHT LIKE
A HILLBILLY, FELLERS.
NOBODY BETTER MESS.
THEY KNOW TOO MUCH.
DON'T LET THEM ESCAPE!
GET THIS SONG
OUTTA YOUR HEAD.
DYSENTERY'S GONNA
GET YOU, DAWG.
I GOTTA GET
THE MEMORY TUBE.
OH, NO, YOU DON'T.
( shrieks )
MABEL, CATCH.
I'LL TAKE THAT,
THANK YOU.
GIVE IT UP, BOY.
YOU'RE NO MATCH FOR
THE UNSTOPPABLE POWER OF...
THAT'S RIGHT, I DON'T WEAR
NOTHIN' UNDER MY ROBE.
NOT GONNA APOLOGIZE
FOR THAT.
MAYBE Y'ALL SHOULD APOLOGIZE
FOR BEIN' A BUNCH OF PRUDES.
All: EWW!!
TIME TO ERASE
THAT FOREVER.
- GIVE ME THAT TUBE.
- NEVER!
THAT MEMORY BELONGS
TO McGUCKET.
THE SOCIETY'S SECRETS
BELONG TO US.
END OF THE LINE.
BY TOMORROW, THIS WILL
ALL SEEM LIKE A BAD DREAM.
SAY GOOD-BYE TO
YOUR PRECIOUS MEMORIES.
NO!!
McGUCKET, YOU TOOK
A BULLET FOR ME.
OH, MY GOSH!
ARE YOU OKAY?
OKAY AS I'LL EVER BE.
( laughs )
WHAT?
WHY... ISN'T...
THIS... WORKING?
HIT ME WITH
YOUR BEST SHOT, BALDY.
MY MIND'S BEEN GONE
FOR 30-ODD YEARS.
YOU CAN'T BREAK
WHAT'S ALREADY BROKEN.
SAY GOOD NIGHT,
SALLY.
UNHAND US!
IT ISN'T SO FUN
BEING TIED UP, IS IT?
- HEY, WANNA DRAW
ON THEIR FACES?
- WHAT?
- TRA-LA-LA...
- HEY, STOP THAT!
THAT'S NOT FUNNY.
IT'S PRETTY FUNNY.
IT'S, LIKE,
OBJECTIVELY FUNNY.
WE'LL HAVE OUR REVENGE.
WE'LL NEVER FORGET
WHAT YOU'VE DONE.
OH, I THINK
YOU JUST MIGHT.
SAY CHEESE.
( all protesting )
THANKS FOR VISITING
THE MUSEUM FOR GOLD MINER
APPRECIATION NIGHT.
BE SURE TO TIP
THE GOLD MINER
ON YOUR WAY OUT.
I'M SORRY,
BUT WHAT'S MY NAME?
WHERE AM I?
OH, MIGHT HAVE
OVERDONE THAT ONE.
YOUR NAME IS
TOOT-TOOT McBUMBERSNAZZLE.
YOU'RE A TRAVELING
BANJO MINSTREL,
WITH A SONG
IN YOUR HEART
AND FUNNY TATTOOS
ON YOUR HEAD.
YES, I AM TOOT-TOOT
McBUMBERSNAZZLE. CHEERS!
♪ TOOT-TOOT
IS MY NAME ♪
ALL RIGHT,
McGUCKET.
ARE YOU READY
TO SEE YOUR MEMORIES?
FIND OUT WHO
YOU REALLY ARE?
I'M NOT SO SURE.
WHAT IF I DON'T
LIKE WHAT I SEE?
WE'VE COME
ALL THIS WAY.
GO ON.
MY NAME IS
FIDDLEFORD HADRON McGUCKET,
AND I WISH TO UNSEE
WHAT I HAVE SEEN.
( all gasping )
SWEET SARSAPARILLA.
FOR THE PAST YEAR,
I HAVE BEEN WORKING
AS AN ASSISTANT
FOR A VISITING RESEARCHER.
HE HAS BEEN CATALOGUING
HIS FINDINGS
ABOUT GRAVITY FALLS
IN A SERIES OF JOURNALS.
I HELPED HIM
BUILD A MACHINE
WHICH HE BELIEVED
HAD THE POTENTIAL
TO BENEFIT ALL MANKIND,
BUT SOMETHING WENT WRONG.
I DECIDED
TO QUIT THE PROJECT.
BUT I LIE AWAKE
AT NIGHT,
HAUNTED BY THE THOUGHTS
OF WHAT I'VE DONE.
I BELIEVE I HAVE
INVENTED A MACHINE
THAT CAN PERMANENTLY
ERASE THESE MEMORIES
FROM MY MIND.
TEST SUBJECT ONE.
FIDDLEFORD.
IT WORKED!
I CAN'T RECALL A THING.
I CALL IT THE SOCIETY
OF THE BLIND EYE.
WE WILL HELP THOSE
WHO WANT TO FORGET
BY ERASING
THEIR BAD MEMORIES.
TODAY, I CAME ACROSS
A COLONY OF LITTLE MEN.
VERY DISTURBING.
I WOULD LIKE TO FORGET
SEEING THIS.
I ACCIDENTALLY
HIT ANOTHER CAR IN TOWN TODAY.
I FEEL TERRI-BIBBLE.
TERRIBLE.
I'VE BEEN FORGETTING
WORDS LATELY.
I WONDER IF THERE ARE
ANY NEGATIVE SIDE EFFECTS...
I SAW SOMETHING IN
THE LAKE, SOMETHING BIG!
MY HAIR'S BEEN
A-FALLIN' OUT,
SO I GOT THIS HAT
FROM A SCARECROW.
HEY, ARE MY PANTS
ON BACKWARDS?
( maniacal giggling
and speaking gibberish )
OH, McGUCKET.
I'M SO SORRY.
AW, HUSH.
YOU KIDS HELPED ME
GET MY MEMORIES BACK,
JUST LIKE YOU SAID.
BUT DID YOU WANT
THOSE MEMORIES BACK?
AFTER ALL THESE YEARS,
I FINALLY KNOW WHO I AM.
MAYBE I MESSED UP
IN THE PAST,
BUT NOW THAT I SEEN
WHAT HAPPENED,
I CAN BEGIN TO PUT
MYSELF TOGETHER AGAIN.
STILL DON'T KNOW
WHAT THAT MEANS.
SO, WAIT, YOU WEREN'T
THE AUTHOR, BUT YOU
WORKED WITH HIM.
DO YOU REMEMBER
WHO HE WAS?
IT'S BEGINNING
TO COME BACK,
BUT I NEED MORE TIME.
AND READING GLASSES.
HECK!
( spits ) I GOT SOME
REMEMBERIN' TO DO.
SO, MABEL,
YOU STILL WANNA ERASE
THOSE FAILED
SUMMER ROMANCES?
YOU KNOW, NO ONE LIKES
HAVING BAD MEMORIES,
BUT MAYBE IT'S BETTER
TO REMEMBER THE BAD THINGS
AND LEARN FROM THEM
THAN TO GO ALL
DENIAL CRAZY TRYING TO FORGET.
THAT'S SOME MATURE
JUNK RIGHT THERE, MABEL.
YEP. MISS MATURE.
THAT'S ME.
HEY, YOU WANNA HELP ME
VANDALIZE THIS PICTURE
OF MY JERKY EX-CRUSH?
OOH, YEAH!
WAIT, LET'S GIVE HIM
BUCK TEETH.
GOING ON THIS BIG ADVENTURE
ACTUALLY MADE ME GET
- THAT STUPID SONG
OUT OF MY HEAD.
- Soos: NICE.
♪ AM I BLANCHIN', GIRL,
WE BLANCHIN' ♪
OH, COME ON!
IT'S ALL SO FAMILIAR.
IT'S ALMOST LIKE
I CAN REMEMBER.
ALL RIGHT,
YOU'RE GETTING CLOSER.
EVERY DAY,
IT'S GETTING STRONGER.
HA! YES! AH!
I DON'T CARE
IF IT'S DANGEROUS.
HOW LONG IT TAKES.
I'M GONNA PULL THIS OFF,
AND NO ONE'S GONNA
GET IN MY WAY.