All aboard for safety and adventure
On the rigid airship excelsior,
Where the pampered luxury of a cruise ship meets
The smoothness of modern air travel.
Yes, when you fly excelsior,
You're flying in style and safety.
Safety?
But isn't hydrogen flammable?
And how, timmy.
That's why excelsior is filled with safe, natural helium.
Why, it's actually flame-retardant.
Neat! and safe.
So, whether you're enjoying excelsior's majestic vistas,
Duty-free shopping, high-stakes baccarat,
Dancing with your lovely wife,
Or even a cigar after a french gourmet dinner,
You'll be enjoying them in style and safety.
All aboard excelsior!
Who would want to put a bomb on that?
Well, that's what we're hoping isis can find out.
Archer: no, why bother?
Some broad gets on there with a staticky sweater and, boom,
It's, "oh, the humanity!"
No, no, that's --
Malory: sterling.
Were you watching some other blimp commercial just now?
Technically, it's a rigid airship.
Malory: filled with helium.
Lana: which is nonflammable. dumbass.
I thought our promotional video covered that fairly well.
Malory: oh, and how. sterling, it's totally safe.
Well, except for the bomb threat.
Malory: no, not to worry, dear.
Isis won't let terrorists blow up your lovely blimp.
- rigid airship.  - my top two agents will be on board.
- nope!  - and i will oversee the operation personally from
What i assume will be first-class accommodations.
Ooh, actually, we are fully booked.
Well, if you think -- oh, i don't know --
This trudy beekman person can thwart a major terror plot --
I suppose we could bump mrs. beekman.
Bump me. i'm not going. if these two can share a cabin.
- nope! - not going to let the terrorists win.
- we'll pose as husband and wife. - nope!
Cyril would totally freak.
Malory, come on, let me stay with you,
And we'll do the whole oprah/gayle thing.
Malory: nope! i need a stateroom to myself,
In case i have a gentleman caller.
Archer: mother, please. lana: please.
Do not make me do this.
Malory: but, lana, think of the nocent lives you'll be saving
And also the fact that this is a direct order.
Lana: at least, tell me it's separate beds.
Lana. lana. lana. lan-a-a-a!
Lana: what?
Danger zone
Terrible, awful, just gut-wrenchingly bad feeling about this.
Baby, i really need you to trust me, okay?
Now, is the cabin small? yes.
And yet, surprising amount of storage.
Ugh, and i will hardly be in here, okay,
Because i've got a terrorist to find,
And i doubt he's hiding under -- what's basically a twin bed.
Archer!
Since it's all drawers under here because look how tiny this room is.
Oh, my god. it's like a broom closet.
And yet a surprising amount of storage.
Oh, shut up.
And, cyril, very eager to know why you're still here.
He was just -- helping lana get settled.
Trust me, cyril. she already settled.
Disembark, cyril.
We're about to launch... or whatever blimps do.
Yeah, what does a blimp do, pam?
Uh, kick your skinny ass!
Now, come on. we got to get off this thing before --
Rela-a-a-x.god, we've got half an hour.
Oh, well, then, make me a double campari and, uh...
I guess, vodka.
We don't normally drink on the bridge.
Well, i don't normally fly on the hindenburg 2.0,
And cyril doesn't normally storm off without even kissing me goodbye.
- so we're all out of our comfort zone. - not me.
My stateroom is gorgeous.
Malory: that -- what's her name? -- beekman,
I bet she's just sick she got bumped.
Yes, she literally vomited from anger,
So if we could just focus on the bomb threat.
Lana: how about crew members?
Anyone who might be disgruntled?
Achtung!
That's lieutenant krauss.
He and i were both up for command of the excelsior, but --
You got it.
Leaving him with motive.
Release the mooring cable.
Come on, it's not larry luftwaffe.
That's --
Oopsie.
Ugh, way too obvious.
God damn it!
We're moving!
I know!
What happened to half an hour?
I lied.
Wh-- why the --
Why the hell are you two still here?
Because i knew you'd be here with mr. archer.
No, no, now, that is --
So ironic, cyril, especially in light of recent...
No. ...rug-burny events. oh, my god!
You two banged?!
I, uh --
See, here's the thing. etfruibasket!
You are just a dog in a manger.
I don't know what that means, pam.
I didn't grow up on a cheese farm.
Oh, for the -- it's called a dairy.
And even the slightest hint of a problem on our maiden
Voyage would kill excelsior's stock price.
So, lana, canvass the passengers and crew,
Learn what you can about krauss -- but, please, be discreet.
Lana: hey, good advice!
Which maybe i'll just sort of
Fold in with my 12 years of experience as a covert operative!
Malory: don't be snotty!
Malory: and, sterling, if there is a bomb, captain, dear,
Where would it do the most damage? probably --
Archer: uh, this new place called anywhere.
This whole thing's a bomb. it's not --
Archer: jesus!
Want to blow us all to shit, sherlock?!
Malory: sterling! archer: what?!
For the last time, the excelsior is filled with nonflammable helium!
Although this is a non-smoking area, sir.
Damn it, he's a prospective investor.
Not after that, i bet.
Forget about krauss.
There's your bomber.
Who?
What?!
That guy.
Beardsley mcturbinhead.
You idiot.
That's sandu singh, the billionaire investor.
He's a sikh.
Oh, so if he's not a muslim, he just gets a pass?
Well, that's called profiling,
Mother, and i don't do it.
Mr. singh is excelsior's majority shareholder.so?
If anything went wrong on this flight, he'd lose millions.
It's a perfect cover. sterling.
Lana: just go look for the stupid bomb.
Relax, what do we have, like four hours before we get to london?
Lana: four hours? malory: are you joking?
The crossing takes 24 hours.
Archer: are you joking?
What? rigid airships combine the pampering of a cruise ship
With the speed of -- some other slightly faster ship?
Uh, hello. airplanes?
Yeah, it's blimps. you win. bye.
Oh, god.
I hope you didn't invest in this.
It'll be fine, though... blimps are terrible.
...as long as nothing goes wrong on this flight.
Oh, captain, my captain, with isis on board,
What could possibly go wrong?
Pick one.
Either "a," i tell lana what
Happened on that scratchy green
Office rug, or two, you get inside me.
Or, "c," maybe i just
Jam this mop into the engine and kill all of us.
I don't think that's how blimps work.
Darn! right, we just sort of float around.
Stupid, naturally safe helium.
But i am liking the jamming imagery.
And the killing.
And are you just gonna sit there?
Yeah, until she tags me in.
What?! i'm kidding!
My back's all messed up.
So, you're ruining cyril's life because,
In your dream-the-impossible-dream world,
It'll make mr. archer jealous?
Oh, pamela.
Yeah?
What's the poem gonna be about when cyril snaps and murders you?
I don't know.
World's gushiest orgasm?
Can you just get out of the way?
What? are you gonna shoot me again?
Yes!
Oh.
Well, then, hang on.
Cyril is already freaked out enough about us sharing
This shoebox without you air-drying your unkempt bush.
Unkempt bush?!
Um, you're one to talk!
My vulva is smoother than a veal cutlet!
What terrible timing. oh, really?
Baby -- did i interrupt something?
Uh, rehearsal with your commodores tribute band.
Archer! cyril, what are you doing here?
I wanted to tell you something very important,
But apparently, you're too busy showing off your vealy vulva!
Cyril!
You know, your whole trust thing -- and i've tried to, okay?
You know what?
We are on a break! oh, yeah?
Yeah!
Well, that's fine by me!
Cyril, wait!
No running! shut up!
- oh, my god. what have i done?- what are you doing?
Go after him.
Oh, you think i should?
Yes!
We're almost out of fruit.
Which is why i find it strange that you're so incredibly calm!
Well, that seaweed wrap just slurps out the stress.
Can't wait to tell trudy beekman
All about it, uh, if we ever meet.
What about you? anything on krauss?
No. shut up.
Have you seen cyril?
Why would i have?
And what the hell is he doing?
Archer: hey, what did i tell you, huh?!
Archer: huh?! there!
Go buy a nicotine patch!
Gentlemen.
No, no, no! what happened to discretion?
Lana: what happened to that bartender?
Malory: right?
Guy sees an empty glass, and all of a sudden, he's judge crater.
Oh, for god's sake! nigel, some chips for mr. --
Archer: archer. sterling archer.
The minimum bet is 10,000, sir -- dollars.
Archer: oh, i stuffed all my money in that guy's mouth.
Well, perhaps we could play for something much more interesting.
Archer: yeah, 'cause that was seriously,
Like, all the cash i had on me, so...
So, if i win, i spend a night of passion with your exquisite wife.
Archer: my what?
Oh, yes, my wife. of course.
Yeah, it's a deal.
But if i win, you tell me where the bomb --
Baccarat! archer: what?
Mr. singh wins.
Archer: wait, wait, wait. we were going?
The von zeppelin suite.
I shall expect her within the hour.
Archer: she's not gonna be happy about that.
Um, what, are you mostly paid in tips?
Almost entirely, sir.
Well, whose fault is that?  i -- you --
Malory: prancing around in your fiacci knockoffs,
Blathering about your vulva?
Lana: hey, first of all --
Malory: i'm just saying,
You're driving cyril straight toward another woman.
Lana: cyril? with another woman?
Mallory, seriously. look at me.
Look at and choke me!
Oh, yes, yes!
Oh, my god, what am i doing?
You're ruining your life, you idiot!
And making it hard to drop a deuce.
Uh, i'm sorry, what?
You. now.
Led zeppelin suite.
You have no proof
Singh's e bomber.
He hinted, lana...
That's profiling.
...that the proof was in his cabin.
Really?
Yes!
So go down there and find it
While i go find the bomb.
Bombs, bombers, vulvas.
You people are just ruining my trip
Well, don't stand here gaping at me!
Go thwart something!
No running!
Zip it, zipperface!
Oh, kidding, sorry.
Hey, have you seen that nerdy
Fruit-basket steward?
Uh, check the kaiser wilhelm suite.
Names on the -- hey, what
Were you doi
Thied
Pers, so don't
It'sboten!
Okay.
Probably merits a archer
Cyril, what are -
Archer, i need your help.
Ink i'm losingre, man.
What gave it away?
My mother's -- why are you
Wearing my mother's robe?!
I can explain this!
I don't think i want you to.
See, it all started
When you and lana --
Cyril, you should tell her this.
I tried!
But you were naked, and it was
All vulva this and vulva that.
Yeah, and as you
Stand here, dick and/or balls
Caressed by my mother's robe --
Ugh! -- lana is waiting for you.
Really? where?
The led zeppelin suite.
There's a von zeppelin suite.
Which i'm sure is what i meant, so go!
Thanks, archer.
You're the best. i know.
So, yes, the bottom
Line is that i was unfaithful to you two
Well, three times, i guess, if a dry-humpy choker counts.
And if you can't see it in your heart to forgive me,
I will forgive you.
Because that's what love is, lana.
It's forgivey.
Which is not a word.
Come on, figgis!
All right, here we go.
Oh, why?
Hello.
So, that's your idea of a break, huh?
Oh, cyril, it's not what it looks like.
Well, then, what is it?
Okay, so, cyril got in over his head. jesus
God, did he  kill her? no, no, no.
He ran from her to go confess to lana.
But, so, then this one starts
Freaking out, and long story
Short, i kind of had to drown her in the tub.
So, you killed her?
Apparently not, so...
Good news.
Shut up, pam.
And did cyril run by here crying
In a woman's bathrobe?
Well, it wouldn't surprise me.
You're driving him stark raving mad
What did i do?
What you do?
Running around all up and down
This stupid blimp --
Against the rules.
...half-naked, tits
Bouncing around like you're at a
Rodeo, then going back to some
Billionaire's suite?
I was trying to stop a
Bomb plot.
Oh, my god.
There is no bomb! more good news.
And just how do you know that?
Because i made the bomb threat.
Trudy beekman booked the very
Last ticket on this flight, so
It was all, "meh, meh, meh, i'm trudy beekman.
I'm on the co-op board, and i'm going on a blimp.
Meh!"
So, yes, i made a phony bomb threat.
Good for you.
And yet you lecture me.
Lovely.
Mm, yello!
So, what would you say if i told you
That  your mother made a phony bomb threat
Just to get a free ride on a blimp?
I'd say that's fairly classic her.
Oh, shut up. and then i'd just sort of laugh...
...at the, uh, um -- the
Whatchamacallit...
Irony?
Lan t ahere'sctuallare bomb on board?
Archer?
Archer -- oh, what the hell?!
Where the are you going?
I got to get my turtleneck.
What the -- i'm not defusing a bomb in this.
No running! shut up!
Oh, and, lana, maybe you ought to grab the kraut.
He's the bomber.
Gott im himmel!
What is this?!
Lana: you know what it is,fritz,
So shut your schnitzel hole and disarm it.
Ah, i get it.
The german guy mit the scar must be the bad guy.
Well, you know how i got this scar?
Saving a jewish girl from a gang of skinheads.
Oh, jesus.
Yeah!
Und so krauss gets a curb party.
Wow, now i feel like an asshole. your words.
But could you be a lamb
And disarm it anyway?
Yeah, probably.
Wha--
Okay, i got the turtleneck and my wire cutters.
Now, where are we?
We're at you just shot
The guy who could disarm the bomb, jackass!
I didn't shoot him!
You think i'd bring a gun on this firetrap?
Well, then who did it? i did!
Captain lammers?!
Nice read, velma.
"keep your 401 in company stock," they said.
"the price can only go up," they said.
Well, guess what.
Um, it didn't?
Who the hell wants a two-day
Blimp ride to london, which is
Our only route?!
Okay, so it's a niche
Market, but --
Blowing it up will send
The stock ice down to zero!
Yeah, that's why i shorted it.
But what about all the other employees?
See, it's that kind of
Selfish shit --
Lana, no!
You'll kill us all!
For the last time, you idiot!
It's not hydrogen!
It's heliu-u-u-u-m!
And what about that are you still not getting, exactly?
Well, obvious the concept, lana.
Sorry i didn't go to space camp.
How about bomb-defusal camp?
No, actually,
Lacrosse camp, if that helps.
I mean, a lot of those skills
Are universal.
Shut up.
Agent gillette, please.
Oh, great.
Come on, people, talk to me!
What are we thinking?
What are we doing?
What are we wearing?
My crisis vest, mr. fat face.
Lana? hey, girl. you there?
Yeah, i'm -- hey, can
You see me?
I see your knock-off fiacci drawers!
You are such a bitch.
Hey, ray.
Let's see that ignition, girl.
Got it?
East german crap.
Probably a gk-31 or -32.
So, uh... so on the side of the timer,
There should be a serial number.
That'll tell me which wire y'all need to cut.
You got it? yeah, i see it.
Ready?
Since first call.
9-3-4...
...t-x-s...
T-x-x? two x's?
No, x-s, like inxs.
In-x-x? "s"!
Jesus, use the nato phonetic alphabet.
What?
Christ on sale!
Is it "s"?
Duh!
"sierra."
Ray, it's niner-3-4...
Tango-xray-sierra.
Thank you, doll.
Now, there should be a dash
Followed by two letters.
Okay.
Okay, so now i want you to
Cut the blue and white wire.
Which one?
There's two of those.
No -- one's blue with a white
Stripe, and the other one's
White with a blue stripe.
Yeah, and both are identical!
No! they're not!
Uh, ray, hon?
They're really similar.
One's a teeny bit...blue, honey.
Which one? i guess that one maybe.
So, wait, which one do i cut?
The teeny bit...blue one!
Okay!
Wait! stop!
You said the two letters after
The dash were oscar-kilo. who?
What? "ok" -- oscar-kilo.
No! "okay"! like, "okay, now i'm gonna tell
You what they are."
Yeah, and then you didn't.
I thought we skipped that part!
Skipped a step in disarming a bomb.
Yeah, which i thought was pretty irresponsible
On your part! why do you always do
This?! why do you always not shut up?!
Stop.
On the radio, when we answer
In the affirmative, we say
"roger."
O-- roger. sorry.
Now, in the serial number,
What are the two letters
Following the dash?
You ready? roger!
The first letter is "b."
"bravo."
Thanks. second letter is "n."
"m" as in "mike" or "n" as --
As in "nancy."
God. you of all people what?! archer
Me of all people what? nothing.
Ray, hon?
Okay, so -- you can say "okay."
Oh, my god!
Ray, can i shoot him? in about five seconds, honey.
Lana, be careful! jesus, the helium!
Right after he cuts the solid-green wire.
The green color is solid or --
Roger! o-- roger.
Cutting the green wire.
Archer!
Jesus! god! what?!
That's how annoying you are.
Your mom's annoying!
How about that?
Let's go there.
Let's go here, where,
Archer, shut up and cut the goddamn wire, already!
You shut up, and i'm doing it!
God!
Oh, my -- ray!
What's going on?
The timer sped up!
Did you cut the green one?!
Yes! roger!
Steven! whoever!
Ray?
What were the last two letters?!
"b," as in "butt hole"! what do we do here?
And "m," as in "mancy."
What?!
"m" as in what?
"mancy."
What did you think i said?
"nancy"!
You idiot!
I can see how, uh...
And then i was like, "you of all --"
Exact same spot! ray?
Ray, tell me what to do!
Do y'all have parachutes?
No!
Well, that would be, you
Know -- problem solved!
Ray!
I don't know!
Push it off with your big-ass hands!
Good luck, honey.
Oh, it's too heavy!
Archer!
I cannot do this alone!
You're not alone!
Baby! you came back to me!
Well, i really --
Lana, there's a lot you and i need to talk about.
And let's do that,
Right after we shove this huge bomb off the blimp.
Okay, but then we seriously need to -- cyril!
Sorry. here we go.
Lana, we're not gonna make it!
Yes, we are, cyril!
We are gonna make it!
Oh, my god!
Lana, we made it!
Hooray for metaphors!
I told you.
Okay, now, then, what did you want to talk about?
Um, well, uh, a lot of stuff, really.
Starting with the fact we just
Bombed ireland.
Um...pretty sure that's wales.
Sync by YYeTs.net
Transcript by Addic7ed.com