Son, did you do your homework?
I don't wanna do my homework!
What, what, what?
- I want Chicken 4 Dayz!
- Oh...
[rapper] ♪ Oh, it's
Chicken 4 Dayz! ♪
♪ It's Chicken 4 Dayz! ♪
♪ Everybody's having
fun At Chicken 4 Dayz! ♪
- I got a drumstick!
- I got a arm.
I got a bucket full of mystery stuff!
[rapper] ♪ Chicken-4-Dayzy,
totally crazy! ♪
♪ Don't ask questions,
just keep eating! ♪
Over at Chicken 4 Dayz,
they pump their
chickens full of hormones
and keep them cooped up in tiny cages.
Now, as a chicken, this concerns me.
Here at Gentle Farms, we treat
our livestock differently.
Lush fields, plenty of dignity,
and Foosball. [chuckles]
The chickens here have wonderful lives
before we harvest them,
so you can eat them.
But wait, Pa, aren't we chickens?
I don't wanna get eaten!
Boy, these animals aren't like us.
They're specifically bred to be eaten,
and genetically modified
for maximum flavor.
When our chicks first hatch,
we lovingly inject them
with natural delicious hormones,
which makes them meat, thereby
erasing any moral gray area!
Now you can feel good
about eating our meat.
It's simple: No one knows
chicken like chickens.
Gentle Farms.
Why put the "Skip Ad" button so late?
I'm not skipping now. I'm invested.
BoJack, you're driving a car right now.
- Oh, right!
- Aah! Oh!
[BoJack] Whoa!
[tires screech, then crashing]
[horn honks]
[clucking]
[♪♪]
[cawing]
Kelsey, ray of sunshine.
And who's this little drop of Jupiter?
- This is my daughter, Irving.
- Your daughter's name is Irving?
Gender-normative names are oppressive.
Well, aren't you a little princess?
What are you doing
outside of the castle?
Mom, your friend is being weird.
BoJack is not my friend.
- Whoa!
- Diane, I need you to handle Irving.
- Handle her?
- It's Take Your Daughter To Work Day.
I took my daughter to
work, she got empowered,
and now I need you to take
my daughter away from work,
so I can actually do some.
Mom, don't pawn me off
onto your assistant.
Can you not fight me on this, please?
Take my car and my daughter,
and go do whatever it is you do.
Way to delegate, captain! Down low!
Nope? Look down. Just
put your eyes down.
My hand is below your eye line. No?
I guess you're stuck with me, kiddo.
Sounds great, old-woman-o.
[cell phone chirps]
What is it, BoJack? I'm
at my dumb niece's wedding.
Not you, honey! A different dumb niece.
I feel like Kelsey doesn't like me.
You're not really the
kind of person people like.
- Right away?
- Uh, sure.
But once they get to
know me, they adore me?
How do I put this delicately? No.
The problem is we haven't
gotten any one-on-one time.
There are always other people around.
Filming me. Feeding me.
Walking me to the garage at night,
because one time I saw a bag
in the wind and I got spooked.
BoJack, the only reason
you want Kelsey to like you
is because she's cold and distant.
Any time someone tries to
love you, you shove them away.
What? No, I don't,
stupid. You're stupid.
Don't be such a dumb stupid idiot, Todd.
Okay, I gotta go. Everyone's
staring at me for some reason.
What? I'm ready. Let's take a picture.
Hear ye! Hear ye!
I call this meeting of
P.B. Livin' to order.
I believe it was Benjamin
Franklin who said:
"You have reached the end
of your free trial membership
at Benjamin-Franklin-Quotes.com."
- What a wise man.
- What's on the agenda, my frienda?
Well, here's an idea.
What if there was a West Dakota?
Todd, isn't that a job
for the State Department?
Well, I got a whole page of other ideas,
each as impractical as they
are prohibitively expensive.
You know what they say:
"You gotta spend money to make money."
So, how can I spend a lot of money?
I know. I'll take a spa day.
- Uh...
- Eyes, prepare to receive cucumbers.
- We're in a meeting.
- You know what they say:
"You gotta skip meetings
to have meetings." See ya.
- Wait, what should I do?
- I don't know.
Oh, maybe you could go on one
of your silly Todd adventures.
You know, whatever you do when
everyone is busy with other stuff.
[sighs] Okay.
[cell phone chirps]
What is it, Todd?
Princess Carolyn, I
need something to do.
A job, or a task, or
a direction in life...
You're my agent. Can
you give my life meaning?
I don't have time for this.
Well, don't stop on my account.
Princess Carolyn, do I have a purpose?
Oh, purpose? Are you high?
Only the normal amount.
I gotta go. They're about
to step on the glass.
Just stay out of trouble.
[clucks]
Uh, okay.
- [horn honks]
- [siren whoops]
[sniffing]
What I want is a hard target search
of every gas station, backyard,
outhouse, pool house...
And can I get a black-and-white cookie,
if it's not too G.D. troublesome?
So, we know the chicken
crossed the road.
But the real mystery is why?
So, what do you want
to be when you grow up?
First I'm gonna go to Brown,
- then I'm gonna go to Yale Law.
- Wow.
Then I'm gonna be the
youngest Supreme Court Justice.
- That's great.
- Or, you know, something in marketing.
Wow.
Would you mind if we
stopped by my house?
I have to do laundry.
So, you just, like, do laundry?
That's, like, your thing?
Okay. This whole attitude
you're putting on?
I must be Shania Twain,
because that don't impress me much.
Is that a reference from the '90s?
You know that was 20 years ago, right?
Hey, I was just like you
when I was a teenager.
I was this badass overachiever
that had these big plans
to change the world.
Yeah? What happened?
Oh, you didn't hear?
I changed the world.
[Todd whistling]
[clucking]
Did you have a nice shower?
I made you a sandwich. Oh,
but it has turkey in it.
Is that kind of weird?
- [clucks]
- [doorbell rings]
[officer] Police!
- [Todd gulps]
- [clucks]
[Todd] Oh, man. [sighs]
What seems to be the
problem, Officer...?
Fuzzyface. Meow Meow Fuzzyface.
A Chicken 4 Dayz
chicken fell off a truck,
and I gotta find her and take
her to the slaughterhouse.
You haven't seen any
chickens running around?
No, I don't think so.
[clucking]
- Who's this?
- Uh, this is my, uh... My wife...
- [clucks]
- Becca! Yeah, my wife Becca.
- Becca Chavez. There she is.
- Okay.
- [clucks]
- Yep, she loves her books.
Big reader. [chuckles]
- Real nerd.
- [clucks]
Back off? Okay, I'm sorry, honey.
Hold on, if you're really a nerd,
who's your favorite Baroque composer?
[clucks]
- Bach? Not Vivaldi? You're insane!
- [clucks]
Yes, I am holding a Bic pen,
but I don't see how that's
relevant, Mrs. Chavez.
- [clucks]
- Sorry. Becca.
- [clucking]
- She's a charming woman.
I do have to look around a little
bit, just so I can say I did my job.
- Uh, don't you need a warrant?
- Only if you're guilty.
[both chuckling]
Well, in that case, mi casa es su casa.
So, if anyone asks, you
were born in La Jolla.
You majored in Communications at USC,
and now you're the booking agent
- for Kings of Leon.
- [clucks]
- Fine, you also book Beck.
- [Diane] Todd?
Aah! I didn't find that
thing in your drawer!
Why are the police outside?
Okay. I met this chicken and she
escaped from Chicken 4 Dayz factory,
and she doesn't speak English,
but she's my best friend and
the cops are looking for her,
and Mr. Peanutbutter went to the spa,
and I love her, and her
name is Becca. Chickenson.
- Todd, breathe.
- But we can't send Becca back.
- They're gonna pump her full of hormones.
- [clucks]
- More hormones.
- [clucking]
I have a plan, but we gotta
get her out of here now.
- Todd, no. Becca doesn't belong to you.
- But she needs our help.
Do you know how much
trouble we'd get in?
There's a policeman in our front yard.
Uh-oh, here comes the
responsible suburban housewife.
Gonna do whatever the man says.
[sighs]
You're right. Let's get out of here.
So, now you're just gonna do
whatever a teenage girl says?
- Jeezy kableezy, grow a spine.
- [clucks]
Yeah, or a backbone.
Thank you, Becca.
[groans]
Here chicken, chicken, chicken.
[clucking]
Oh, oh. Well, we're off to the beach.
Just me and my wife, and our
teenage daughter and our maid.
- What? Why am I a maid?
- Silence, maid!
Honey, do you want to sit
in the front or the back?
- [clucks]
- And why not? Maid, you can drive.
Hope there's not too
much traffic on the 134.
Okay, bye-bye, officer.
So long. Have a great day.
Wait a second. The 134
doesn't go to the beach.
Unless you took it to the 10.
But then why wouldn't you
take the 405 to the 10?
Hold on, this pen isn't a Bic.
No, no, this doesn't add up at all.
Wait! That man's wife was a...
chicken!
[news theme music plays]
Fowl run afoul. A funky
chicken has flown the coop,
and for a concerned
populace, the sky is falling.
Michael Morgan, Chicken 4 Dayz CEO,
this is a public safety hazard,
and your company is responsible.
Admit it, you counted your
chickens before they hatched,
and now, those chickens
have come home to roost.
Tom, I want to take full
responsibility for this mishap.
That's why, for a
limited time, everybody,
we are offering our special
Full Responsibility Poppers
at participating
restaurants for only $4.99.
Tell me, though, if one sees
this delicious escaped
chicken in the street,
should they approach it, or...?
Oh, no. I want to be very clear that
this is not like a friend chicken
you see at school or work.
This is a special kind of food chicken
that has lived its entire life indoors.
This chicken is not socialized
for the outside world.
- Sounds like my ex-wife. Hey-yo!
- [chuckles]
Oh, Tommy.
Look, the safest place for this
chicken right now is with us,
so we can kill it,
turn it into a sludge,
and then press that sludge
into a delicious patty.
I'd like to take this
moment to apologize
for the earlier crack about my ex-wife.
Shannon, we shared 14
beautiful years together.
How do you respond to allegations
that factory farming is
"torture," or "cruel,"
or "like a terrifying movie about
some strange dystopian society,
but in this monster story, the
horrifying monsters are us"?
Relax, Tommy,
everything we do is completely
legal and FDA-approved,
so, therefore, it is fine.
I have no follow-up questions.
- Okay, Todd, what's your plan?
- What?
You said you had a plan.
Oh, yeah. My plan was:
Ask Diane for help.
And now my plan has been completed.
Nice follow-through, Todd.
We have a 'roided out chicken
and the cops on the
lookout. What do we do?
Hey, geniuses, why don't
we take her to Gentle Farms?
Yeah, no one knows
chicken like chickens!
They couldn't say that in
the ad if it wasn't true.
- [clucks]
- Yeah! Book Beck. You remember.
[Diane groans]
- And cut! Company move to...
- Great news, blue-collar types.
Instead of crew lunch
today, your star has arranged
for his favorite burrito
truck to bring you lunch.
It's me, I'm that star!
[all cheering]
We're not breaking for lunch yet.
Or we could break for lunch,
and you and I could
get to know each other.
The crew has more work to do.
Once they've had a burrito, they'll
be off their circadian rhythm...
[cell phone rings]
- What?
- Los Angeles P.D.
Are you the owner of a 2002 Volvo
with a "Reelect Al Gore" bumper sticker?
As relevant today as it was then.
Are you aware said Volvo is currently
harboring a fugitive chicken,
along with a teenage girl,
a small, sprite-like man,
and a maid of some sort?
That's my daughter! Not
the maid. The other one.
I'd wager they're making
a run for Gentle Farms.
Don't worry, though.
We'll bring your daughter
home, dead or alive.
- Alive! Alive!
- We're the L.A.P.D., ma'am.
- We'll probably make the right call.
- Wait, wait, wait...
All right, troops, listen up!
I'm ready to go after these
rabble-rousers with all...
Oh, no! Not until you get a warrant!
Ah, damn it, I hate due process!
You're a loose cannon,
Meow Meow Fuzzyface.
No, I'm not. I'm a cannon,
maybe, but a loose cannon?
Is that what you think of me?
I think you play by your own rules.
No way, he thinks rules
were made to be broken.
These are all attributes
of a loose cannon.
No, I'm just a reckless renegade.
- Sergeant Stone's a loose cannon.
- Aah!
You shut your trap, Fuzzyface.
I'd say Stone's more of a cop
on the edge with nothing to lose.
- That's a different thing.
- Now I'm just confused.
Is Meow Meow Fuzzyface
a loose cannon or not?
All right, put on a pot of coffee.
We're gonna get to the bottom of this.
[Stone groans]
Aw, man.
So full of burrito. Ooh.
Uh-oh, siesta time.
I need to go. Irving ran off
with a fugitive chicken in my car.
We can take my car. This is perfect.
Why is this perfect? My
daughter could be in danger.
Yes, I agree, but we can use the
car ride to get some one-on-one.
I mean, who is BoJack?
I'm sure I can find another ride.
Every second you waste
finding another ride,
your daughter gets closer to getting
her eyes poked out by a mutant chicken,
or worse, death, or slightly
better, teen pregnancy,
or worse again, salmonella.
Okay, fine. Let's go.
Yay! I'm calling this road trip the 007,
because we are gonna bond.
Up top? Down low? Either one? Both?
[Diane] Oh, wow, you guys
have a movie night here?
- [Todd] Oh...
- And we have 20 acres of pasture,
where our chickens
have hours of free play.
See, Todd? She'll be happy here.
[Levi] She sure will.
[both] Because no one
knows chicken like chickens.
Thank you for saving this poultry
from a terrible life at a factory farm.
You're a hero.
But what if Chicken 4
Dayz tries to get her back?
Don't you worry about your friend.
- That chicken belongs to us now.
- [Diane] Whoa!
- Where'd you get that gun?
- You mean originally, or just now?
- Just now.
- It was in that barrel.
- And what about originally?
- Also that barrel.
Look, Becca, I know this
is hard to understand,
but I have to go, and
you can't come with me.
[clucks]
No, no, you don't need
to book Beck anymore.
Now you can just be a chicken.
See, this is where you belong, okay?
You hear me? I don't want you no more.
You weren't the best friend I ever had,
and I never loved you! Now get, Becca!
I said get!
[sobbing]
[Becca clucking]
She really stretched out that dress.
She was so horrified,
she checked into rehab.
So, I'm kind of the reason
Drew Barrymore got sober.
Did you like Never Been
Kissed? If so, you're welcome.
Can we have one conversation
that isn't about you?
I don't understand why
you need me to like you.
I don't need you to like me.
It would be fun if you liked me,
because I'd prove my parents
were wrong to never support me,
because I earned the admiration
of an authority figure,
proving I have intrinsic worth,
but it's not a big
deal or anything. Jeez.
Great story. You should put that
in a podcast, so I can unsubscribe.
Can this piece of junk go any faster?
It's been screwy since I hit
that deer a couple weeks back.
Probably should get it checked out.
[tire blows]
[both yelling]
[sighs]
Probably should've
gotten it checked out.
- Those farmers seem nice.
- Yeah.
I think Becca will
be really happy there.
She'll have a nice life.
Yeah, until they kill her.
Well, yeah, but of all the places
that will eventually kill her,
Gentle Farms seems like the best.
This doesn't feel right.
Becca was our friend.
- No. We gotta get her back.
- Uh, what do you mean?
Remember when that guy
cocked his gun and said:
"That chicken belongs to us now"?
He wasn't doing that because
he likes cocking guns.
- Then we'll just bust her out.
- Todd, there's nothing we can do.
Where else would Becca go?
She doesn't even speak English.
Well, we gotta do something.
Look, I know I'm a screw-up
and all my ideas are terrible,
but with Becca, I was
responsible for something.
I had a purpose.
Ah. I guess you wouldn't understand.
[groans]
- [tires screeching]
- [Irving and Todd yell]
- Oh, my God, Diane!
- All right. Let's bust her out.
Yes! Okay, and afterwards,
will you get me an iPad?
- What? No.
- But I really want an iPad.
Maybe you wouldn't understand.
Don't push it.
All right, all right, we've agreed.
He's a loose cannon, but he gets results.
- I can live with that.
- Now, you go bust those perps.
You'll need a maverick,
a by-the-book rookie,
and a curmudgeonly veteran
one week from retirement.
Go, go, go!
[men speaking indistinctly]
[news theme music plays]
We have received word that authorities
are now en route to Gentle Farms
in an attempt to preempt the
pursued poultry at the pass.
Do we have a graphic for
this? No? Where's the graphic?
No, I'm not gonna go on
until we have a graphic.
So, make one. I'll wait.
Yeah, hold on, America,
Randy's gotta figure
out how to do his job.
Because if I don't
have a graphic, Randy,
people who are just tuning in...
Why am I explaining this to you?
This is basic journalistic...
I swear to God! We'll be right back!
Just got to place the jack
in the right jack apparatus.
There, I have got...
No. I have no idea what I'm doing.
That was me acting. Pretty
convincing performance, huh?
There's more to me...
Are you capable of experiencing a moment
that you don't then make about you?
What was your plan to get out of here?
I don't know. Some hick will come by,
and I'll give him an
autograph for a tow.
Boom, his life's changed,
and you and I are on our way.
Oh, my God. I'm going to
lose custody of my daughter.
The only reason I took
this movie is for her.
This is my one shot
at a big studio movie.
If I blow it, I'm back to making
small, critically acclaimed movies
about lesbians learning how to recycle.
You think I want to be an indie darling?
Who's gonna fund Irving's education?
- Marla? With her seasonal nut butters?
- Yeah, Marla sucks, right?
Indie-darling daughters
don't go to Brown, okay?
They end up at cute pat-on-the-back
factories like Vassar,
then move back in with
their indie-darling mothers
and make puppet shows
with their tampons,
and they get a profile
in New York Magazine,
and the cycle continues.
Oh, my God, I'm a terrible mother.
Hey, I know terrible mothers,
and you're not a terrible mother.
Hey, aren't you the
horse from Horsin' Around?
And you're the director
of Women Who Love Women
Who Love Recycling.
Give you a lift in exchange
for a couple autographs.
There he is. Right on time.
Shh, shh, shh.
Everyone keep quiet. We gotta...
Ooh. Whoa, whoa, whoa!
[grunting]
[wind chimes tinkling]
[gong sounds]
They probably didn't hear that.
Uh, that's probably a coincidence.
[Levi] Someone broke onto the farm!
Maybe they're rehearsing a one-act play
called Someone Broke Onto the Farm
and someone just said the titular line?
[door opens]
[gasps] This way.
- Oh.
- Irving, this isn't safe.
Get in the car, lock the doors.
Don't be a badass and argue with me...
- Yeah, okay, bye!
- Okay.
Go, go, go! [panting]
Uh...
[clucking]
Becca?
Who's making that ruckus
in my chicken coop?
[all clucking loudly]
- Becca, where are you?
- Becca, are you...?
Becca?
Is this you?
- [clucks]
- Becca?
To... To... Todd?
Oh, I found her!
Diane! This one's Becca!
No! Todd! Don't you get it?
- They're all Becca.
- Oh.
Okay, go, chickens! You're free.
Go, run to freedom!
For generations they
will tell your story!
- [Levi] Who goes there?
- Oh, oh, oh, shit!
- We gotta hide!
- Go, go, go!
[Todd panting]
Hide, hide! In here! Someplace safe.
Come on, come on. Oh, no!
[clucking]
- Shh, shh. Becca, no, no, no!
- Shh.
[Levi] Only we know how to care
for these creatures, you hear?
Like I say: No one knows
chicken like chickens.
- [cocks gun]
- [laughs]
Oh.
- Diane, I'm sorry I got you into this.
- [sighs] It's not your fault.
I don't know why I always
get into these messes.
You know, sometimes I
feel like my whole life
is just a series of
loosely-related wacky misadventures.
I think that's just what
being in your 20s is.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I'm supposed to be the adult
here, and I'm a total mess.
You kidding? You're the
coolest person I know.
- Really?
- Yeah. You always know what to do,
and you don't take shit from anyone.
Is that how you see me?
Of course. You're like Lara Croft.
In Diane's body.
- [Levi cocks gun]
- [Todd whimpering]
- This is our chance. Let's go!
- Come on!
[Diane] Go, go, go!
[all gasping]
Please. Take me with you.
I hate it here. I don't
want to kill chickens.
I want to design video games
that help kids learn math.
Oh...
Whoa!
I am so sorry.
Okay, that was crazy! Just go.
Let's get out of here!
We're free, we're free! Oh, shit.
[siren whoops]
[tires screech]
Well, well, looks like
birds of a feather...
go to jail.
- [clucking]
- Why was he wearing sunglasses
at night?
I hope you folks like community service.
- I do.
- What? Oh.
Oh, my God, Irving,
thank God you're safe.
Mom, I'm fine.
Stop embarrassing me in
front of my cool friends.
What? Cool?
I mean, that's cool
that you think I'm cool.
I don't care or anything,
but, you know, it's cool.
Hey, this guy. What'd
you get arrested for?
- Being too cute?
- [chuckles]
I want to be in his cell.
- Listen up, everybody.
I, famous celebrity BoJack
Horseman, have an announcement.
I'm going to ask you to drop all charges
on account of me being a celebrity.
We gracefully accept the
requisite slap on the wrist
and a brief, but
ultimately pointless, trial
in the court of public
opinion. Good day.
Well, you are famous, so
you are all free to go.
[Stone yells]
- But what about Becca?
- Took care of that, too.
Called in a favor with Drew Barrymore,
and she'll pay off Chicken
4 Dayz to adopt your friend.
Does she have a meadow that
Becca can frolic around in?
You think Drew Barrymore
doesn't have a frolicking meadow?
That is the dumbest thing I've heard.
I learned something today.
When you think something
isn't about you,
you find a way to save the
day and realize that it was,
all along, all about you.
[groans]
Plus, I got you all a burrito truck!
- Hooray!
- Yay! I'm great!
So, after all that, the
only thing that saved Becca
was that BoJack was
friends with Drew Barrymore?
- Yep.
- So, did anything we did matter?
- Nope.
- I think it did.
I think we made a difference.
A small one, but a difference.
Yeah, I think we did, too.
I think we really changed
things for the better.
Subtitle sync and corrections
by awaqeded for www.addic7ed.com.
♪ Back in the '90s ♪
♪ I was in a very famous TV show ♪
- ♪ I'm BoJack the horse ♪
- ♪ BoJack! ♪
♪ BoJack the horse Don't
act like you don't know ♪
♪ And I'm trying to
hold onto my past ♪
♪ It's been so long I
don't think I'm gonna last ♪
♪ I guess I'll just try
And make you understand ♪
♪ That I'm more horse than a man ♪
♪ Or I'm more man than a horse ♪
♪ BoJack! ♪
Boxer versus raptor.
Na-Na-Na-Na-Na-Na-Na-Na.