[pam sobbing]
[clears throat]
Uh, could I, um...
[sobbing continues]
What's wrong?
My-my-my-my--
Pam. Pam!
sis-sis-sis-sis--
[sighs]
hold this.
Ow! God dammit, dude.
Well, I'm sorry,
But I've got other shit
to do today.
Now, what the hell
is wrong with you?
My sister edie
is getting married
To don ekblad, jr.
Of all people,
And she asked me
to be a bridesmaid.
Um...
I should be
maid of honor, dicknuts,
But no,
guess who she asks instead?
Uh...
Midge olerud!
No!
Yes.
Midge "hey edie,
"let's me and you blow
pam's boyfriend arn
Behind the goddamn grain
elevator" olerud!
You had a boyfriend
named arn?
Well, he didn't know
I liked him, but--
Midge and edie did.
[cries]
pam!
Okay, jesus.
Calm down, ike turner.
I don't want
to show up with a black eye.
Not a real
diverse crowd, huh?
Eye, idiot, eye.
Although, no.
Not a lot of black guys
in rural wisconsin.
And, I don't want
to sound racist,
But--
power through it.
A black guy would
be better than no date,
Which is what
I'm taking now.
When is it?
Saturday.
Day after tomorrow.
[burps]
Screw it, I'll go.
[gasps]
really?
Really, really, really?
Yeah, why not?
Oh, man.
Wait till they see--
Wait, that's how
you ask a woman out?
Yes.
Wait, no,
I don't need a back-story.
Yes you do. Shut up.
You're gordon shumway,
And you own a 500-acre
dairy farm in upstate new york,
With 600 holsteins and two
herringbone milking parlors.
Okay, a, that's alf's name,
And two,
what's more impressive,
A pathetic cheese farmer
Or the world's greatest
secret agent,
A.K.A., me, sterling archer.
Oh, yeah.
[woman on p.A.]
attention,
now boarding flight 934,
To green bay, wisconsin.
Come on, archer,
that's us.
Flight 934,
to greenbay, wisconsin.
Yeah, you're booked
through to new york.
Will you be needing
anything else?
Huh?
Oh, is there a place
that sells down jackets
And thermal underwear?
[laughs]
I'm, uh,
what do you call it?
Coldblooded.
[lana]
archer? Archer?
Archer!
[groans]
Have you seen archer?
Did you look in here?
I--
that is what I'm doing now.
Then, I guess
go look everywhere else.
You know...
[cheryl/carol]
starting with
dick-cheese, wisconsin.
Excuse me?
Him and--
he and...
Whomever, and...
Whoever, and...
[gasps]
If you wake this child,
I will climb inside you
With my shoes on.
He and pam
are at her sister's wedding.
In wisconsin?
[baby cries]
[lana groans]
happy?
No, no, no,
he's got her all weekend.
I'm going upstate
for sere school.
So take her with you.
To survival school?
Big whoop,
hang her in a bear bag.
[growls]
so... Mallory...
Nope. Ron and I are going
To our house in the hamptons,
And, trust me, it would
be no place for a baby.
You're back together?
Like, for real?
And happier
and stronger than ever.
Try not to burn
the place down.
And you, my tweedy widdle--
What, are your boobs
full of corn syrup?
Excuse me?
Feel that,
she feels chubby.
She's a baby.
A fat widdle baby,
yes you are, yes you are.
[crying]
You're fat widdle baby.
Fast forward
to me buying her liposuction
For graduation.
I hope you do
burn this place down.
She said not to.
[gasps]
she said try not to.
[archer]
you're kidding.
How either,
in this universe,
Or any of
it's infinite parallels,
Could I possibly
embarrass you?
[pam]
by dressing like
a maitre d' on a dinner cruise
For gay republicans?
That's a thing?
[pam]
I don't know,
but you don't want
Edie dogging you out
in front of the entire school.
The entire what?
[pam]
rehearsal dinner.
Shut up.
Come on, what happened?
Did she dump pig's blood
all over you at the prom?
No, not pig's blood.
Wait, what?
Hang on,
did she really?
Oh my god, pam...
You look amazing.
Really?
I mean, you know,
relatively.
Shit-ass.
But you've
got to pace me,
I'm sewn into this sumbitch.
So for every ounce
that goes in,
An ounce gotta go out.
So, diuretics?
And laxatives.
There's a sundae bar.
What could
possibly go wrong?
[knocking]
Who the shit is that?
[barry]
is it barry?
Does that mean barry possibly,
literally froze his nuts off
In the wheel-well of a 747
So he could murder
the shit-eating archer?
Yes it does, other barry.
Oh, yes.
[knocking]
[archer]
okay. Jesus christ.
[laughs]
uh, wow.
You have got to be edie.
Uh, I'm archer,
uh, pam's boyfriend.
Bullshit, my asshole.
Pam, hon?
Edie's here.
And you will be civil
and polite.
And you will not let
her push your--
[edie]
spamela!
Get your fat ass out here.
[breathes deeply]
Uh, she should
be right out, she's--
[screaming]
[glass shattering]
Yikes.
Guess I should get in there
and break that up.
[elevator dings]
[pam]
wait, wait, wait, wait.
Yeah, come on.
You comin'?
No, but hey,
I know it's late notice,
and I really hate to ask,
But would you mind
keeping a.J. For the--
What?
I'm hitting door open.
You can't see it,
but I really am.
Oh, my god, it's just like
maximum overdrive.
Ray!
Lana!
On Monday
let's talk about
How scary
this was for me.
[groans]
God dammit!
Let me go!
No, now just calm--
let me go!
Shit, she's gonna--
Jesus christ, woman!
Whoo!
God dammit!
[spits]
happy?
Less than I was,
to be honest.
When?
When you were chugging balls
Behind whatever
gay strip joint
She hired you at?
Whoa.
Told ya,
it's that jacket.
First of all,
pam, shut up.
I'm not the one
who chugs balls
Behind buildings,
And even if I were,
They wouldn't belong
to that dude arn.
[laughs]
Oh god,
you told him about arn?
Arn didn't even
know she was alive.
Okay,
you know what?
Besides what arn's
balls taste like?
[laughs]
I--
ah! I am out of here.
Pam, wait!
[laughs]
wow,
and here I thought
She was kidding
about the pig's blood.
[laughs]
no...
It was--
it was calf's blood.
[laughing]
[cries]
stupid, frickin' edie.
I'll show her
what arn's balls taste like.
Wait, what the?
Barry?
Hey...
You.
[body thuds]
[lana]
hello?
Krieger?
You in here?
Hey, you!
What can I do you for?
So, hey, um,
archer totally flaked on me.
Mallory and ray
are being lame,
And cheryl is-- cheryl.
So I was wondering
if you could do me a favor.
Yep, yep, yep,
but, first,
Who is this little person?
Um, a.J., my baby,
Who I've had for,
like, six months,
Who you've met.
Mm-kay.
Ooh, and who also
has a poopy diaper.
[gasps]
great bacchus plateau,
It works!
What? What does?
The k-9000
infrasonic pulse rifle.
What do you mean?
What does it do?
I assume you're familiar
with the brown note.
I am not, no.
What? The brown note,
The frequency
that makes humans
Shit their pants,
or their onesie.
[sighs]
I'm pretty sure
that was a coincidence.
That's what they said
about tesla's death ray.
So, this favor...
Lana?
Wait, lana.
What's the favor?
[lana[
just promise to use
your powers for good!
[laughs]
No.
[archer]
yes.
No.
Clean the jizz out of
your ears, jizz-ears.
I'm getting married
tomorrow,
So tonight
at my rehearsal dinner,
I get all you can eat
prime rib
And bottomless vin rogue.
Gimme that.
Put it down.
We are going
to go find pam,
And then you
are gonna apologize
For hurting her feelings.
Why do you care?
You're just a-- wait.
Are you really
her boyfriend?
Mm-hm.
Oh, and a secret agent,
so...
[phone rings]
And, not only
am I a secret agent,
I am the world's
greatest secret agent.
Mm... Hello?
[barry]
jesus, archer.
You're not even the greatest
secret agent in that room.
[laughs]
actually, barry,
That's where you're--
wait! Barry?
[barry]
hey, dummy.
How did you get--
where are you?
How did you even
know I was here?
[barry]
uh, I followed you.
What do you mean,
you followed me?
Okay, that's obviously
your abusive ex-boyfriend,
So I'm just gonna
tip on out.
[barry]
I was on my way to new york
to kill you,
When I saw you
in chicago, idiot,
And now you
are gonna follow me.
That is, if you ever wanna
see your buddy--
Uh-- wait,
what was your name?
[spits]
your worst frickin'
nightmare.
[archer]
pam?
Oh right, yeah, it's pam.
Anyway, if you don't wanna
spend the next year
Signing for packages full
of her head and feet and shit,
Meet me out
by the old grain elevator.
[barry]
pam says edie knows
where it is.
Now, you listen to me,
barry, you--
[dial tone]
barry!
God damn,
son of a cyborg bitch!
What,
he give you anal warts?
He kidnapped your sister,
you jerk!
What?
Who'd wanna kidnap pam?
I'll tell you in the car.
Come on!
Look, I know you're bitter
'cause you people can't
get married or whatever,
But all you care
to eat prime rib!
[sighs]
well, edie, I was almost
half-way hoping
It wouldn't come to this.
Come to what--
[cyril]
hello? Lana?
No...?
What are you still
doing here?
I thought you had
rambo sleepaway camp.
Sere school, and I did,
But archer hosed me,
and I don't have a sitter.
Oh, well you should
have asked--
I asked everybody,
even krieger.
I-- wow,
so you'd ask krieger
To watch your baby
before you'd ask me?
I didn't, well--
that would be weird.
Weirder than the guy
trying to make
Some kind
of ejaculation ray?
No,
it's a pants-shitting ray.
Okay, well, then,
that's new, but--
Cyril, look--
how about this?
I'll drive
you both upstate,
And get us a motel room.
[laughs]
what?
For a.J. And me.
While you run around the woods
eating snails and beetles.
That way if you get anxious
about being away from her,
We're right there.
This is weird.
Why is this weird?
Because what kind
of sick bastard
Travels with duct tape
and rope?
No, we actually
made a couple of stops
While you were
knocked out.
Had to get more
tom for the collins--
Oh, and also
rob a gun store.
Wait, what?
Well, technically,
burgle.
How long was I out?
Mm... 20 minutes?
Dammit!
Yeah, that is not
good for you.
No,
turn around dick-nuts,
I can still make
the rehearsal dinner.
After we rescue pam.
Now, shut up.
Oh, and un-shut up
for a second.
Is this the way
to the grain elevator?
Ah... Oh, yeah,
right down that road.
Take a left.
Take a left!
Even for me,
that was pretty lucky.
Wa-hoo!
Rental car!
[barry]
there we go.
Looking good, barry.
Well, thanks,
other barry.
Archer comes in
to save her,
And boosh!
K-k-k-kill zone!
So you're just bug-nuts
crazy, huh?
[laughs]
crazy like a fox!
Who's bionic!
And, whose fiance
dumped him,
For literally
the dumbest guy in russia?
Who want waffle?
I forget to make waffle.
Oh, and just so you know,
my worst nightmare,
Which is actually recurring,
Is me and santa claus
getting chased through the snow
By lurch
from the adam's family.
Uh, why did
you tell me that?
[laughs]
exactly.
[archer]
piece of shit rental.
[edie]
you drive like a...
Egg.
I-- no, I don't,
and also, shut up
Because right now
I'm going to explain
What cyborgs are,
and why they're a threat,
To our entire
way of life.
[cyril]
I mean, not now,
obviously.
But, someday.
Someday soon...
[snoring]
I am gonna
re-hit that.
Huh? Hm?
Hey, you.
Hello.
Wait.
Who's laws
of what's its?
Asimov's three laws
of-- look,
Never mind.
They don't even apply to barry
Because he's a frickin'
cyborg.
[barry, singsong]
archer...
Come out and play.
Ugh, and also
a gaping, prolapsed anus.
So, grain elevator.
Besides a place
to blow farmers,
What's the point?
To store grain,
dumbass.
Yeah, but you elevator
it way the hell up there,
Then-- wait, cows don't
go up there to eat it,
Do they?
Oh my god,
no!
It's gravity fed back down
to trucks and trains and shit.
Which are on the ground.
Yes!
See where I'm going
with this?
Why not make it horizontal,
so the cows can just walk up
And eat whenever?
So just a mile long trough
of grain getting rained on
All the damn time?
I-- well, no.
It would have like
a salad bar roof on it,
You idiot.
[barry]
said the dumb waiter.
Get it, archer?
As in, you're dumb,
and you dress like a waiter.
[pam]
told ya!
God dammit, pam,
This is exactly
what a man should wear to a--
Holy shitsnacks!
What the--
pam?
[sighs]
yeah, and just a heads up--
[growls]
[pam]
whoa!
Dammit, pam.
How about a--
oh, wait by heads up,
Did you mean--?
[grunting]
Seriously, barry,
why all the anger?
Because katya
broke up with me!
[laughs]
Too soon?
Edie, cut me down!
Oh, wow,
where to start?
Even in a new dress,
you look like ten pounds of shit
In a five pound bag.
The whole town thinks
you're a giant asshole
For moving to new york city.
You can just
say new york.
Oh, and dad was right,
you'll never find a husband
Unless you convince
a blind man
You're a seeing eye pig!
[cries]
I meant cut me down
from here!
Yeah. Duh.
But you know
you're no prize, right?
Excuse me?
He said--
[growling]
[laughs]
[thuds]
Archer! Do something!
Flower box.
Shot gun.
[grunts]
[thuds]
[pam]
ow.
[growls]
[gagging]
Hey, track suit,
If anybody's gonna choke
my sister's bitch neck,
It's gonna be me.
[laughs]
what are you doing?
What you got a little
shot gun? Huh?
Yeah,
remember right now?
When I'm a frickin'
cyborg?
[archer]
barry, just for you,
I got explosive ammo.
You what, now?
Jesus christ,
you could have killed me!
Shut up!
Huh, I mean,
I'm not a doctor,
Or, a robotisist,
But, uh,
that can't be good.
So, hey,
why don't we all do this--
[gunshot]
[archer]
oh, god.
Oh!
[machine voice]
forgot what I was gonna say.
[screams]
[objects crashing]
[scream continuing]
[body thuds]
[rattling]
So, thank you...
For?
Saving your life?
I thought you were
thanking me...
For dropping
those truth bombs.
What?
You'll never find a husband.
So, you really
think he's dead?
[archer, sighs]
only one way to be sure.
[edie]
hello? I'm sorry, what?
Shut up, no,
uh-uh. No!
What are you saying,
don?
[police officer]
sir, sir, over there.
Is that a man?
Yeah,
you're damn right it is.
Hey, but slow down, though,
we're, hey--!
Jesus christ, arn.
Huh. I think I got
a blowjob out here once.
[edie]
a what? I'm sorry,
did you say a blowjob?
What? Yes!
Of course it's off, don!
[screams]
So, apparently,
don over-served on vin rogue,
And increasingly impatient
for his bride-to-be's arrival
At the rehearsal dinner,
Let midge olerud suck him off
behind the sundae bar!
[laughs]
Too soon?
So thank you, pamela,
for ruining my wedding.
Oh, and also,
my life.
You ruined my life!
Are you happy?
Yes.
[chuckles]
all I wanted.
[laughing]
[man]
made in georgia.