MURPHY (O.S.): Time and
tide, they wait for no man.
MURPHY: Nor do I, Mr. Tunt, nor do I.
And unless my demands are
met, I will launch my nerve
gas missiles on New York,
Washington and Miami in...
Eleven hours and -- oh look at
that, eleven minutes.
Hey, make a wish.
CECIL: Uh, I wish you wouldn't
launch nerve gas missiles on
New York, Washing-
MURPHY: And I wish you fools
would stop destroying the oceans! Overfishing,
industrial runoff, don't even get me
started on whaling, oh, and
plastic bottles?! That's --
I can't even - there is a floating
mass of garbage in the Pacific
twice the size of the United States!
Oh, and where the hell
is the news crew I asked for?!
CECIL: With me! And with your permission,
I'm sending them down in the DSV.
MURPHY: Good, yes! I need to
get my message to the world!
Who'd you get? Oprah?
CECIL: Bigger.
LANA: Ya know...
MURPHY: Hello. Is that her?
LANA: I -- oh right,
he can't see us.
MURPHY: Which has really got me...
nettled!
MURPHY: Alright, Mr. Tunt, send them down.
But if this is some sort of ruse...
CECIL: Are -- was there
a follow-up, or...?
MURPHY: No, I was leaving
the consequences to your
imagination. But trust me, they are grave.
As in watery grave?
CECIL: I -
MURPHY: Sealab out!
God damn it! Off! Turn
off, you... [zzzrpt]
LANA: So, I have a question...
MALORY: How are none of these a minibar?!
TIFFY: Oh my God, I know what
you mean, right? I mean it is a
giant floating biodiesel-
powered hotel room...
MALORY: Don't get snotty with
me, missy! You people lure us
out here to help the government
recover a hydrogen bomb-
LANA: Which, let's be honest,
you were going to
hold for ransom.
MALORY: Reward! When the whole
time you knew this crazy Murphy
character was going to bomb
New York with nerve gas?!
CECIL: Well!
LANA: Not to mention D.C.
and Miami.
MALORY: Which no one
who matters will miss.
LANA: What about your
South Beach condo?
MALORY: Hello! Florida real
estate collapse! It's farther
underwater than Sealab. But if
my homeowner's policy covers
nerve gas attacks,
that's a win-win.
LANA: Wow. So my question,
ignoring the obvious one of why
an ocean research lab has nerve
gas missiles in the first
place! Is how many men
does Murphy have?
CECIL: Mmmmmlike, two?
LANA: Oh, then -
CECIL: Score. Two score, so
around forty, sorry, should've
finished that thmmpf.
LANA: Sooo, since we're talking
about forty hostiles, I
have a follow up question.
ARCHER: Something
something danger zone?!
LANA: Ahhhhh!
ARCHER: I know, I'm not even trying anymore.
LANA: Archer-
ARCHER: Noop! Randy! I'm
Cameradude Randy, and this
pathetic, trout-shouldered excuse
for a boom operator is Chet.
CYRIL: Shut up, what's
pathetic is your plan!
LANA: Wait, you have
an actual plan?
ARCHER: Duh, yes Lana. So,
obviously they're gonna search
us for weapons when we get down
there, so wait whaaaaaaaat?
Something else danger zone.
LANA: Get Murphy alone, get
him at gunpoint, and make him
disarm the missiles. Ya know,
that might actually work.
ARCHER: Of course it'll work, I've thought
through every aspect of the mission.
LANA: Hence those ridiculous
fake mustaches, since Murphy's
never seen you before and has
no idea what you look like?
GILLETTE: God damn it, Archer!
ARCHER: No, that was just an experiment.
I wanted to see if Ray looked
gayer without his.
GILLETTE: Ya know...
ARCHER: But you don't. You just look as gay.
Boop.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com | sync to web-dl by aneurysm
TIFFY (O.S.): Sea Tunt to DSV Goddess.
Wait for my command to
disengage the coupler.
LANA (O.S.): Roger Sea Tunt, on your-
ARCHER (O.S.): Noop! Lana
move, I'm skippering.
EVERYBODY (O.S.): Archer, no!
ARCHER (O.S.): Goddammit I'm skippering!
EVERYBODY: AAHHHHH!!!
CECIL: Huh. Mildly
inauspicious.
LANA: Asshole.
ARCHER: What Lana, I clearly
called "skipper!" And I clearly
said "seatbelts," so... You
only have yourselves to blame.
GILLETTE: Really?
LANA: Jesus, Ray!
Your nose is broken!
GILLETTE: Really?
LANA: Cyril, gear bag!
First aid kit!
ARCHER: Just give him a couple of tampons.
What, that's their job.
LANA: Really?
ARCHER: Just give him some tam-
LANA: I don't have any!
ARCHER: Do you...
think that was wise?
LANA: Meaning?
ARCHER: Well I'm just assuming,
I mean, your breasts
are slightly bigger, you're-
LANA: Shut your stupid
mustachey dickhole and drive
the goddamn submarine!
ARCHER: Slightly irritable?
CHERYL/CAROL (O.S.): Shut up!
Jesus, will you drop it?!
He tried to have me committed
so he could steal my
inheritance! I hate him and I'm
never speaking to him again ever!
PAM: But -- okay granted, that
was super shitty. But trust me,
you don't want to go through
life hating your only sibling.
Take my sister Edie...
CHERYL/CAROL: Ha, ha, ha, you have a sister?
PAM: Edie, yes, shut up, and
when we were kids she was so
mean to me? Always teasing me,
calling me Spamela, rubbing
cheese curds in my eyes? One
time she stabbed me in the neck?
CHERYL/CAROL: So, now you
guys are super-close, or...?
PAM: Ha ha ha, hell no, I wouldn't
piss on her neck-stabbin ass if
it was on fire.
MALORY: Ugh, is this
the infamous Edie?
CHERYL/CAROL: Yeah, Pam thinks
I should forgive Cecil since
he's the only
family I have left.
MALORY: Who could forgive a person who
buys a boat this big with no bar on it?!
CHERYL/CAROL: There was a ton
of booze on the helicopter...
MALORY: Exactly, was...
ARCHER (O.S.): Yeah sorry, I had to ditch it.
CYRIL: Well yeah, who needs a
first aid kit when you've got
ten gallons of booze?!
ARCHER: Three and three-fifths
gallons, Cyril, and I counted
'em so keep your mitts off!
Except to pass me one up here, but-
LANA: Oh great! The world's first DSVUI!
ARCHER: May I finish?! But
since I have zero experience
skippering submersibles, I
should probably have something
light! So Cyril, I'm
thinking coffee liqueur?
MALORY: I mean, not
even cooking sherry?
PAM: I got some Kentucky Moon in my-
MALORY: Ooh, gimme!
PAM: Dut dut dut dut! You drink
it, you replace it. Grain
alcohol's a key component
of a good bug-out bag.
MALORY: A what?
PAM: Bug-out bag? Oh
my God, for teotwaki?!
MALORY: The bear
from Star Wars?
PAM: The end of the
world as we know it!
CHERYL/CAROL: Pam's like, gay
for doomsday, she thinks our
whole society's gonna collapse if
we run out of oil or whatever.
PAM: If?! You mean when!
Wow, and that is a perfect
example of a pre-post-peak-oil
mindset. The --
MALORY: Ahhh. Say, this stuff
is pretty good. What
did you say it was?
PAM: Basically pure ethanol?
MALORY: Huh. Well God
bless corn subsidies.
CHERYL/CAROL: Who're
you, Earl Butz?
MALORY: You say that
like it's a bad thing.
ARCHER (O.S.): Oh for the--
I said I was sorry!
CYRIL (O.S.): No you didn't!
ARCHER: Oh. Well I
was planning to.
GILLETTE: Oh, well
then no hard feelings.
ARCHER: Good, because your
shitty sarcasm notwithstanding,
I'm glad that's behind us so we
can enjoy what is probably a
once in a lifetime ad-
LANA: Rrrowrff!
ARCHER: -- venture, again?
Seriously? Why are
you puking so much?
LANA: Ugh, because
shut up and steer.
ARCHER: Here, take a
pull off this guy.
LANA: No! For the
like, ninth time, no!
ARCHER: Yes, c'mon, it'll take the edge off.
And I think I
speak for everybody-
CYRIL/GILLETTE: No you don't.
ARCHER: -- shut up, when I say we'd all
be a lot happier if you weren't so...
LANA: What, anxious?! About a
half-drunk first-time-driving-a-
submarine idiot taking me to the
bottom of the ocean to face
forty eco-terrorists led by a
crazy person who's about to
bomb the entire east
coast with nerve gas?!
ARCHER: I was gonna say-
LANA: What?! What were you gonna say?!
MURPHY: They're going to say
that I've gone insane, that
I've lost my mind. And that's fine, let them.
Because the real insanity is the
systematic, my God the almost
deliberate way, those bastards
are destroying our oceans.
And I hate that it's come to this, but
I truly don't see an alternative.
So, you all know what you have to
do, and I know you won't fail me.
Nor I you, gentlemen...
nor I you.
ARCHER: I was gonna say "bitchy and
periody" but then I thought better of it.
ARCHER (O.S.): Okay, we're getting close.
Let's go over
the legends again. Lana?
LANA: I am tough-but-fair investigative
reporter Sojourner King.
ARCHER: Which, ugh, whatever.
Cyril?
CYRIL: [sigh) Chet, sound guy.
ARCHER: That's it? C'mon Chet,
the devil's in the details!
Like, I'm Randy Magnum, local
Emmy-winning cameraman and
nationally ranked
pro kitesurfer.
LANA: No you're not.
ARCHER: Well Randy Magnum is!
Ray, go.
GILLETTE: I am segment producer Carl Channing...
ARCHER: Oh my God, c'mon...
GILLETTE: And -- what's
Randy Magnum ranked?
ARCHER: Fourth.
GILLETTE: And third-ranked
pro kitesurfer.
ARCHER: What?! No you're not!
GILLETTE: Carl Channing is.
LANA: Nobody is a nationally
ranked anything! That is the
worst legend you could possibly
have, it would literally take
ten seconds to check it out!
ARCHER: Yeah, Carl.
LANA: Okay, shut
up, there it is.
CYRIL: Jeezy Petes,
that thing is huge!
MURPHY: Sealab to DSV, over?
LANA: This is-
ARCHER: This is DSV I'm skippering!
MURPHY: Um, okay. You
sound pretty excited.
ARCHER: I am, actually.
It's my first time.
MURPHY: Hey, super.
You're clear to dock, so
just head for the lights.
And I'll be waiting for you.
[zzrpt]
LANA: Was that -- did he sound -- do
you think this is some kind of trap?
ARCHER: What? No, I don't think it's a trap!
Although I never do...
And it very often is.
LANA: And that's how they died...
ARCHER: Right?
MALORY: A little peach juice, a little
of that old Kentucky Moon, and... boom.
You've almost got
yourself a Bellini.
CHERYL/CAROL: Mmmm!
PAM: Holy shitsnacks!
MALORY: Well it's no Harry's
Bar, but here you don't have
Hemingway grabbing
your tits every time you-[flrp]
PAM: Did I misread that?
MALORY: What do you think?
PAM: No?
MURPHY (O.S.): No, my men
are guarding the missiles.
CYRIL: Well there
goes that plan.
MURPHY: What plan?
LANA: To... do a one-on-one interview,
just you alone, with the missiles?
MURPHY: No, we're doing it on the
bridge, I've already got it all set up.
LANA: But I really think we
should do it wherever the
missiles are, to underscore
the gravity of the -
MURPHY: The bridge is
where the chair is.
LANA: But-
MURPHY: The bridge is where the chair is!
ARCHER: Yeah, Sojourner.
MURPHY: Thank you, uh...?
ARCHER: Randy, Randy Magnum,
I'm a local Emmy-winning
cameraman and nash -
LANA: Nooo!
ARCHER: -- shunally ranked pro
kitesurfer, second in the
nation, actually, which even the most
cursory internet search will corroborate.
LANA/CYRIL/GILLETTE: [sigh]
MURPHY: I really doubt
we'll have time, Randy.
MURPHY: We only have ten hours before
I'll be forced to launch my missiles.
LANA: Which are where
again, exactly?
MALORY (O.S.): You heard me!
I want fifty million dollars!
TIFFY: Pff, join the club.
CECIL: Right?
MALORY: That's how much I could've gotten
for the hydrogen bomb, so that's how
much I -- what do you
mean, join the club?
CECIL: Oh, that's just an idiom, it means-
MALORY: I know what it means,
you toboggan-wearing ass,
why did she say it?!
CECIL: Oh. I assume
because I'm penniless?
MALORY: What?!
CHERYL/CAROL: Ha, ha, oh.
Wait, what?
CECIL: (sighs) That's why I
tried to get control of your
inheritance. And I'm sorry
I did that, Beans. I just
wanted to help people, but all these
foundations are so expensive.
CHERYL/CAROL: I know, but Cecil!
You really spent your
whole inheritance on...
the poors?
CECIL: Well, and scientific research.
The Sealab alone cost
two hundred million.
MALORY: Wh-?! How did
it cost that much?!
CECIL: Well apparently they
bought a bunch of nerve gas
missiles, and hid that expense in the budget.
Which I never bothered to read.
Or even look at.
MURPHY: Look at this place!
Such a colossal boondoggle! We
don't do any research, really,
and building it, I mean, the
environmental impact was just insane!
LANA: So... why did
you take a job here?
MURPHY: To save the ocean! And
also my salary is six hundred
thousand dollars a year.
EVERYBODY: What!?
MURPHY: I know, but don't put that in there.
Let me just read
my list of demands. Ahem.
One, a fifty-year, worldwide
moratorium on all fishing. Two-
CYRIL: I'm sorry, did you mean whaling?
MURPHY: That's number
two, if you'll let me -
LANA: Wait, you want
to end all fishing?
ARCHER: For fifty years?!
MURPHY: At least. The
fish have to replenish.
LANA: Okay, that's it, I'm calling bullshit.
I want to see the missiles, now.
MURPHY: What, no, you can't, you-
LANA: You don't have any missiles!
MURPHY: Yes I do! I've got...
like fifty.
LANA: Fifty.
MURPHY: Ten?
ARCHER: That's still a lot.
LANA: Shut up. Captain Murphy, how long
have you been down here all alone?
MURPHY: (sigh) Two years.
Nobody had been paid in months,
the foundation was broke...
CYRIL: Not surprising,
given your salary.
MURPHY: Yeah, paid three years in advance.
He is the world's worst negotiator.
LANA: And you're, sorry, but
you've obviously had some kind
of psychotic break, so I think
you should come with us, and -
MURPHY: I'm not going anywhere!
Nor are you!
CYRIL/GILLETTE: Lanaaa!
LANA: Archerrrr!
ARCHER: Murpheeee!
I -- dammit, I had something
about point-and-shoot, but -
MURPHY: A gun?! Are you insane, don't you
know how much pressure we're under?!
ARCHER: Honestly, and I don't know why
this is, but it never really gets to me.
CYRIL: Wait, I think he
means water pressure!
MURPHY: And air pressure! The tiniest
hole in the hull would be catastrophic!
ARCHER: The hole!
Is gonna be in you!
LANA: Archer, no! Don't shoot.
MURPHY: Okay okay,
look, it's gone!
Now please, put the gun away!
ARCHER: No, I will put on the safety!
Which should be...
dammit, I wish Krieger
wouldn't do these idiot mods.
KRIEGER: ("drum solo")
Duhduhduhduhduhduhduhduh bow dow dow dowwwwwwww!
Dow dow dadowwwwwwwww!
ARCHER: Wait, yeah, that
clearly says "safe," and even
Krieger's not that crazy...
[click]
ARCHER: Okay, now slowly
kick the knife over to-[BLAM!]
CYRIL: Dammit!
LANA: Oh my God...!
MURPHY: Okay, okay, okay, uh,
okay, one of two things is
going to happen now...
[SPRZZINK!]
EVERYBODY: Oh! Okay! Oohhh!
[SPRRZZZRIINK!]
EVERYBODY: Aahhhh!
MURPHY: Okay, now one of one thing
is going to hap-[BWOOOOOOSH!]
EVERYBODY: OHHHH..
[zzzzzztttttt]
CECIL: Uh? Well now there's no signal at all...
TIFFY: Wow, oh my God, I'm
having the weirdest
djà vu right now.
CECIL: Ya know...
TIFFY: Here, lemme jailbreak
your phone, it's a totally
reversible process.
Oh, bricked it!
[SPRRZZZEINK]
EVERYBODY: OOOOHHHHHH!!!!
MURPHY: Hatch!
Emergency hatch!
[WHUMP WHUMP WHUMP WHUMP!]
ARCHER: We don't wanna
go outside, idiot!
MURPHY: It's the next pod!
ARCHER: Oh, duh.
MURPHY: I'll hold it open!
Go, go!
LANA: Aaaagh... ungh!
CYRIL: Aaaagh...
GILLETTE: Aaaagh...
LANA: No no no no no -- Assholes.
ARCHER: Wooohooohooohooooooof!
Ow.
FEMALE VOICE (O.S.): Pod One, flooded.
Pod Two, flooding.
ARCHER: So what, now we die in... a break
room I would die to have at ISIS?!
GILLETTE: Right?
CYRIL: Maybe not, if he shuts the ha-
MURPHY: Aaaaaaagh!
[KAKROONCH!]
EVERYBODY: Ewwww!
MURPHY: Rrrgh, and I just refilled the cans...
LANA: C'mon you guys,
get it off of him!
MURPHY: No no, there's no time...
(cough) Plus I think
the weight of it's the only
thing holding in my intestines.
EVERYBODY: Eww.
MURPHY: Save yourselves. Let
this compartment flood, up to
that next hatch... Then seal
it behind you, and run.
This is pod two, it's about
a hundred yards to the
DSV at pod six, but pods three through
six are still watertigh-[GRRRRNKOOOSH]
FEMALE VOICE (O.S.): Pod three,
four, five, six. Flooded.
EVERYBODY: Aaaghhh!
MURPHY: Yeah, that's not ideal.
Okay, there's -wait, why
did a TV crew have a gun?!
LANA: We're not a TV
crew, we're from ISIS.
MURPHY: ISIS?! Jesus Christ, no
wonder this all went tits up.
EVERYBODY: Hey!
MURPHY: Forgive my candor, I
just felt my spleen slip out of
what was my anus. (coughs) That
locker over there, open it.
CYRIL:(grunts)
(gasps) Scuba gear!
LANA: [gasp]
ARCHER: Dibs on best!
GILLETTE: Oooh, y'all I'm not
certified, is that gonna be a problem?
MURPHY: Well, not the biggest problem...
LANA: There's only three.
ARCHER: Sooo...
MURPHY: So one of you is going to drown.
ARCHER: Yep, got that...
MURPHY: Temporarily.
EVERYBODY: What?
MURPHY: Hundred yards to the DSV.
Best case, for a strong
swimmer, two minutes. (coughs)
The water's ice cold, help delay
the brain damage. Use the
defibrillator on the DSV...
to restart the heart.
LANA: Yeah but whose heart?!
MURPHY: (coughs)
Weakest swimmer.
LANA: Wh-? Aww, screw you guys!
ARCHER: What, Lana, this isn't -- entirely
about race! Guys, back me up here.
CYRIL: Well I was all-county in the
hundred meter freestyle in tenth grade...
GILLETTE: And I have bionic legs...
CYRIL: Plus I'm super scared...
ARCHER: Plus you're a woman?
LANA: I -- yeah, a
pregnant woman!
ARCHER/CYRIL/GILLETTE: What?
LANA: That's why I haven't
been drinking, that's why I've
been puking, and that's
why my boobs are so huge!
ARCHER: Well I wouldn't
say "huge," but -
CYRIL: When were you
planning to tell me?!
LANA: (sighs) When I finally figured
out how to tell you it's not yours.
CYRIL: Gnk?
MURPHY: Awwwkwaaaard...
(coughs) Ignore me, sorry, I'm
dying. Crushed, by an off-brand
drink machine. (gasps) Oh my
God, just like that old gypsy woman srgbgh...
CYRIL: Gnnk! Gnnk! Gn - [THWAK!]
ARCHER: Get it together! We both know
this isn't your first time as a cuckold!
Or at least now we both know it.
And for real? You're pregnant?
LANA: Five weeks, long story, yes, but-
ARCHER: Shut up. Here.
LANA: Wh-? But-
ARCHER: Ray's half robot,
Cyril, miraculously, is good at
something, and... Lana, you're gonna be a mom!
Just promise me
you'll be a better
one than mine.
CECIL: Because I'm worried
something may have gone
terribly wrong down there...
MALORY: Well if it did, we
can't do anything about it, and
if it didn't, all the more
reason to drive this tub to Bermuda
for some duty-free champagne!
LANA: Archer, that
shouldn't be that hard.
ARCHER: Ff-ff-ffrasing...
[cough/choke]
LANA: Okay, here it comes! You just gotta
relax and let it go in your mouth!
ARCHER: Ff-ff-
ffrasinglrrgllrg...!
LANA: Archer?!
ARCHER: Laggaah?
ARCHER: Gly gluggve ggglooo...
LANA: I know. Ray, now!
GILLETTE: C'mon, hurry!
CYRIL: Move! Scarlet
Letter O'Whora!
LANA: Cyril! It was a...!
Donor, you shithead.
C'mon, hang on Archer, two minutes!
Your brain can -- almost spare that!
GILLETTE: So hey, this may be a
weird question, but you know
where she's registered?
CYRIL: Wh-?! What do you think?!
GILLETTE: Lanaaa!
Would you hurry up?!
LANA: (panting) Said the guy
apparently too busy counting
his bionic legs to help!
GILLETTE: You're gonna sass yourself right
out of a carseat! Now c'mon, hurry!
LANA: [panting/straining]
GILLETTE: Cyril! Get
ready on the airlock!
CYRIL: Yeah, yeah...
LANA: Here, go go go go go.
GILLETTE: I got him I got him!
LANA: Cyril now, blow it!
CYRIL: Blow me,
boom, nailed it.
[FWOOOOOSH!]
LANA: Clear?!
GILLETTE: Clear!
[zzzttt bmmm]
LANA: Again!
GILLETTE: C'mon,
he's dead let it go!
LANA: Clear?!
GILLETTE: Clear!
[zzzttt bmmm]
[beep, beep, beep]
LANA: Archer?!
EVERYBODY: Oh!
GILLETTE: Is he...? Are you...?
ARCHER: The man who
cheated death?!
EVERYBODY: Oh! Thank God.
LANA: Oh my God, Archer, I can't -- I
mean, I don't even know how to thank you!
ARCHER: Well, you could name
your kid after -
LANA: Noop.
ARCHER: Then just get me topside. I need
to brush Ray's tongue out of my mouth.
GILLETTE: I didn't give
you mouth to mouth!
ARCHER: C'mon, admit it, you Frenched me!
You can lie but your boner can't!
GILLETTE: (laughing)
Cut it out, Archer!
ARCHER: Yeah, look at ya!
All blushy!
LANA: Archer be careful, the defibrillator-
[BZZZZRPT!]
MALORY: So. Although Sealab was destroyed...
CECIL: It was insured for
three times its value, so
now I'm richer than ever.
CHERYL/CAROL: And I have forgiven you,
for being such an incorrigible douche.
MALORY: No one cares, because
most importantly -
ARCHER: I cheated not only
death, but also somehow
irreparable brain damage!
MALORY: That remains to be seen,
and shut up, because Lana
is going to be a mother!
CYRIL: Three cheers for
little Johnny Bastard!
PAM: Hip, hip!...Ahem.
Inappropriate.
MALORY: The point is -- and seriously,
shut up -- everybody has a happy ending!
GILLETTE: Really?! Ol' Ray
gets a happy ending?!
ARCHER: Ray-
GILLETTE: Or does Randy
Roughhouse here zap him with a
defibrillator and fry the CPU
that made his bionic legs work?!
ARCHER: Ray, I'm sorry! C'mon,
I was wrong!
GILLETTE: Really.
ARCHER: Yeah, without the mustache
you look, like, a billion percent gayer.
Boop.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com | sync to web-dl by aneurysm