(Electricity crackling)
Fargo.
All new wednesdays at 10:00.
Starts April 19 on fx.
Woman: Son of a bitch!
Woman (Announcing):
Fxx presents Archer.
¶ (Slow jazz) ¶
man: Oh death, where
is thy sting?
Oh grave, where is
thy victory?
For man that is born of woman
hath but a short time to live,
and is full of misery.
He cometh up and is cut down
like a flower.
He fleeth as it were
a shadow.
In the midst of life,
we are in death.
In the midst of death,
we are in life.
Lana: It was a nice service.
Malory: Hmm.
And he had
a good, long life.
He did, for a heroin addict.
Sad Archer wasn't there.
Or here.
It's been a long
couple of months.
Three, next week.
You should go sleep
in a real bed.
I'm fine. I want
to be here if--
when he wakes up.
Lana: Yeah.
Did the doctor...?
The same.
Could be tomorrow,
could be another three months.
Could be...
Yeah.
Well, I guess I'll go.
I'll try to bring
a.J. By tomorrow.
Or Friday.
We'll be here.
At least he doesn't know
woodhouse died.
That would break his heart.
Mm-hmm.
Although there's no telling
what he knows.
Or what he's thinking about.
Well, dreaming about,
i suppose.
No.
No, no, no!
No!
(Grunting)
Noooo!
¶ (Jazzy theme) ¶
(grunting)
Let me go, goddammit.
Come on!
Go easy, Archer.
Poovey, I swear to Christ,
I will punch you
right in the... genitals.
It's okay. Let him go.
You big lummox.
Oh, Jesus. Woodhouse.
So, where are you, figgis?
You got any leads?
What do you think happened?
I think he got too far
behind on his dope tab,
so sometime last night
his dealer
punched his ticket for him.
Yeah, and wouldn't that
be convenient?
(Chuckles)
Not for him.
You little rat fu--
(Whistling)
Oh!
Now, scram, Archer!
Ow. Son of a--
i mean, just ow.
You can claim the body
at the morgue.
But that better be
the last time I smell you
anywhere near this case.
Yeah, we'll see about that.
Yeah? And we'll see
how you like it
when I yank
your p.I. License.
(Sighs)
See you around, poovey.
Take it easy, Archer.
Oh, hey, and Archer?
Come to think of it,
where were you last night?
Ask your wife.
(Growls)
Ah, you know his wife left him.
For you, Archer,
'cause you screwed her tits off
at the precinct cookout.
So then she thought the two
of you would get married
and live happily ever after,
but then you were like, "what?"
Exactly. That face
right there.
I-- (Groans)
How does that help?
Mm, humanizes you?
(Whistling)
Hey, pal. You got a second?
I do not, actually,
and I am not,
come to think
of it, so screw.
Hm. I'm sorry.
Let me rephrase that.
What--?
Do you know who I work for?
Do you know how much
i don't care?
About what?
Living out the week?
'Cause we're both
out of luck, friend.
I left all my cash
at the track.
But if maybe you wanted
some dope...?
Do I look like
a junkie to you?
I don't know.
I try not to judge.
You used to sell
to this guy.
Yeah, woodhouse. He--
wait. Used to?
He's dead.
What?
Oh, for the love of--
he was one of--
no, he was my best customer.
So, he was paid up?
Paid up? He paid in advance.
Yeah. He was not great
with money.
(Chuckling) Right? I mean, who
tips their dope dealer?
So, I guess we're done here?
We're done when I say
we're done.
I'm sorry.
Let me rephrase that.
(Growling)
(Sighs)
(Snarls)
Okay.
So, one of two things
is gonna happen here.
Oh!
(Clatter)
Hm. Wonder what
the other thing was?
¶ (Jazz trumpet) ¶
goddamn.
Is it your feeding time already?
(Growls)
I wish you wouldn't
antagonize him.
Well, I wish you
could hold a tempo.
(Rimshot)
Which, clearly, sarcastic.
No, it wasn't.
(Snores)
No, thank you, zerk,
that will suffice.
(Zerk growls)
Huh?
Wha-- what's-- what--
ah, there he is.
The infamous Sterling Archer,
private eye.
And I trust you know
who I am?
I do. But what do I call you?
Mother will do.
And so, you do know who I am,
but you don't care?
What? No, i--
that's what you told
my bartender
when you stuck a gun
in his ribs.
I-- well, first of all,
your bartender sells heroin.
Gasp.
And I pulled my gun
because I'm trying to find out
who killed my partner.
That would be woodhouse.
Yeah. He-- how'd
you know that?
It's my business to know a great
many things, Mr. Archer.
What would you say
if I offered you a drink?
I'd probably say bourbon.
Old buncombe,
if you've got it.
Oh, I have a bit
of everything.
So I hear.
Hmm.
How do you take it?
Usually alone.
Thank you for making
an exception.
Please.
And so, I do hope you'll
forgive Mr. zerk
for his hands-on approach.
Maybe.
But I sure won't forget it.
Yes. I believe that
was the point.
I meant--
i know what you meant.
Cigarette?
No, thanks.
Never took it up.
Really?
But I thought they loaded
all you g.I.S down
with cartons of them
on your way up the gangplank.
They did.
Supposed to help
keep you alert.
I guess I found it all
stimulating enough.
Hm. Normandy?
Yeah.
Omaha beach.
By way of north Africa
and sicily.
And after normandy,
through France and Belgium,
all the way to Berlin.
Well, I had to get to Berlin.
I'd sent
all my clean shirts ahead.
Mm-hmm. Speak any German?
You know. "Don't shoot,"
"i surrender,"
"Hitler's the tops,"
stuff like that.
Mm-hmm.
Bronze star with two oak leaves
and "v" device.
Legion of merit.
Croix de guerre with palm.
Silver star with two oak leaves.
Distinguished service cross
with one oak leaf
and "v" device.
Three purple hearts.
It goes on, Mr. Archer.
Yeah, senior year,
i was voted class flirt.
And yet, you turned down
a battlefield commission
to second lieutenant.
Well, after class flirt,
i mean--
in fact, you left the army
at the same rank you went in.
Buck private. And do you know
what that tells me?
I need a new lock
on my diary?
That you don't like
taking orders.
Yeah, or having
my time wasted.
So, if you'll excuse me--
oh, no. I will not.
Excuse me?
No.
I just said.
Sorry?
Me too.
I-- wait. No. I meant--
I know what you meant.
I-- look, I'm just trying
to find the bastard
who killed my partner.
With which, perhaps,
i can help you.
With which-- hang on.
Wait, really?
Perhaps. But before i
could help you,
I would need you
to help me.
I'll do anything to find
woodhouse's killer.
And then avenge his death.
Well then, Mr. Archer,
what would you say if i
offered you a job?
I'd probably say yes.
And also bourbon.
Mother: Len trexler.
I assume you're familiar
with him?
Archer: (Chuckling)
Who isn't?
He's the biggest mobster
in L.A.
Well, maybe not
for much longer.
Why, is he sick?
Wh-- no, you ass.
Although you could say
that his time has come.
Wait. You want me
to help you make a move
against len trexler?
Whose hobby is dissolving
people in acid?
Oh, now, trexler doesn't do
the actual dissolving.
That would be
his enforcer, Dutch Dylan.
I don't care who
does the dissolving.
But if you help me,
i can help you.
Perhaps. You made that
very clear.
Look, all I need you to do
is go down to pier 9
in long beach tonight
and simply observe
and report back.
No.
Oh, come on.
I thought you had guts.
And I'd like to keep them
in their current location,
I.E., inside me, not melting
in a 50-gallon drum of acid
with my shoes and feet
and face.
¶ Never know how much
I love you ¶
¶ never know how much I care ¶
¶ when you put your arms
around me ¶
¶ I get a fever that's
so hard to bear ¶
¶ you give me fever ¶
¶ when you kiss me ¶
¶ fever when you
hold me tight ¶
¶ fever in the morning ¶
¶ fever all through
the night ¶
¶ you give me fever ¶
I'm in.
Excellent.
Then find killer,
uh, revenge do.
Careful what you wish for.
You just might get it.
¶ Till you sizzle ¶
¶ what a lovely way ¶
¶ to burn ¶
that's some set
you got on you.
I mean, not your-- i--
I meant--
i know what you meant.
Uh, yeah.
Uh, let me start over.
My name's Archer.
Lana Kane.
And, I'm sorry,
but have we met?
If we had, you'd remember.
(Rimshot)
Gillette: Stop it.
And so, um, you're
the singer here.
Wow. And you must be
an old gypsy woman.
Close. I'm a private
investigator.
I'm doing some work
for your boss.
And apparently doing it
with a fresh new take
on the word "private."
Can I buy you a drink?
Hmm. Bottle of pbr.
(Chuckling)
Pbr. Wow.
I-i would have
thought your tastes
were a little more, um--
Pierre beauvais. Rouge.
Ah.
Problem?
No. Not-not when you're
pulling down
25 bucks a day
plus expenses.
And what sort of
daily expenses
does a semi-private
investigator incur?
Bullets?
Daily.
Or, I don't know,
maybe a surf-and-turf dinner
at the Polo lounge?
Un-huh.
And then maybe a room upstairs,
at the Beverly hills hotel.
Uh-huh.
And then, maybe--
I'm gonna leave you here.
Between hope and despair.
What the hell does that mean?
Before you shoot a big,
salty load in your pants.
Shut up. How much
for the champagne?
$26.
Wha-- I'm not paying 26 bucks
for a bottle of frustration.
(Growls)
(Groans)
You're lucky my ear hurts.
There.
Plus tip.
How about the tip of my cock?
(Rimshot)
Gillette: Stop it!
So, in that scenario,
would I take your penis
in my hand? My mouth?
Asshole. Wait, no.
I mean-- not-- goddammit.
Archer:
Pierre beauvais Rouge.
Hardy har har.
Hey, 1933 called.
They want
their gold digger back.
Meanwhile, I have to dip
into my rainy day fund,
which is barely enough to buy
an extremely nice umbrella.
Wait. What the--
holy shit.
Leave it to woodhouse.
Now I can find his killer
and take revenge.
Although... I better get moving
if I'm going to make it
to long beach in time.
Okay. So, first thing
tomorrow morning.
Well, or probably
after breakfast.
After which, I just remembered
I'm getting a haircut.
But after that,
vengeance will be mine.
Oh, duh.
Just like you always
said, woodhouse,
"lock the safe, Archer,
you dumb twat."
I wanted to get mixed up
with mobsters
like mother and len trexler
about as much as I wanted
a new hole in my head.
But I meant it when I said
I'd do anything
to find woodhouse's killer.
Although, truth be told,
I'd also do anything
just to see Lana Kane again.
So here I am, headed straight
into the belly of the beast.
Nothing between me and death
but my wits
and the cold, blue steel
of my .45.
(Chuckles) I have no idea why
I'm telling you all this.
Or why I picked you up.
I don't even know
where you're going.
(Whines)
Hopefully long beach.
(Barks)
Well, too bad.
(Whispering): Because I don't
need a spirit animal,
and if I did,
he'd be an ocelot.
Torrent downloaded from RARBG
Okay. Observe and report.
So easy, even a cop
could-- wait.
What the--
hm. Now, what's a nice,
unmarked LAPD girl like you
doing in a place like this?
(Engine approaches)
So, what's trexler importing?
Some new, improved
people-melting acid?
Dammit, they're in defilade,
i can't see what they're doing.
(Sighs)
I gotta get higher.
That ought to do.
(Sniffs)
Now, that is a lovely
parting gift.
And who's our lucky
contestant, Bob?
Come on, you bent prick,
look up.
Dammit.
Man:
Come on, move it.
Archer: Huh.
Let's go, let's go. Come on.
Guess trexler's not opening
a Chinese restaurant.
I mean, in this economy?
A whorehouse, though,
bet that's pretty much
recession-proof.
Move, goddammit.
(Cries out)
(Archer gasps)
(Panting)
Okay, Archer, just stay calm.
Yeah, good advice.
Ow!
Oh. Still tender, huh?
What the hell are you
doing here?
Asking you the same thing.
None of your damn business.
Everything is my business.
Oh. Including white slavery?
Yes, incl-- wait. What?
Those girls are
tied up, asshole.
No, they're not,
they're just--
ah, dog dicks.
Yeah, so--
but wouldn't it be
yellow slavery?
(Scoffs)
Wh-- I don't know, racist.
White slavery's just as racist.
What?
No. You know, if you
differentiate between,
like,
cotton-picking slavery--
Jesus Christ.
...And then white slavery,
that's--
sexual slavery, then.
Okay.
Archer: Goddammit.
(Engine starts)
My point is I think we're
both anti-slavery.
Yeah, you're a regular
granville sharp.
But since I'm guessing
that was
your boss taking
the payoff--
but he didn't know
about this part.
Or any part,
'cause he wasn't here.
Wow. Well, I'm sold.
Really?
No, dickhead.
And neither are they.
Whoa. Look,
I don't know what the hell you
think you're gonna do.
Well then, that makes
two of us.
What are you--
oof.
Well?
Goddammit.
Son of a bitch!
(Grunts)
(Sighs)
I mean...
So, funny story.
Jesus, it's the cop, poovey.
So, yeah. So--
(screaming)
(Grunting)
(Panting)
(Sniffs)
Okay.
One of two things is gonna--
(Gunshots)
Wh- what--
what?
...The shit?
They knew me from work.
Ugh.
What? You think they
heard that?
Because, just so i
understand you,
your theory is
the truck backfired,
whereas your theory
is fireworks.
They are Chinese.
What in Christ foo Yung
could they possibly
be celebrating?
Who knows? They got
their own calendar.
(Sighs)
Go back there,
you team of oxen, and--
(Door opens)
Can I help you?
Out of the truck.
(Chuckles)
Do you know whose truck
this is?
Do you know how much
i don't care?
That's cute.
No, seriously.
You're making a--
(Grunts)
...huge mistake. Huge!
Do you hear me?
Yes. We're right here.
Well, you better just kill me.
That's--
(Clears throat, deeper)
That's what I said.
Because when, not if,
i find out who you are,
I'm going to liquefy you.
Okay.
Same goes
for those Chinese whores.
So I'm serious.
You better kill me.
So, you're saying when I drive
this truck out of here,
you'd prefer I drove over your
head, not your ankles.
Wait, what?
No, no.
No, I meant--
i know what you meant.
(Screaming)
(Crying)
What?
Nothing.
I mean, I feel like i
already know the answer,
but are you crazy?
How are they my responsibility?
Because your crooked boss
took a payoff to let them
off that boat.
What am I supposed
to do with them?
Get 'em jobs.
There are plenty of Chinese
restaurants, laundries--
now who's racist?
No. Because those are places
where other Chinese people
already work.
They don't speak
English, dumbass.
I do little bit.
Then shut up.
(Gasps)
I'm so sorry.
I can't even imagine
the day you've had.
God, the week.
The life.
(Chuckling)
Shut up.
Seriously.
Sorry about the laundry thing.
You're doing this,
end of story.
I--
a story in which
a Los Angeles police detective
murdered three people.
(Sighs)
Dick.
Thank you very much!
Thank you!
(Sighs)
Super.
Now I get to go report
what I observed.
Then drove a truck over.
So, first, maybe a drink.
Or 12.
Goddammit!
Goddammit.
(Phone rings)
Who the hell is this?
Mother: Guess.
(Gulps)
I-i was just coming
to see you.
Oh, goody.
Because I am just
on pins and needles--
well--
...to hear how you turned a
stakeout into three dead,
one crippled, and len trexler
ready to go to war.
How do you already
know that?
And I swear to god,
I've got half a mind
to just kill you myself.
I--
but the other half says you're
slightly more use to me alive.
If--
for now.
I--
because now you owe me.
My office, Archer.
First thing tomorrow morning.
(Dial tone)
(Sighs)
Ahem.
Mr. Archer?
Depends. Who's asking?
Charlotte vandertunt,
heiress to the vast vandertunt
publishing fortune.
And I would like
to hire you...
To murder me.
Okay.
(Gasps)
¶ (Jazzy theme) ¶
man: Made... in Georgia.
Captioned by
media access group at wgbh
man: Special bulletin.
Los Angeles, California, 1947.
Nobody knows
who anybody works for.
Do you know
who I work for?
And I trust you know
who I am?
Do you know
whose truck this is?
Archer: Dreamland.
All new wednesdays at 10:00.
On fxx.
It's gonna take an hour
at this time.
Wow, look at Stan's yard.
Someone's been busy.
(Laughs)
Clearly not in ours.
Maybe Henry can do
some work today.
Yeah.
I forget your back
is always bad
this time of year.
Only when
there are leaves--
when did you
wash this last?
The Americans.
(Engine starts)
All new Tuesdays at 10:00.
On fx.
¶ (Romantic orchestral)
(Gasps, screams)
(Crying)
(Screams, cries)
(Woman cackling)
Feud: Bette and Joan.
All-new, Sunday at 10:00 on fx.
(Electronic game sounds)
(Radio squawks)
Woman:
Don't forget your pies.
(Sniffles, clears throat)
(Clears throat)
(Door bell jingling)
(Electricity crackling)
(Traffic passing)