GILLETTE: Okay, okay, you got it, you
got it, you -- Good morning, floor.
[ Beeping ]
Good morning asshole smoke alarm!
And good morning, medical bills.
Oh, and your friend, crippling debt.
No no no no no no!
Good morning, bittersweet memories.
Good morning, bag of the unspeakable.
And good morning to you, Archer...
The other shitbag in my life!
It's broken?
REPAIRMAN: Huh?!
GILLETTE: The elevator's broken?
GILLETTE: The elevator.
REPAIRMAN: Huh?!
GILLETTE: The elevator!
REPAIRMAN: Outta order.
GILLETTE: I can see that!
REPAIRMAN: Why the hell did you ask?
[ Strained grunts and groans ]
MALORY: You're late.
GILLETTE: I --
ARCHER: Jesus, sweat much?
GILLETTE: The elevator's broken --
ARCHER: No shit.
GILLETTE: -- and once again, you parked
that ridiculous car in my space!
ARCHER: Well, A, the El Camino is not a car --
GILLETTE: Truck, whatever!
ARCHER: Nor is it a truck, it's a--
LANA: Vehicular hermaphrodite.
ARCHER: Shut up, and B...
wait, what was B?
I dunno, we'll say B was "shut up."
And are we done here?
I need to go not pack some
shoes, since I'm gonna buy
about ten pairs when we get there.
GILLETTE: Get where?
LANA: Roooome!
GILLETTE: What?!
Not for the Morelli thing!
I planned that entire operation!
MALORY: Yes, and you did excellent legwork...
ARCHER: But now it requires
literal legwork, Ray, like
walking, and maybe running.
Although hopefully not running,
because I'll be in brand-new shoes.
GILLETTE: That is so unfair!
ARCHER: Not as unfair as
how laid I'm gonna get.
Ciao, bella, ho scarpe nuove!
LANA: Sorry, honey.
CYRIL: Yeah, we'll bring you a present.
GILLETTE: Oh, blow me.
ARCHER: Why?
You couldn't feel it!
GILLETTE: [Weary sigh]
KRIEGER: [ A-hum ]
GILLETTE: What.
KRIEGER: Nothing, I'm just curious...
GILLETTE: A bag.
I piss and shit in a plastic bag.
KRIEGER: Me too!
But actually, I was wondering
if you'd like to walk again.
GILLETTE: No, Krieger, because this
way I never have to buy new shoes!
KRIEGER: Yeah, but is that worth it?
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
GILLETTE: Robot legs.
KRIEGER: No, this has nothing
to do with robotics!
I'm talking about bionics!
From the Greek for... like... kickass!
GILLETTE: Is there a
Greek word for "insane"?
KRIEGER: Yes!
I mean I assume there is, but --
GILLETTE: If you think I'm gonna
let you turn me into some
cyborg zombie like Katya --
KRIEGER: Whoa whoa whoa whoa, no!
"Zombie" implies I raised
her from the dead.
GILLETTE: Oh, then I'm
using it correctly.
KRIEGER: No, you're not.
For one thing, Katya
wasn't completely dead.
GILLETTE: Just pretty dead?
[ Involuntary shuddering ]
KRIEGER: So pretty...
GILLETTE: Hello?
KRIEGER: Hm?
Oh, so, nothing a few hundred
thousand volts couldn't cure.
The human body's basically
a potato clock.
GILLETTE: So, it's gonna
look like I'm leaving?
But that's only because I'm leaving.
KRIEGER: Why won't you let me help you?!
GILLETTE: Besides the fact
you'll probably kill me?!
KRIEGER: Yes!
GILLETTE: Because it's wrong!
And I may have wandered pretty
far from the church, but I do
still believe there are some
things that only God should do!
KRIEGER: Like give you an erection?!
GILLETTE: I'm assuming you mean "give
me the ability to have an erection"?
KRIEGER: Also, yes.
LANA: No!
ARCHER: Yes, Lana!
LANA: We don't need a --
ARCHER: Rocket launcher, si, molto pronto!
RODNEY: Mmmmmmmneeww, not on the pre-approved
list of equipment for this mission.
ARCHER: The what?
RODNEY: The --
ARCHER: I heard you!
RODNEY: Why'd you ask?
LANA: Pre-approved by whom?!
ARCHER: Oh, now you're on my side.
LANA: Shut up.
ARCHER: Common enemy.
CYRIL: That's how Lana
and I started dating.
LANA: Shut up.
Pre-approved, by whom.
RODNEY: Ms. Archer.
ARCHER: Wh-?
She doesn't know what we need!
LANA: The last time she was in the
field they were still using muskets!
CYRIL: Really?
LANA: Seriously?
CYRIL: No?
ARCHER: Look dipshit, my mother obviously
doesn't know about this stuff, so --
RODNEY: So she goes by my personal,
professional recommendations.
LANA: I'm gonna need you to repeat that.
RODNEY: I said --
LANA: No no, shh, after I come back there
and pull your tongue out
through your -- Asshole.
ARCHER: Ew.
CYRIL: Ew.
RODNEY: You'd need a bulldozer
made of acid to get in here.
ARCHER: Ooh, or Spacebot!
RODNEY: And if you continue to behave threateningly--
LANA: You haven't seen threateningly.
RODNEY: You'll need one
to get out of there.
ARCHER: Remember Spacebot?
Guys?
KRIEGER: And so, a small power
unit goes here, on your uh,
spiny thing, which sends electrical
impulses to your muscles and ligaments and
stuff, which I will fuse to a
vanadium alloy endoskeleton,
replacing your current, um, legbones.
GILLETTE: I have to say it kind
of worries me you don't know the
names of the actual bones.
KRIEGER: Who cares?
Zrrp, they're in the dumpster.
GILLETTE: Ew.
Wait, then all I need is the power
unit, not a bunch of vanadium bones!
KRIEGER: Yeah, but they're awesome.
GILLETTE: But if you don't put everything
back where it's supposed to go...
KRIEGER: I've already done it twice!
There you go, Conway.
Plus when I'm taking out the old bones
I take tons of pictures with my phone.
GILLETTE: Oh, well then
what could go wrong?
KRIEGER: Seriously?
GILLETTE: Sarcastically.
KRIEGER: Oh.
Because you could die.
GILLETTE: I realize that.
And I'll, ya know, sign a release form or whatever...
KRIEGER: Oh, that's not
necessary.
GILLETTE: Really?
KRIEGER: No, I mean if, God
forbid, the worst happens...
there's lots of dumpsters.
GILLETTE: Jesus.
KRIEGER: Sure, if he helps.
GILLETTE: Whew, okay,
so when do we do this?
KRIEGER: Well, you should already be
feeling the effects of the anesthetic...
GILLETTE: The... God damn it, Krieger!
KRIEGER: So whenever my
assistants get here.
PAM: What's up, spaghetti-legs?
GILLETTE: Wait a minute!
KRIEGER: Yeah, where's Carol?
PAM: Gettin' that list
of shit you wanted.
LANA: Thank you!
CHERYL/CAROL: Seriously!
What am I, hourly?!
CYRIL: Are you not?
CHERYL/CAROL: I don't know!
LANA: Move.
Oh, and when I'm through
talking to Malory?
I wouldn't be surprised if you
find yourself out of a job.
RODNEY: I would.
CYRIL: Burn.
LANA: Cyril?!
ARCHER: Is it Halloween already?
CHERYL/CAROL: I don't know!
ARCHER: Then why are
you dressed like that?
CHERYL/CAROL: Because, duh, I'm helping
Krieger turn Ray into a stupid cyborg.
ARCHER: A what?!
CHERYL/CAROL: But I guess
some cyborgs are smart...
ARCHER: What are you talking about?!
CHERYL/CAROL: Well, you gotta
be pretty smart to fool the ol'
Voight-Kampff machine.
ARCHER: In Krieger's lab?!
CHERYL/CAROL: Anywhere,
duh, it's portable.
ARCHER: No no no no no!
CHERYL/CAROL: Uh, yes it is.
Yo, Magnum P.U.
I need a lead-acid battery, fifty
units of plasma, some bolt cutters,
and something called a -- Defrimbulator?
That's a made-up word.
RODNEY: They're all made up.
CHERYL/CAROL: [ Laughs ]
Mind! Blown!
GILLETTE: Yeah, what could go wrong...
ARCHER: Ray's gonna be a cyborg
over my dead body!
Or preferably his!
But somebody's!
GILLETTE: What could
possibly, go, wrrngzzzzzz.
PAM: Hey, should I wash my hands?
KRIEGER: I didn't.
ARCHER: Krieger! Krieger!
Krieger open this goddamn door!
Krieger I am gonna count to one!
PAM: Oh that's right, he hates robots!
KRIEGER: For the -- this! Is a robot!
Gillette is a human being!
But he won't be for long if
you don't clamp that artery!
ARCHER: One!
ARCHER: Brett?
What in the hell...?
RON: Were those gunshots?!
MALORY: Oh, who knows with these people,
it's one calamity after another.
RON: That's, yes, exactly, that's why
you need a nice long relaxing cruise!
MALORY: But I really really really
really really don't think I'll enjoy it.
RON: Sure you will.
ARCHER: Brett?!
LANA: Archer!
What the shit are you doing?!
ARCHER: Um, investigating
a ballistic anomaly.
C'mon, walk and talk.
I don't even think he's on this floor, but
idiot Brett still managed to get shot.
LANA: Yeah, he's the idiot.
ARCHER: Right?
CYRIL: You idiot!
If I hadn't checked the time at that
exact second I'd be dead right now!
ARCHER: Which reminds me, Grover Cleveland
called, he wants his watch back.
LANA: Archer --
ARCHER: He left two non-consecutive messages.
CYRIL: This was my
grandfather's, you ass!
ARCHER: I'll buy you another one!
Now how were you holding
it, like, exactly!
CYRIL: I -- I dunno, like this I guess...
ARCHER: Okay, sooooo... Boom.
C'mon, this is awesome, it's like
we're the Warren Commission.
Look look look, check it out!
It's a real magic bullet!
LANA: Why the hell were you shooting
at Krieger's door in the first place?
ARCHER: Oh shit, right!
Brett, this might be some kind of record!
So if you can move, don't!
I gotta go stop him!
LANA: Stop who?!
ARCHER: Whom!
LANA: Archer!
ARCHER: Krieger!
He's making a gay terminator!
LANA: Aaaaand yep.
Officially confused.
CYRIL: Yeah, did he mean
a terminator of gays?
Because Krieger's creepy and
weird, but he's not homophobic,
I don't think, so he must've meant...
well, no, aren't terminators asexual?
KRIEGER: Not when I'm done with him...
PAM: C'mon, how's that even
supposed to -- fit inside
another human being?
KRIEGER: Oh.
That shouldn't be doing that.
There we go.
PAM: No no no, do it again, do it again, do it a --
KRIEGER: This man is barely
clinging to life, woman!
Get a hold of yourself!
PAM: Sorry.
KRIEGER: And then get a hold
of your goddamn beer can!
PAM: Sorry. Jeez... Ehh...
KRIEGER: Blood pressure?
PAM: I'll be honest, it's not great.
KRIEGER: Wh-?
I'm talking about his!
PAM: [ Burps ] Me too.
MALORY: Since when?
ARCHER: Since the... the new intelligence,
Mother, from Ray, about the mission!
MALORY: That says you
need a rocket launcher?
ARCHER: Yes!
RON: Can I --
ARCHER: No.
RON: -- just sort of interject
here, Malory, this is exactly
what I'm talking about, with the stress...
MALORY: Ron?
ARCHER: Seriously, Ron,
why aren't you at work?
RON: Because I spent thirty years building
the business so I don't have to be!
Because I hired good managers!
Walk into any one of my six dealerships --
ARCHER: Not six...
RON: Next year it'll be seven, sport,
we just broke ground in White Plains.
ARCHER: That's actually
fairly impressive.
RON: You have no idea.
With that city council?
MALORY: Ron this isn't a car dealership, it's --
RON: The same principle!
You build it, hire people you trust to manage it --
MALORY: Ha!
ARCHER: Yeah, ha.
RON: -- and then you collect
the fruits of their labor!
Because don't, please, don't
take this the wrong way, babe -
but you're not getting any younger.
MALORY: You said a rocket launcher?
ARCHER: I did.
I did say a rocket launcher.
MALORY: Then give this to whosits.
ARCHER: I will.
I will give this to whosits.
RON: And call me if you ever wanna
test drive the new Coupe de Ville.
ARCHER: Well, I just got a new El Camino...
RON: Oh, so you're all set.
That'll hold way more
Hispanics and lawnmowers.
MALORY: [ Explosive laughter ]
ARCHER: Wow.
MALORY: I know!
That's why I can never stay mad at him!
RON: Right?
Wait, why were you mad?
LANA: Because I think Krieger's doing some kinda...
bionic shit to Ray's legs!
CYRIL: And Archer, obviously --
LANA: Would rather see Ray dead!
CYRIL: Jeezy P, I mean, besides Barry and
Katya, what is his deal with robots?
DOCTOR: Servant, call an ambulance.
WOODHOUSE: Yessir, right away sir!
MALORY: An ambulance?!
DOCTOR: He needs emergency surgery.
And even then, it'll be a miracle
if we can save his testicles.
MALORY: But... what could
have caused this?!
WOODHOUSE: Mumps?
DOCTOR: Or who knows.
The important thing is,
what are you doing tonight?
MALORY: I -- oh!
Well, I said I might meet some
people at this thing downtown,
but it sounded like it'll be pretty
heavy on Negroes and jazz, so --
DOCTOR: I happen to
love Negroes and jazz.
MALORY: Oh!
Well then I'll just get my coat.
WOODHOUSE: And I'll wait here?
For the ambulance to take your
grievously wounded child to the
hospital for emergency surgery?
MALORY: Yes, Woodhouse, and then you
can go buy some wax for your cross.
LANA: Krieger?
KRIEGER: Oh my God... I'm
a little busy right now!
LANA: Yeah I know, are you cyborging Ray?
KRIEGER: No?
LANA: Look, I think it's great if you are --
KRIEGER: Then yes!
LANA: But I think Archer's
gonna try to stop you!
He's kinda freaking out!
KRIEGER: Let him!
That door came off the Graf Spee!
To get in here he'd need --
RODNEY: One RPG-7 launcher and two grenades.
As per the note from your mother.
ARCHER: Thank you, uh, sorry,
what was your name again?
RODNEY: Rodney.
ARCHER: Thank you, asshole.
MALORY: What in the...?
Why aren't you people on
the way to the airport?
LANA: We may have sort
of a, uh, situation.
MALORY: And what sort would that be?!
RON: This is what I'm talking about...
MALORY: Ron!
If you keep it up, this headache
you gave me is going to last for
the next three to five nights.
LANA: Look, don't worry, I can handle it.
MALORY: But --
RON: Let her handle it!
She seems capable.
LANA: Hey, thanks.
RON: Reminds me of the head mechanic
at my dealership in Yonkers.
He's a black.
LANA: Wow.
RON: I know, and head mechanic!
Now c'mon, babe, let these people do
whatever it is you pay them to do,
and let's go start our weekend.
MALORY: Alright, but
don't miss that flight.
God knows how long it takes to
check in with a rocket launcher.
LANA: Oh, shit!
CYRIL: Well calling the
airport's not gonna help.
ARCHER: Oh, and one last thing, Rodney,
when I get back from Rome, you're --
RODNEY: Hang on oooooone second.
Armory.
CHERYL/CAROL: Hey will
you bring me a present?
ARCHER: No.
RODNEY: Mm-hm. Mm-hm.
Ooookay.
You were saying?
ARCHER: I... shit.
Something about an asskicking
with handmade Italian shoes?
RODNEY: Well, think about
it, you've got time.
ARCHER: What do you think you're doing?
RODNEY: What do you think you're doing?!
Obtaining armory materiel under false
pretenses is a fireable offense!
ARCHER: Oh my -- I basically just lurch
from one fireable offense to the next!
CHERYL/CAROL: Ugh, like the
infamous "Luau Incident."
ARCHER: Jesus Christ, how many times
do I have to apologize for that?!
CHERYL/CAROL: Once would be nice!
ARCHER: No.
Rodney open this door.
RODNEY: Give me that weapon.
ARCHER: Oh.
You mean this rocket launcher?
Because I bet it would open the door.
RODNEY: No, that is
inadvisable at this time.
ARCHER: Ya know, if I asked it nicely.
RODNEY: I seriously wouldn't do that.
ARCHER: Yeah, because you're not awesome.
MALORY: Oh, and what
fresh hell is this?!
RON: Whatever it is, they can handle it!
MALORY: They can't even
handle a simple luau!
My God, what they did to that pig...Brett?!
BRETT: Heeelp...
BRETT: Nghhh...
MALORY: Great, now I get to slog
my new Delmans through a lake of blood.
I want that all cleaned
up before Monday, mister!
Do you hear me?!
RODNEY: No... Because
that room is blast-proof!
ARCHER: Mawp.
Maaaawp.
Mawp.
PAM: What the shit was that?!
KRIEGER: Hopefully the last remaining
shred of Archer's eardrums.
LANA: That crazy son of a -- come on!
CYRIL: Why is your instinctive
response to run toward explosions?!
LANA: Mmm... because
I'm not a giant pussy?
CYRIL: Although, somehow,
incredibly single.
LANA: Wh-?!
I go on... tons of dates!
CYRIL: With who?!
LANA: Men!
Men models!
Men who model!
[ High pitched whine ]
CHERYL/CAROL: -- permanent damage
to my earballs because you're too
chickenshit to take your candy-ass to
the future and smash the defense grid
so Skynet --
RODNEY: Whoa whoa whoa!
Not cool, man!
That is not at all cool!
CHERYL/CAROL: Rodney you
mind your own dicky beeswax!
You got another one in ya?
RODNEY: Ew.
ARCHER: I don't --
CHERYL/CAROL: Tease.
ARCHER: -- and I'm sorry for that one --
CHERYL/CAROL: Don't be.
ARCHER: -- because I'm just
gonna say it, I think it's
suuuper creepy you get sexually
aroused by physical violence.
CHERYL/CAROL: Well but
also emotional violence.
ARCHER: Wow.
CHERYL/CAROL: Yeah.
ARCHER: That's even creepier.
So are you gonna open the damn door?
RODNEY: As soon as you
give me that weapon.
ARCHER: Wh-? Do you honestly wanna
live through the rise of the machines?!
Which you won't, because no one will?!
RODNEY: I --
ARCHER: It was rhetorical!
So now if you'll excuse me... I
have an entire human race to save.
RODNEY: What is he... hey
that's ISIS property!
ARCHER: What this?
RODNEY: Yes.
CHERYL/CAROL: Take me with you!
ARCHER: Shut up!
CHERYL/CAROL: Ooh, yeah, even
that little bit's enough to get
the engine revved up.
So Rodneeeeeey... Tease!
CYRIL: Jeezy Petes...
CHERYL/CAROL: Cyril what're you doing right now?
CYRIL: I --
LANA: Helping me find Archer, where is he?!
Super.
CYRIL: Are you calling the airport again?
LANA: Cyril shut your goddamn mouth!
CHERYL/CAROL: [ Involuntary
shudder of pleasure ]
KRIEGER: Hey, guess
what's not a good time?
Wait, where?!
PAM: Gotta be somewhere in there...
KRIEGER: Not you!
And did you count right?!
PAM: What, to five?
Dicknuts?
LANA: Krieger!
KRIEGER: Look, you gotta
keep him away from the lab!
We're almost done, if somebody
can find their last beer!
PAM: [ Burps ] I can
promise it ain't my last.
KRIEGER: I mean, I doubt he can find it...
ARCHER: God damn it.
I told 'em, I said -- Maps!
All through the HVAC ducts!
Or just at the, whatever, junctions.
MALORY: I won't even waste however much
dryerase it'll take to write that down.
ARCHER: No, Mother, because you
were too busy wasting it on
"Fourth of Ju-Luau!"
KRIEGER: But still, see
if you can flush him out.
I'd hate to use the nerve gas.
LANA: Do not!
Use the nerve gas!
KRIEGER: And yet incredibly single...
LANA: How the hell do we flush him out?
CHERYL/CAROL: Uh, duh...
REPAIRMAN: Huh?!
LANA: I said, how hot can you make it?
ARCHER: No no no... It's already happening...
LANA: Holy shit, already?
GILLETTE: Yeah, I actually
feel pretty good.
How is that possible?
KRIEGER: It's a proprietary blend.
And barring some sort of massive infection --
PAM: Don't look at me,
found number six!
KRIEGER: You should be
up and around by Monday.
GILLETTE: Well then can I go home?
Cause it's hot as balls up in here.
ARCHER: The thermostat's
becoming sentient!
Oh God!
That's how Maximum Overdrive started!
MALORY: Well I'd be lying if I said I cared...
LANA: Wh-?
Malory, Ray can walk again!
GILLETTE: Buh-duh-buh-baaaaa!
MALORY: You mean mince?
GILLETTE: Ya know...
MALORY: Maybe he can mince to
the bank and apply for a twelve
thousand dollar loan for a new furnace!
Why did you idiots leave it
on ninety all weekend?!
ARCHER: Your clothes.
Give them to me.
CYRIL: Aaagh!
ARCHER: I'm kidding, obviously, I wouldn't
be caught dead in a sweater vest.
Now, if you'll excuse me...
PAM: Just like Fourth of Ju-Luau...
CHERYL/CAROL: Yeah, if you
slid a pig under him.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com