When you two first came into my office,
I was like,
"This marriage is not going to last."
But you've really put the work in.
I deem your marriage fixed.
Thanks, Dr. Janet.
We couldn't have done this without you
and your many novelty certificates.
Well, this has certainly been a big year
for the Rabitowitz marriage.
It certainly has.
But now it's New Year's Eve and, Katie,
my New Year's resolution to you
is to spend more time
with my wonderful wife, who I--
- [cell phone rings]
- I gotta take this.
-Oh, um, but--
-Hello.
Hey, partner, big news. Huge news.
I'm all ears.
The Flight of the Pegasus
just lost their lead.
They start shooting next week.
So what you're telling me is David Pincher
needs a new star immediately
for his three-picture young adult
dystopian future franchise?
Yup. What's that I hear?
Beep beep.
Someone's calling on the other line.
That's strange. Hello?
It's Oodles of Money calling.
Will we accept the charges?
Why would Oodles of Money
be calling collect?
I don't know. Don't accept the charges,
we cannot afford it.
I gotta go in. I'm sorry.
Okay. But make sure
you're back before, you know.
Deal. Best deal I ever made.
[kisses]
Boom!
What's black and white and sexy all over?
Chuff Hollister.
He's young, he's hot,
he's Australian or British or whatever.
We can paint over his stripes
so he looks like a horse.
I can see the headline now:
Chuff Hollister is...
The next Pegasus.
BoJack's got star power and grit
up the wazoo. I can't imagine...
Anyone who would appeal
to the audience more than Chuff.
He's got sex appeal...
- Gravitas...
- Youth...
- Experience...
- And abs coming out of the wazoo.
And what a wazoo it is.
- This would put Gekko-Rabitowitz--
- On the map.
The map of profitable agencies, that is.
Perfect, because without it
we could be in--
Real trouble. We did not hit
our projected earnings for the year.
The year's not over yet.
We still have one day to go all out.
Rutabaga, do you think
we have the spunk and moxie--
That's a good name
for a lady detective series.
--required to pull this off
and save the agency?
Hell yeah, I do.
That would be a great title
for a movie about marrying Satan.
How are we losing money?
Vanessa, we're getting Chuff this part
and coming out on top.
I know we will,
because we're the good guys.
[funky electronic music]
♪♪
Suck a duck a duck a dick, dumbshit.
- Hey, Sarah Lynn.
- Hey, loser.
Did you get a call
about that Ethan Around thing?
- You're not gonna do it, are you?
- I'm sorry, what thing?
Ethan Around, the Horsin' Around
sequel series Brad's trying to get made?
He called to ask me, I asked him,
can you put a bullet in my brain?
That would probably be
a better career move.
Wait, slow down.
Did you say Ethan Around?
I know.
It should be Sabrina Around, right?
That's a show people would watch.
Sabrina doing cool skateboard tricks
and eating kettle corn.
Hold on, if this was a real thing,
why would Brad call you and not me?
Who knows?
Why do people do anything?
Why did I make the cartoon tree grandma
from Pocahontas my emergency contact?
Are you sure this whole thing
isn't just a semi-lucid fever dream
from mixing the wrong pills?
Did you not hear?
I'm clean and sober, eight months.
Really? That's incredible.
Yeah, I wanted a change in my life.
Because I heard
if you stop doing drugs for a while,
the first time you do them again,
it's amazing.
-What? No, just stay sober.
-Ugh!
Whatever.
Call me when you're ready to party.
- [tires screech]
- [crashes]
[horn honks]
Well, that's troubling.
Can you believe they're doing
a Horsin' Around reboot without me?
What do you care?
You're about to be nominated for an Oscar.
Not the point. This is about respect.
BoJack, is this really a good idea?
[phone rings]
Tools. Brad speaking.
You're doing a new show
in the extended Horsin' Around
cinematic universe and you didn't call me?
Hey, BoJack.
Ethan Around is just an idea I had.
It's not officially happening or anything.
I would love for you to be part of it,
but the horse died in the series finale.
So? We could write around that.
The Horse dying was just a dream.
The Horse had a twin brother,
comes back as a ghost.
Ethan missed the Horse so much
he built a robot Horse as a tribute.
"I've heard of overloaded motherboards,
but this is ridiculous."
Those are off the top of my head,
they're all gold.
I'm surprised you're so into the idea.
I've been having trouble
getting networks on the phone,
but with a big star like you attached,
we could sell this right away.
I wouldn't say I'm attached...
Don't move.
I'm getting the next flight down to LA.
- Right now?
- And purchased.
BoJack, for the last 20 years
I've been telling people
I didn't need the trappings of fame,
that I was better off,
happy with my little B-plus life
at my little B-plus hardware store
in little B-plus Olympia, Washington.
B-minus children. But it's a lie.
I miss the warmth of the spotlight
on my face.
The thrill of telling a joke
and feeling it land.
Is that a thrill you experienced?
The sitcom stage is my home,
and I'm tired of denying myself that.
I'm ready to come home.
Great.
-Why did you let me call him?
-Ugh.
Ah, smell that Labrador Peninsula air.
Keep an eye out for my brother.
- How will I know which one's him?
- He's the one that looks like me.
- Got it.
- [ringtone] Who's that dog? Mister P--
- Hello?
- Hey, Mr. Peanutbutter.
Is this an okay time to talk business?
Yeah, I'm just waiting
for Captain Peanutbutter.
What is that, like, a cereal?
No, my brother.
- He's picking us up at the airport.
- Nice.
Speaking of driving people places,
Cabracadabra
had a killer holiday season
and I think New Year's
is going to be even bigger.
I'm loving that segue, Todd.
You are a conversational Magellan.
Turns out there's a huge demand
for a safe space for women. Who knew?
Honestly, never would've crossed my mind.
So I was thinking, what's the next step?
What if we made our safe space
for women...
[crashes]
...also available to men?
That's an untapped market.
All right, then it's agreed.
No goodbye?
He's a conversational Amelia Earhart.
Mr. Peanutbutter and
Captain Peanutbutter in the same room?
What is this, a flashback episode?
Captain Peanutbutter, you old so-and-so.
- Get over here.
- [Diane] Careful.
[both laugh]
Where's Mrs. Captain Peanutbutter?
She's in Alaska running the Iditarod.
She sends her love.
And this noogie.
Whoo!
Diane, this is my big brother.
Big brother? I'm five minutes older.
And you always will be.
It's nice to meet you, Captain.
Hey, put that thing away.
You're family.
- [growls]
- [Diane] Oh!
So David Pincher is about to shoot
the Flight of the Pegasus trilogy
in New Zealand,
and BoJack is perfect for the lead.
A part like that would really underline
that BoJack's more than just an actor,
he's a movie star.
If I'm doing that,
I conveniently won't be able
to do that dumbass
Ethan Around show.
Use that when you tell him I won't do it.
Why don't you tell him
you don't want to do it?
I can't. I'm like a father figure to him--
I slept with his mother.
- Gross.
- No.
I slept with her 20 years ago.
She was young then, not gross.
Ugh!
Hey, loved you in
The Caveman's Valentine.
- Hmm?
- Nothing? The Caveman's Valentine?
Samuel L. Jackson had that big beard?
Look it up.
- When you start laughing, call me.
- Will do.
Do we have an offer
on the Pegasus movie?
I'll get it, Kalamata.
Don't get your pita in a wad.
Wow. Flight of the Pegasus.
This must be
what Robert Downey Jr. felt like
when he woke up on that
stranger's bathroom floor
and found out he was gonna be Iron Man.
[man on radio] It's another unseasonably
warm day in the Labrador Peninsula
and things are looking sunny
all the way to the new year.
It really is true what they say...
[both] Nothing bad ever happens
on the Labrador Peninsula.
Oh, paradise.
[children laugh]
Uncle Mister. Uncle Mister.
Now who let these little monsters
onto my peninsula?
We're your nephews.
What? I don't remember my nephews
being made out of candy.
- Gobble, gobble, gobble.
- [all laugh]
Look at those children.
Little miracles, right?
They're adorable, not that
I value them based on their looks.
Because, of course,
children in society today
are often reduced to their cuteness.
I can't wait to get
to know your children as people,
so I can specifically
compliment them individually
on the foundation of their characters.
Well, one day they'll die, just like us.
Uh...
- Do you believe in the soul?
- What?
Life is the most precious resource
we have. Remember that, Diane.
Okay.
[laughs] Pretty great, right?
Did you tell your brother
about the A-B-O-R-T-I-O-N?
The audition?
No, I could never tell him about that.
He thinks I'm offer-only,
it would break his heart.
Wait, what audition?
- No, the abortion.
- Oh, no. Should I have?
He said some weird stuff to me earlier.
The kind of stuff you'd hear
in a sad Creed song.
Or a happy Elliott Smith song.
Oh, he's probably just razzing ya,
but he's a good dog. All bark, no bite.
Sorry, that's a Labrador expression.
I guess in human terms it would be:
He's all talk, and no shooting you
with an assault rifle.
Is that what you think humans do?
Am I wrong?
[Rutabaga] Boom! This is David Pincher.
And this is everyone who works for him.
Now unfortunately for us,
everyone on this board
must really like their boss's movies,
because for the holidays,
they're all Gone Girl.
Thank you, except for her. Boom.
The assistant to David Pincher's
casting director.
Wait a second, I know that face.
Why does she look so familiar?
- Oh, fish.
So when I found out
that the best assistant I ever had
was working for David Pincher,
I mean, what are the odds?
Did he hire you because of your cute
little Benjamin Button-nose?
I'll put in a good word for BoJack,
but I'm just an assistant.
Just an assistant?
Laura, assistants are everything.
You're the first people in,
the last people out.
You know everyone's real name, age,
nose, teeth, and tits.
You have power, because in today's economy
the only true power is information.
I want you to use that power.
I want you to get your boss
to pick BoJack as his Pegasus.
I always believed in you, Laura.
The question is:
do you believe in yourself?
Wow, that's--
I'm sorry, did you just make that up?
Because that was--
Is that a speech you had ready to go?
- Will you do this for me?
- Of course.
You went to bat for me when I tried
to get a promotion at Vigor.
I pushed so hard for you.
I did everything I could.
I mean, we gals gotta look out
for each other. Right?
Right.
[thunder cracks]
So you're talking about a merger?
Since my dad croaked
I've been running Vigor myself,
and I've been doing a pretty good job,
A-minus/B-plus.
But I could use a few more experienced
hands to help guide the ship,
- because being a boss is really hard.
- Yes.
Princess Carolyn can be a proud woman.
I'm glad you came to me first.
I would have gone to her directly,
but sometimes she yells at me
and I do not like being yelled at
and that is just something that people
need to understand about me.
I'll talk to her, when the time is right.
[groans]
[thunder]
So on the new show Ethan is the dad,
and he's raising three little horses.
You couldn't have told me
this over the phone?
This show is going to change my life.
I'm taking the kids out of school
and moving everyone down here.
I just had an offer accepted
on a house in Sherman Oaks.
As long as I don't change my mind
before the new year, boom.
Two million dollars, gone.
- The new year? That's tonight.
- I know.
Did you talk to my agent
by any chance?
- No.
- She didn't call you?
I talked to her, and I don't know
if she wants me to do it.
You know how agents are.
Just remember,
I'm not the bad guy here.
I hear you loud and clear.
Don't worry.
We won't take no for an answer.
I think my schedule's gonna be tough--
Might be going to New Zealand.
We'll work around your schedule.
Those bastards got my quote
so damn high.
We'll pay it.
No obstacle is insurmountable.
- As long as you want to do it.
- And I do want to do it.
Get me out of this thing.
This asshole's giving me everything
I ask for. What a nightmare.
- Tell him you don't want to do the show.
- I can't. It would destroy him.
Destroying people is what I pay you to do,
so I don't think about the people
I'm destroying.
Do you not know what an agent is?
- [knocking]
- [Ethan] BoJack, are you okay in there?
Is it number one or number two?
That cat's running circles around us.
What are we going to do?
Maybe we can distract her?
I'm thinking laser pointer.
If we're going to beat her,
we need to think like her.
Instead of convincing the Pegasus
people they don't want BoJack,
what if we convince BoJack
he doesn't want Pegasus?
Fantastic. How do we do that?
Kelsey.
Kelsey? That's what I said when
they said you wanted to meet with me.
I figured you never wanted
to see me again.
I never want to see anyone again,
but there's a book I've been trying
to turn into a movie and I need your help.
It's a coming-of-age story
about a girl who likes jellybeans.
The option expires tonight at midnight,
unless I can find a big enough star
to secure funding.
Frankly, I already gave up on it.
Then my agent said,
"Maybe BoJack's interested."
So the reason
you think I'm right for the role
is because I'm a big enough star
to secure funding?
Don't get smart, BoJack.
You're not good at it.
You're really giving the hard sell here.
I hear they've got you locked in
to some fantasy dystopia thing.
Are you just gonna do stupid bullshit
for the rest of your life?
For work or, like, in general?
I saw something in you,
something most people don't know you have,
and it kills me that instead
of sharing it with the world,
you want to hide it under some
wonderland unicorn nonsense.
It's a Pegasus. Unicorns are for babies.
The movie I want to make
isn't glamorous or sexy.
You don't get to be the big hero
everybody loves.
You get to be a guy
who works at a gas station,
who gets in a fight with his daughter
about jellybeans.
That's the whole movie.
It's small and it's real.
And you'd get to work
with a director who sees you.
And I can't sell it any better than that.
You're right, that one scene
we shot that didn't even make it
into the Secretariat movie
was the best thing I ever did.
Why am I wasting my time
with this other stuff?
- So you're in?
- Let's do it.
Great. How's your little friend
with the face?
Is he up to his old tricks,
getting into scrapes?
[laughs] What a little scamp.
Will you tell him I said hi?
Kelsey's movie sounds perfect.
Is it the nobody's-gonna-see-it element
or the fact you'll be working for peanuts?
This jellybean thing could show the world
that BoJack's more than just a movie star.
- He's an actor.
- Yeah, well, that's great,
but I've been working all day
on getting him the Pegasus movie
you said would show the world
he's a movie star.
I don't want that anymore.
I want to do something real.
You realize how much money
we'd be walking away from?
This isn't about money.
Doesn't matter to me.
- Yeah, it doesn't matter to you.
- Right. So what's the problem?
Maybe you can find a way
for BoJack to do both?
You're supposed to be
this amazing agent, after all.
I'll see what I can do.
New beers for the new year's?
We got a regular
Maya Angelou over here.
Good times.
- [cell phone rings]-
- Oh, it's Todd. Gotta take this.
- Maybe you can call him back later?
- Todd!
Don't be too long,
or I'm gonna drink all your beer.
[sighs]
Diane, do you ever look up at the stars
and feel like
they're tiny holes in the sky,
sucking out all the oxygen,
and suddenly you can't breathe
because you're thinking about how small
you are and how meaningless it all is?
Uh... I guess.
It's so cruel to let people love you.
All you're doing is promising
you'll one day break their hearts.
Cool fire pit.
So it turns out men love safe spaces
for women even more than women do.
You gotta read some of these comments.
Queefburglar69 says:
"These sexy lady chauffeurs
always get me where I need to go."
That's unambiguous.
The only problem is some of the drivers
have been complaining
about the new customer base.
The workers are allowed to complain?
We gotta tighten up that ship.
Most of the new passengers
are perfect gentlemen,
but we've found that a growing number
are rating our drivers
not on performance but on "bangability",
which creates an unfair advantage
for our "bangable" drivers
and creates what some
of our more homely employees
have dubbed a hostile sexy-ocracy.
Whoa!
Well, our first priority is creating
a safe space for women,
so if our women
don't feel safe in that space,
we should replace them
with women who do.
Where can we find women who are
comfortable around gentlemen?
I know. A gentleman's club.
That's perfect.
To Whale World.
Well, you didn't hear it from me,
but I pulled some strings and you're in.
I always knew you were a superstar.
Let's get drinks in the new year
and work out the deets--
That's a fast way of saying details
for people who don't have time
for every detail of the word details.
Vanessa Gekko on line two.
Great, put that raggedy-ass bitch on.
I'm gonna bat her around
like a ball of foil.
I know you're excited, but we are still
in a very precarious position,
and I wonder if foil-ball-batting
is the best tack here.
Judah, this is where I live.
Watch and learn.
Hey, we heard BoJack and Kelsey
had a great meeting on Jelly Belle.
Gotta tie this up tonight
if it's going to happen.
BoJack would love to do the movie,
but you're gonna have to work
around his Pegasus schedule.
Oh, um... That might be tricky.
Then you're gonna have to match
his Pegasus quote.
- He won't do it for a penny less.
- Princess Carolyn--
Even with a star like BoJack,
Kelsey can't get that kind of money.
Well, then, work around his schedule.
You're overplaying your hand, PC,
and I'm calling your bluff.
I'm barreling towards you fast, Gekko,
and this Mack truck ain't gonna blink.
That's not fair. I was clearly
establishing a poker metaphor,
you just changed it to a game of chicken.
My court. My rules.
Court? What game are you playing?
Bye.
- Damn it!
- Question:
Am I the faulty bike tire pump
I had in seventh grade?
Because I just blew this thing wide open.
- Talk to me, soldier.
- I have been scouring old emails.
I didn't know what I was looking for.
I knew there was something.
And I found it. Bam!
[gasps] Hot shit on a ham sandwich,
this is amazing!
[ringtone]
Sweet crap on a croissant,
Katie's going into labor!
Go, I'll take care of this.
Family comes first.
Thank you. You make me stronger.
[dance music plays]
Why is my house filled with sexy orcas?
It's the Cabracadabra New Year's party.
These are our drivers.
Oh. Uh, where's Emily?
She left.
She said she didn't feel comfortable here.
She certainly didn't feel comfortable
paying for the food she ate.
Yeah, okay, BoJack.
[doorbell rings]
I got champagne for my real friends,
'cause that's what you are.
- A real friend.
- He doesn't want to do your show.
- What?
- BoJack is about to win an Oscar.
Why do you think he would want
to do your soon-to-fail sitcom
about the further adventures
of a carb-faced nobody?
- Oh, maybe--
- You are not a television star.
You have no talent and I am forgetting
your face even as I'm looking at it.
Pack your bags.
Go back to Nowheresville.
Thank you for the champagne.
Best regards, Ana Spanakopita.
Oh, God, the house!
I gotta pull my deposit! Pick up--
Oh, no. I dropped my phone in a bog.
Something is going on with your brother.
You need to talk to him.
We don't really have the kind of
relationship where we talk about things.
Labs prefer to keep things playful.
You know what they say about dogs?
Talking to each other is rrruff.
I'm serious, Mr. Peanutbutter.
And I'm serious that you should drop it.
If something was really wrong,
he would tell me about it.
Would he?
I know he's your brother,
but he's hiding something from you.
Why do you think you know my brother
better than I do?
Just because you have a shitty
relationship with your family
doesn't mean every other family
has to have drama too.
I wanted to come up here
and have a nice time.
This place is an escape for me.
- Okay, I'm sorry, I just--
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I should not have shouted at you.
I just...
I need to go for a walk.
- Oh, hey.
- Hey, is there something going on?
Because I know there isn't,
but if there is, you would tell me, right?
But there's nothing to tell,
because nothing bad ever happens
on the Labrador Peninsula.
- Okay, I think you should sit down.
- Why?
- I need to talk to you. Sit down.
- I will not sit down.
- Mr. Peanutbutter, sit.
- Okay.
- I got a twisted spleen.
- No.
It's not fatal, necessarily.
Everything's gonna be fine.
They still have to run some tests.
- But it's going to be fine?
- Yeah.
Promise me it's going to be fine?
You're my big brother.
That means you can't lie to me about this.
Mr. Peanutbutter, you are the best
runt of the litter a guy could ask for.
No, don't do this.
- But there might come a time...
- Please.
...when you're going
to have to be the captain.
[sighs]
What is this, a very special episode?
[both laugh]
[both howl]
[howling continues]
What? What do you mean?
What happened?
It's a no-go on BoJack for Pegasus.
I don't understand, Laura. I...
I just wanted you to know.
I did everything I could.
- Hey.
- [Kelsey] Look...
If you didn't wanna do my movie,
you should have just told me.
I do want to do your movie.
Oh, yeah? Why did your agent
keep demanding more money?
- What?
- The option's expired and I'm screwed.
Ugh! Why did I get my hopes up?
Why do I keep letting you get my hopes up?
Kelsey, this is a mistake.
It's a mistake I keep making.
Next time, BoJack?
Do a girl a favor,
don't break her heart by inches.
Do it all at once.
It'll save everyone some time.
Huh?
[crowd] Ten, nine, eight...
Oh, good, you're still here.
I wanted to get a head start
on the 2016 budget.
It'll be a challenge, but assuming
BoJack books Pegasus--
BoJack didn't book Pegasus.
- So he's doing the jellybean movie?
- That fell apart, too.
We're gonna have to cut some costs.
Our social media division
is a luxury we can no longer afford.
If things don't perk up the first quarter,
we might be looking at broader layoffs.
- Do you ever read a room?
- I'm sorry, is this a bad time?
Is midnight on New Year's a bad time?
I don't know.
Why don't you run that through
your robot analysis protocol?
Get back to me
once you've assessed the data.
I am not a robot. I am a human being.
You want to make some cuts?
Why don't you cut that stupid beard?
Everyone who walks in here thinks
this place is run by a homeless person.
I apologize if my appearance
or demeanor is unprofessional.
[sighs] No, you're perfect.
Everybody's perfect except for me.
Go home, Judah.
- Would you like me to shave the beard?
- Just go home, Judah.
Happy New Year, Princess Carolyn.
[cell phone rings]
[sighs]
[whimpers]
Hello, little ones. Mama loves you.
And you. And you. And you.
- They're so beautiful.
- And you, and you, and you.
- Rutabaga, we got it.
- Yeah?
Chuff Hollister is the new Pegasus.
We saved the agency.
- That's incredible, honey.
- Wow, everything worked out.
You gotta love a happy ending.
♪ Back in the '90s
I was in a very famous TV show ♪
- ♪ I'm BoJack the Horseman ♪
- ♪ BoJack ♪
♪ BoJack the Horseman
Don't act like you don't know ♪
♪ And I'm trying to hold on to my past ♪
♪ It's been so long
I don't think I'm gonna last ♪
♪ I guess I'll just try
And make you understand ♪
♪ That I'm more horse than a man ♪
♪ Or I'm more man than a horse ♪
♪ BoJack ♪
Boxer vs. Raptor,
♪ Na-na na-na na-na na-na! ♪