KELLOGG: Mayday mayday mayday,
this is Commander Kellogg of
I.S.A. Space Station Horizon, [garbled]
secure transmission [garbled]
Commander Drake.
Tony, the crew has [garbled],
and we are under [garbled].
I say again, we are under [garbled].
Croatoooooan!
DRAKE: And that, Mrs. Archer...
MALORY: Ms.
ARCHER: Don't.
DRAKE: Ahh -- Ms. Archer, I beg your pardon --
DRAKE: -- that was the last
transmission from the Horizon.
ARCHER: Which, obviously pretty vague.
DRAKE: Vague?!
You heard Commander Kellogg, he
said the Horizon is under attack!
LANA: Well, under something...
ARCHER: He could've been saying underfinanced.
DRAKE: What?
MALORY: Sterling -- ARCHER: What, they're
always whining about needing more
money for their boondocks.
LANA: Doggles.
ARCHER: What?
DRAKE: You think space
exploration is a boondoggle?!
LANA: Well c'mon, in this economy?
DRAKE: Exactly!
Now, more than ever, is when
we need to look to space
for the solutions to
mankind's problems.
In just two hundred years,
Earth's population will exceed
her capacity to produce enough food.
And even as the famines begin,
global war will erupt as fresh
water becomes scarcer than gold.
But if we begin now, using the lessons
learned aboard Space Station Horizon,
a small group of brave
colonists, can terraform Mars.
And mankind can finally slip
the surly bonds of Earth,
to live forever among the stars!
ARCHER: Yeah, Lana.
LANA: Wh-?
ARCHER: Jesus, read a
book once in your life.
So where does ISIS fit in, Commander?
DRAKE: Well -- MALORY: Well I think
that's a bit premature, until we discuss
our fee structure.
DRAKE: As to that, you
can name your price.
LANA: Oh now they've got --
MALORY: Enough!
Commander? As to our role?
DRAKE: Horizon has an
international crew.
American, German, Chinese, French--
ARCHER: Ba-dum-bump!
Sorry, I thought "French"
was a joke DRAKE: Is mutiny
funny to you, Mr. Archer?
ARCHER: I dunno, maybe a mutiny of clowns...
DRAKE: Because I fear that one
faction, led by radical
nationalists, has mutinied.
LANA: But who?
Which one?
DRAKE: Well if I --
ARCHER: If he knew, he would tell us!
MALORY: Read a book!
DRAKE: And since I don't know which
faction is behind the mutiny --
LANA: If there even was one...
DRAKE: -- I can't trust anyone at the I.S.A.
Which is why I came to ISIS.
MALORY: Because of our loyalty.
DRAKE: Or lack thereof.
MALORY: Or whatever.
DRAKE: Because I need a small
cadre of highly trained agents
to fly into orbit and help me
to retake control of Horizon.
LANA: Nooope!
ARCHER: Yeahhhp!
LANA: Archer!
ARCHER: Lana!
LANA: He just said "highly-trained"!
And last time I checked, none of us were
even lowly-trained to be astronauts!
ARCHER: Well how hard could it be?
DRAKE: Incredibly.
MALORY: But since apparently money is no object...
DRAKE: The training schedule
will have to be highly compressed,
because the shuttle Intrepid is
launching in three days.
And I won't lie to you, this
mission will be dangerous.
ARCHER: Would you say we'll be
venturing into a zone of danger?
DRAKE: Well yes, obviously.
ARCHER: No, but -- how
would you phrase that?
DRAKE: I -- the zone
will be one of danger?
ARCHER: No, I mean say --
oh forget it, never mind.
And you never mind and also shut up.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
ARCHER: Oww!
Jesus Krieger, that's the bone!
KRIEGER: Oh, da mean doctor take widdle
baby's bwud, and widdle baby goes --
owww!
ARCHER: You're a baby.
And astronaut training
sucks complete ass!
Literally!
What is the deal with all the enemas?!
KRIEGER: Uh --
ARCHER: And why do you need so much blood?!
And wait, now that I think about it --
DRAKE: Why is this man in
the restricted area?!
KRIEGER: Who, him?
DRAKE: You.
ARCHER: Wh-? Krieger!
KRIEGER: Uh -- smoke bomb!
DRAKE: And why aren't you
with the other trainees?
ARCHER: I was told I had to
undergo a bunch of extremely
invasive medical tests.
DRAKE: Well normally you
would, but by our doctors.
But since you're on such an
accelerated training schedule --
ARCHER: Six enemas is a luxury
we can ill afford, got it.
MALORY: Six?!
ARCHER: Or -- who knows,
he put me under.
Maybe twelve.
DRAKE: Now you've wasted half a day,
so the other trainees are way
ahead of you.
ARCHER: Not for long they're not!
[loud crash]
DRAKE: Well he's eager,
I'll give him that.
MALORY: Well, you inspire him.
With all those medals
on that powerful chest.
Your wife is a very lucky--
DRAKE: I'm a widower.
MALORY: Oh!
Difficult to meet people,
isn't it, in jobs like ours.
I only mention it because I also happen
to be single -- DRAKE: Yes, I know.
Excuse me.
MALORY: I hope to God that was alcohol.
LANA: No!
ARCHER: Yes!
LANA: Dammit Archer, it's--
ARCHER: It's my turn!
Cyril! Cyril!
Drake said lemme fly it!
CYRIL: Cut it out, Archer!
I'm landing!
C'mon, baby, keep that nose up...
[SMASH]
CYRIL: What the --?!
SEXY ROBOTIC VOICE:
Explosive decompression.
ARCHER: Happy, Cyril?!
You just destroyed Alderaan!
LANA: Dammit, that was closer than any
of us have gotten to actually landing!
ARCHER: A, because you're all crap, and
B, who cares, we're not gonna land it!
CYRIL: What the hell --
DRAKE: -- is going on in here?!
LANA: Archer --
ARCHER: Saw an electrical fire in the simulator,
and knowing that my colleague's
life was in danger, I --
DRAKE: You acted without thinking!
LANA: As always.
ARCHER: Not always...
DRAKE: Well, thank God you did -- LANA: Wh-?
ARCHER: But almost always!
DRAKE: -- because that's exactly
the kind of decisive action
this mission calls for.
You could all learn something from him.
EVERYBODY: Oh my God...
DRAKE: Starting with a little training exercise we
lightheartedly call... The Vomit Comet!
And if you're wondering why we call it that...
LANA: [huge retch]
GILLETTE: Gagh!
Aw, it's all in my hair!
CYRIL: Oh Jeezy H. Petes!
ARCHER: What the hell is
wrong with you, Lana?!
DRAKE:... that's why we call it that.
LANA: What possible reason, could there
be, to subject human beings to --
SKEWWWWWWW...
ARCHER: Such mind-shattering awesomeness!
DRAKE: The KC-135 flies in a parabolic arc--
ARCHER: Woo-hoo-hoo-hoo caaaaaaaaaares!
DRAKE: -- which allows us to achieve
weightlessness for about thirty seconds.
We'll do this twenty times --
ARCHER: Woooooo! Weightlessness!
DRAKE: -- so you can get acquainted
with the sensation of being weightless.
It takes some time getting used to, but --
CYRIL: Ow.
DRAKE: Agent Kane.
Are you alright?
LANA: Yep.
Yep yep yep.
GILLETTE: What is going on with you?
LANA: Do not like.
GILLETTE: What're you, crazy?
What's not to --
LANA: [huge retch]
GILLETTE: Oh.
CYRIL: No! Archer, noooo!
ARCHER: Yeesss!
CYRIL: Please don't do this!
ARCHER: What's that?
Sorry, I couldn't hear you over the
sound of the vawshiiiit!
DRAKE: Looking good!
Only nineteen more to go!
LANA: Nineteen more times...
Until there was literally
no more fluid left in my body.
CYRIL: Yeah, and thanks
so much for that.
LANA: Cyril...
ARCHER: She's not the one who kept riding you into it
holding your mouth open.
CYRIL: Jeez, even in zero gravity you're
an assho -- ARCHER: You were saying?
To the wet-towel wielding
survivor of fifteen years of
boarding school locker rooms?
LANA: Wait, fifteen?
ARCHER: Or -- whatever,
the normal number.
LANA: Twelve?!
DRAKE: Yes, we will
launch in twelve hours.
We received another
transmission from the Horizon.
They can't wait.
LANA: But we haven't
been trained properly!
ARCHER: To what, wear a seat belt?
Actually, is it a
five-point harness, or...?
DRAKE: I admit this isn't an ideal scenario --
LANA: Speaking of,
what's the scenario when
we get to the Horizon?
We don't have a tactical plan, we don't--
DRAKE: We'll have plenty of time
to discuss our plan of
action during the flight.
LANA: But --
MALORY: Lana!
What has gotten in to you?
CYRIL: More like what got out of her...
GILLETTE: Sir, I'm not sure Lana-
sorry honey - is physically
capable of spaceflight.
LANA: Ray!
Actually I may not be cut out for it.
DRAKE: I'm sorry to hear that, Agent Kane...
Because you're going.
ARCHER: [chuckling] To a zone,
which is one of danger.
SEXY ROBOTIC VOICE:
T-minus ninety seconds.
DRAKE: Roger, Control,
all systems are go.
Next stop, Horizon.
Okay. Archer.
ARCHER: Sorry, are you talking to me?
Or to her, who why is she here?!
MALORY: Because Tony invited me!
ARCHER: Tony?!
What, you trying to get my mother
into the Million-Mile High Club?!
MALORY: Sterling!
DRAKE: Archer...
GILLETTE: Would you calm the hell down?!
ARCHER: I am calm!
And I'm also outta here!
DRAKE: Take your hands
off that harness.
ARCHER: Make me!
Oh, and just so you know?!
She -- Can't breathe.
MISSION CONTROL: Uh, Flight,
we're showing suit number two
with an oh-two malfunction.
DRAKE: Double-check that, Control,
I'm showing green across the board.
MISSION CONTROL: Stand by.
DRAKE: Roger, standing by.
Doo do doooo...
MALORY: Tony, please!
He'll behave!
Won't he!
ARCHER: Ip.
DRAKE: Excellent... Because I won't-
I can't - let anyone jeopardize the
success of this mission.
MISSION CONTROL: Flight, oh-two
on suit two is showing normal.
But uh, keep an eye on it.
DRAKE: Oh, I will.
ARCHER: Hooray...
DRAKE: Resume countdown, Control.
MISSION CONTROL: Roger, Flight.
SEXY ROBOTIC VOICE: T-minus five... four...
DRAKE: Exciting, isn't it?
SEXY ROBOTIC VOICE:
Three.
Two.
One.
DRAKE: I think it is.
SEXY ROBOTIC VOICE:
Ignition.
MISSION CONTROL: Liftoff.
DRAKE: Just relax, and
rely on your training!
LANA: Which we didn't have!
DRAKE: Because Phase
Two's a little rough!
ARCHER: Phase Two?!
What's Phase -- [BOOOOM!]
EVERYBODY: Aaaaaaghhhhh!
DRAKE: That was Phase Two.
LANA: Did not like.
DRAKE: Wait'll you see Phase Three.
EVERYBODY: What?
DRAKE: I'm kidding, there
is no Phase Three.
Just a little space-humor.
ARCHER: Yeah, funny stuff.
DRAKE: Right?
Right, then... I want to brief you
all on we can expect when we dock
with Horizon.
LANA: Ugh, can we expect a pharmacy?
ARCHER: Lana, it's not a strip mall.
Although I assume there's a bar?
DRAKE: A bar?
ARCHER: Or whatever, cantina.
DRAKE: Ah... No.
Please pay attention.
We'll dock here, move forward on foot
toward Horizon's bridge, and --
CYRIL: Wait, on foot?
DRAKE: Horizon has artificial gravity.
See how it spins on its
longitudinal axis?
ARCHER: Lana, look at it spin.
DRAKE: When we reach the bridge,
we'll retake control of Horizon.
But we can expect heavy resistance,
I'm sure the mutineers are armed.
ARCHER: With what,
slide rules and Tang?
DRAKE: The M-41 Mark Two plasma-pulse
rifle with concussion grenade launcher.
EVERYBODY: Oh shit!
DRAKE: On "kill" mode, the M-41
fires lethal plasma ammunition.
On "stun" it fires an ion pulse.
Similar to an EMP.
ARCHER: And can it be
fired with an erection?
MALORY: Ugh.
LANA: Archer! Muzzle?!
ARCHER: Relax, it's on stun Lana.
DRAKE: Careful.
Even on stun it can --
ARCHER: Oops.
DRAKE: Clear!
LANA: Clear! GILLETTE: Clear!
CYRIL: Owwwwwww!
DRAKE: Whew! As I was saying, it's possible
for the EMP to stop a man's heart.
ARCHER: So "stun,"
maybe a bit of a misnomer.
CYRIL: Dammit, Archer...
ARCHER: I'm not the one who was all sweaty!
DRAKE: Mr. Archer, that's twice you've
jeopardized the success of this mission!
There will not be a third!
MISSION CONTROL: Uh, Flight,
we have a problem...
ARCHER: Well don't look at me...
DRAKE: My God, on this trajectory we'll miss
Horizon!
Control, what happened?!
MISSION CONTROL: Burn rates were
good, Flight, uh... stand by.
Uh, Flight, we're showing that
you are grossly overweight.
PAM: Oh, for --!
I wouldn't say grossly!
CHERYL/CAROL: I would.
DRAKE: I would be well within my rights
to jettison both of you into space!
MALORY: Well within them!
LANA: Malory!
DRAKE: However!
For uh, numerous reasons - one being
this ship can't actually do that -
I've decided take you with us.
EVERYBODY: [Sigh of relief]
DRAKE: But I want to
know how you got aboard.
PAM: Whaddya mean, how?
Mr. Ar --
ARCHER: Yeah so that safety's tricky, huh?
DRAKE: Clear!
LANA: Clear! GILLETTE: Clear!
PAM: Owwwwwww!
CHERYL/CAROL: Awesome...
PAM: Son of a shitsnackin whore... DRAKE: Mr. Figgis!
Lock that man in the cargo hold.
ARCHER: Who, me?
CYRIL: Aye freaking aye.
DRAKE: Ms. Archer.
MALORY: In case I need
to sterilize something?
DRAKE: Get strapped in.
Agent Gillette, monitor
this woman's vital signs.
Agent Kane, come with me.
I may need some help
getting us to Horizon.
So that we don't die writhing in
agony when we run out of oxygen.
ARCHER: Yeah, been there, no picnic.
Speaking of, great for picnics.
The tofu teriyaki, not so much.
PAM: There's teriyaki?
CYRIL: No!
ARCHER: Cyril, c'mon, lemme out.
CYRIL: No, you jerk!
You shoot me in the heart with a
space-blaster... ARCHER: Wh-?!
You're still mad about that?!
CYRIL: Not to mention whatever idiot
reason you had for smuggling Pam on board!
GILLETTE: You're screwin
him, aren'tcha?
PAM: Whaaaaaaaat?
Yes.
CYRIL: No!
Because if we don't die, for all
I care you can rot in there!
ARCHER: Cyril?! Cyril!
Well good luck fighting a bunch of
whatever, space-pirates without me.
[BEEP] you, space.
DRAKE: Come on baby,
just a few more seconds!
Damn it!
I don't know if that was
a long enough burn!
Agent Kane, I need a readout!
For God's sake, woman, Dramamine!
LANA: It makes me sleepy...
CYRIL: I think we're okay, sir!
DRAKE: Thank God.
Because we're out of fuel.
CHERYL/CAROL: What?!
How are we gonna get back to Earth?!
DRAKE: There is fuel.
On Horizon.
CHERYL/CAROL: Well I didn't know that.
DRAKE: The flight computer
will dock the ship.
Assemble the boarding party.
CHERYL/CAROL: Nor was I told
there would be a party.
Lana, what're you wearing?
DRAKE: Bio-matrix composite body armor.
Effective against small-arms fire.
And we need all the help we can get.
GILLETTE: Since there's
only four of us.
CYRIL: Yeah, that seems kinda... few.
PAM: Heck, if you need some help, I'll --
DRAKE: No!
We can't jeopardize the women!
LANA: Cough.
MALORY: Well not you...
DRAKE: No, no, no, Agent Kane,
I'm afraid your particular skill-set
outweighs your --
SEXY ROBOTIC VOICE: Docking complete.
CHERYL/CAR: Is that a ghost?
PAM: Nope.
DRAKE: Boarding party,
into the airlock.
SEXY ROBOTIC VOICE:
Gravity engaged.
DRAKE: Weapons on stun, fast
and hard to the bridge.
And remember, these are mutineers.
Even if they try to say --
CYRIL: Suppressing fiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiire!
DRAKE: Otherwise.
Just follow me.
LANA: And try not to
shoot me in the awshit!
GILLETTE: What the hell.
LANA: Is wrong with me?
DRAKE: It's the artificial gravity!
You have to readjust to it!
LANA: I'll get my inner ear right on that...
DRAKE: We don't have time
for this, they're --
HORIZON DRONE: There they are!
Get 'em, get 'em!
Drop your weapons!
CYRIL: Suppressing -- So does
this run on batteries, or...?
DRAKE: Fiiiiire!
EVERYBODY: Get some! Get some!
DRAKE: We're pinned down!
LANA: Really?
CHERYL/CAROL: You don't
think I could rock this?
MALORY: Couple things...
One, I don't know what that means.
And two... hang on.
Hang on.
And two, you obviously don't know
what "boarding party" means.
CHERYL/CAROL: Who am I, sixteenth-century
female Irish pirate Grinne O'Malley?
Or her sole female descendant!
ARCHER: I'm sorry.
PAM: For what?
Space-blastering me in
the frickin tits?!
Or tricking me into that
fart-locker to get blasted into
outer goddamn space on the off
chance you might wanna bang me!
ARCHER: Both I guess, look --
PAM: After you blew me off
for Katya the big-titted cyborg!
Littleiss, uh...
ARCHER: R2-double-D2?
PAM: Nice.
ARCHER: Thanks, and I'm sorry,
but you gotta let me out, Pam,
they're fighting
space-pirates out there!
With Cyril!
CYRIL: It's supposed to fire.
What is wrong with you?
ARCHER: And Lana can't even stand up!
LANA: You idiot, just
reset the -- unghff!
GILLETTE: Jesus, like a
dog in a station wagon.
DRAKE: No, no!
We're losing the beachhead!
ARCHER: They're running
out of time, Pam!
PAM: Oh, alright...
ARCHER: That being said... quickie?
PAM: Meh.
Whew!
Okay, good luck.
ARCHER: Thanks, normally
I'd say I don't need it,
but I can barely feel my legs.
PAM: I call that the MOAB.
It stands for --
ARCHER: I know!
What it stands for, I was there,
please don't say it out loud.
Now if you'll excuse me, I need to...
Kick some space-pirate ass!
Woooooo!
EVERYBODY: Archer?!
ARCHER: Hang on?
Yes, Archer, duh.
And if you're done doing each other's hair, let's --
DRAKE: Let's retake the shiiiiip!
ARCHER: Or just run around
interrupting people.
DRAKE: Gagh! I'm hit, I'm hit!
ARCHER: Oh, for -- Do I
have to do everything?
He asked, intending to be facetious!
LANA: I'm sorry!
I don't know what's wrong with me!
ARCHER: Besides suffering
from gigantism?!
LANA: Shut up.
DRAKE: The bridge!
We have to make it to the --
ARCHER: The bridge, yes, I heard you!
So unless we're going the wrong way...!
DRAKE: Uhh... oh.
No, that's it right there.
ARCHER: Then shut up! God!
Okay, now what?
You can un-shut up.
DRAKE: The com-link, by the door...
Commander Kellogg?
It's Drake!
KELLOGG: Tony?!
ARCHER: "Tony?!"
KELLOGG: Oh my God,
am I glad to see you!
We couldn't have held out much longer!
DRAKE: Well, we got here
as fast as we could.
KELLOGG: My God, you're wounded.
Put him here, please, and we'll take those...
ARCHER: Uh, oh.
Yeah, here you go...
KELLOGG: Oh dear, are you wounded too?
LANA: No, just --
DRAKE: Just a little space-sickness.
But eventually she'll get acclimated.
LANA: I -- eventually?
KELLOGG: Yes, she's strong,
good breeding stock.
LANA: Wh-?! Hey!
ARCHER: Whoa, Charles
Benedict Davenport.
Uh, the father of eugenics.
Seriously guys, read a book.
DRAKE: And two more on the Intrepid,
stowaways, almost as good as her.
KELLOGG: Two more?!
Then we can populate Mars
even faster than we'd hoped!
CYRIL: What? GILLETTE: What?
LANA: Did you say Mars?!
ARCHER: Oh now your ears --
wait, why did you say Mars?
HORIZON DRONE: Don't you see?
They're the mutineers!
DRAKE: Welcome to the... Danger Zone!
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com