MALORY: Item six.
EVERYBODY: [ whoa, whoa ]
CHERYL/CAROL: Yeah, we're
not done with item five!
MALORY: Well obviously we are,
because I just said "item six."
PAM: Where the hell're we supposed to
eat lunch if you close the break room?
MALORY: Wherever you'd like.
As long as it's not Le Cirque,
Lutèce, Elaine's, 21, The
Russian Tea Room, or The Palm.
CYRIL: Like we can afford to
eat lunch at any of those.
MALORY: All the better.
Saves us all the embarrassment
of my snubbing you.
LANA: Malory --
MALORY: And, shut up, it will
save me God knows how much on
exterminators... That
break room is disgusting.
A pig wouldn't be caught dead in there.
CHERYL/CAROL: Yeah it would.
KRIEGER: Aww, Pigley Two...
MALORY: And you!
Mister "I Can Solve Your Ant Problem!"
KRIEGER: First of all, it's Doctor
"I Can Solve Your Ant Problem"...
KRIEGER: And second of
all, here's your refund.
I really thought that would work.
ARCHER: What were you
going for, ant-strength
relative to the size of a human?
KRIEGER: Shut up.
MALORY: Everyone shut
up, because item six!
Talk to Pam today, because somehow,
and seemingly impossibly soon, it is
once again time for... peer reviews.
PAM: Yaaayyyy!
LANA: Ugh, how can you not hate those?
PAM: I dunno, maybe I'm the only
one who cares about this being
an efficient and supportive
work environment...
CHERYL/CAROL: Maybe you're lame.
PAM: Maybe you can shut
your dick-holster.
So see me after, I've got
everyone paired off.
Well, except Ms. Archer.
ARCHER: Wait, why don't
you have to do it?
MALORY: Well I would... if I had
a peer in this entire building.
Item seven.
Oh.
You all remember Lucas Troy...
EVERYBODY: [ groans ]
PAM: Shitbag.
ARCHER: What're you talking
about, Luke's awesome!
He's a kickass agent, a great wingman,
he can drink Ireland under the table...
back when we were training
together we tore it up!
MALORY: Just like his ISIS contract!
I trained him for a year, and
the minute he's worth a damn he
goes to work for ODIN?!
ARCHER: She said, oversimplifyingly!
MALORY: Wh-?!
And so, congratulations to all our
new agents, but especially to our
highest-scoring recruit, Lucas Troy!
EVERYBODY: [ cheers ]
ARCHER: Way to go Luke!
TROY: I'm going to work for ODIN.
ARCHER: He was still awesome.
And my best --
LANA: Only --
ARCHER: -- shut up, my best
friend, Mother, which is why you
hated him, because you were
jealous of our relationship.
CYRIL: So, you two were
in a relationship...
ARCHER: Wh-?
No, not the Ray kind!
GILLETTE: Meaning?
ARCHER: Homosexual, Ray.
So, so obviously.
What's not obvious, Mother, is why my
best friend, the awesome Luke Troy,
is on your stupid agenda!
MALORY: Oh, right, let's see here...
Doo doo doo dooo... oh.
He's dead.
ARCHER: He's... what?
CHERYL/CAROL: Dead!
Jesus, clean the secretly gay for
Lucas Troy out of your ears.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
ARCHER: This is crazy,
how could Luke be --
LANA: Gay?
ARCHER: Dead! Lana.
And your little, whatever, gay
innuendos don't even merit a --
PAM: Reach-around?
Owww! Jesus!
CHERYL/CAROL: Ha ha!
It's just like my birthday
party all over again.
Remember?
PAM: Nooo!
CHERYL/CAROL: Yeah.
Because you weren't invited.
ARCHER: Mother, tell me
exactly what happened!
MALORY: To lure a black market
arms dealer into the open,
Troy was posing as a nuclear
scientist who had stolen enough
uranium for a dirty bomb.
ARCHER: Oh, that is
classic Luke the Spook!
Hey stupid, here's your fake uranium,
click, handcuffs, drops mic on stage.
MALORY: Yes, that was the plan.
But somehow, thanks to what I
just assume is ODIN idiocy,
Troy acquired real uranium.
ARCHER: Even classic-er!
The bad guys would obviously
bring a Geiger counter!
MALORY: And ten million
dollars in bearer bonds.
And when the smoke had cleared,
four ODIN agents were dead, and
the uranium, the bad guys, and
the money had all disappeared.
And so had Troy.
ARCHER: Doesn't... prove anything.
LANA: Oh for -- Archer, if it
walks like a duck, and quacks
like a duck, and murders a
bunch of its fellow ducks...
ARCHER: Then maybe the duck
knew there was a mole!
Ever think of that?!
That maybe there's a
fox in the henhouse?!
A wolf in sheep's clothing?!
Or one of the other tricky animals?!
MALORY: Well, we'll never know.
The plane he escaped in
crashed, in Vermont.
ARCHER: What, no, I bet he faked his
own death so he can expose the mole!
LANA: There is no mole, and faked it how?
ARCHER: Paging Dr. Cooper!
Dr. D.B. Cooper!
Lana, he obviously bailed out and --
LANA: And then...
landed safely, buried his
chute, ran ten miles to the
crash site and then strapped himself
into the still-burning wreckage?
ARCHER: That... that could be anybody.
MALORY: Well, anybody
with his dental records.
ARCHER: What?!
MALORY: Yes, Sterling, I'm --
actually no, I'm not sorry.
He was a traitor and a thief,
and so I'm glad he's dead.
ARCHER: If he is!
Because you've always been
insanely jealous of my friends!
ARCHER: So if you'll excuse me,
Mother, I have to go clear
the name of an American hero.
MALORY: Does he seem... almost
a little too fond of Troy?
LANA: Yeah, and you
know he was gay, right?
MALORY: As a tangerine.
In jean shorts.
GILLETTE: But, I thought
Troy was already dead.
ARCHER: Because he wants
you to think that!
But I have a list of all his
known aliases, so see if any of
them used a passport!
Oh, or a credit card!
LANA: Yeah, like at roughtrade dot net.
ARCHER: Lana, I will hire Kenny
Loggins to come here and
play an acoustic set while I
slap some sense into you.
LANA: Pff.
Ray, back me up here.
Luke Troy, yes or no, gayest dude ever.
GILLETTE: Uh...
TROY: Dude, what, it was just the tip!
GILLETTE: Meathead fratboy asshole jock
maybe, but no, definitely not gay.
LANA: What?!
ARCHER: Boom!
Sorry.
What.
What?!
I knew it!
Where is he?!
And why don't we leave the
terrace door open, Woodhouse?!
Exactly, because he's a frickin lemur!
Ray, call me when you find a lead!
I'll be somewhere in or on top of my
building, shooting tranquilizer darts at
the world's shittiest pet.
LANA: Told him when he bought it.
PAM: And I'm telling you these
reviews are mandatory, and
since I outrank you...
OWEN: Hang on, lemme check this
imaginary list of all the
people I report to...
Doo doo doo doo dooooo...
PAM: Okay.
LANA: What the hell is this?
PAM: This, mustache on
a penis, is Rodney.
OWEN: And since there's only one name
on this list, you must be Ms. Archer.
Cleverly disguised as a large man.
PAM: Meh-heh!
He's the new, whatever, gun librarian.
OWEN: Armory supervisor.
LANA: Hooray, what's with the cage?
OWEN: Oh, some wacky new thing the kids
are doing, called inventory control?
PAM: Ms. Archer's pissed cause a buncha
guns and stuff keep going missing...
KRIEGER: Oh, and lemme know
if you want a good deal on a
gallon of irradiated ants.
LANA: Well, whatever.
I need some range time, so just
scuttle back into the tiny
little domain over which you
have power, and get me a
thousand rounds of nine mil, wadcutter.
OWEN: Absolutely.
Just fill out these requisition
forms, in triplicate.
LANA: Wh-?
For a few lousy bullets?!
OWEN: Well one, they're
excellent bullets--
LANA: Are you gonna stand there,
in what I just assume are
two-inch lifts, and tell me
Archer filled out your stupid forms
just to get a tranquilizer gun?
OWEN: No I am not.
LANA: Well?!
OWEN: He filled them out to get,
doo doo dooooo, two H&K MP-five,
two thousand rounds ammunition
for same, twenty mark-two
fragmentation grenade...
LANA: Wait a minute...
PAM: Yeah, that lemur is hosed.
OWEN: Fourteen days survival
ration, two night vision goggle,
two each arctic camouflage parka
and pant, and, doo doo doo doooo,
two pairs snowshoe.
LANA: Son of a bitch!
That phone call was --
ARCHER: Loooooooooooooooke!
Dude, I knew you faked your
death because a mole framed you
for stealing that uranium!
TROY: Dude, that is such a relief, I was
worried they turned you against me.
ARCHER: Are you kidding?
Dude, bros before... apparent
threats to national security.
TROY: Archer, you sure
you're up for this?
Because this thing... it runs deep.
ARCHER: Dude, I love deep
TROY: Said your mom!
ARCHER: Haa!
Classic you!
Allright, GPS says I'll
be there in four hours.
Don't worry, Luke... I'm coming for you.
TROY: [ Ahh ]
ARCHER: What was that?
TROY: Phrasing.
ARCHER: Nice!
Queer!
Wait a -- oh my God, holy shit!
No, Vermont has liquor stores.
Right?
Yeah they have to, it sucks there.
LANA: Cyril, not now.
What's the signal strength
on Archer's cellphone?
CYRIL: The doohickey says he's
about thirty minutes away.
And my point was, we could've
easily done it by now.
LANA: And my point, is that
pursuing a dangerous rogue
agent, isn't the optimal
time to do peer reviews!
CYRIL: Coulda done it ten times by now.
LANA: God damn it fine frickin review me!
CYRIL: Section one, Team Dynamics.
Question one, "Does
employee cooperate with..."
Oh. These are all "Strongly Disagree."
LANA: You --
ARCHER: Pussy!
TROY: Shut up, it went down wrong.
ARCHER: Said your... oh.
TROY: Yeah, doesn't work there.
ARCHER: Mmmmokay, say
"Thanks for coming."
TROY: Nooope!
ARCHER: No, seriously, if anybody finds
out I helped you I'll be disavowed.
TROY: I know.
Dude, I know.
Thank you.
ARCHER: For...?
TROY: Nope.
ARCHER: God, what a dick.
TROY: Said your mom!
Boom!
ARCHER: Dammit!
TROY: So easy...
ARCHER: Okay, I got an El Camino
full of rampage here,
so what's the plan?
TROY: Right, yes, okay, so, I know
it doesn't look like much now...
But it has tons of potential.
ARCHER: As a... base of operations while
we track down the mole who framed
you for murdering your colleagues and
selling uranium on the black market?
TROY: No, asshole.
As a bed-and-breakfast.
ARCHER: Uhh...
TROY: Twin Oaks.
You like that?
For the name?
Twin Oaks?
LANA: Seriously?
CYRIL: Yeah, according to the doohickey
it says Archer's in that direction --
LANA: Are you reading it wrong?
CYRIL: Within two hundred meters.
LANA: I bet you're reading it wrong.
CYRIL: Section two, Interpersonal.
"Does employee frequently
criticize oth --"
CYRIL: Strongly agree.
Somewhat disagree?
LANA: Somewhat shut up.
Come on, we're going on
foot, through the woods.
I've got a bad feeling about this.
TROY: I know, but imagine
it all fixed up!
ARCHER: No, yeah, I mean obviously it's --
TROY: It's gonna be amazing,
dude, look at these floors!
That's heart of pine!
ARCHER: Yeah, so look --
TROY: Look at this mantelpiece!
Mahogany!
There's another seven!
Eight fireplaces, dude,
how nuts is that?!
ARCHER: Pretty nuts...
TROY: Said your mom!
ARCHER: Yeahhh... so, um, about
un-framing you for treason and murder...
TROY: Yeah, I dunno, man, it kinda
seems like what's the point, you know?
ARCHER: I don't, actually.
TROY: C'mon, there's too much evidence!
I mean it's all fake, obviously, but...
ARCHER: Exactly!
Dude, there's a mole in your agency!
We gotta catch him!
TROY: But then what?
Then there's another mole, or a
double agent, on and on, it's
all just secrets and lies, man!
ARCHER: Yeah, it's espionage.
TROY: I can't go back to that
world, man, I'm too tired.
ARCHER: Hopefully that's just neurological
damage from scraping lead paint...
TROY: No, it's --
ARCHER: Because turning
the Munsters' house into a B&B
is an insane response to your situation!
It'd be cheaper to build a brand
new house out of actual money!
TROY: Yeah, I know it'll cost
a fortune to fix her up,
but money's not a problem.
ARCHER: Why, wait, why
is money not a problem?
TROY: And my situation, is anyone who
could hurt me thinks I'm already dead.
ARCHER: I -- wait, and
who was in the plane?
TROY: Hm?
ARCHER: I said who was in the goddamn--
TROY: No no no no, what the hell?!
LANA: How could you not see that?!
CYRIL: Because I only have two eyes, and
they were busy looking for hunters!
LANA: Why, is it pumpkin season?!
CYRIL: Is that a thing?!
TROY: Archer, were you followed here?
ARCHER: Wow, okay, a little insulting.
I think I know how to spot a tail, so --
TROY: Is your... phone on?!
ARCHER: Wh-? No!
Jesus, what kind of... wallpaper
are you thinking about?
Because how about a textile?
ARCHER: Lana, listen.
LANA: No, you listen!
We're -- [ Airhorn ]
ARCHER: Ha ha haa! Leave it!
VOICEMAIL LADY: The voice mailbox of...
[ Airhorn ]
Is full.
Goodbye.
TROY: Why is Lana Kane -- and is that
the geeky little accountant dude?!
-- attempting to breach my perimeter?!
ARCHER: I honestly don't know, but
why are -- you doing that?
TROY: Because they are a threat.
ARCHER: No they're not!
TROY: To our future together.
ARCHER: Especially not Cyril!
He's -- wait, I'm sorry,
whose future together?
TROY: Yours and mine, dumbass.
ARCHER: You lost me.
TROY: No, Archer, I thought I had--
ARCHER: No, yeah, you did.
TROY: -- but then you came back to me.
ARCHER: Don't take this the wrong way?
But I'm getting an extremely gay vibe.
TROY: Wh-?
Jesus, dude, I'm not gay!
ARCHER: I --
TROY: For other men!
ARCHER: Lost me again.
TROY: I can't really explain it?
I mean, you know me, I've banged
more hot chicks than I've
had hot dinners, but...
There's just something about you.
ARCHER: That... makes you gay for me?
TROY: Well, I don't
really like that word?
ARCHER: Well sorry, I
didn't invent English.
TROY: It's more like... a
singular samesex attraction.
ARCHER: Can I, um, my
head's kinda spinning...
TROY: I know, this is a lot to process.
ARCHER: No, literally.
TROY: Well, figuratively.
If it was literally...
ARCHER: The wine... you drugged the wine?
TROY: Yeah, sorry, I thought you might
freak out when I told you all this.
ARCHER: Pfff, sunnersannable, I'd do me...
TROY: And also when I told you I
actually did steal the uranium
and murder my fellow agents.
ARCHER: You dick...
TROY: To fund our life together, dude!
Which will start right after I
go murder your fellow agents.
ARCHER: Way way way way, hang on.
You had same wine, how you not get drug?
TROY: Coated the inside of the glass.
ARCHER: Heh!
Classic you!
PAM: Well this is a frickin disaster!
MALORY: I know.
When Ron said we were going on a
cruise, I almost vomited blood.
PAM: No. Nobody's doing
their peer reviews!
MALORY: Pam, the word "disaster"
implies it's something
that actually matters.
PAM: It matters to me!
MALORY: Well, but you don't.
PAM: Well then maybe instead of
doing my job I'll go hang out
in Vermont with Luke Troy
and all the other assholes!
MALORY: What?!
PAM: Oops.
MALORY: Trace Sterling's phone, and
scramble every available field agent!
I want them all converging
on his location!
GILLETTE: They... kinda already are...
CHERYL/CAROL: There's only like
two of 'em.
PAM: So why are these damn
peer reviews so hard?!
Only like ten people work in this
whole goddamn chickenshit outfit!
Sorry.
CHERYL/CAROL: Don't be.
It is a chickenshit outfit.
CYRIL: Look, for your information?
Blaze orange is the safest color to wear
to avoid being accidentally shot at.
LANA: What about intentionally shot at?!
TROY: Oh man, this is almost too easy...
LANA: Oh for -- seriously?!
TROY: Yeah, gotta give 'em a head start.
One Sterling Archer,
two Sterling Archer...
Ooh, Sterling Archer-Troy.
We can take each other's names.
I'd be --
ARCHER: Luuuuke!
C'mon, you're not thinking straight!
A, you wildly underestimated my
liver's ability to metabolize toxins!
And B, why would you possibly have these?
LANA: Because I'm not the idiot
who took his idiot clothes off!
CYRIL: Just your jacket,
c'mon, I'm freezing!
LANA: No!
CYRIL: I am gonna give you the worst
peer review in the history of... them!
TROY: Hey, Lana!
LANA: Where's Archer?!
Did you kill him?!
TROY: He's fine.
Unlike your aim.
Guess you never learned
how to shoot, huh?
LANA: What?!
First of all!
Shitass!
TROY: Or take criticism.
CYRIL: Strongly agree.
LANA: And from where?
CYRIL: Under.
Wear.
TROY: What was it we used to call you?
CYRIL: Truckasaurus?
LANA: Cyril?
TROY: No, it was...
oh yeah, Spray-and-Pray!
LANA: Dammit!
TROY: We also called you Shirley Temper.
LANA: Uh, Cyril?
TROY: Which, ya know, lame.
But accurate.
Again, unlike your aim.
Which is why I always thought
it was weird that you only ever
carried two magazines.
CYRIL: Section three,
Organization Skills!
LANA: Cyril!
CYRIL: "Employee is often
unprepared for important meetings!"
Strongly agree!
LANA: You left your gun
in a pile of clothes!
CYRIL: Because I had nowhere to put it!
LANA: And yet you found room for a
twentypage wad of Pam's
stupid peer review!
CYRIL: It's important to her!
ARCHER: Okay, so... Don't really
know what to make of that.
Unless... Wait, no, get
it out of your head.
Predator only hunts in tropical jungles.
I assume.
And desperately hope.
[ gunfire ]
ARCHER: Dammit!
MALORY: Well?!
Have you found Sterling?!
GILLETTE: Well his phone's in this house.
It's about twenty miles north of
Bennington, so I assume it's a B&B.
MALORY: Well, you would know.
And if you want to keep those teeth,
missy, you won't suck them at me!
GILLETTE: You know...
MALORY: Shut up, have
you tried calling him?!
[ airhorn ]
ARCHER: Ha ha haa! Leave it!
GILLETTE: Yes.
- VOICEMAIL LADY: The voice mailbox of...
- MALORY: You could've just said
so, you little -- Alright!
I swear to God, you people?
KRIEGER: Just say the
word on the nerve gas.
Feel like I owe you a freebie after
the whole ant-Krieger thing.
CYRIL: I can't, go anymore, can't do it.
LANA: Section Four, Running.
Employee sucks ass at it.
Strongly agree.
TROY: Lana?!
Little geek dude?!
CYRIL: My only regret, is I won't, get
to turn this in, because it is scathing.
LANA: That can't possibly,
be your only regret.
CYRIL: Well there's dating you.
Actually no, that was... far and away the
best thing that ever happened to me.
So as much as I'd like to, I don't
think now's an optimal time for that.
LANA: Aww, really?
CYRIL: I mean, if you
think we have time...
LANA: Cyril!
CYRIL: Ahh!
Yeah we don't have time!
LANA: Not for this, dickbrain.
For that.
CYRIL: What, what is... oh. Ohh, okay!
LANA: But do get naked.
Panties too.
CYRIL: Yeah, they're called briefs?
LANA: Yeah, you're a grown man?
ARCHER: Yeah, that's our Lana.
Let's see, so judging from the shell
ejection she was firing at...
What I really hope was not an ent.
Because that is like the
last thing we need.
An entmoot.
Oh my God what if I'm gay for Tolkien?
TROY: Dude.
Seriously, not that it's gonna
matter in thirty seconds...
But what is your problem?
CYRIL: Well, besides Lana ditching me...
TROY: For what, an entmoot?
Ya know, cause she's got
those big-ass tree-hands?
CYRIL: I'd have to go with hypothermia.
TROY: Well, I know a cure for that...
CYRIL: Oh my God, not in my face!
TROY: Said your mom, BOOM!
Sorry, that's terrible to
hear that right before you...
What in the... hell... is...?
LANA: Well, you know what they say.
Big hands... Big dick.
TROY: Noooooooooo!
LANA: Ew.
CYRIL: Gross.
ARCHER: Luke?!
LANA: Archer?!
ARCHER: Shut up, Luke?!
TROY: Archer?
Oh dude, is it bad?
ARCHER: There's a... kind of
a lot of blood down there.
TROY: Said your mom.
Oh my God, I'm sorry.
ARCHER: Seriously.
TROY: No, for everything.
The uranium, killing my fellow
agents, that hobo I set on fire
after I paid him to get his teeth
drilled to match my dental records?
Jesus, the dentist?
ARCHER: God damn, dude.
TROY: I know.
But I only did it because I wanted
us to be together, forever.
LANA: Called it.
TROY: I've loved you
since the day we met.
So mostly I'm sorry for... remember
that training mission in the D.R.?
ARCHER: Uh... yeah, tap-and-trace
on the Cuban embassy.
Then we got shit-housed on mamajuana.
TROY: And then you
passed out in your room.
ARCHER: Um... yeah...
TROY: Well, after you
passed out, I --
ARCHER: Luke?
If you really do love me?
TROY: You know I do.
ARCHER: Then please don't
finish that sentence.
TROY: Dude.
It's my deathbed confession.
C'mon, I'm dying.
ARCHER: Well I'm not, so please, don't --
TROY: After you passed out.
I snuck into your room with a
big bottle of suntan oil, put
on some Al Green, and...
ARCHER: Noooooooooooooooooooooo!
ARCHER: Can we have the radio?
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com