So, at the end of the day,
I'm just a regular guy trying
to live a regular life.
Remember that time you peed
in Drew Barrymore's car?
Uh, yes, I remember that.
Why do you remember that?
It was in your book.
-You should do that to someone here.
-What? No.
Well, anyway, I can't believe
I'm on a date with BoJack Horseman.
I feel like that anonymous girl
from Chapter 8 of your book
mixed with the pluck and determination
of that anonymous girl
-from Chapter 12.
-We don't need to dwell on the past.
Wait, shut up.
Is this the restaurant you bought
when you were trying
to show up Mr. Peanutbutter?
-Uh... No.
-Hey, this table's a little wobbly.
Want to yell at the waiter
and make a scene?
-No, I don't need--
-Come on, do that BoJack thing
where you make a big deal
and everyone laughs,
but at the same time we relate,
because you're saying
the things polite society won't.
That's not-- Ugh...
-Is everything all right over here?
-No, everything is not all right.
This table's been wobbling all evening.
If I wanted to flop around and get seasick
for an hour, I'd call your mother.
-Something in that area or...?
-Take me home now
and don't let me get out of bed
until I turn horse-colored.
-What are you doing?
-Did you want me to stay?
No, I wanted you to leave more quietly.
Some of us here are trying
to forget you exist.
"Forget you exist."
Classic BoJack. Love it.
[BoJack sighs]
[Claire] Oh, my God, are you Todd?
[Todd] Uh, yes.
[Claire] "Shut up, Todd!"
[Claire laughs]
[Todd] Aw, okay.
[♪♪]
Hey, Todd, can you drive me
to get my car?
I wanted to be responsible last night,
so I Ubered home
-and left my car in the fountain.
-Sorry, BoJack.
I gotta get ready for my grand opening.
It's finally happening. My Disneyland.
I realize that by saying "what"
I might set off a chain of events
whereby we continue this conversation,
but what?
Well, remember when I first moved in
and I kept asking
-if we could go to Disneyland?
-I do not.
And then you said
that there was no Disneyland.
-No.
-That Disneyland was a made-up lie,
like the tooth fairy, that parents use
to get their kids to behave.
-Oh, yeah, that shut you up.
-Sure did.
But then I thought,
why isn't there a Disneyland?
People would love it!
So, I took matters into my own hands,
and over the last five years,
I built my own Disneyland.
You've been doing this for five years?
How have you never mentioned it?
I bought that cheap plot of non-arable
dirt by the toxic waste dump
-up the hill from the old fire station.
-Okay, Todd.
-I'm gonna build a Disneyland.
-Sounds great, champ.
If it wasn't for that,
she never would've gotten sober.
Just finished drawing up blueprints
for that Disneyland I'm building.
Kind of busy here, Todd.
So, it turned out to be a good thing
I peed in her car.
Sorry for all the noise.
Got this crew of worker bees
to help me build my Disneyland.
Okay, I get it. You are building
your own Disneyland.
-Literally the first I'm hearing of this.
-Anyway, tomorrow we open the gates.
Finally, people will have a place to go
after they win the Super Bowl.
But you do know
that there already is a Disneyland?
-Yeah, I built it.
-No, I mean the real Disneyland.
You mean, the one in the hearts
and minds of children everywhere?
-The one in Anaheim!
-I think we're saying the same thing.
Are we?
Well, I think it's safe
to take the cone off.
I can do it for a small co-pay.
Can't say I'll miss it,
but we did have some crazy adventures
together these last few weeks.
Honey, would you rub my chin for me
so I can remember things?
Oh, um, okay. Uh...
Yeah, memories.
Hey, where should we go for my first meal
after the operation?
It's not an operation,
but we could go to Storky's again.
Oh, yeah! We're finally due
for our free sub.
"Storky's,
where your 81st sandwich is free."
We've been there 80 times?
It just opened last month.
Yeah, but you love it, so whenever
you suggest it, I always say yes.
Yeah, but 80 times?
Well, that'll be $6000.
Good thing you're getting
a free sandwich, huh?
What the...?
Huh?
Okay, you guys. [yells]
You vultures are killing me!
I'm sure he's talking about
other vultures.
Ah, the Valley.
Because sometimes you wanna go
where no one knows your name.
-[Pinky] BoJack Horseman!
-Pinky? Hey, how are you?
[stammers]
Oh, great!
-How's the book biz?
-Who knows?
I jumped off that burning ship.
Print media? What a joke.
Now I got a job
in broadcast network television,
a booming industry
with nowhere to go but up.
Oh, God.
-What are you doing here?
-Oh, my boss loves this place.
Do you know Wanda Pierce?
Wanda just got named head
of programming at MBN.
We're here to celebrate.
Well, that and she just woke up
from a 30-year coma.
Wait, she just got out
of a 30-year coma
and she's the head of programming
at a major broadcast network?
She's been with the company 30 years.
Everyone above her kept getting fired.
Besides, she's got
some really fresh ideas.
I am really feeling
The Kirk Cameron Show.
I don't even need a pilot.
Let's just order 22 episodes.
How about a new show
where celebrities try to guess
whether or not people have talent?
We'll air it three nights a week.
[all gasp]
Okay, what if we got relevant superstar
David Copperfield
to make
the World Trade Center disappear?
I hate to be the one to tell you this,
but David Copperfield really isn't
a big draw anymore.
Actually, everything feels fresh
if you just forget
the last 30 years ever happened.
Huh.
[woman over PA]
And here's a special request.
I've never even heard of this song,
but let's give it a spin:
"Special Feeling."
Wanda, meet
the one and only BoJack Horseman.
-Who?
-BoJack.
-BoJack Horseman.
Is that name supposed
to mean something to me?
[light rock ballad playing over speakers]
-Do you want to go skate?
-Nah. You know what they say,
you can lead a horse to roller,
but you can't make him rink.
[laughing]
-What?
-That's really funny.
-You're funny.
-Really?
Oh, my God. You should be on TV,
[gasps]
which, holy shit, they're flat now.
Actually, I was on. You know what,
I'm sick of talking about me.
Let's talk about you.
[Wanda] Next thing I know,
I'm waking up from a 30-year coma.
So, now I'm sleeping on my sister's couch,
but it's not ideal.
She's molting.
You know how sisters are.
Oh, jeez, got a couple curly guys in here
with the regulars.
How hard is it to look
before they bring it out?
-Excuse me, miss?
-I know, isn't it cool?
-Like we're getting away with something.
-What?
Don't you love it when appetizers have
a little crossover episode?
It's like when you're watching
Happy Days and Mork shows up.
Oh, yeah, I guess.
Or like when Kramer was
on Murphy Brown.
-Who?
-Hey, you want to get out of here?
I don't want MBN to just be another boring
old network, you know what I mean?
-Yes, totally.
-I want to take risks.
I want to swing for the fences, you know?
Otherwise, what are we doing?
Oh, my God, is it morning?
We stayed up all night talking,
-and we didn't even have sex.
-Well, it's not too late.
Oh!
-That was fantastic.
-Oh, yes.
Of course, I haven't had sex in 30 years.
I hope.
-Something's wrong.
-What is it?
I don't know, I feel weird, like I want
to spend more time with you
-even though I know we just had sex.
-Oh, okay.
No, you don't understand.
We already had sex,
but I still want to spend time with you.
Is that normal? Am I normal?
What is happening to me?
We can spend more time together.
I want to do things with you.
Fully clothed, sober, in daylight hours.
-Okay.
-I don't understand these feelings.
Let's get food? Or walk in park? Or--
Oh, God, it's coming. I can't stop it.
-Do you want to go to Disneyland?
-Okay.
[carnival music playing over speakers]
[child crying]
Disneyland has a lot more sparking wires
and loose nails than I remember.
Please hold your questions
until the end of the tour.
Here we have
Mr. Todd's Wild Death-Coaster.
The name is a work in progress,
but we wanted to work "death"
into the title for liability reasons.
And this is Gabe Jr.,
the Grease Fire of the Caribbean.
-This is boring. I want to go home.
-Vincent, be nice!
He's a little cranky
because he just got adult braces.
-You mean, braces.
-Princess Carolyn, stop embarrassing me!
Ugh.
And here we have Cinderella's
magical pile of used mattresses.
[child] Help!
Is it a good idea
to keep all those mattresses
-so close to an active grease fire?
-Where's your sense of wonder, Diane?
-Your friend is really negative.
-Yeah, don't be so negative, Diane.
-What?
-You know I hate negativity.
I mean, I don't hate it because
that's also negative, but you know.
[quacks, then yells]
[children laughing]
-Hey, Mr. Peanutbutter.
-Hey, buddy. This place is amazing.
It's like some sort of Disney version
of Knott's Berry Farm.
Oh, that's exactly
what I was going for!
I can't wait to get involved
and really spray the old
Mr. Peanutbutter scent on everything.
Uh, I was sort of thinking of this
as kind of just my thing.
Well, technically, you did build this
while working for P.B. Livin,
so I have the blah-blah-blah
of first refusal or whatever.
Oh, uh, okay.
I mean, that's just good business.
We're in this together now, Todd,
and nothing will distract me from--
Erica! You can't be here.
This place is filled with children.
Coach said he saw you headed
to the visitor's locker room
with a steel pipe.
You really think I'm the guy
who busted that pinto's leg?
'Cause if I am, you should be
a lot more goddamn scared of me.
Hey! My girlfriend's here.
Look, everyone! I have a girlfriend!
Sure. We'll cut there.
The middle of your line
is as good a place as any.
-What are you doing here?
-Just wanted to stop by.
We're filming Hey, I Think
You Can Dance! next door.
Look at you, all professional.
Like Natalie Portman in that movie
where she was a professional.
Who? [giggles]
People are watching.
Ugh.
The first time BoJack dates a woman
his own age,
she's basically just
a stunted 20-year-old.
Well, BoJack's stunted, too.
He got famous in his twenties,
so he'll be
in his twenties forever.
After you get famous, you stop growing,
you don't have to.
Every celebrity has
an age of stagnation.
I'm glad I never got famous.
I mean, I did write a best-selling book,
but I'm not famous-famous.
It doesn't just happen
when you get famous.
Your age of stagnation
is when you stop growing.
For most, it's when they get married,
settle into a routine.
You meet someone
who loves you unconditionally
and never challenges you
or wants you to change,
and then you never change.
But mostly it's just the famous people,
right?
Stella! Stella!
Corona Light.
This place is incredible.
I wanted to make you feel at home,
and nothing was bigger in the '80s
than '50s nostalgia.
It really feels like I'm back in the '80s,
feeling like I'm back in the '50s.
It's like if Back to the Future
and Peggy Sue Got Married got married.
[man over radio]
Okay, teenyboppers,
let's take things back
to the '50s, '50s style,
with this classic '50s hit
that everybody remembers:
"I Just Met My Perfect Match."
[do-wop ballad plays over speakers]
Wanda, these last few days
have been so amazing.
You've given me a fresh start.
In fact, it almost feels like
I just woke up from a 30-year coma.
I'm sorry, did you say you just woke up
from a 30-year coma?
-Oh, no, not me. Her.
-That's insane.
I just woke up from a 30-year coma.
[record stops]
Whoa!
Sorry about that needle skip, folks.
Let's start that song again
from the beginning.
[do-wop ballad plays over speakers]
I'm Alex.
-Wanda.
-And I'm BoJack.
It's been really tough for me
these last few weeks.
I've never seen Home Alone and everyone
makes me feel like a freak because of it.
-You've never seen Home Alone?
-I've never seen it!
-Also, I don't really know what a DVR is.
-Neither do I!
-No one does. It's just a magic box.
-Wanda, we have so much in common.
Really it's just one thing.
You can't count each individual thing
as a different thing.
That's like saying I have a lot
in common with Kanye West
because we both breathe air.
[both]
Who? Jinx. Buy me a Coke Zero.
What's a Coke Zero?
I have no idea.
[both laughing]
We gotta hang out more. I didn't know
there was anyone else like me.
Give me your fax and pager number
so I can add them to my Rolodex.
Tubular.
[BoJack sighs]
I don't trust that guy.
I bet he's seen Home Alone.
BoJack, I'm starting to lose
the thread of your character.
You think you can drop the jealous
boyfriend routine? It feels a little done.
You're right, I'm sorry.
Call me Snoop Dogg
-because I will drop it like it's hot.
-BoJack, I don't--
I got that one! Snoopy the dog.
From "Peanuts." Okay.
I got here as fast as I could.
Where's this next Haley Joel Osment?
-That was a lie to get you here.
-Aw, fish.
-There's never a next Haley Joel Osment.
-And there never will be.
Sorry I tricked you, but with Todd
running his own Disneyland
and actress Margo Martindale
in prison
for some reason I don't remember,
you're the best friend I've got.
Now grab the binoculars. I need dirt
on Wanda's new gentleman friend.
No, BoJack. What's the play here?
You'll find one little imperfection
and harp on it
like you do with my boyfriend?
You do understand what my "thing" is
with your boyfriend?
You'll just push her
into this other guy's arms.
Wanda likes you. Why ruin that?
This is Comrade Alexander
calling KGB High Command.
It's been two weeks since I woke up,
and I still have not been contacted
by my handlers.
I am awaiting orders to take down
the American dogs and pigs
and other various animals and humans.
Come in, KGB High Command.
Slap my salami, the guy's a commie.
Hey, what's going on here?
You've been served
with a cease-and-desist from my clients,
the Walt Disney Company.
I wanted to make sure what we were
doing here was 100 percent legal,
-so I called a lawyer.
-Wait, what?
As it turns out, it's not legal at all.
Who knew?
-Mr. Peanutbutter.
-We'll see you in court.
-The food court?
-No. Regular court.
Okay. But also I'm hungry, so I might
just stop by the food court first.
Let the record show, this is the single
dumbest case I've ever adjudicated.
-Mr. Chavez?
-Okay.
I'm just gonna throw this out there.
Is it possible maybe when the other guys
tried to copyright the name Disneyland,
they wrote down something else
by mistake,
so "Disneyland" is still up for grabs?
Okay, well, let's have a look
at the Articles of Incorporation to see
if Walt Disney accidentally trademarked
the wrong name. I'm sure these--
[stammers]
-What?
-There's a typo. Di-isneyland.
With two "i"s. That son of a gun
trademarked the wrong name.
May I, counselor?
D-I-I-S.
This is unambiguous.
-I find in favor of the defendant.
-Aw, shit.
-You're the defendant.
-Aw, sweet!
Your Otter, this is a gross miscarriage
of justice.
Hooray! Gross miscarriage!
And that's how I turned my dream into
what I call "The Happiest Place On Urf."
Urf is a made-up magical kingdom
I added to the Disney canon.
-Americans, they like this theme park?
-Oh, they love it.
It represents everything
America stands for.
Da.
-I mean, yeah.
-We did it, buddy!
Actually, I did it.
I had the idea to build a park,
I did all the work and I beat the lawsuit.
-Well, there's no "i" in "team," right?
-But there is an "i" in "Disneyland."
And unlike that other Disneyland,
this Disneyland only has one "i".
What are you saying?
You're not welcome
at my theme park anymore.
There's only room for one goofy dog there
and his name is Pluto.
Todd, no.
I've told the bees
if they see you to sting you on sight.
You understand. It's nothing personal.
It's just good business.
And that's how we do business on Urf.
-I don't like you like this.
-I learned it from you.
If I could get everyone's attention.
You're probably wondering
why I invited you all here tonight.
You said it was to celebrate
Todd's legal victory.
Right, but obviously,
I don't care about that,
so you're probably wondering
the real reason.
[Princess Carolyn]
No, we just took you at face value.
We have a special guest here tonight.
Alex. Or should I say "comrade"?
[BoJack gasps]
-Why would you say "comrade"?
-Oh, I forgot to explain that part.
Alex is a KGB agent
bent on destroying America.
[all gasp]
-It truly is a small world after all!
-Alex, is that true?
Okay, yes. It's true.
I was a deep-cover KGB operative
before I went into my coma.
I've been trying to contact
my handler in Russia,
but I can't reach him
and I don't know if I ever will.
[all] Aww!
No! He's-- It's not adorable!
He's a soviet sleeper-agent
who doesn't realize the Cold War is over.
I felt totally alone in this world
before I met Wanda.
And then I met all of you, my friends.
But if you're gonna kick me to the curb
just because I think
you're all capitalist swine
and want to see your way
of life destroyed, well, so be it.
-Or should I say, So-vi-et.
-Oh! Cute. Wordplay.
-That's not even good wordplay.
-Wait, how did you know all this?
-BoJack, were you spying on him?
-He is literally a spy
trying to destroy America,
the country we all live in.
How am I the bad guy here?
BoJack, I am really bumping on
the whole you-not-liking-Alex of it all.
-You told me you were going to drop it.
-Yeah, but--
I don't care about Alex.
I want to know what happened
to the amazing guy
I spent the last few days with,
because if this is who you are,
I don't think I like it.
Alex, would you take me back
to my sister's place?
Sure thing, Wanda.
And I can get you there fast
because I'm always Russian.
[all] Aww!
Seriously?
[BoJack sighs]
[Princess Carolyn gasps]
I got here as fast as I could.
Where's the next Dakota Fa--?
Oh, I get what happened.
Could you get me a beer from the fridge?
I didn't want to stand up.
Wait, no. I don't deserve beer.
You called me all the way over here
to not get you a beer?
Why do I always do this?
I push away everyone I care about.
Oh, do you? I never noticed that.
Look, you obviously really care
about this girl
and that scares you,
so you sabotage yourself.
That's my problem.
I'm too good at sabotage.
-Why am I so good at everything I do?
-Hey, I got a crazy idea.
How about you just stop sulking
and go win her back, dummy?
You're right. I gotta win her back,
put it all on the line. You know what?
I think I will have that beer,
can you get it for me?
[sighs]
-Why do I bother?
-Hey, grab a beer for yourself, too!
Actually, I want both beers!
-Wanda.
-What do you want, BoJack?
There's something I gotta say.
When I was--
-Todd! There's something I gotta say!
-Hey, I'm kind of already doing--
I never should have tried
to make your thing my thing!
I just got excited and wanted to smear
Mr. Peanutbutter all over everything.
I should have been supporting you,
like this support beam.
-Or a different support beam.
-It's my fault.
The point of Disneyland isn't
to make money and win lawsuits.
But I forgot that.
So, these two were so consumed
by greed that it destroyed them.
You know, I came here today
to blow up Disneyland.
-You what?
-But now I realize,
I don't need to take down capitalism.
Capitalism sows the seeds
for its own destruction.
It's a snake that eats itself.
It's only a matter of time.
[whistling]
Hey, buddy, let's just say we-- Oh!
Oh, no, no, no. No!
Gabe Jr.!
Quick, Todd! The mattress pile!
Jump to safety! No!
Bees, help!
Your queen commands you!
No! Bees! Come on!
[groaning]
-You gotta-- Over the--
-What is it, boy? What's wrong?
-Hey, there's trouble.
-Did some kid fall down a well?
No, no, no! Listen.
He's trying to tell us
a kid fell down a well.
-Let's go, go, go! Come on!
-Bad, bad, bad. You gotta--
No, no, no, listen!
Wait, Wanda, we need to talk.
-But the fire.
-I don't care about that.
Look, the great guy you've been
getting to know, that's me.
That other guy,
the guy from the party,
that's me too and you need
to know that. I'm not perfect.
I'm cynical and I'm possessive
and I can sometimes fly off the handle.
I'm not always the best
at being not terrible.
I gotta say,
I'm not loving this pitch so far.
But I want to be better,
I'm trying to be better.
And when I'm around you,
for the first time in 30 years,
I feel like I can be.
Wanda, you make me want
to be a better man.
Wow. That's a great line.
-Did you just come up with that?
-Yes.
Hey, boys and girls,
this is your park DJ speaking.
And as the Titanic's band played on
as the ship sank,
so too will I spin one last record
as my DJ booth is engulfed in flames.
[slow rock ballad playing over speakers]
[both grunting]
Hooray!
Mr. Peanutbutter.
-You saved me!
-No.
I saved us.
Woo-hoo!
-I want to give this a real shot.
-I don't know, BoJack.
I just got out of my coma,
and I don't have time to waste
if you're still figuring your shit out.
Plus, it's hard to think straight
with this fire everywhere.
-Move in with me.
-What?
I know it feels fast.
We barely know each other.
It's crazy, but I like you.
And sometimes you gotta swing
for the fences, right?
-Okay.
-Yeah?
Yeah. Let's move in together.
Let's do it.
It's crazy, but let's do it!
[laughing]
♪ Back in the '90s ♪
♪ I was in a very famous TV show ♪
-♪ I'm BoJack the horse ♪
-♪ BoJack! ♪
♪ BoJack the horse
Don't act like you don't know ♪
♪ And I'm trying to hold onto my past ♪
♪ It's been so long
I don't think I'm gonna last ♪
♪ I guess I'll just try
And make you understand ♪
♪ That I'm more horse than a man ♪
♪ Or I'm more man than a horse ♪
♪ BoJack! ♪
Boxer versus raptor.
Na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na!