(Electricity crackling)
(Announcer:) FARGO.
All new wednesdays at 10:00.
On  FX.
(Woman:) Son of a bitch!
(Woman Announcing:)
Fxx presents ARCHER.
(Schnuckiputzi purring)
So, uh, what are we doing?
Are we just
jumping right into this,
or what's the deal?
(krieger whistling)
(Door opens)
(Growls)
Alrighty!
And how's our patient?
- And, follow up, where is our patient?
- (Meows)
- Meaning?
Okay, you know what?
You're about as helpful
as tits on a...
- (yells)
- You!
- (Meows)
- Look what you've done to me!
(Hoarse voice): Yeah, right?
I'm a monster!
You're a miracle!
You didn't even have feet!
Now look at you,
walking around on new legs,
with hands
that can crush steel...
(high-pitched voice): And, I mean, don't
try it right now, obviously, but...
- (gasping)
- Look at me!
I'm a Goddamn freak!
And I don't know
who I'm gonna kill first,
you or that
son of a bitch Len Trexler.
Well, first of all,
it's "whom."
Uh, no, it isn't.
It absolutely is.
Doesn't matter.
But if it'll help you decide,
this serum, which is sort of
the key to the whole deal,
I call factor-K.
- And?
- And your body
will reject its new components,
and you will die in agony,
unless you get
an injection of it.
Wha... well,
give it here, shitbeard.
Uhh! Goddamn it.
Ow. Okay, that kind of hurt,
and I'm already
in a pretty bad mood,
so I'm gonna kill you first.
So, any last words?
Every 12 hours.
Cryptic. Nice.
Usually people just
blubber and beg,
and those big gloobs of snot
run outta their nose, but you...
if you don't get a shot
of factor-K every 12 hours,
you will die.
- Bullshit.
- Which... and that's fair,
- but...
- Let me guess.
You're only gonna make enough
for one injection at a time.
(Chuckling)
Well, I am now.
- Goddamn it! Yeah,
- So, like an insurance policy.
- How long does it take you to make it?
- I don't know. An hour?
Well, then, I guess I'll
wake you up in about 11 hours.
Wake me... (Grunts) (Body thuds)
What the... are you...
Dreamland... has a whole Goddamn
Nazi Robot farm in the basement.
In this economy!
(Figgis:)
Hello?
Hello! Son of a...
Hang on.
(Lighter clicks)
What the...
oh, for the love of cocks!
(Sighs)
I mean, seriously, just...
Goddamn it.
♪♪
*ARCHER*
Season 08 Episode 05
"Archer Dreamland: Sleepers Wake"
Hello!
Can anybody hear me?
Man, that thing
is outta control.
Hello! Hello!
Somebody! Hey!
(Flame whooshes)
What the...
no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Help! My pubes!
(Sobbing) (Thudding)
My Goddamn pubes are on fire!
(Muffled) All right.
I guess let him out.
Now that second lunch is ruined.
(Sobbing, yelling)
(Coughing)
Aw, man!
Some of it got in my mouth.
(Scoffs)
How long was I in there?
How should I know?
Usually dead people don't just
climb out of these drawers
with their big bushy
birds on fire,
so for all I know,
you're that Zombie
- that got walked with!
- That what?
In the movie I walked with a Zombie.
The Zombie Titular.
I'm not a Goddamn...
I am Lieutenant Cyril Figgis,
LAPD, you sentient shit-sacks!
- I showed you my shield!
- And if you'd show it to me again...
I don't...
whoever hit me took it.
(Gasps) Goddamn it!
And my service weapon!
And yet they left you
your lighter.
Wait. When I got pistol-whipped,
I was talking to an English guy.
We don't have an English guy.
I... you have to remember me!
Uh, actually, I don't.
And also, I don't, so...
- Oh, you think you're pretty smart,
- Huh? I mean, smart enough to know
you cut a finger off one of my cadavers...
- which, ew.
- And also gross abuse of a corpse,
which is punishable by...
I know all about
gross abuse of a corpse!
- Yeah, that's kind of my whole point.
- (Growls)
As the lord our God himself
is my witness,
upon the conclusion
of my current business,
I shall return to this place
and visit upon you an apocalypse
of such terror and destruction
that you will rue... rue the very
fact of your miserable birth!
I'll be here.
I actually won't.
Well, unless it's before Friday.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
What's it you're leaving to do?
- Lumber inspector.
- Huh. Didn't know that was a thing.
That's because
you have no vision.
This, Danny...
(Sniffs) This is your world.
Yeah.
Please, Figgis, for your sake,
tell me you're joking.
It's just a temporary setback,
but I am going to fix this,
trust me.
That's the whole point.
I don't trust you.
I wouldn't trust you
to fix potato (Bleep) Salad!
You're probably
one of those assholes
who puts relish in it!
I mean, first my whores,
and now Charlotte Vandertunt?
How many women can one man lose?
Oh, plus your wife.
Would you...
Oh! Mr. Trexler,
I swear to God that I will
get you your million dollars.
You know, you say that
with the confidence of a man
who has a lot longer to live.
I...
(Click, dial tone)
How'd that go?
How do you think it went?
- Not great.
- Ya think?
Yes.
Because while I was
getting pistol-whipped
and shoved in a drawer
at the morgue...
losing precious time, not to
mention my gun and my shield...
you were supposed to find
Charlotte Vandertunt.
And, so, how did that go?
(Pounds desk)
Also not great.
But more importantly...
because we know Archer
broke her out of jail,
and we know he's working
for mother, so...
Son of a bitch!
I bet she's gonna try
to ransom Charlotte!
Wait. Shut up.
"More importantly" what?
- What is that smell?
- What is what smell?
(Sniffs)
That. Smells like cuy.
- What the hell is cuy?
- Roasted Guinea pig.
- Huh?
- They blowtorch the
hair right off of it.
- It's like the national dish of Peru.
- (Sighs) Did...
- Or is it Ecuador?
- Did you...
which one's the native habitat
of the spectacled bear?
- Did...
- Wait. Shit. They both are.
Hang on. Uh, hey, let me
see your service weapon.
Huh? Yeah. Here.
Now, Peru has
the pisco sour, but...
Did you find
Charlotte Vandertunt?
Tell me before, so help me God,
I put a bullet in your
big fat stupid face!
(Clears throat) First of all,
that's just hurtful.
- (Gun cocks)
- And second of all,
it doesn't matter where she is,
just where the ransom money is.
Hmm. Presumably
with the Vandertunts.
So all we gotta do is...
insinuate ourselves
into this whole deal,
like we're there to help,
and steal the ransom
during the exchange.
Yeah. It's a piece of piss.
Now, aren't you glad
you didn't shoot me?
(Sighs) For now.
Although I'm sure at some point
I'll regret that decision, so...
why is there blood
on the barrel?
What? No.
That's, um, hot sauce.
Well, why is there
hot sauce on it?
With a couple of hairs
stuck in it.
- Oh, sweet Christ.
- What?
Did you beat a Guinea
pig to death
with your service weapon,
slather the thing
in hot sauce and eat it?
Yep!
Well, I officially regret
my decision.
(Chuckling)
Man, I almost always do.
(Gong bangs)
(Chattering in Chinese)
Hey! Who keeps leaving
the Goddamn seat down?
Looking your way, Huizhong.
(Poovey:) So, how are we gonna
play this with the Vandertunts?
We're gonna play it that
you keep your fat mouth shut...
- Again, hurtful.
- While I explain to them
that the cavalry
is finally here.
Yes, it's right here,
as per your demand...
a million dollars
in unmarked, untraceable
20, 50,
and 100-dollar bills.
Okay. Good. Good. That's...
sheer idiocy on your part,
frankly.
I'm sorry?
As well you should be.
- What do you...
- I mean, including the bag,
which, by the way, was a gift,
the whole thing must weigh
a good 50 pounds.
- Well, too bad. I...
- I mean, an envelope
with a hundred sammies
would've been so much easier.
- A hundred what?
- Sammies.
After Salmon P. Chase,
the man on the $10,000 bill?
Well, what the hell
am I supposed to do
with a $10,000 bill?
Well, what does one do
with a twenty-dollar bill?
- Buy a single orange?
- That's...
just make sure the money's
at the drop by midnight,
and that you follow
my instructions to the letter.
- Mmm, like a reverse scavenger hunt.
- (Sighs)
And once we have the money,
we'll arrange for the return
of your sister.
Oh, right. Yes. Sorry.
I forgot that part.
- And that's a firm firm?
- Yes.
And no cops, at all, anywhere.
No police.
Also a firm firm?
- Yes, it's a firm firm!
- Wait. Why?
What? I... I don't know.
No reason.
I'm sorry.
This is my first kidnapping.
Well... (In spooky
voice): Or is it?
(Evil chuckle)
Jesus Christ.
(Click, dial tone) Ciao!
Alrighty, then.
Who's for cuy?
(Figgis yells, gags)
(Muffled gag)
(Sniffs)
Yes,
that's probably why
you smell burnt hair.
But don't judge them
by their looks.
They may seem appalling...
(Chomping)
But trust me,
they're quite delicious.
(In spooky voice)
Yes, delicious.
Like all taboos.
(Muffled):
You're frickin' weird.
- I mean, just weird.
- (Lana:) What is?
(Gasps)
Lana! Uh, I mean, Miss Kane.
I... I mean, uh...
"Lana" is fine.
- I'll say.
- You'll say what?
- Nothing.
- Ah. A man of mystery.
Well, you know,
mainly in the sense
that I try to solve them,
you know...
- On your own.
- Well, yeah.
I mean, since my partner died.
- Which I actually should really...
- I meant without the police.
Without the who now?
"No cops, at all, anywhere,"
I believe were your exact words.
My exac...
were you eavesdropping on me?
Yes.
Did you have a follow-up
to that, or...
no, actually,
because you caught me
totally off guard
by not denying it.
But how much of that
did you hear?
Depends.
What's your angle, shamus?
(Chuckling) Well, uh,
probably about 30 degrees.
(Rimshot) (Gillette:)
Diminishing returns, cliff!
But I'm not working
any angle, so...
So, then, you wouldn't
need any help?
- No, I... why are you so interested?
- No reason.
Just thought maybe you could
make it worth my while.
Well, I... I can't, so...
What if I made it
worth your while?
Umm...
No.
No what? Wait. What?
What? At the club,
I said, "umm,"
and then I was gonna say, "no,"
but then you didn't
let me finish.
- Oh, you finished, all right.
- Yeah. Maybe try woolite?
Which, by the way,
makes one of us!
- Oh, please! Wait. Seriously?
- Get out.
'Cause I'd be happy to,
you know...
- Get... (Chuckles)...
- St-stay and watch you finish.
- Out!
- Jesus!
Look, if you... ehh!
(Sighs)
Great.
Now I have no liquor.
Just a big fat pair
of blue lady-balls.
(Speaking German)
(Meows, purrs)
(Spits, groans) That's my mouth!
(Whining)
Get outta here!
(Spits) Oh!
(Spits) If I wanted your
asshole on my mouth,
I'd do it while you were asleep!
Which we've never
talked about, but... ow!
My face!
How long was I out?
(Meows)
Oh, that helps.
Man, I gotta warn Trexler
Dutch wants to kill him.
Mainly because Trexler
hasn't paid me for my work yet,
but... also because...
say what you will about
der robotik ubermenschen.
Sure can punch good.
(Man laughing)
I'm sorry, darlin',
but you're gonna
have to repeat that.
(Clears throat)
I said,
"I had a little towel,
"but I lost it walking here,
so I need your clothes,
your boots,
and your motorcycle."
(Laughter)
Oh, is that all?
Yeah.
That oughta do it.
You, uh, sure you don't need me
to, uh, check your oil?
(Laughter)
Oh, okay.
And by that remark,
I assume you're referring
either to my robotic limbs
or offering to plunge
your finger,
and/or penis, into my anus.
(Men) Ohhh! I'll plunge
my fist into your...
(chuckles)
Were you gonna say "anus"?
(Bones crack)
(Screaming)
'Cause a finger's one thing.
- But a whole fist?
- Aaahhh!
That's like...
(Yelling)
I just never understood that.
(Crying out)
And I'm not trying to judge.
(Grunting)
But it's like, at some point,
you gotta question your choices.
(Yells)
Whoo!
I don't know. If it's two
consenting adults, (Zipper zips up)
I'm like,
"live and let live."
But if you want me
to let you live, chief,
I'm gonna need those keys.
Here. (Whimpers)
Take 'em!
Hey, thanks.
Oh, and if turns out
you lose that arm,
just give me a call.
(Chuckles)
I got a guy.
He what?
- Uh, is going to kill you.
- Was I not...
what are you talking about?
- Why?
- Stop it!
What, I should be calm
when you tell me
a Goddamn robot
wants to kill me?
No, not you.
Wha... wha... then who?
No. Sorry. You.
He wants to kill you.
The good news is,
without my help,
he'll be dead in...
Ten hours.
Okay, well,
my house is a fortress.
I got a ton of guys.
We'll outlast him.
Yeah. You say that...
Feels pretty good, huh, Dutch?
(Chuckles)
Yes, it does, other Dutch.
Yes, it does.
(Sighs)
Goddamn it.
(Mother:)
I think you're confused, doll.
(Charlotte:)
I am not in the least confused!
I don't care if my family
does pay the ransom.
I'm not going back there!
I meant you were confused
about me caring
what you did after the payoff.
You're not planning
to blindfold me
and hide me in a bomb shelter
with limited oxygen
and send my family cryptic notes
about how to find me in a race
against time for my life?
Who are you, collective
pseudonym Carolyn keene?
What? Who would go
to all that trouble?
Johann schmidt,
aka the red skull,
in my Nazi
Kidnap-Slash-Rape fantasy.
- (Growls)
- Ew!
Right?
Shut up.
Look, tonight your brother
is going to drop
the ransom money
at the Griffith observatory.
Archer is going to retrieve it
and bring it to me.
And if nobody screws up,
once I have the money,
you're free to go.
Well, but that's my whole point.
(Sobs)
Go where?
- (Growls)
- Who knows? Maybe a handsome
- young Nazi scientist will take you in.
- (Door opens)
- Do what now?
- (Gasps) What the hell are you doing?
Just filling
the coolers with ice.
You know,
normal bartendery stuff.
Oh, so suddenly
you work here again? - I...
- What happened to your face?
- I...
- Did someone catch you snooping?
- (Zerk growls)
Uh, no, I walked into a door...
Repeatedly.
Oh, yeah.
My mother used to do that.
Well, you better not have been
snooping on me, mister.
Are you... pfft! Come on!
I wouldn't do that!
(Quietly:) So, Archer's the
bagman for a kidnapping, huh?
Okay, then.
Because you know
what happens to snoops.
- They get... poops?
- What?
(Cecil:)
It's just that the kidnappers
were extremely clear
on that point.
No police, at all, anywhere.
Well, of course they're gonna
say that, but trust me...
I trust him.
He brought me a finger.
(Chomping)
(Sighs) Only you. What?
All I had today was some cuy.
(Gulps)
Oh, and congee.
Oh, and a bunch
of salted duck eggs.
Look, we'll be right behind you,
so just follow
their instructions,
drop the ransom off,
and with a bit of luck,
we'll get it and the kidnappers.
Okay, but I have a bad feeling about this.
(Engine starts)
Well, I don't care.
Hmm. Fair enough.
Do you wanna go?
(Belches)
(Hot dog thuds)
(Archer:) I thought I made it
pretty clear to the little weirdo
that I didn't wanna see any cops
near the drop.
I guess you can't
blame the guy for trying.
Plus, it's not like I can't
handle Figgis and Poovey.
But I may have to wait them out.
Whatever.
You paid for an hour.
Well, that's my whole point.
It may take a lot longer
than an hour...
well... and I'm not
paying you any extra.
- What?
- But feel free to hike the five miles
back to sunset in those heels.
What the hell?
Who brings a hooker?
(Cecil) (Quietly): Okay. Here's the topiary
garden. (Car door opens, closes)
Which I wish I could buy it so
I could burn it to the ground.
Topiary.
My God, what rubbish.
Shrubbish!
(Laughs)
So freakin' weird.
(Cecil:) Hmm.
Well, I suppose
that looks like a mushroom.
What? It's clearly
a mushroom.
Well, then...
(Grunts)
(Loudly):
All right, then. I'm off.
Alone, as I arrived,
with no police anywhere!
(Sighs)
I mean...
Seriously.
Okay, Archer.
It's your move.
(Car engine starts) Damn it.
I gotta at least tip her.
This is definitely gonna take
longer than an hour. (Car departs)
Man, I wish I had a...
Smoke grenade?
What the shit?
(Poovey) (Coughing):
Goddamn it!
(Figgis:)
Will you come on?
No, no, no, no, no, no!
- God... Damn it!
- (Car departs)
(Sighs)
I guess it's not his move.
- (Engine starts)
- (Screams) Jesus!
Sorry. Here. Take these.
What the hell are these for?
Um, I guess, parting gifts?
What? I don't know. Maybe you
can sell 'em or whatever.
Because, listen, this car chase
is gonna get a little crazy...
well, then, let me out!
Stop the car!
Let me finish!
Because my point is,
I don't really
have time to stop.
(Screaming)
But I'm not gonna have that,
so I'm gonna need you
to kind of jump out.
Are you nuts? I'll slow
down a little, obviously,
but when you hit the
ground, (Screams)
You're gonna wanna kind of roll.
(Grunts)
(Body thudding)
Yeah, just like that!
Good instincts!
Asshole!
Seriously!
(Figgis:) They're gaining on us!
Step on it!
Trust me,
it's totally stepped on!
Oh, son of a...
(Cocks gun)
Oh, shit.
(Gunshots)
(Tires screeching)
(Yells)
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no!
(Engine sputters, stops)
(Sighs)
Goddamn it.
Did ya get 'em?
No. I got somebody, though.
(Laughing)
Wow. Good policin'.
(Cocks gun)
Shut up.
Son of a...
(Tires screeching)
No, no, no, no, no, no!
(Crashing)
(Crashing stops)
(Coughing)
Oh, Goddamn it.
(Crash)
So...
How was your evening?
(Clears throat)
Uh, not g-great.
(Growls)
(Knuckles crack)
And I assume about to get worse.
♪ ♪
Synchronized by srjanapala
♪♪
(Man:)
Made in Georgia.
(Man:) Dateline,
Los Angeles, California, 1947.
Forecast: It's going to rain...
Lead!
(Sinister laughing)
So you're just... (Groans)
Straight-up crazy.
(Blows raspberry)
Archer: Dreamland.
All new wednesdays at 10:00.
On FXX.
It's gonna take an hour
at this time.
Wow, look at Stan's yard.
Someone's been busy.
(Laughs)
Clearly not in ours. Maybe
Henry can do some work today.
Yeah.
I forget your back is always
bad this time of year.
Only when there are leaves...
when did you wash this last?
THE AMERICANS.
(Engine starts)
All new Tuesdays at 10:00.
On  FX
(Wind whistling)
(Footsteps crunching)
(Man grunting)
(Gunshots)
(Hissing, squeaking)
Announcer: FARGO.
All-new wednesdays at 10:00 on  FX.
(Man:) I'm getting paid to learn
how to run a business,
do things when I want
and how I want,
get paid more
than some office job.
I got freedom.
(Siren wailing)
Freedom from all of it.
(Dog barking)
(Siren wailing continues)
(Man exhales)