PAM: Aw c'maaaahn!
Clock yer skinny ass out already, and
let's go get outside some dranks!
CHERYL/CAROL: Ugh, I can't!
I have to cover her stupid
phone in case those stupid
pirates call with a stupid ransom
demand for Mr. Stupid Archer!
MALORY: Carol?!
Carol! Have they called?!
CHERYL/CAROL: No! Ma'am!
But rest assured I'll let you
know the minute they dooo!
MALORY: Rest?
My God, who can rest...
CHERYL/CAROL: Not me, apparently.
CYRIL: Or me!
I have to re-do the annual
budget because she's blowing it
all on this so-called
rescue of Archer!
PAM: Well his plane did crash,
and the distress signal was last
heard coming from a known pirate
fortress, so... CYRIL: So?!
That doesn't mean Ray and Lana have
to bankrupt ISIS getting there!
GILLETTE: Oh, would you relax?
You rent a boat,
that money's gone.
This way, we can sell
it when we're done.
I bet it'll come out cheaper.
LANA: I wasn't talking
about the boat.
GILLETTE: I think five grand
for the week was a steal.
Look at him, he is lithe.
LANA: So a twink escort your rent, but --
GILLETTE: That's different!
I mean, they did ask if I wanted to
actually buy him, but I thought...
LANA: What, that I'd
be weird about it?
GILLETTE: I -- LANA: That I, perhaps
due to my race, might have a problem
with the concept of
owning a human being?
GILLETTE: I actually just
thought I'd get tired of him.
LANA: You?
Mr. Can't Even Commit To A Pet?
GILLETTE: Wh-?
Yeah hi, two cats!
One of whom I think has FIP, so...
commit that.
CYRIL: You know how hard I
worked on this budget?!
Nights, weekends, canceled my
vacation, and now it's all wasted!
PAM: Wasted, exactly,
let's go be that!
C'mon, happy hour at
Pita Margarita's!
CHERYL/CAROL: Is...
that what it sounds like?
PAM: Only if it sounds like a shitload
of tequila and some A-rab hoagies.
MALORY: How dare you?!
PAM: Arab, sorry.
MALORY: Oh shut up, how can you
even think about happy hour
at a time like this?!
When probably as we speak, my poor
Sterling is being tortured by pirates!
CYRIL: I wish... MALORY: What?!
CYRIL: Wish you
wouldn't say that!
Because I'm sure he's not being tortured...
ARCHER: Aaaaaaaaaaaagghhhhhhh!
Ohhhh my God, stop, stop, stop,
seriously I can't take anymore!
Whew! That was insane, I never
even heard of that position!
Did the missionaries not
swing by here, or...?
NOAH: Excuse me?
Sorry, pirate-king Archer?
ARCHER: What! Noah!
NOAH: Ready for the
uh, morning briefing?
ARCHER: Noah, I'm half drunk and slathered in...
every bodily fluid there is.
So yeah, this is about as
piratekingy as I'm gonna get.
Brief away!
NOAH: Okay, item one! The --
ARCHER: Noah.
NOAH: Yes sir?
ARCHER: Good morning.
Sync & corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
NOAH: O.K. Item one.
The huge morale problem.
ARCHER: How do we have
a morale problem?
NOAH: Well first of all --
ARCHER: C'mon, karaoke night's a big hit...
PIRATE: Roti dan mentega,
bakar dan selai!
ARCHER: Woooo!
We have an awesome feast every night...
Woooo!
Not to mention
intramural lacrosse!
Woooo!
So how can they have low morale?
NOAH: Well um, besides all of those
things, they haven't been paid.
ARCHER: So pay 'em, what do you
need, new payroll software?
Cyril always handled
all that stuff.
Payroll, budgets, he's a genius at that crap...
CYRIL: Just find the money,
Cyril!
You're an accounting
genius, Cyril!
That's right you bitch.
I said it.
So good luck finding all
these Swiss accounts!
Mwah ha!
Mwah ha ha ha ha haaaaaa!
PAM: Whatcha doin?
CYRIL: Aagh!
Hey, Pam... NOAH: No, we don't need --
ARCHER: Oh! And dealing with
disgruntled employees, Pam's great at that...
PAM: Izzat innernet porn?
CYRIL: Uh, yep!
Just, um... just jackin it.
PAM: Can I watch?
Or izzat weird?
CYRIL: It's... kinda weird.
PAM: Is it?
CYRIL: Yes.
ARCHER: I think it's because
she's such a good listener.
NOAH: And she sounds lovely.
But you don't need an HR rep and payroll
software -- ARCHER: Couldn't hurt...
NOAH: Sir! Please!
Pirates work for shares, and
since you became pirateking
there hasn't been any booty, so --
ARCHER: Gonna have to go ahead
and disagree with
you there, buddy.
NOAH: From pirated ships.
ARCHER: Oh.
I thought you meant from the --
NOAH: Native girls, no.
ARCHER: Sorry, I don't know
all the pirate terms yet.
NOAH: Well --
ARCHER: I'm new! To all of this!
Especially the actual,
you know, piracy part...
It's not really what I expected.
Dammit, I said get over there!
For the jillionth time,
nobody is raping anybody!
Actually no, you know what?!
Now nobody gets anything,
because I'm letting him go!
[ Grumbling ]
Shut up!
He's a small business owner!
If he loses his ship
he'll be ruined!
You can go.
Ooh, but can we get about
fifty pounds of tuna steaks?
NOAH: Which you let him
talk you down to twenty.
ARCHER: Well?!
You know what kinda margins
those guys work on?
NOAH: I actually don't...
ARCHER: Well nice Ph.D.!
NOAH: My field's anthropology.
And I'm actually just
a doctoral candidate?
Or I was, until these guys captured
my research vessel and enslaved me...
ARCHER: Ugh, not this again...
NOAH: So I was thinking, if you freed me...
ARCHER: You're my
translator, I need you.
That's why I made
you first mate.
NOAH: Which also went
over pretty badly.
ARCHER: Yeah, people hate you
so let's just put a pin in the
whole... manumission thing.
NOAH: But --
ARCHER: Noah!
Morale's low enough as it is.
And I bet I know who's to blame!
NOAH: No kidding... RILEY: I'm not
kidding, this Archer guy's gonna get you
all killed. He --
ARCHER: Riley!
RILEY: Archer, what
a coincidence.
I was just talking about you.
ARCHER: With who?
Cause that bucktooth little shit
doesn't even speak English!
BUCKY: I do little bit --
RCHER: No you don't.
BUCKY: -- and correct
syntax is "with whom!"
NOAH: Man, that is not
gonna help morale.
RILEY: Yeah, Bucky's an
incorrigible gossip.
ARCHER: Who -- to whom you
are forbidden to speak!
I locked you down here so you
couldn't contact my mother,
not so you could,
whatever, sow disharmony!
RILEY: You're sowing
plenty all by yourself.
Face it kid, you're a
bust as a pirateking.
ARCHER: King, exactly!
And unless you want to spend
the rest of the afternoon with
a bunch of scorpions,
don't forget it!
MALORY: And remember,
this is a rescue mission.
LANA: I heard you.
MALORY: So don't charge in there all
crazy, machine-gunning everything
in sight.
LANA: When have I --
MALORY: I'm sure you'd love it
if Sterling were killed in some huge crossfire.
LANA: Wh-? No I wouldn't!
MALORY: -- but just try to
control all your jealousy and,
ick, sexual frustration.
LANA: Oh no, you're breaking up.
MALORY: Lana.
LANA: I mean, am I jealous because
Archer gets preferential treatment?
Yes.
But am I still attracted to him?
GILLETTE: Is a pig's ass pork?
I'm sorry, did you wanna hear what I
think, or just what you wanna hear?
He asked, pretty sarcastically.
BUCKY: Raja lemah!
Raja lemah!
BUCKY: Kita
memerlukan raja baru!
ARCHER: Whoa whoa!
Bucky! What is this?!
BUCKY: We hold
erections for king!
ARCHER: Well, flattering, not really necessary...
NOAH: He means elections.
ARCHER: Okay, that makes
more -- wait, what?!
BUCKY: Time for new king!
Raja baru!
PIRATES: [ grumblings ]
ARCHER: Okay, pirates!
Hey! Take a knee!
Noah You wanna...?
NOAH: That won't translate.
It's like last week when you said "lend
me your ears" and they were like "Apa?"
ARCHER: Damn it --
NOAH: I can't do idioms.
ARCHER: Shut up.
Then unshut up, and tell them I understand
their frustration... NOAH: Do you?
Saya mendengar anda!
ARCHER: But you don't change horses in mid --
NOAH: Idiom!
ARCHER: Now is not the
time for a new king!
NOAH: Sekarang tidak
ada raja baru!
ARCHER: Because the
king is strong!
NOAH: Raja yang kuat!
BUCKY: If you so strong...
melawan raja!
PIRATES: Yah!
Melawan raja!
ARCHER: What's melawan raja?
NOAH: King-fight.
If the king loses to a challenger in
one-on-one combat, he has to step down.
Or just be dead.
ARCHER: Since when?!
NOAH: Since 19... always.
Did you not read the
orientation materials?
ARCHER: Woooo!
Mmmmore skimmed it?
BUCKY: Enough talk!
Melawan raja!
ARCHER: Okay Bucky, we'll melawan raja...
NOAH: Oh, one thing --
ARCHER: Noah shut
up and translate.
I accept your challenge!
NOAH: Cabaran diterima!
ARCHER: Because your mouth's been
writing checks your butt can't cash,
NOAH: Anda -- Do you even
know what an idiom is?
ARCHER: Colloquial metaphor.
NOAH: No, it's -- well actually yes, but
I really think this is a bad idea --
ARCHER: I'm not remunerating
you to think, Noah!
Even if you weren't a slave.
And your three-fifths of an opinion
is noted, so -- oh sweet Jesus Jones!
NOAH: See, Bucky doesn't
have to fight you himself.
He can choose a stand-in.
ARCHER: Who is... huge!
NOAH: That's what I was --
ARCHER: Why didn't he come out for lacrosse?!
BUCKY: You lucky
I don't let him!
ARCHER: Let him?
NOAH: He's Bucky's girlfriend.
ARCHER: Way to eschew traditional
gender roles, pirates.
NOAH: Yeah, they're fascinating...
BUCKY: Now we melawan raja!
And then we see who is
bucktooth little shit!
ARCHER: It'll still be you.
Listen --
BUCKY: Melawaaaaaaan rajaaaaa!
PIRATES: Mela-wan, ra-ja!
Mela-wan, ra-ja!
ARCHER: Hey, maybe there's a way
to make some money on this.
Bet on me.
NOAH: I would, but who'd bet on --
wait, don't you have that backwards?
LANA: No.
Because you know what I bet?
GILLETTE: I bet I kn you're gonna tell me...
LANA: I bet after we Zodiac in
past the reef, take out at least one O.
P., make our way through a jungle
full of Claymores, neutralize the fortress
garrison, and finally extract that
kidnapped-gettin ass sonuvabitch, he's
gonna be all like -- ARCHER: Woooooo!
LANA: Wuhhhhh!
Like this whole thing was all just part of some...
dumbshit master plan.
GILLETTE: She said, trying
to convince herself that
she no longer ached
for his -- Oww!
LANA: I'm sorry, what
were you gonna say?
GILLETTE: Cock.
ARCHER: Suck it!
Cause I'm still the king!
BUCKY: This no fair!
You break the rules!
ARCHER: What rules?!
We're pirates!
BUCKY: Melawan raja
mean hand-hand combat!
ARCHER: Boo-hoo, show me!
Show me where it says that!
Take your time. I'm hourly.
BUCKY: I know it in here somewhere...
Damn! Okay, maybe it don't say
this exact words, but everybody know --
ARCHER: Nooop!
Fair is -- well it wasn't exactly
fair, but since it wasn't expressly
forbidden... tough titties!
Wow, I never realized how
much we rely idioms.
BUCKY: You win this
round, Archer!
ARCHER: Duh.
BUCKY: But every
dog has its day!
ARCHER: See? Idiom.
BUCKY: And when that day
come Bucky make you sorry!
- Bucky make you say --
- Mayday mayday mayday...This is Rip Riley
calling ISIS, over.
ARCHER: Noah.
NOAH: That's not me.
ARCHER: I know that!
RILEY: Damn it, is that the P.
A.?!
Way to eschew traditional
labeling, pirates.
ARCHER: Fascinating.
Because since when is there a
radio in the damn dungeon?!
NOAH: God, you really shoulda
read your orientation materials.
ARCHER: Noah!
NOAH: Radio room!
RILEY: Mayday mayday mayday,
this is Rip Riley calling ISIS.
Mayday may --
MALORY: Rip?!
RILEY: Finally. Malory, listen to me very --
MALORY: How's Sterling,
is he hurt or -- oh God, have
the pirates tortured him?!
RILEY: Uh, no.
MALORY: Oh thank God, I was --
wait, are you under duress?!
If you are, key
your handset twice!
RILEY: I'm not under duress, I'm --
MALORY: Well, that's exactly
what you'd say if you were under duress, so --
RILEY: Malory!
I don't have a lot of time, so
please listen very carefully...
MALORY: I'm listening!
RILEY: Your son, is--
ARCHER: Nooo!
[ BLAM! ]
MALORY: Oh my -- Carol!
Somebody?!
CHERYL/CAROL: What.
MALORY: Sterling... I think...
he's been shot!
CHERYL/CAROL: Oh my God.
So then can I go home?
ARCHER: I told you, I'm
not going anywhere!
Especially not back to ISIS, and especially
not now that I just shot -- What I
assume was the only radio?
NOAH: Yeah, "See about getting a
back-up radio" was itemmmmm five.
ARCHER: And item one, is Riley
get your ass back in your cell!
NOAH: Item one's actually
the morale problem.
ARCHER: Noah?
RILEY: More like
potential mutiny.
NOAH: Yeah, right?
Gonna go ahead and
change "morale problem"
to "potential mutiny"...
ARCHER: No! You're not!
Because there is no mutiny, potential
or otherwi -- BUCKY: Pemberontakan!
PIRATES: Pemberontakan!
ARCHER: So, is that Malay for --
NOAH: Mutiny, yes.
So I guess I should upgrade it from
"potential" to -- RILEY: Incipient?
NOAH: Ooh, nice...
ARCHER: No!
Do not upgrade that mutiny, Noah!
I will tell you!
When it's time!
To upgrade the damn -- Mutiny, okay, so...
What comes after incipient?
RILEY: In progress?
NOAH: Nailed it!
Oh, this is great.
This is just great for my ears.
ARCHER: This is what I was talking
about, with the whole tinnitis thing!
You hear that high-pitched whine?
It's like NOAH: Eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee!
ARCHER: Noah!
NOAH: Aagh! What?!
ARCHER: I -- well for one thing, I'm
kinda regretting making you first mate!
NOAH: Me too!
Now I'm... management!
RILEY: Archer!
ARCHER: What?!
RILEY: Shut up! Noah!
NOAH: What?!
RILEY: What'd you say
about a back-up radio?!
NOAH: That we need one!
It's itemmmm... Five!
RILEY: Oh well that's just--
ARCHER: A battering ram?
BUCKY: Archer! Kami membunuhmu!
ARCHER: What was
that, what'd he say?
NOAH: "We're going to kill you."
ARCHER: Oh.
Thought they were surrendering.
RILEY: Why?!
Would you think that?!
ARCHER: They did before!
For no good reason!
RILEY: At least then we
had assault weapons!
Now we've only got -- give me that!
ARCHER: Yeah go nuts,
Sundance, it's empty.
RILEY: It's empty!
Because you emptied it!
Into the only radio
on the island!
ARCHER: All six, right in the ten ring...
RILEY: Well, congratulations!
We're trapped!
ARCHER: We're not -- Trapped.
Okay yeah, we're trapped.
NOAH: Uh, heah gang...
why don't we just use that?
ARCHER: Well obviously
we're gonna use that.
PIRATES: Hantu!
BUCKY: They not ghosts!
They just white!
PIRATE: Rasis.
BUCKY: You're racist!
MALORY: Those dirty
pirate bastards!
They killed my baby
boy-hoy-hooyyy!
CHERYL/CAROL: Oh now, you don't know that for sure...
MALORY: You're right!
That sound could've
been anything!
Like... a firecracker!
Orientals are crazy
for firecrackers!
CHERYL/CAROL: Oh
my God, and rice?
MALORY: Or maybe Rip shot a
pirate, and Sterling yelled
"No" because he didn't want
to give away their position!
CHERYL/CAROL: And opium.
MALORY: Yes, you know,
I bet they've escaped!
CHERYL/CAROL: oh my God...
and rice.
MALORY: Because if anyone can
escape from a pirate fortress,
it's Sterling and Rip.
Especially if they cooperate.
RILEY: Damn it, quit stepping
on my hands, you idiot!
ARCHER: Quit bossing me around!
You're not my -- wait, tell me
there's no chance you're my father.
RILEY: Not unless
you're -- Fifteen.
ARCHER: Thank God.
RILEY: The feeling's mutual.
Because if my son was as big a bonehead
as you -- ARCHER: You have a son?
RILEY: Wh-? No.
ARCHER: Then shut up. Noah!
Where the hell does this go?!
NOAH: I don't know, down!
ARCHER: Wow, you're only a doctoral candidate...
NOAH: Hey guy, my field's
anthropology!
RILEY: Good luck
with the job hunt.
ARCHER: Right?
NOAH: Not that it's any of your
business, but I plan to teach?!
ARCHER: Anthropology.
NOAH: Wh-? Yes!
RILEY: To anthropology majors.
NOAH: Hey ya know what?
ARCHER: Thus continuing
the circle of why bother.
NOAH: Anthropology is an
important field of study!
ARCHER: I'm pretty sure somebody's
already named all the different spiders!
NOAH: Wh-? That's arachnology!
ARCHER: I know!
Equally huge waste of time!
NOAH: Hey speaking of,
can we go back up?
ARCHER: Oh my God.
Not really.
Why?
NOAH: Just curious.
ARCHER: Go go go go go!
RILEY: Waaaagh!
ARCHER: Waaaagh!
Oh, shi -- That was just
a flash-bang grenade!
Still super-bad for your ears,
So when we get outta here,
you should go see my
ENT doctor, he's good.
RILEY: How the hell are we
supposed to get out of here?!
ARCHER: Isn't this your cell?
RILEY: Yes!
ARCHER: So how'd you
get out before?
RILEY: I bribed Bucky!
ARCHER: Noah!
NOAH: What?
ARCHER: That is
annoying as shit!
And I doubt we can bribe Bucky again,
since I crippled his girlfriend...
RILEY: So what're we
supposed to ow?!
ARCHER: I dunno.
MALORY: But I may as
well go home and rest.
If they haven't escaped already,
Lana will be there any time now,
and she'll get them out.
And it's not like I can do anything from here...
CHERYL/CAROL: Exactly!
So why do I have to stay?!
MALORY: Because Lana may call.
Or because I said so.
Pick one.
CYRIL: Who's jackin' it?
MALORY: And why the hell
are you still here?
CYRIL: I, um, this is,
uh, what was I doing?
MALORY: Whatever it was, you
better pray it had about
three coats of Scotch-Gard.
CYRIL: And that it wasn't, ick, Pam...
LANA: His narrow twinky ass
better not steal the boat, is all I'm saying...
Oh! And just,
before we get in there, I am
not still attracted to Archer!
I'm sure he's still attracted to me,
I mean, he'd have to be Uh, blind...
not to, um...
I am so sorry about that.
Does it hurt?
Ray, seriously, I'm sorry.
Oh, now you're giving me
the silent treatment?!
What're you, six?!
GILLETTE: No...
Just professional.
Hey, pirates...
ARCHER: Okay, then how 'bout this?
We set Noah on fire--
NOAH: What?
ARCHER: -- and when they come to
put him out, we overpower them.
We don't have a lighter.
Well, then, I'm out of ideas.
And also, out of ***.
Because no rescue for you, hotshot.
- We catch your friends on beachy.
- But...
Ray? Holy shit, wheredcha...
get that eye-patch?
What are you, in pirate disguise?
Great job, buddy.
Looks great.
Lana?
You came all this way?
To rescue me?
Oh, my God.
Archer, don't.
Still got it pretty bad for me, huh?
Archer...
- Archer... Archer, don't you dare say...
- Whoo!
Sync & corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com